<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My cause of death right there https://t.co/QSnuWMl69m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS. EPISODE. HAS. GOT. ME. EMOTIONALLY. UNSTABLE. @MelissaPonzio1 I COULD REALLY USE ONE OF YOUR AMAZING HUGS RIGHT NOW ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸ #TeenWolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN ONE OF YOUR FAVOURITE YOUTUBERS @Nikki_Glamour REPLIES TO YOU ON SNAPCHAT OKAY BYE I CAN DIE HAPPY NOW ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless @sailor_mews she the real mvp ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish this was a joke but its so true https://t.co/6Uz872rd2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad idea to wear my bottom retainer tonight... almost 5am and I'm in pain but need my teeth to straighten again ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY STYDIA AND SCILES HEART I CAN'T HANDLE THIS WTF JEFF YOU TRYING TO KILL ME SLOWLY?! ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸ #StilesisBack #TeenWolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erkut_tunc me tomorrow KMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am emotionally unstable right now #shadowhunters https://t.co/AbrLvJ7nVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh well that makes more sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh BITCH I'M OLDER THAN YOU DID YA FORGET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 MINA THE HUMAN FLAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The monks are fighting over a concession card ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R0YALTICS I really don't understand what the problem is with their Aussie accent and why they have to "get rid" of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkroastfranta awh â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkroastfranta I just watched and like you said ball of emotions rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkroastfranta OKAY GRABBING MY EARPHONES NOW AND WATCHING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkroastfranta I have to go do my makeup so I have to watch it later but the longer I wait the more excited and anxious I get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkroastfranta I LOVE THIS ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Malitta_Samer @shawniezess @luvhazzx @VoidAllisonn_AA @MTVteenwolf Miecz - Sword SÅ‚aw - Shortcut from the Polish word for glory/fame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin *MieczysÅ‚am THE LINE ACROSS THE L IS V IMPORTANT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#3wordsbetterthanIloveyou I LOVE FOOD â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my new PT! She's bomb AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN STILIES' NAME IS THE SAME AS YOUR GRANDFATHER'S NAME ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can this hour hurry up? I just want PT to be over and done with ughh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh She's in for a beating of her life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh SO WHICH BITCH'S ASS ARE WE WHOOPING THIS SAT?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin yeah it's a salon only exclusive sorta thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin no, Pro Fiber by L'Oreal Paris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin originally was, still have to cut it tho bc split ends and stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin yeah my hairdresser gave me this amazing shampoo + conditioner + treatment set and my hair is so much better than it +]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin sure is, hairdresser said I need to cut heaps... still haven't and probs gonna end up with shoulder length ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin I lowkey miss my dark hair but I think I'll hold on to the blonde for a while before going back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin is it bad that I think you look better in darker hair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my PT isn't training anymore I'm so devo ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH THE SHADE ðŸ¸â˜•ï¸ GLAD I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO THINKS SO https://t.co/u4Fbf6GQow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mixakruxgomez @simplyygomez people started mysteriously leaving idk even I supposedly "left"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simplyygomez don't have Whatsapp babe sorry â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally ME https://t.co/v690v2cmFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh sadly, it will. Sometimes people are friends with you just because you hang out 7 days a week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh I know but I'm saying welcome to my life because literally only 2/6 school friends hung out with me since I left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@void_lrh welcome to my world where no.1 excuse is "you live too far away" and 2nd is "I have work"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan and Hayden are so Scott and Allison 2.0 ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniel is trying to get back together with me yet again LORD HELP ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAlRYTROYE da faq? How does one get that from AIYLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@temproaryfjx LITERALLY ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isak shooing away his friends when Even comes is the most hilarious thing I've seen ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin yeah I know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin yeah obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin yeah we're better off waiting for Sydney in June]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin same! so far no one important for April which suits me because I'm overseas ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin can they like come back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin SAME OMG LITERALLY LOOKED AT MY SHIT ASS COLLAGE THIS MORNING AND WAS LIKE TO MY MUM "I MISS THE TEEN WOLF CAST"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sad moment when Troian will no longer be in the same city and timezone as you ðŸ˜žðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LYRICS! https://t.co/ijPu1Uk75n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[literally everyone is using my photo of Troian...so who am I suing first? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can it be next week already?! #shadowhunters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bellisario_pl @natalayx your convo with Troian is famous in my country ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoelyhel no idea, I don't watch it on netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoelyhel it comes out tomorrow!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SelenaxEmison @SleepintheGardn Thank you â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalayx fuck the dot it's not noticeable ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mixakruxgomez @SleepintheGardn SHE WAS THE SWEETEST HUMAN BEING! SO SO LOVELY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin did my fandom gain a fan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammysjustin did you finish?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May I say 2 hours and 23 mins into 2017 and I'm so happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY NEW YEAR!!! ðŸ’¥ðŸŽ‰ðŸ’¥ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalayx yeah I need to start hitting the gym 3-4 times a week since I have only 4 months left to lose 10kgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalayx thats so easy to do honestly, all you gotta do is go for a 15-30 min walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU'RE KIDDING ME RIGHT? OMFG! 2 MORE DAYS! THERE BETTER NOT BE ANY MORE DEATHS! #RIPDebbie ðŸ˜­ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must plan a wardrobe change my cousin will not be able to copy ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 wtf? You're so close to ending, just let things be! ðŸ˜¡ https://t.co/MTi1nfELv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still can't believe she's gone ðŸ˜­ðŸ’” RIP Carrie, my favourite galactic princess â¤ï¸ #ripcarriefisher #Devastated https://t.co/ENHBTlRyNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matildaa___ I was too once I found out, esp. that it wasn't MTV that annouced the cancellation, it was one of the actors ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drxnksugg people are just lazy and disrespectful honestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drxnksugg exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drxnksugg "In England you can drink on the streets" WELL BITCH THIS IS STRAYA RESPECT OUR RULES OR LEAVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I finished eyewitness, think it's time for me to see what SKAM is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[literally laughing at anyone who hasn't seen Rogue One and thinks Jyn is Rey's mother ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sailor_mews you're probs not up to that episode then lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 4am Christmas Day and I've just applied to college...let's hope I get in ðŸ€ðŸ¤žðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent 4 hours doing my makeup... new record]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Carrie's okay ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@temproaryfjx you tell me to do that but you never listen even when I say "don't"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enemybiebers *too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dom said this week's sesh would be hard...hoping she forgot about it and will give me something easy bc there's no doubt I'll be lightheaded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend https://t.co/iMfa3FnJnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*finishes watching Eyewitness* https://t.co/0iiautFDq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11 2017 is a good year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH THE SHADE https://t.co/KrZRxnbPS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to @emlarge for getting me to watch Eyewitness just by tweeting about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[literally https://t.co/qeVEHbPJ94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annalisatobia yeah I know, taking things into my own hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sailor_mews also RIP Tyler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sailor_mews she ain't ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sailor_mews YASS SCREAM QUEENS! NOW I KNOW WHO TO MSG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annalisatobia one that reached out to me still hasn't responded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FLAPPYHEMMINGS Food? Seriously? You worry about the food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZLAYSUS please tell me he didn't fuck you over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RogueOne was good, absolutely hate the ending but I understand why it had to be that way]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>