<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainl7 I forgot about this I'll have to catch up. But I love Rochelle because she doesn't know how to do this stuff because why should she.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainl7 Trying to explain to vegan they have to be careful of the wine they are drinking is difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a joke

Q: Who has a greater fear of stairs &amp; is less in touch with reality than the president?
A: Me, with my dissociative seizures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainl7 Linked up with Temperance which in the US was extremely female led (to a lesser but still significant part of UK)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickypickard @ScarredForLife2 Does this mean the PIF worked or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pickeick2666 @LFBarfe Which at £20 a pop doesn't feel like it, does it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickypickard @ScarredForLife2 I know, they appear at friends parties and all I think "we need a bucket, we *need* a bucket"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pickeick2666 @LFBarfe It's a difficult one isn't it. Because things need to be paid for but how do you balance that with gouging?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pickeick2666 @LFBarfe The alternative is to charge an entry fee, which can be harsh of the kids of less well off or disinterested parents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickypickard @ScarredForLife2 Another one terrified by the Sparkler ad. I'm not alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairy_Gmother Oh good because the obvious political firestorm is a hell to handle as it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairy_Gmother Are you alright? 

Barring the obvious political firestorm going on around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your big old inefficient freezing cold kitchen. Kippers are fine. A wee galley kitchen all tight and warm, the stink infects everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Michael Burke discussing why Kippers fell out of fashion on #RoyalRecipes. No mention of how they stunk of 70s/80s kitchens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until it takes on @VictoriaCoren live on @BBCFOUR, I'm not interested. https://t.co/m31iPfKJ2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magslhalliday The Absolute Vodka bottle hiding there, does that still have enough contents to get you through the work? 😄😋]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ on a bike this is a real quote https://t.co/CFTgsL71sE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NykoAleksander @sixteenthCgirl oooh looks like someone's got themselves a new profile pic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe £20 for that? How do I organise a mass protest for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoyalOpera It's about revenge. That's all you need, now enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe What is the quality of staging? Is it a Gang Show or more like a turn up and watch them try?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been watching Royal Recipes, it's pretty much Daytime Fodder but it has @DrAnnieGray on it and I love food history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe And that's only one parent per child. Two parents plus a granny is the average.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe Bugger me, my former choral society didn't charge that and we hired professional soloists and an orchestra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe What? £20?! I understand they have to recuperate the cost of the venue but a £5 should do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddieRobson What are the odds on my choice https://t.co/9OoFOpBTia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cath_fletcher How about dodgy bookkeeping…oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather good Audible Daily Deal today https://t.co/mOcOQnv9HX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlopGazette Are you saying this is a rubbish idea? https://t.co/9OoFOpBTia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're wanting a taster of opera, I don't think you can go wrong with snaffling a few tickets to this and turnin… https://t.co/VpCG6d9hfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any chance of someone slipping laxatives into his coffee? That way there is consistency in his outpourings at both… https://t.co/4UHVzoXcvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipjcowley @Jezebel Is this an MP you even wish your wife or servants to have sex with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaturner101 @Mumbler3 It's about this guy and he goes up a mountain and ends up in trouble. 

That could be any book about a mountain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaturner101 @Mumbler3 In my bookshop days, we'd get a constant stream of people asking for half remembered books promoted on daytime tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PulpLibrarian Why is he being served by a cow? Is the coffee flavoured with beef?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 I think for women it's the influence of the corset. It takes Joan Sutherland and Birgit Nilsson to break that sound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 …But it is beginning to drift off to self congratulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 Listening to the episode now, she's picking stuff she claims she never got to hear after recording…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 Never been a fan of Schwarzkopf, her voice was very tight and sharp. It's not a sound you hear off sopranos nowadays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJaninaRamirez Do it on this, Anheuser Busch bought the painting and reproduced it in nearly every bar of they ow… https://t.co/nPE69w55ga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlopGazette A) Big name movie actor B) Wacky Comedian C) Someone with curly hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlopGazette It can be fun trying to come up with the least likely candidate. The bog-standard stuff is dull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiver on Toby Jones #DoctorWho #NewDoctor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A CGI Peter Cushing #DoctorWho #NewDoctorWho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronaldo Villiazon for the next Doctor, singing his way through the whole role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanCalman You and Tom Hardy flying through the universe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 What I wouldn't give to have a time machine back to 2012 again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScarredForLife2 I'm still terrified of Sparklers to this day https://t.co/hNZw3D8i8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boobygraffoe Look at that guy at the back https://t.co/h7kB1gh9IY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell Harty a useless interviewer, John Hurt giving decent answers despite the clumsy questions https://t.co/fpytrKhKGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevRichardColes it will look akin to this. Information down the cables. If you have two laptops you can doublechec… https://t.co/vhGfunWB03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…it's one of the few ace cards we have left, meeting the Queen. Used correctly she can be a powerful insult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As all the weary Willies come out to say the petition won't work. I say, that's not the point. The man is obsessed with ratings &amp; prestige…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'know what Margaret, dinnae be cracking open the Birtwistle at 11pm. Leave it for tomorrow https://t.co/IR7M6mCisJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Nowadays https://t.co/yvH8CI51G9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also congratulations to @MrJohnDorney and @bigfinish for winning with Absent Friends https://t.co/VPusJsybeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @DanRebellato, Blood, Sex and Money was the audio highlight of the year. https://t.co/VPusJsybeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitlovelace Reminds me of Peter Griffin and Dateline https://t.co/JWxqkzlKXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitlovelace Wait is *this* what was scheduled between 3pm and 7pm? Do they have to pause every now and then to explain the plot to him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Arn @Mumbler3 Only time I ever hear that show is in small shops, where all the staff are wishing it would finish soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 The Laughing Policeman fake laugh was used in those creepy glass case marionette things that went off when you walked past them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pursuit of power leads to destruction and turmoil. https://t.co/4CbuQ0pWg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article starts mediocre and then descends into a patchwork guessing game of what Edinburgh is like. https://t.co/ROll7QB8SK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitlovelace Actually, 4 hours for a movie? Is he watching Götterdämmerung?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProResting That's the plot of a porno, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 Alot of it is Underneath the Arches and Lilli Marlene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 Is this the article which complains about the lack of Classical choices and therefore means he's never heard R3's Private Passions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a) what a fucking Nimby attitude b) it already has as we've discovered a MP and a Knight can't travel to or through… https://t.co/Ipx0xCyk6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Albert wore a onesie. So that's why they are called that. "Onesie's sleeping drawers" https://t.co/uKGqngKAfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheencr Have a look in the Non fiction section for the My Story historical novels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheencr Cathy Cassidy does some really hard hitting stuff that belies the sparkly covers they are put in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheencr Debi Gliori - Pure Dead series. Pratchett's Johnny series and his Tiffany Aching series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible news to wake up to. Hurt was an amazing talent, the Dante's Divine Comedy he did for Radio 4 was moving. https://t.co/owqZHnzHko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always we have an unconditional place, we should use it to do something weird. Give Europe a laugh #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans it is important in it bollocks up early response and it can involve you reading an apology backwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half an hour later I'm cracking open the @Lucy_Worsley. Wars of the Roses which would lead on to my avatar. Italian Operatic Tudors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans @johnmitchinson Difficult thing, tv turns on a pin with populist vs academic. Meades is one of the few that can do both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmitchinson @TheSimonEvans His BBCFour show on Italian Facist Architecture is solid stuff. https://t.co/naKW91UUBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt @MrKenShabby I'm happy, I'm happy and I'll punch the man who says I'm not https://t.co/o49AtALKXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell Oh Freud is impactful but only in in the way I'd impact on his bollocks if I ever met him. #Dissociative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell But the most influential academic book since 1900?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell 1700? Then Adam Smith would be *far* more influential. Post 1900 then Keynes is the economic pin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell P.S. Modern Ireland by Roy Foster is a double threat. Brilliant academic book, brilliant popular history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFBarfe He's found some Fred Emney Picks a Pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell Note the point of your book prize. "Modern" academic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell It's easy to get a précis of Keynes work because he's a past figure. But it's moved on in 80 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell If you want to get into modern social economics then Amatya Sen is the game changer today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell Keynes' work is great but it does have the whiff of modern politics about it, like everyone buying Piketty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner @FernRiddell Hmm, I bet 10 years ago he'd be in the long list only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FernRiddell @greg_jenner And Keynes as your 'modern' economic thinker when you could have Sen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prodigalbum I know it's not the number at the front. 19th?… no that's Victorian Sherlock times isn't. 

"17th"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans classy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans you need a thin silver topped Can so you can point randomly at buildings and have people assume there is some feature there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmorrish @EddieRobson Not if it's still made from Concentrate it won't, does no one know the difference between British and English wine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans Ooh, I will but only if you listen to Elzadie Robinson which I got as an AutoRip for an Erik Satie CD https://t.co/sdQw5ICVI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans I assumed you wanted to cut up the otherwise constant stream of hot takes on whatever is going on now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans Video wise @ChannelArchive and @BBCArchive aren't bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans Feeds that post images or video without comment on a certain topic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSimonEvans Are you following @womensart1. That's your lovely twitter feed of images. We all need a database of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebeccaRideal You see it looks like the beginning of the Habsburg jaw. Big lower lip and a deep curve in the chin = protruding lower jaw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>