<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got this in! Any cat lovers can help? https://t.co/KZYHl3oEXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you do that? Like if you do...hehe https://t.co/fXEtujX3bo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The February course is now full! 
Thank you so much for your support!
The next one will be in July. If you are... https://t.co/JpceuMrLEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! Whatever your political point of view is, we are all animal lovers, this man wouldn't even let the animal... https://t.co/wVrQUDkZ5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab your tissue, you are going to cry... https://t.co/4jJCW9FdAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat found! Please share! Her human must be going mad looking for her! https://t.co/TIsJPBp4l5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: Cat Bereavement coffee/tea chat coming up soon. Share to anyone you think might need this. https://t.co/EGB02GN7dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all cats! It's the Big Cat Week! https://t.co/TxdpK4hLK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat Catcher service thus morning! 
Gus got into the carrier in 5 mins! 
Mission accomplished! SUCCESS!! 

If you... https://t.co/A7tZk5RIwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know that? https://t.co/Tb9u6JNKzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 2 spots left now! Sign up quick before it's gone! No more course will be run until the summer! https://t.co/bnPuByEden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[æ­å–œç™¼è²¡ï¼Œæ–°å¹´å¿«æ¨‚ï¼
It will be Chinese New Year in a few hours time. We will you all a very happy year of the Rooster and... https://t.co/pq7eLYF5ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is actually a book about the benefit of having cats! https://t.co/AT64Lv9wnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know animals can sense when natural disaster is coming before human does? 
Maybe these animals are telling us... https://t.co/BpYAiGyH5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark your calendar. And please share with any cat lover you think who might benefit from this FREE event. https://t.co/iSPX4HMBdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 4 spot left for this essential course. It can mean life and death to your pet or any animal you come across... https://t.co/JalvVBxrMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know there are lots of products at Ikea that are not designed with cat in mind but are really great cat... https://t.co/7V87LYu1SA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know there are lots of products at Ikea that are not designed with cat in mind but are really great cat... https://t.co/lemFTHIqaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a smart idea if you ever need to deal with this! https://t.co/jQIa9Joj2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ideas! https://t.co/IKSMXsIFZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a simple DIY project for kitty... https://t.co/lfdZ00G8Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buddy is one of our most fascinating customer. He travelled for 6 weeks from Sandymount to Grand Canal so that he... https://t.co/LU7Jh6EgDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final update for Zuki the cat! He has just moved into his forever home. Thank you so much for all of you who... https://t.co/pTHOgddzq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A causal coffee/tea chat in the safe environment with like minded people. Everyone is welcome. You don't need to... https://t.co/tlTIzYD9Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Maow follower Lily is crazy about Da Bird! Her mom only just arrived home and she immediately went through... https://t.co/3wOPWPSHSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have indoor-outdoor cats, you might want to get some cat houses for them when it is raining outside...... https://t.co/u2n1Rftyw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have indoor-outdoor cats, you might want to get some cat houses for them when it is raining outside...... https://t.co/OTGjHIaEMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting FREE recorded webinar from American SPCA for those of you who are involved with cat rescue,... https://t.co/f186UyGcdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very unusual of us to share a post of a bank! But maybe we can have some fun with this question too! Tell! https://t.co/SQveNhuTFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you actually a cat in human form? Tell! https://t.co/JfjTaf4vy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone up for living with a big cat? Ha! https://t.co/JcnGYQ8TxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of a cat humour to give your Wednesday a boost! https://t.co/5DfJqIhASN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many great tips!... https://t.co/qSTtiGo0Bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know a lot of you are planning for your holiday for 2017. Have you thought of putting an emergency plan in... https://t.co/71gCisCdju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The the ultimate question! https://t.co/xVk8IE65js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea! Simple DIY project and they will love it! https://t.co/4LlXcEoAnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most amazing DIY catification project I have come across! 
A cat house under the bed from one of the... https://t.co/gvvLNxH7xH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ever wonder what does your cat do all day when you are gone? Ha! https://t.co/M5u77GKHyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Miaow Ears everyone! https://t.co/c9xtKswsyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Monkey whom we helped to meet his flight in Dublin Airport. His humans were moving out of Ireland but on... https://t.co/rTrBnY9o9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope this is not going to affect us hugely! 
Any customers who have booked for today and tomorrow, please be in... https://t.co/1TYTEjqJdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not on commission but thought maybe you guys will be in as much shock as I did when I saw this! https://t.co/lyZfgVGIOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maowry Catsmas Nutmeg! https://t.co/3HWc1cWx7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know how I prepare myself for Catsmas sitting? I will show you what's in my bag ðŸ˜œ... https://t.co/29dOQOJWbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maowry Catsmas everyone! https://t.co/rQ7fpigJzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Founder has picked up Zuki this afternoon so he can spend Christmas with her until the 28th. 
Blood test comes... https://t.co/PnXBBaZFWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long day ahead today through New Year! Got this as a treat to keep me going for afternoon/evening round! https://t.co/aN8Qz2EkQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahem! Year end evaluation time! https://t.co/4q1DF2zbyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure we have lots of fluff in the house to help little birdies! https://t.co/GGnXINZge5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I am preaching to the choir here. But just in case you need something written to justify to your friends... https://t.co/O2WVSJTdTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has a cat THAT food motivated? Um... https://t.co/9Wdh5hTJNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updates on Zuki the cat and we have also attached an itemised vet bill so you know where we are at right now. We... https://t.co/EFCcBkdGWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIVER STOCKING STUFFERS! 
Last minute Catsmas shopping for your kitty cat! Order today to receive by Friday.... https://t.co/zeLnTpg4uG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this festive season, it's particularly difficult for those of us who have lost their cat this year. In some... https://t.co/DZLRNiDUuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this festive season, it's particularly difficult for those of us who have lost their cat this year. In some... https://t.co/BBqy2zkp4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this festive season, it's particularly difficult for those of us who have lost their cat this year. In some... https://t.co/OxLmKr7GNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me to express our condolences to Maggie's human. She has sent us a beautiful story. Maggie has been... https://t.co/iuVsA8ufcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuni wants to say THANK YOU for all your help! He is working hard on getting better. And if there is a human out... https://t.co/RJODEaBH5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuki continues to do well. He is eating and drinkin.
It's confirmed that he is neutered so someone must have... https://t.co/MMsejzy15Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know of a pet shop in town that has reasonable cat food collection? I know about Petland on Camden street... https://t.co/88oTE8KOdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for the wonderful support we got in the past 16 hours! We are floored by the generosity of our... https://t.co/BXBBJBzzEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these safety tips so to make sure your kitty have a Maowry Catsmas... https://t.co/6GAdfSDnk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please help the cat found on 17 December - now named Zuki. Thank you. https://t.co/oHBNMKC2sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE!
Cat (now named Zuki) found in Glasnevin on 17 December is now at Botanic Vet to be treated for starvation... https://t.co/a8CjcpZ76n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VOLUNTEER IMMEDIATELY NEEDED! 
One of us found a cat last night, extremely friend and sweet but in very poor... https://t.co/DgAtWp7Xw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi cat lovers! One of the common reasons we hear when people want to rehome their cat is because of pregnancy.... https://t.co/mYPAI2nSQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! OMG! There is a cat collection at Cath Kidston Grafton I don't have the money for the whole collection! HELP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas shopping for your cat! The Guinea version is already out of stock! Snap up this equally amazing turkey... https://t.co/DSquiXqGxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas shopping for your cat! The Guinea version is already out of stock! Snap this equally amazing turkey... https://t.co/nwjCxq03SZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FREE SHIPPING now offer for these 3 amazing toys! 

- Valerian Cat Pillow from a family farm in Germany by three... https://t.co/iO11r4ITD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down to last Cat Catcher in stock now! Same maker as the world famous Da Bird toy. Once this is gone, I won't get... https://t.co/FpccGesPOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catsmas shopping for your cat or cat lovers in your life!
Dragonfly is by the same maker of the world famous Da... https://t.co/J9B5yaTqgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet you guys don't know I have an extensive cat library at Maow Care HQ. I have uploaded my full collection so... https://t.co/zV940Rx4lu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As featured on Jackson Galaxy's show - My Cat from Hell. Da Bird is the most amazing interactive cat toy. It's... https://t.co/7YUNo8pAIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real men love cats! But we already know that! https://t.co/stPVLoDdoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As featured in Jackson's Galaxy's show - My Cat from Hell. 
We are Ireland's exclusive stockist for Da Bird toy.... https://t.co/L71Snex63V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know we do Gift Voucher? It can be used for cat sitting, behavioural therapy, new parents consultation,... https://t.co/vT8vMeULX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAOW CALENDAR IS HERE NOW!!!

Those of you who wanted them and want to collect please come forward. Fresh out of... https://t.co/KsQdiQSoiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know steps like that at IKEA is really good if you have an older cats? As they age, they might lose... https://t.co/p4bzoboqMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone has a cat like this? ðŸ™€ðŸ™€ðŸ™€ https://t.co/9oUOScQDbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must watch! So many great ideas for environment enrichment! https://t.co/eqOAA3Mxtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat lovers, please join me to express our most sincere condolences to one of our followers Aisling who lost... https://t.co/D7yfNfzHlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having coffee today with Julia from Vets for Cats! Really enjoyable cat chats! https://t.co/ehMkaKEndU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maow Calendar 2017 design is here now!!!

If you want to order your calendar, you can either process it through... https://t.co/d0qppCYONL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went in to a meet and greet today and the new customer has this!!!
It's a cat advent calendar from Lidl... https://t.co/z7xHBZEOFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey cat lovers! 
Thank you so much for your support of yet another year of Maow of the Year competition.... https://t.co/zh9rrMaU7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is better with cats! https://t.co/b9H89uTBBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maow of the Year competition is now over! Thank you everyone for entering their cat for the competition and for... https://t.co/fnBCEZemik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat lovers! Last few hours to vote!! https://t.co/amH75l3EG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you voted yet? Two days left only before closing! https://t.co/TMhBjua6AT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to vote if you haven't already done so! Not a stressful election for a change! https://t.co/VhpKhULsn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Bella, we rescued her 4 years ago, she was just a little kitten when we took her in, since then she has... https://t.co/eI4CfnPMfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are my gentle, beautiful Maine Coon brothers, Raf and Piet. Here they are helping me love from Holland to... https://t.co/Usu9BLkeha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of the year again! Please help us to choose top 10 cats to be our Maow of the Year! They will each... https://t.co/eaIpi0O4Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of the year again! Please help us to choose top 10 cats to be our Maow of the Year! They will each... https://t.co/R2NMrOwbNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always lovely to see a cat loving man...ðŸ˜»ðŸ˜»ðŸ˜» https://t.co/JsY4xB7aU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great tips here! https://t.co/PSXwMg9Fpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 6 newly certified Pet First Responders! You are prepared to help any animals in trouble now! Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the students is down with a flu, anyone interested please step forward! Last spot left! https://t.co/imgQXHH153]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter is coming and I will be doing a lot of this... https://t.co/Dz4L7HLxQr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>