<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Steve Bannon the Second Most Powerful Man in the World? Time Magazine https://t.co/AbtaohxiOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi suggests Donald Trump get his mental health checked https://t.co/Lt3EeHXV7p via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof Richard Wolff tells Thom Hartmann giant corporations who have spent billions on plant in low wage economies will clash wi Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle This looks like a fair assessment of the conditions that are likely to precede terrorism. https://t.co/NeDLG65pJ5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle Sorry. Simplistic US biased explanations I will avoid. I would rather do a search on "terrorism Chomsky" or Ahmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle Which is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps everyone else knows this?Why do radical Moslems become terrorists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u think of all the wars producing refugees, most are wars for resources like oil. So does oil on our land really belong to us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan Times is writing about buying citizenship in New Zealand. Rich? Worried about a possible Trumpocalypse?… https://t.co/Xnnbw89pC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So let's not idealise Obama or Kennedy. Trump's behaviour is a wakeup call for all to examine the history of Americ… https://t.co/AoZbbjJRsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A handy guide for Malcolm Turnbull on dealing with Donald Trump | Dominic Knight https://t.co/R3VngJJCSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too excited about the future of electric vehicles https://t.co/ZkSaJvU5xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And ghastly in Kapiti too. When are we eventually going to get a summer? https://t.co/gHDjljA0ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/WZgn53EAWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenation @jbowtie Can't stand it. Next we will be hearing him say "Nobody, no nobody respects religious freedom more than I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the currency circulates slowly, it does little good. Worgl experiment worked miraculously in 1932.#gesell https://t.co/bbhkE0E7Tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should all be asking the Einstein in us "How do we redesign our political economy for a post fossil fuel age?" L… https://t.co/stPGEVkeAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The importance of velocity of circulation of money and what a small Austrian town did in 1932. We are in #deflation… https://t.co/jGB9jEZlil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All change or no change? – Longreads Long term perspective on Trumpism etc https://t.co/WxI2d5AaYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a great front page to @NafeezAhmed website https://t.co/zJR6iUgfCt
Humanity, knowledge, understanding, compassion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time to mobilise to create the new world that can arise after Trump is right now. Design the post fossil fuel economy from scratch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has left the White House on Marine One on an unannounced trip, White House has not disclosed destination https://t.co/hO1PZj0HAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Monbiot: connection, kayaking and being an uncool dad https://t.co/mfJDNAK4uQ via @positivenewsuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a graph in here of growth of various economies that explains the nostalgia for the past. https://t.co/gRLfZ00iU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon Versus Trump https://t.co/GHurITWkcL 'I suspect Steve Bannon is going to fail to corral the peripatetic brain of Donald Trump']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon Is Given Security Role Usually Held for Generals   https://t.co/9EKkgBCwIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is calling the shots in the White House. That's terrifying | Lawrence Douglas https://t.co/UX98IC8mJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infusing Washington with Goldman alums isn’t exactly an original idea.  He had to do it bigger and better https://t.co/JRyJYSIUDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How climate change is affecting the west of New Zealand's North Island. https://t.co/3AYQebQcUo A gardener adapts. @CubaRaglanGuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the #oil on the planet can’t save a financial system in overshoot, but another world is still possible https://t.co/TRg2dFfL44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-conventional oil like tar sands is what we are going to be relying on https://t.co/TRg2dFfL44 Nafeez Ahmed's ne… https://t.co/s3lWFhK6GI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nafeez Ahmed's brilliant new article on oil, politics, crisis, Trump https://t.co/TRg2dFfL44 #EROI #qualityofoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To overcome our threshold of crisis, a new adaptive, transformative systemic response is urgently required. https://t.co/TRg2dFfL44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not running out of oil, but we have reached a plateau in easy, inexpensive conventional oil production https://t.co/TRg2dFfL44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impeachment or Impairment -- the Inevitability of Trump’s Removal: https://t.co/0FuBJs6I4u’s-removal#.WJE0W-4b_88.twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump’s immigration policies are an opportunity for NZ via garethmorgannz - https://t.co/Z47SGoGvk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news The Opportunities Party Announces Candidate for Mt. Albert via garethmorgannz - https://t.co/S9up7fpKh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Trump is what we needed to stop interfering in other countries, stop making drugs illegal and find a better economic system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marijuana smuggling from Mexico to the US has dropped by 50% from 2010. Many states had decriminalised it! https://t.co/SuRtbtVPBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Nixon declared a war on drugs, the US has spent more than a trillion dollars to fight a losing battle https://t.co/SuRtbtVPBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The simplest way to end the refugee problem is to stop producing refugees.  Pls RT. Stop bombing Muslim countries!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the focus on an immigration ban and not on wars that produce refugees? https://t.co/XTeq10Uh0C  Stop producing refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Trump, “draining the swamp” means filling it with new layers of golden sludge – Nomi Prins https://t.co/ZMeqIHklDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now why would we be surprised? #\Trump has more Goldman Sachs in his administration than any other president. https://t.co/JRyJYSrjeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are giving government back to the people – of Goldman Sachs. https://t.co/JRyJYSrjeX Nomi Prins once worked there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's business interests in middle east exposed even by Bloomberg. https://t.co/FJEGn6cDco. Omitted: countries where he has interet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debate on Trump immigration ban promises to spill into SCOTUS confirmation hearings https://t.co/FJEGn6cDco via @bpolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman CEO takes lead on Wall Street in slamming Trump travel ban https://t.co/YPKYEw0z43 via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delightful Dutch video re making America great again. https://t.co/cXxQk66n7x. We need humour for sanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask PM Bill English to tell President Trump to end Muslim Ban. Sign the petition: https://t.co/0qVPxkztDj via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is America Experiencing A Fast Moving Coup? Make America less safe is actually part of the plan? https://t.co/dKtJFTsQWC via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anvesaka88 @JeffreyGoldberg @vali_nasr @TheAtlantic @davidfrum Didn't quantitative easing cause the precariat that put Trump in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is scary Now address what happened to the world economy after peak oil and bank dominance https://t.co/1cFI5hFqjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkikaye All very nice but can you persuade your boss  to condemn this ban on muslims? Pitiful effort so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ What a brain he had! He did wonders to reform medical politics in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh goodness. This is a challenge to the brain Superb https://t.co/oD8KQ3RR7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans can get rid of Trump by invoking the 25th amendment. No doctors, no impeachment needed. https://t.co/KrEbNC2pkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an embarrassing leader New Zealand has. I guess he would have been one of the last to condemn Hitler's moves,… https://t.co/NKS8pySJoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fastest columns on my tweetdeck are bannon, #theresistance #stoppresidentbannon. I will not rest until #25thamendment goes as fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man behind Trump? Still Steve Bannon https://t.co/u7wp63LA8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just completing my forthcoming e-book called The Big Shift: Rethinking money, tax, welfare and governance for the next economicsystem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelenabartermad I am looking for a shorter phrase or word for "decentralized eco-socialism". @Aybrow @bryankav123]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHartley_ And what is more it is a malignant narcissism too. That psychotherapist's report on Trump. Invoke 25th Amendment Section 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillEnglishMP was slow to respond to an issue causing anguish around the world and his response was inadequate. https://t.co/wvI635Y73Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals in America Please listen to Robert Fisk + Noam Chomsky and discover who you have bombed all round the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing pictures of New Yorkers protesting on @AlJazeera "we are a nation of immigrants" Statue of Liberty backdrop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry @BillEnglishMP ur just not convincing on the #migrantban and seem so "relaxed" you deserve to flop . 24 hours too late too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems as though John Key has left a 'very relaxed' cabinet . First Bill English then Nathan Guy today @JohnJCampbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our most important allies in the fight against ISIL are the vast majority of Muslims who reject its apocalyptic ideology of hatred. McCain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From someone is a distant country, I urge you to keep doing all in your power to avert WW3. Thank you. Please RT https://t.co/LwoyMJ0V1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain From New Zealand, I admire what you are doing to counter #trump and #bannon in their irrational provocative program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between them these Republicans will have to study the 25th amendment to get rid of #trump without impeachment. Easy as..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important list of allies for those who oppose Trump and his dangerous appointment of #bannon https://t.co/VQiNx6fAK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Bannon flattered and coaxed Trump on policies key to the alt-right https://t.co/z8KGwClkc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz RNZ this morning 11.30 politics session. Near the end, Matthew Hooten predicted #topnz will do well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IonaPannett There are several judges now but the Homeland Security ignores court rulings.. Constitutional crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi, Emeritz etc omitted from the #travelban Fisk doesn't mince words here https://t.co/XxF1UmUySB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America has bombed, directly or indirectly, five of the seven nations on Trump’s banned list. https://t.co/clxYeXhBr3 Robert Fisk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we expect US embassies to have 3 queues for visa applicants. One for Muslims, 1 for Christians, and a 3rd marked ‘Other?’: Fisk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Slams McCain, Graham: "Stop Trying To Start World War III" | Zero Hedge https://t.co/xLnKhyt5uG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They Don’t Just Hide Their Money. Economist Says Most of Billionaire Wealth is Unearned. https://t.co/SurhIQGTOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone invent a short synonym for "decentralized eco-socialism" please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer Nadal battle the best form of reality tv Don't miss it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mikhail Gorbachev: 'It looks as if all the world is preparing for war' https://t.co/JxrwGTzSZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBRMark More like how Trump will destabilize an already precarious global economy #debt #assetbubbles + past peak of unconventional oil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot He does already Follow Mark Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A massive spike in insider selling since inauguration https://t.co/bIXkU8Yj9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Bannon wants to destroy the state... https://t.co/PptQuaebp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Charlie! https://t.co/P9GmnMlfN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @cjsbishop @TrevorMallard Bishop is waiting to get a steer from his boss. #Ethics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @Robert2909 So this is corruption at its wors. Impeachable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmmoore Would u be interested in enquiring about finding a way for good republicans to use 25th amendment s4 removing Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked my student why he voted for Trump. The answer was thoughtful, smart, and terrifying. https://t.co/5X8YVS4JW6 via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justsayingDMY @ajthompson13 @pmbillenglish Pull the other leg!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol So how come the video is not available for viewing in New Zealand? Because we are part of the Five Eyes club?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US judge halts Donald Trump's immigration order after airport chaos erupts across nation – New Zealand paper https://t.co/f7WV6jAUeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like the staff at Homeland Security are going to have to defy orders. Bannon with Nazi views is in charge now. #stoptrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcalabra Well if you liked my tweet about invoking the 25th amendment section 4, please RT #stoptrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish Your duty as a PM is to denounce Trump's ban on Muslims. First they came for the Jews, then they came for the...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish Come on Bill. Will you turn away families, children and discriminate on the grounds of religion? #muslimban]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>