<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham You'll be needing a tin hat at this rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gemofagite Merry Christmas ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsPriddleX It's contagious!! I like it ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard first Christmas song of 2017 - a little girl walking in Shanklin was singing Jingle Bells. Merry Christmas ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Come back 2016, all is forgiven]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham He can have mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham What state were the shoes in when he came home from school?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham They look nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance French Boulangerie, wish we had one here. Have a great week - from a wet IoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you next year https://t.co/ZmlWKaretx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFranceShow I'd head to 1st floor to hear @ianmodmoore &amp; @lillyzazou &amp; the culinary displays (in fact I did on Friday &amp; enjoyed it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore It's a hard life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance We'll agree with that! Could be another reason for liking France!! ðŸ˜€ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore Very funny Yann, and I hope this afternoon goes well (&amp; your journey home)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very good read. I won't spoil it but the Netherlands get a mention ðŸ˜€ https://t.co/Ma4ZKRmth5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance @UK_FranceFR @franceiine @ParisJeTaime @atoutfranceukpr Beautiful is right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham T**g has more subtle means. It involves claws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gemofagite Love the photos ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful day in #Normandie https://t.co/xYqflc57ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannef55 How do you get an odd 62p?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Sounds familiar. The only time ours go out is to fertilise the garden - and then they're straight back in wanting feeding ðŸ˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham @Number10cat I can get you two feline helpers, as well as more dreamies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannef55 @SkyNews Couldn't have put it better myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham I wonder what Cruella's hidden agenda is? World domination with the Orange One?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes 2 of us https://t.co/V0rQSBWsnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Saw this &amp; thought of you xx https://t.co/tnKHfXrCo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images What a beautiful place. I can see why Monet liked the place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sproccotask That's what I thought (saves on refilling the glass too)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Perhaps the nylon stretches xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gemofagite You're famous - you'll be giving autographs soon ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds a very good idea https://t.co/jsjQUwUEdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham It quite possibly does untune itself, metal strings can expand in heat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lillyzazou Well if today was anything to go by you'll do well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore Oh yes. Front row, cat owner who'd read your books. We thoroughly enjoyed your performance. Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham You're doing well, just work at it and you'll get to be an accomplished player. Just a little bit a day. Use S as a singerðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lillyzazou You did! Wonderful performance. Thoroughly enjoyed it ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another photo of #LillyZazou at @TheFranceShow https://t.co/IQPU8wohR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LillyZazou on stage at the @TheFranceShow Okympia London. She was good. Merci Lilly https://t.co/Iy6G63b1oS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore Looking forward to seeing you this afternoon ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jan_Marshall Thanks Jan. Have a good weekend xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Look forward to it!!  Happy compiling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Another reason is their wine. Cheers ðŸ¾ðŸ·ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance 1 reason I like France is they have much better manners than the UK (&amp; yes you can quote me). Still like their cakes though ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Delicious is the first description that comes to mind (&amp; better than cakes in UK). Ok for starters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images We stumbled across Falaise by accident - and keep going back. We love the place ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham When ever I see her or hear about her I keep singing Cruella de Ville!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Falaise. Great Chateau, interesting market on Saturday and as for the cafes... ðŸ˜€ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡·ðŸ˜€ https://t.co/rkMfGrPwPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runalongwomble @ZoeMarkham It's time for the IoW to declare UDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannef55 You certainly have!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraging news for #CF sufferers. #CureCF https://t.co/JW4CNWXx9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad Paisley - Today. Love this song https://t.co/j09TEqhCur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this song, Today by Brad Paisley https://t.co/DncUAGCP1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runalongwomble @ZoeMarkham Makes three of us then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham He's a dead loss. I used to vote Labour, not while he's in charge. Not voting for Cruella either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images You're welcome ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham That is so true ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Well done!! (on doing well on the diet that is!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Agreed. Sod Corbyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElfieHaupt Looks cold but nice. Hope you're ok Elfie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachs_charlie &amp; the rest of the year! Thankfully it hasn't the stigma it used to have. Hope you're ok. Hugs xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images Looks a nice place to relax in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance @ParisJeTaime @loco2 Looks delicious. Better than you get on IoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yes! Now that sounds a good idea ðŸ˜€ https://t.co/6uZACoUMW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannef55 I thought of you when our local BBC radio station broadcast the result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Sounds fun ðŸ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Very wise young man ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham AA 12 steps? Is that where car breaks down, wait hours...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacksC93 @Normandythennow So will I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't we do this in England? https://t.co/8JKKNgfmY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Normandythennow What a great read. Enjoyed how you came across the village - &amp; the diary was quite amusing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting reading!! https://t.co/hms7bu8iQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Looks a good place to visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Your mission, to boldly go where no one has gone before...  BTW it's foggy here (&amp; cold)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham What did you have in mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Yes but Cruella thinks she IS sovereign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore You seem to have this spot on. Look forward to seeing you at the @TheFranceShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham That's why I play a tuba - but all the best to you. Look forward to seeing you on You Tube ðŸŽ¶ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sproccotask @tourscotland Can't stand Trump (or Theresa May) and I like the description]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful place to visit https://t.co/zU5DQAe9tX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifefrance Cheese and I disagree, unfortunately. Mrs S however loved a goats cheese she had in #Normandie, but she can't remember the name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachs_charlie Happy penguin awareness day xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham You are so right (as usual ðŸ˜€) xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham You'll have to read it when Small has gone to bed ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham So when he's a famous author (like his mum)...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham I didn't know that!!  Thanks Small]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Normandie open road. Wonderful! #MagnifiqueFrance https://t.co/3ZjO95qweZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham As you say no need for that, but my cat 'T' &amp; I will sort them out for you if you want. You'll get there one day, keep going xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Pleased the meds are working and she's more positive. Pass on our love. Thinking of you too xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Hope the treatment works #FingersCrossed xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Any news on your mum?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Totally agree!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham And that's just the children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jan_Marshall Hi Jan. Hope you're keeping well. Take care xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham Fingers crossed here too. Wishing her all the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeMarkham I've got one like that, Ruby (aka Her Majesty)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images You're welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@france_images I try to take photos of 2CVs whenever I see them. Not many on the IoW these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Normandythennow An interesting but sad tale. Thanks for sharing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacksC93 like the photo Jackie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmodmoore Enjoyed reading your blog. Can't wait for the next book!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>