<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickyPDillon it's literally 4am and I'm watching your videos so yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankieJGrande @joangrande she should teach you how to follow me ;) see what I did there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatrygood ryan, what's your fave song off of Empires by Hillsong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlfredoFlores watch this, it will change your life. I promise. https://t.co/w56uWgdoKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we have great convos https://t.co/5Q2LnLHVmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ballingerstbh PAIGE WTF I LOVE YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bubstinbieber YOU'RE TOO KIND, PRETTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my faves I'm so in love â¤ï¸ https://t.co/Vq6ylGs4Zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm literally only posting this because my friend has a really cute mirror âœ¨ https://t.co/eh6iLEdy7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rachleen and plaid. a concept. https://t.co/1uqthxHC6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT MIC DROP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ballingerstbh Paige dance for me and I'll pretend to be youðŸ˜… all for the notice ðŸ¤ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefenColalillo my grandfather uses emojis! https://t.co/F29GNfHp9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cwahlyyy hey bois https://t.co/U3P0jGYX8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zoe and Hailey are best friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colleensgeek daughter you're so pretty I'm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller happy eat chilli and chips and chicken wings and other greasy food day!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look how cute https://t.co/mrjKzczxQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ballingerstbh @MissRBaller Paige we agreed not to speak of the zucchini again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellaisabella13 why didn't she sing bing bong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel plays the iMessage games. Uhm Rachel hit a girl up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love coming home to a Rachel livestream ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadyleen I love how you tagged me first god bless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually feel like all my friends irl are always annoyed by me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colleensgeek OMG WHAT THE FRICK FOR REAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller I've been inactive all day and I come back to this. IM SOBBING. THE DOGGY IS SO CUTEðŸ˜­ https://t.co/7ActfnMZ34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol i just got drunk heather and shay to sing baby by justin bieber. i love life. @HeatherKONeill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tonight my youth pastor, who I consider friend, told me she was proud of me and that's the first time in a while someone has told me that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller good morning!! Make sure you do your candy crush spin.. gotta get those free boosters gurlðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 goood morning queen!! Have a great Saturday, ILYðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning y'all gonna be pretty inactive today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night. I love them so much. They make me happy. ðŸ’œ https://t.co/1Mt4zWQyJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller gooodnight Rachel!!! I'm so excited at the thought of you having a live show and your daily vlogs. I love youuuuðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 goodnight gurl!!! Thank you for everything you've done for me. You mean so much to me. I love you ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller I'm at a hotel and I realized how bad the lighting is but there's outlets on the lamp in between both beds so it's a bonus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to listen to the actual version of Closer and some how my brain literally made me say bing and bong. I love life!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just realized I haven't listened to bing bong today. Such a tragedy. Gonna do that now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_s_hawkins and on the 7th day god created Jonathan Hawkins, and it was good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 I love you and you mean so much to me! Thanks for always inspiring me. ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUSTIN IS BACK ON INSTAGRAM IM NOT OKAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdbcolleen basically they've taken over my life. Like someone will say hey everybody and I'm like wow Rachel Ballinger exists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idk if it's just me but somehow I relate everything to Colleen and Rachel and like I'll be in class and just zone off and think about them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller RACHEL FYI THIS IS BIG EXCITING NEWS!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAHAHHA CHRIS AND JESS AND GWEN AND TIM AND COLLEEN AND TRENT ARE ALL GONNA BE SUPPORTING RACHEL AT HER SHOWS. ASK ME IF IM OKAY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine a machel hugging pic. I'm actually sobbing right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdbcolleen AND IF COLLEEN GOES TO SUPPORT HER YOU GET LIKE THE HQ PICS WITH RACHEL AND THE CUTE CANDIDS WITH COLLEEN IM NOT OKAY SKSKSKSKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdbcolleen to see Rachel? Well, if Rachel has her own show people are going to be showing up for HER!!!! Like, I'm sobbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[okay here I am getting really emo but like you know how Rachel supports Colleen at some of her shows and after you meet Colleen you get -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMAGINE A MONTAGE TO START OFF THE SHOW OF JUST RACHEL SAYING "HEY EVERYBODY"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller you know Toronto is a big city in Canada right?  Don't neglect us xooxox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littleballer_24 hey look colleen noticed us!!! https://t.co/CEbUtQ0dON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller did you do your candy crush spin today?? Gotta get those boosters gurl!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would buy this hands down. (Edited by @qtballingerx) https://t.co/iN3oefqF22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my favourite tweet to this day https://t.co/YbAxFP9INz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherKONeill tell Jon to get back on twitter and snapchat. Love, me and @shadyleen xoxox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller yay you're finally getting your hair cut! https://t.co/1kD4dzT9Ww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning @MissRBaller ! Don't forget to do your free candy crush booster spin, lol. I hope today is great. I love you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just voted for @colleenb123 for youtuber of the year #ShortyAwards. https://t.co/6lkVbjJsJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night. These two have a special place in my heart. ðŸ’œ https://t.co/vfZNOUDq6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night @ColleenB123! Your dedication has always inspired me, this week more than ever!! You're so amazing. I love you. Feel better ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night @MissRBaller. Thank you for always making me so happy!! You mean the world to me. Love you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 3:42 am. I have to be up at 6. Why am I awake??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleheartcmb OK TRUE. both are iconic af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdbcolleen i'm also trying to nail the lyrics but i can't seem to get the Bing to Bong ratio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmbjustin are you ready for your life to be changed for the better??
.
.
https://t.co/Dopfqeu7gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefenColalillo omg me too i literally watched them last night and was dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rachel is the literal love of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm currently listening to Bing Bong for the 5th time in a row. How's your night going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissRBaller do you still shave your left armpit first? #rachelsroom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLEASE @ColleenB123 https://t.co/l7owBh5V9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmbjustin IM A LEO TOOO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 explain what poutine is to the people who don't know what it is. #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 make this the last question or I'll unstan #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 #ColleensCorner how does one properly stalk a fan on twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 veggie tales or haters back off??  #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 thoughts on Justin Bieber?  #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 what's your favourite thing about Canada ? #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 when you watch other YouTubers do you prefer vlogs or main channel content? #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 if you had to move out of America right now where would you want to live #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 rap about tea #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 would you rather never be able to eat cookies again or never be able to eat Taco Bell again? #colleenscorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 do you have any more emo diary entry's you can read #ColleensCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 10 people liked this the people have spoken we would like to know https://t.co/DDl3PBexAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenB123 when was the last time you washed your bra? #colleenscorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Korsoto gonna be a lit time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadyleen @ColleenB123 @MissRBaller okay u literally probably live like 25 minutes away from them now that you're in LA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok new layout thanks to @Gmusic99. Literally the best layout maker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MirandaSings you also love Patrick but you betrayed him rude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wear pink forever so I can die happy https://t.co/7Xx1SFAPV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you're gorgeous ihy https://t.co/zG3DfleVNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay why do I stan the hottest people ever. https://t.co/3NfeKwMWsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@qtballingerx okay you're a cutie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afichonado you're a stunner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just took a 20 minute shower to avoid all the work I have to do and realized I basically just gave myself less time to do my work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perflenator THAT FIRST PIC. YOURE STUNNING. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whenever we do selfies for colleen and  rachel I realize how wonderful and beautiful this fandom is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@halaxrachleen OKAY YOU'RE PERFECT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danifishkin1 thank you so much, but gurl look who's talking!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ballingerstbh hi you're hot af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SelfiesForRachel https://t.co/XFy1KNWTtN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>