<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardCowley2 UNBELIEVABLE!! What's the world coming to. We're suppose to just let over testosteroned boys do what they want?? Think not!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe if I poke the ragger, it will dry faster. https://t.co/uVbtZcPNgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellie isn't happy because she has to wait for her daggers to dry after being washed this afternoonðŸ˜®ðŸ˜® https://t.co/cHwwwRb4sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyMeanie What a twat. Janet, WAKE UP!! Its NOT dress up time at preschool.ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@decisiveman AMEN to that.ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthYeoFarm Good grief. How ridiculous.ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badpenny1931 Or it's a confirmation that they agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheepio Thanks for thatðŸ˜¨ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerphill1983 @IrishFarmerette Hope it gets thoroughly cleaned ..... oh sod it just buy a new one for the kitchen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowdenJohn @rattycastle We have a Doris 3 doors down. A former minister who has a potty mouth &amp; has a bad temper to boot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie the park toss bags of food waste over their fence. It just beggars belief the rubbish I find on my walk every morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie to be. Smashed glass bottles are the worst. Cleaned up the remains of 2 bottles this morning. Even ppl whose houses back onto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie it all again. The hooligans have burnt 2 of the 4 bins in the park &amp; ppl are still throwing bagged dog poo where the bins used]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie Sometimes I spend more time picking up rubbish than actually walking with my dogs. You pick it up on Monday &amp; Tuesday you can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture expensive, in the thousands of Â£Â£Â£. A lot different from the $5-10 admin fee, sign here and swear allegiance to the Queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture I'm not going round calling myself an Aussie Brit. I've done the written tests &amp; have residence permit - citizenship is very]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture Totally agree. Even though I've been in the UK for 11yrs, I won't hand over my Aussie passport. Bit hypercritical, I know but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie to stop them. You should see the rubbish left behind after weekend fixtures. Disgusting. No respect for anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie And the little kids who play football think its funny to stomp on the plants. Neither the parents nor the coaches say anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie I didn't know little girls knew such dreadful language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie spoke to him. When I told a little girl to stop picking the daffs ....ðŸ˜¨ðŸ˜± I was so shocked with what came out of her mouth. I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warmwoolie Last yr a man in his late 60's or so picked a HUGE bunch. I got photos of him doing it &amp; asked why he did it but ran away when I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick I've replanted a lot of Blue bells &amp; planted several varieties of alliums so with the daffs, it should be a nice show this yr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick next door digging them up. https://t.co/C8ZHqWCJtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick Some are still short but others are quite tall. I've had to put mesh over the bulbs to stop the cat from https://t.co/LSnUzgeko5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture I really don't understand this 'I'm a Lebanese Australian' or whatever. This is only a recent thing &amp; should be stopped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture 4yrs later when we applications for citizenship, we handed in our old passports. We were AUSTRALIAN &amp; had no need for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussiefuture In 1968, my family moved to Oz from Europe. When the plane landed in Sydney my dad said "from now on we only speak English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp @BBCNews If I told you what I want to do to this lowlife, I'd probably be arrested for inciting violence or somethingðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinksRobbie Stunningly beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick @warmwoolie huge bunches, kids run over them, pull the flowers off &amp; throw them around. I get ready ticked off when I see itðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick @warmwoolie We have lots planted in the park at the back of our place. Every yr I look forward to the blooms &amp; every yr ppl pick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick The ones in the garden will probably start blooming next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheepio "Mmmmmmm, nice software" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1GarethWynJones @achrisevans @ScottQuinnell Looking forward to the programme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoryInPicture @SueStradPhoto My bro always has a habit of doing that. I'll never forgive him for the nasty email he sent last MarchðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheepio When we were kids, my bro &amp; I used to tell every one they were made of crushed nits &amp; flies ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ more for us ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatashaDeVil I'm so with you there. I don't want to watch TV or news. It's either "who's died" or "WTF is Trump up to now"ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHeughan @karenandmimi @leanneaguilera You have come so far my kilted one ..... Sam, honey, you do know how may books there are?!!?ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian @croquetfgarcia Made my children's clothing too &amp; now finishing a dress for my 90yr old mum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian @croquetfgarcia Been making my own clothes for 43yrs. Skirts &amp; trousers were too short, tops &amp; blouses never fitted properly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmFanOne @sheepio I live in "sounds like a different language" land that most people think is actually part of England but WE'RE NOTðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willpenrievans And may I say Will, you AND your wife have done a brilliant job ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thartsalot why bother stay up?!ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thartsalot Tia is sweet. We feed all the dogs when madam gets us up &amp; then go back to bed 3/4hr later as they do so https://t.co/1geSnoRrdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thartsalot Yep. 3 1/2 yrs of this &amp; the novelty has well &amp; truly worn off. Tia has done that since puppyhood. Nothing we can do to stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huwthomas_Wales @cardiffcouncil @welshlabour needed. It's in an appallingly state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huwthomas_Wales @cardiffcouncil @welshlabour Rd. We had a letter to say the FOOTPATH was going to be resurfaced, something desperately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huwthomas_Wales @cardiffcouncil @welshlabour I'd like to know who was responsible for traffic calming islands to be removed in Tweedsmuir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp How are you doing, lovely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp Very timely post. Woke with sinus pain - right side of my face - head, eyes, ear, cheek bone, nose &amp; sore teeth ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janelouise0911 @HandmadeHour Starting cast off row on latest shawl. Only 446 stitches instead of the usual 1000's. https://t.co/0ugp8UHvhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cldwrites I thought it was Saturday too, then I realised the MiL was going out today so it must be FridayðŸ™Œ so still have the wk'end aheadðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thartsalot Mine usually does that EVERY morning. Got to sleep in this morning to 4:50amðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twisted0909 @SP_EnergyPeople islands taken away at 3 points. Street now a race track!ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twisted0909 @SP_EnergyPeople Letter from Cardiff council informed us of footpath resurfacingðŸ™Œ badly needs doing. Instead, traffic calming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stan_sdcollins Good morning Stan. Gorgeous photo. Well worth getting up for. ðŸ™‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 The only problem with the bread being so delicious is that it doesn't last long.ðŸ˜° We're supposed to be on a dietðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 I put in a bit more dried yeast as the recipe calls for, leave it to rise for twice as long which gives open texture. DelishðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 Wholemeal/multi grain. Do my own &amp; basically throw everything in it. No probs with MiL pinching any, she only eats whiteðŸ˜±ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilkDamask @philamuseum Absolutely beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 Oh yummy. Made some bread today. https://t.co/jRYfFjfq0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stan_sdcollins Great photo. My son loves doing B&amp;W photography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick Ooooppps, yes I did. A huge parcel of material. Glad my partner was out. Quickly hid parcel under the bedðŸ˜ to be retrieved laterðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick 2mins after I wrote the 'amnesia' tweet, a UPS van pulled upon front of my house. I was about to say "I don't remember buying .."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizLovick I have that with yarn AND material. I have amnesia when it comes to both.ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ Hope it was as delicious as it looked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paraicodonnell Good God, did someone nick his gummy bears &amp; swap them with sour snakes. ðŸ˜¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionagraham13 Stop it, stop it!!!! My stomach is growling BIG TIMEðŸ˜±ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mamalonglegs @ZwartblesIE @aplayfulday @BBCCountryfile @isleyarns Don't forget, there are many other sheep farmers in UK are doing same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheepio That's where he belongs IMOðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColvinLouise My heart goes out to the LGBT family/community in the States. It will be a new 'Dark Age' ðŸ˜–ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenPtbo @RichardCowley2 @JustinTrudeau @CarolHusband Honour killings ARE barbaric &amp; have no place in civilised society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraceySpicer @OurWatchCEO @OurWatchAus @newscomauHQ Should've just cleaned out my deemed &amp;walked out. That last 4 days was absolutely hellðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraceySpicer @OurWatchCEO @OurWatchAus @newscomauHQ Got my marching orders day after Oz Day. Told boss I had the right to 1 wk's notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KRihanoff @MuntBmunt Stop moaning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuntBmunt @KRihanoff When it comes to that, Big Brother should be the first to go along with Gogglebox. Neither watched nor want to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KRihanoff @MuntBmunt all of life. If you're bored with telly, do something else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KRihanoff @MuntBmunt You can always change channels, watch a DVD or switch off &amp; read a book or play Scrabble. A TV is NOT the be all &amp; end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of making one of Trump. Maybe using 4" nails instead of pins. https://t.co/NoX0XX7icW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColvinLouise He has the idea that now he's #POTUS, he thinks he can run the country like 1 of his companies. He's in for a rude awakening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melkettle We saw it last wk. When the grandmother said she was "the crazy lady; every village has to have one", I was gone, tears flowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColvinLouise If he wants a fight, ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColvinLouise I thought it was a joke at first. What we've been working/striving for +20yrs has been wiped out in secondsðŸ˜±ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitScotland Absolutely worth it! WOW!!ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmersOfTheUK You have one smart little girl there.ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineMatch1 @missmuckyduck around the house all day.ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineMatch1 @missmuckyduck It did, Christine but it was too cold &amp; dampish to hang the towels out. Have had them drying on the heaters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OurWatchCEO @OurWatchAus @TraceySpicer @newscomauHQ In 1979, I was fired from my job for getting engaged. No discrimination laws then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineMatch1 @missmuckyduck that need washing AND drying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineMatch1 @missmuckyduck Not in Cardiff. Dull &amp; grey like yesterday. Hope the rain stays away as I have a huge load of very mucky dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilkDamask Crisp,  clean &amp; summery. Very nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionaLakeAus Run like the devil's on your tail coz the sand is soooooooo effin hot it will burn your feet ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp Wasn't any use. Same GP wrote letter to judge during our divorce that made LT look like he was in I'll health - he wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp reported my visits &amp; what was discussedðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp GP told my(then, now very ex) husband I'd been to see him. So much for patient confidentiality. Changed GP as other one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp glass of red wine &amp; to stop bothering him. ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp Heard them all. And my favourite "you don't look like you're depressed". GP sent me home &amp; told me to go home &amp; have a large]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowangelmrsp Thank you. I also make earrings and bracelets and knit &amp; crochet scarves &amp; shawls. https://t.co/LU8ONuYoA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marygnip Ya think???? Don't get you're hopes up :(]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>