<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Spread middle at november 1st for first assassination attempt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Ruby pops it he loses 2-3l and probably race. Relied on horse to wing it and horse didn't respond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blaming Ruby seems stupid. Horse galloped at the fence and didn't put himself right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alrigg @Betfred Fred got to find his ways to take a bit of % on the refreshments. 60% on the swinger ain't gonna pay billz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alrigg @Betfred hearing you bought the lot and went down Albert park with some knock off Bacardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan piss off you enormous pig headed cunt sausage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KBAndersen @KermodeMovie the one in the sea off florida quite exceptional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Elgin price vs Neon Wolf is just wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gentsdeal you still playing in the 4th div of the Filipino darts league btw?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 Kinloch, 6/4 Coral]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carvillshill Brain Power has the Seagulls kind of profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a lovely big unit and has all the potential to be 155 and more but should 1.75 over estimates him imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This American Tom is far too short. Price is making him ~155 horse on his 4th run with fragile substance to what he's done so far. Lay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some mad yokes out there taking sub 2.20 Thistlecrack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick Traynor is a yoke #ridiculousnonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caspar_Lee my friend Erin wants to give you a big &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markthecard @kemptonparkrace @gcunning12 what was expected?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The British people can actually go fuck themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moroccans everywhere!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Least Aidan now knows he has to train 20+ group 1 winners in the year to be recognised as the best trainer in ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland playing well but christ Australia have been fucking dreadful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably just me but not having this Ireland price at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only assume Nevo drinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelgolby friend came round eating cooked chicken from his trouser pocket. Went ballistic and called his parents. Friend never returned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AD is just a phenomenal writer. https://t.co/giNipbBgrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devastated. Rest in Peace Simonsig. You were be able to canter all over everything upstairs now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest chaser we'll ever see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An all time great and my hero. Very sad we'll never see him again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus America you really have some ignorant, retarded fuckwits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony for all those who voted for him is that he'll make deals and screw over anyone he pleases in an instant. He'll be hated by all 1yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that baffles me is how so many women could have such little self respect or solidarity &amp; vote for a rampant misogynist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smith on University Challenge. Beavis or Butthead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in peace you massive tool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this Flintshire price is silly really. He's been winning pony races at no price. They might be over the top but F &amp; HR coupled against these]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikespence8 absolutely with you here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Capri should be more like 4/6 poke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Australian bred horse in the Melbourne Cup... one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gentsdeal #thewifeisleverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gentsdeal #prayfortherefswife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In his entire coaching career, this will be the biggest price a Guardiola team has ever gone off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[accordingly to this woman you're not supposed to expect much when you're 9/2 in the King George]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[saara might actually be my favourite act on x factor ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[saara is so good its actually unfair. Shame she's from abroad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as much as I love Idaho as an animal how the hell is he odds on on firm ground in such a tight race?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky should be hauled before Ofcom for putting matches like this on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidjohnsonTF my head hit the table hard there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if Piers Morgan was running for office it would make sense. But his idiocy seems to be bereft of purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilBlundell ah the lads only play on when it's Showtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carvillshill didn't Aidan try that in the MC a few years back &amp; get hauled in front of stewards?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This OOSG price looks wrong. Hardly had a tough season. 2 wks plenty of time &amp; this bunch wld be tailed off in any Arc ever run. Shd b 4/6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Type have a valid MO, but not having an antepost book or even anything at all 5pm b4 Champions day cant be good for business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you're not having your conks on the 20's US Army Range ew then you're doing it wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my love for Henrik Stenson is actually becoming worrying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fucking have him Rors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please fuck off. please please please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at the point where the result of the match is irrelevant as long as McIlroy destroys Reed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speith &amp; Reid are absolutely floored. Stenson &amp; Rose are a smash up at 2.14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeejayOV2 be surprised if it gets softer than leopardstown the last day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeejayOV2 how soft can it get now though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I assume the lads are going to adjust this alice springs price on the show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the boy is just unreal sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In sporting terms being 4-0 down this early is not very significant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was upsetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May my eyes never see that unibet ad again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found really is some beast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RacingTrends fighting fifth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Elliptical looks better than her price in the 15:40. Miles the best last time when totally missed it. Bundles of natural ability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITV are really blowing this aren't they.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck are you supposed to do when your mother checks up on you on a night out ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sutts109 wagon morons. Have a drink. 
 Fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[here's what damages Racing's image: twatty whinging bookmakers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this should be some craic...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hahahaha let the hedging commence. Bit late now lads. https://t.co/GF16i582c6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning's biggest revelation is how many still watch the morning line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[absolute fucking standard today. 8 wide. FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martial has an ex wife?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikespence8 played squire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[each way yankee today. Consecutively each have been gubbed at 1.04, 1.16. 1.1, 1.05. lolz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilBlundell alongside the emergence of his voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This golf is astonishing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coolmore, who I'd say is the best part of a stone worse than Ballydoyle has now beaten her twice :'-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alrigg Robert Kilroy Silk looks like he's been on the booze in France for 3 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales or Portugal in the final lols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hating the rural, elder working class has never been so easy. You've simply fucked yourselves &amp; your prospects til kingdom come. Cunts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[be some craic if he failed a drug test now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seems like all the other players have decided Dustin should win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the one thing DJ has in his favour here is that he's as thick as two short planks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what the hell has happe3ned to DJ? 4/9 to even money on the machine in 2 mins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and in one fell fucking swoop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finishes last or beaten trading odds on. Game by the nutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i suppose the only solace this week is that im not doing my bollocks travelling around France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok Roy has definitely lost it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales are absolutely floored here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[comes off the defender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bye Woy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they'll trot out that it isn't their national sport, but Wales are shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savage claims it cant be handball if you're not looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if England showed a modicum of patience here this would come easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for the love of god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found too big here. No guarantee whatsoever that the jolly will go round here.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>