<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Has everyone in Tea Party gone mad ?! Seriously! RT https://t.co/c3UQzSxUsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is always prayer! RT https://t.co/4RubaEZaSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a very naughty silly boy! RT https://t.co/T5cfkS9fyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now it's time for him to go too! RT https://t.co/imeiKLaI9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Brandis is now rewarded and made the High Commissioner of U.K.! Go figure! RT https://t.co/bvQvJctVTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should never have been allowed to run without disclosure first ! RT https://t.co/JcCVCphOWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been only one week!!!!RT https://t.co/ump6zxS7qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hero! Stand up for what is right! RT https://t.co/2sPwg8T85U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon just can't make these fraudsters stupidity up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what a hero looks like! RT https://t.co/9LV5uw1MUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of you Sally, and the USA should be too! RT https://t.co/Uh8w9w14wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Sally!!! Proud of you! RT https://t.co/JCJc1ynk4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koch brothers too! Too hot to handle!RT https://t.co/CIRRXWUy3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC she chose ethics and morals over money! Good for her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is so lucky to be free of his regime! She chose ethics over money!RT https://t.co/Wxcxw6E5ay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/EIuncQlNQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm spoke on US policy before? Why not now?! RT https://t.co/XhGsmso5kF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attacker a white supremacist murderer! You should mention that! RT https://t.co/lXSJptFhYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DobsonJan @bbclornag sadly, I think this is true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is our Foreign Minister?! Having fun in Hollywood! #MuslimBan https://t.co/m31yC2hFFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are Oz demonstrations?!RT https://t.co/AlPbe0N8aR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sychophants rule eh?! So Oz ok makes things fine? RT https://t.co/Z4RQg8xYz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is his job?! Ask Murdoch? RT https://t.co/tuVpisMpwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third Reich?! RT https://t.co/VAYl3J27Cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let them eat cake! RT https://t.co/EdO7VxauLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdoch is an American! Bit awkward eh SkyNews?! RT https://t.co/YSaGsM5xBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man of courage and principal. Where us our Govt?! Sigh! RT https://t.co/YmGWcALxxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNP learns nothing! RT https://t.co/PiVZs10yy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when she criticized Gillard for going glam! RT https://t.co/gACJOlb87v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CybrarianPete @SkyNewsAust @GChristensenMP Shame on you David, expected so much more from you. #racist nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't make this stuff up! RT https://t.co/UKPShHztCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda hard not to feel ill! We know who pays for this dont we!RT https://t.co/r7KugwTGxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you seen this?!@MarkDiStef Yikes! RT https://t.co/UiKzaZr0DT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post truth media are known to us all! MT Trump Supporters Are Playing With Fire: Welcome To The Age Of Unreason - https://t.co/xJGgRFQXGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly! What has Turnbull given away! RT https://t.co/tKauw0YYtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great read RT The First Lesson Of Trump’s America For Australia: Take The Far-Right Seriously - https://t.co/sdmYURRrWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/EIuncQlNQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! Trump is crazy! Is this a democracy or a dictatorship?! RT https://t.co/zQZ3aFj90B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He stood there and clapped when Trump signed! RT https://t.co/EBvEJjfMkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um...you know the answer to that question! RT https://t.co/qzb6zSC44A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau says Canada will take refugees banned by U.S. https://t.co/QyqDCSRYVz via @NewsHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNP are rubbish managers! RT https://t.co/wtRieq18xA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is also terrifying! Putin has helped Trump schism the United States of America! RT https://t.co/1vdWFbcdqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US airports on frontline as Trump immigration ban causes chaos and controversy https://t.co/4hc69Gweq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet @HkarterKarter did they color coordinate or just know the power dressing of red and black! Yikes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNP getting rid of the moderates! RT https://t.co/elSGQsIR5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clive James: ‘We are told, over and over, that President Trump will destroy the world. How do people know this?’ https://t.co/PG0Wh71GHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for gold: Trump, Louis XIV and interior design https://t.co/N0Orapdx4c via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a waste of space! At least he had a lovely holiday on us! RT https://t.co/8KOmyUyGfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just imagine the saving if we didn't buy the Jets! RT https://t.co/q4qXwEDvh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly he has been appeasing all and sundry as PM RT https://t.co/uaRgqqA4NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Susan Ley get offered an ambassadorship too?! RT https://t.co/vrwIlRsVLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do these MPs actually work?! RT https://t.co/lhP2LC4w4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what Brexits Theresa May has done! RT https://t.co/93rS4XHEkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so it begins! Fascism! RT https://t.co/ezNTzZ3tqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! Please don't normalize this dangerous fool! RT https://t.co/AKIxiUdg3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of "tools"!!!RT https://t.co/8xvOlOZVJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet your bottom dollar! It's all on us!RT https://t.co/Zy2Nxq0K8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hasn't power and wanting to keep it, changed Turnbull! RT https://t.co/sB70N6mzm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dangerous oafish narcissistic fool! RT https://t.co/iJJSOvYsC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/EIuncQlNQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May is the new Chamberlain! Crawling to Trump! Icky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is Oz path under LNP! RT https://t.co/mLuSj2GLFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pandora's box! Anyone can then be tortured and justified! RT https://t.co/oIE3QVk23y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianSmedley @ABCNews24 Oz still doesn't recognize the first Australians in the Constitution! Insulting and ridiculous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! Governing all Americans, eh?! RT https://t.co/sqTqrtNbH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!!!! Scarey...no, terrifying! And U.K's May is courting this madman! RT https://t.co/rwXCNjkpES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scarey! Aligning too strongly with Trumps USA. What could possibly go wrong?RT https://t.co/0UvZfWHnKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No self awareness! RT https://t.co/N7EYU4CH20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's awfully good of her! What a Trump sycophant! Who are pulling the strings on these puppets?! RT https://t.co/JkS8fHKhgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is mad! RT https://t.co/yzHWD5zcjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting times we live in! RT The weakening of the 'alt-right': how infighting and doxxing are taking a toll https://t.co/RNB1pRcICz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful read. Oz didnt appreciate what a great PM and person Gillard was and is! Stark reality now! RT https://t.co/RpPOJM7QX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine 500 days of Turnbulls rule, doesn't time fly?!RT https://t.co/6Tethf9OAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV journalists need to find a new way to handle Kellyanne Conway: https://t.co/SV7VWDgkCv via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good having friends in high places! RT https://t.co/ODXKTzR67u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess Trump means we are on our own...RT https://t.co/dk7R0sI3JV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously time for a new Govt.! RT https://t.co/JaMGG6CEHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could think of a many better ways to spend $31billion! Nuts! RT  https://t.co/I8aQPAlkUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just imagine there are pple who actually believe and agree with this nut! RT https://t.co/5xWvWiogt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/EIuncQlNQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes to both! RT https://t.co/UiBHNlYBJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those RW nasties big part of why Baird decided to leave! RT https://t.co/I0vvqahKoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A power broker in the LNP Nasty Party! RT https://t.co/XqaPAGSkbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that Abbott's LNP thought she was a hero and backed her and paid for her all the way! RT https://t.co/2rpiRstouo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't unscramble even a small omelette! TPP is over. RT https://t.co/adpXnmR035]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colvinius Does that mean that the Oz car industry has a chance to be revived ?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We will see! He shouldn't have be sworn in until all these issues resolved! RT https://t.co/IMHUaCw1bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a deep breath world! RT https://t.co/v1ccSF2P8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oz and the world need to realize that we are all on our own now! #trump https://t.co/pZ2z0RodiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhysam @GreenJ shysters the lot of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is doomed! RT https://t.co/sPnqR638dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! Going to war with China next! RT https://t.co/eWt36f8GOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tragically, the Oz car industry and thousands of jobs and lives were destroyed at the feet of the TPP! @mjrowland68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leigh must be getting worried?! She should! RT https://t.co/bAUnpx2v7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whose going to explain tariffs to Donald?!RT https://t.co/OqJVzjtUeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could anyone get away with not revealing tax data! No data..No POTUS job! RT https://t.co/gWYYYEy6Vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World hopes! RT https://t.co/B9xjpyF5lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deniseshrivell @POTUS Snake Oil Salesmen and Carpetbaggers. Silly,  desperate people get hoodwinked through the centuries!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold taps and 7 star luxury all your life doesn't help ones empathy or smarts! RT https://t.co/FubAcDKa8s]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>