<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[PFF's put together an awesome Super Bowl media booklet. Some gems in it: #SB51 https://t.co/wV1FobweHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtstaples Correct, yep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danieltkelley @Pat_Thorman 'The winner is a Mr C Collinsworth, from...']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh come on. This is like a bad satire. https://t.co/XbswKpaEkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtstaples If you pass an accurate ball but the receiver drops it, you'll get a good passing grade and bad receiving grade on that play. Etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting way of dividing it up https://t.co/MxAX7xjl4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to play this https://t.co/2JcLpOoqiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[advises not endlessly picking WRs in 1st round. https://t.co/IY4kyrCceA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to see if he can make an impact for Dallas in 2017. Like a bonus draft pick https://t.co/C63Q6FDKtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once or twice. https://t.co/tYwWGW8KNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nfldrafttalker So? This is my Twitter account, not theirs. They have their own one. I'll talk about whatever i feel like whenever i feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nfldrafttalker I'm using my own twitter account to talk whatever the hell I like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nfldrafttalker I haven't promoted anything. I asked a question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Clarence Thomas basically a full-blown fascist judging by this graph? https://t.co/nIuk4R1l77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, but in the pantheon of 'not well' that was REALLY not well. https://t.co/ad6QC8dAGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags Yeah, I'm fine with that. Just seems that you need that direction from the outset (Browns?) rather than just reacting to a call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags Right, but again, this isn't exactly in the 'positive' column for the move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags Like I say, who cares if it all works out, but the process as laid out atm would be really concerning to me if I was a 49ers fan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags HC + GM liking each other can't hurt, but you're now gonna have rookie HC with no experienced check/aid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags and hand him a 6-year deal off the back of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSchrags That's the point though, right? The story as presented atm is they had their process, Lynch calls up and offers and they junk it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously none of it matters if Lynch ends up being really good (or more importantly new head coach does...), but the process is worrying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zbeg @zbeg strong one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 49ers really don't look too good from that John Lynch hiring story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeGebran ten?? Man I suck at moving the needle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People, follow @GeorgeGebran. Man did sterling work over the past few days helping pull together some very cool PFF super bowl content]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionsroar99 except it hasn't touched most of the ones that do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SalParadise26 So? Nobody's claiming it's not a half assed ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionsroar99 of which there are few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionsroar99 it is, just a very half assed one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionsroar99 like Saudi Arabia? Oh wait, they're not banned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM  80% of terrorists attacks since 9/11 have been committed by U.S. citizens, and 64 percent were born in the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM if it's about security and danger then he's looking in the wrong places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM again, he's taken a dozen swings at bat and hasn't come close to addressing the single biggest safety issues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM he's signed 12 executive orders. Which of the 12 address violence or safety domestically?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoyleToMyCapo just because it's an incomplete ban doesn't mean that's not its focus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM who cares what he said, he's said all kinds of horse shit. What has he done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM long enough to tackle number two on the list? Where's #1?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM and how's that part going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM eh, not really. If it's because of danger posed by citizens then job one is domestic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @ChloeAEM when do you start deporting Americans, since they're the cause of many?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in fact deleted. Openly hypocritical. https://t.co/4TsayKGjb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @NicolaLucas you're aware that not one attack in last 20 years has been from anybody from that banned list of countries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @NicolaLucas they are being turned away or detained. Barred from entering. That is a ban. Even if temporary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealROCNation @NicolaLucas being against it until you came into power the conveniently changing your mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball and yet anybody invoking fascism/Nazi parallels is getting carried away..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR_DougFarrar Stick to Trump tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMWeinstein Look in your own backyard. My country remains incompetent, not fascist. Yours on the other hand..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECU WR Zay Jones had 2 TDs taken off the board in the Senior Bowl. 1st one cos no replay, this one because of a hol… https://t.co/21peJNmAIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hello, Zay Jones! Frame by frame suggests this is TD even in NFL. Right toe taps just before the knee https://t.co/CHqLVIcENA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key point on Travis Frederick this year from @PFF_Mike https://t.co/IdntwD4LaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brjr_klhr Well, they're limited to the palms of your hands and fingers. Fred Belitnikoff used to catch passes with his forearms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brjr_klhr Everyone has the same gloves, not everybody is doing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBJ just makes 1-handed catches look too easy https://t.co/Ckmi56wM6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual pro bowl skills comp quote: "That drone is so high it's actually above the sun." Uh...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PriscoCBS Yep, FACT! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Scorsese movie imo. One of my top five ever. https://t.co/OQturgbBza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys looking up the word 'dwindling' then asking somebody to explain that to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I'd hate to have said he was declining a couple of years ago.. https://t.co/wdM8dfBs1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how many 'all time great hits' are completely illegal now. https://t.co/0uu4iYs641]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDaveHooker fire away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArifHasanNFL @eric_j_thompson put it in a box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thread https://t.co/a78d2D0lOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, hope he makes it back at all https://t.co/MXGGfBslNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR_DougFarrar @washingtonpost 'what would that look like'? Short answer: the 1700s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_6o3 Think of all the time in a game where nothing's happening. Commercial breaks, time outs etc. We're working on the tape during those]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_6o3 Multiple people working on it as the game's going on. We don't have to wait until it finishes to begin the work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_6o3 20-years later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cvantis Yeah, got destroyed. Even found an extra pressure on top of the 11 he gave up to White.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Super Bowl XXXI the Green Bay Packers had 26 total pressures, and Reggie White had 11 of them by himself. 3 of the team's 5 sacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PFF has its first game of Reggie White graded! I know this will surprise you, but he was freaking dominant in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorJRogers where are you on Kupp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[subset analysis ftw https://t.co/SSlNuIvBIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PP_Rich_Hill @MikeClayNFL Last 3 games they're up significantly. Still only around 50%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting approach https://t.co/nYHjv8f88s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool picture. I'd have really wanted to move those 2 chairs in front though https://t.co/u9ceY9Nuuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to the PFF Podcast. Last 2 days we have an awards rundown and Senior Bowl show:  https://t.co/QQ5Hm5c60w
iTunes or search PFF Podcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Mike I don't feel I've been vocal enough about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosscarrick16 @PFF_Gordon My hunch is they'd recover even if you did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well hello @PFF Senior Bowl grading https://t.co/7g4Z2deQzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsPaperInfo Oh I disagree. I think in a world with those monstrosities these were the lowest point humanity ever reached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Murray_Kinsella 23 with that hairline? No wonder he went cueball so soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah '84 Marino statistically was completely ridiculous vs peers. https://t.co/EiFGYKJUOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanu is 5 for 5 career passing, with a perfect passer rating. 2 of the prettiest deep passes you'll ever see, and they've been setting it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a man into prop bets I'd put money on Sanu throwing a pass. https://t.co/2Oc7uvq0x5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking out the Maroons t shirt today, @FlemESPN https://t.co/CXmz2ZWOH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder They really didn't. 276 of those yards came after contact in those 2 games. 12 broken tackles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder He was great this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder Actually Ajayi being #2 is almost 100% in spite of the OL. He led the league in yards gained AFTER he was hit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_6o3 @tyschalter Depends on the outlet. There's no one master coverage here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of thing must piss non-sports fans off no end. https://t.co/xBaF7mMNNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyschalter @Duffyd87 @fbgchase And causes all kinds of issues, cos now people think compare = equate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyschalter @Duffyd87 @fbgchase Don't think that's just a US thing, but it's an odd phrase, since compare seems to cover it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duffyd87 @fbgchase @tyschalter Somewhere along the line people forgot the second part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duffyd87 @fbgchase @tyschalter No, this is the point. Definition of compare https://t.co/GDJgvy4F2x 'similarities AND differences']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder A top 5 unit? The Miami OL was terrible as soon as Mike Pouncey went down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duffyd87 @fbgchase @tyschalter Comparing doesn't mean the things must be similar. It's a positive or negative conclusion exercise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder Because offensive line play can't be summed up in a sack number?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisRings How do you define route running? His was good enough to completely change how he was used as a RB. No WR can say that this yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GooseGrinder What part of it is off?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>