<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Our leaders MUST fix this. @ONECampaign is demanding action – add your name https://t.co/WZjKDo2cFe https://t.co/30Fx1Wx6gC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign @Greenpeace petition to get #cocacola to support  bottle return scheme. In U.K. We use Millions of bottles which should be reused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmcdonnellMP can't you act even more like TMs doormat. So you won't stop even a bad Brexit! We once had politicians who put U.K. First]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelSJohnson glad 2 hear on #channel4news say we should have #vetoBrexitoptions.Torys have no mandate on type of exit .P.Sovereignity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately @UKLabour seem to, by and large, cut from same cloth,very sad to see. https://t.co/0l0mexBuPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why Lib Dems are now only party who have best interests of whole of UK at heart https://t.co/gaA08YLMSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denmark has spent on renewables, most of its power now comes from them often more than 90%, we have the potential w… https://t.co/y3u0OvQpw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is staggering that so many MPs,knowing hard Brexit  is bad for UK are sheepishly doing the right wing Tories job… https://t.co/RMOlAEf4Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well he probably was if his past is anything to go by. Good for Lab MEP https://t.co/ynWcnKeVrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[04 February | London | Protest: Stop Trump's Muslim Ban - Stop May Supporting It https://t.co/zEg7AKorZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour  this is Democratic way not the stitch up which is an affront to Democ @DavidLammy is rt. Brexiteers vote… https://t.co/8bkQU59yZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keir_Starmer ur  vote tonight can make or break UK we must have chance 2 decide on outcome not half a doz. rtwing… https://t.co/9HnTCjExrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keir_Starmer so why are your colleagues not voting against Art 50 tonight. We need promises that electorate have v… https://t.co/1MQgvIxHJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyThornberry this is why you and rest of @UKLabour  should vote against invoking Art50 tonight. This is an affr… https://t.co/FMTwpmBbnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour if you believe in doing best for U.K. Don't vote for invoking Art50 tonight! https://t.co/m4MUBp61pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may  read this and act on it if you really believe in Parliamentary Democracy don't put cart before horse! https://t.co/x4TeoQ6dlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that fraud! https://t.co/oQlhCna0VQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Attorney Channing D. Phillips: Drop felony charges against journalists who covered Inauguratio... https://t.co/aLMwJECFTV via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely and as he seems to get worse each day the welcome party will grow accordingly https://t.co/DpLev3fm0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just pledged on a great project Unite for Europe - National march to Parliament @crowdfunderuk Check it out: https://t.co/5qskycGYBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask @Theresa_May to condemn Trump's ban on Muslims entering the US https://t.co/UgUFckfAxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm supporting Unite for Europe's March to Parliament, 25 March 2017 #StopBrexit https://t.co/RTOiY3f4MJ @uniteforeurope @crowdfunderuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May, demand an end to Trump’s Muslim ban https://t.co/0HvfhPIBKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/bmKBEzfg2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadiq Khan: Declare London independent from the UK and apply to join the EU. - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/8NfkJ9GFe2 via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March against Donald Trump https://t.co/FBvl9pEf4q via @Open_Britain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliament set to debate Donald Trump's UK state visit after petition to cancel it gets more than 900,000 signatures https://t.co/b1XFbdzxE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do we need a head of state? Have your say. #WinningTheArgument https://t.co/x3YrQJrOOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour if all those who feel Brexits bad for UK voted to stop article50 it could stop it. Lack of principles...t… https://t.co/xrTEAuAkb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KwasiKwarteng so 52v48% is "an overwhelming majority" but you told SNP on #channel4news 66v33%" is almost even split" r u stupid ur devious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long ago if the PM mislead Parliament they'd be a goner. How,sadly, things have changed. https://t.co/8ADggw2UDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Brexit does happen I imagine it won't be just youth clubs https://t.co/ZQnfGzWmxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Lab MP who votes for it, believing it to be the wrong thing for U.K., should be ones 'punished ' if that's what… https://t.co/Pdgkl87D8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For now! https://t.co/n3HnziBlTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidDavisMP We're still Parliamentary Democ?The will of people should be decided by an election not rigged refere… https://t.co/5wSUVVdky4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The will of the people didn't matter when the £350million disappeared, nor promise in Tory Manifesto to stay in SM… https://t.co/LYI6uOfCRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually it's sad. https://t.co/seJeIGyspl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All three! https://t.co/Bp5Hxdk2SH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we're not,we want Parliament to decide! Isn't that what UKIP claimed to be all about"Parliamentary Sovereignty "Or… https://t.co/5FCHY4Z2Fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With her Blind Trust Funds @ theres_may is probably one of the few winners along with most of her cabinet https://t.co/jTvzEmri2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear hear😀 https://t.co/sEb36UVxTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sajidjavid so strategy and industry don't go together! Well in Germany they do,no wonder we've lost our steel industry with on watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may do you really expect us to believe the poorest will benefit from a tax haven UK full of immigrant olig… https://t.co/DJsKxUXvOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time someone questioned him, there are many more topics which he should be questioned on https://t.co/fxPrdvLPpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope so but H of Commons should do what they know is best for U.K. i.e. Remain https://t.co/kyRaJX5gKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may like Spicer ur becoming a laughing stock. We see with own eyes state of NHS, schools...Saying it's all good doesn't make it so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they really believed immigration was such a "problem" they could stop non EU immigration now. They don't as our… https://t.co/arRYbXAYNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not much different at all.Would @michaelwhite want his kids on such contract? Sauce for goose... https://t.co/VDoPSdqBeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly as the man said "what do you believe me, or what you see with your own eyes"   Our NHS, housing,schools etc… https://t.co/vNg3V6wW0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may this is why people voted Brexit your gov did not protect the few rights they have. It is not immigrati… https://t.co/guY6YRk6hY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may spin this one but "who do you believe,me,or what you see with your own eyes" wake up # Brexit a disast… https://t.co/jFhX5MgSoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on lies, misinformation and no information, so Democracy will be loser https://t.co/TQUrrS1zvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For White House read #brexittories! https://t.co/q0BaFLXza5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Aronbanks and his insurance co. Will laugh all way to Bank as will many # Brexiteers . #save our NHS https://t.co/Ww39qYQ9s8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may  and we've not even left. Good luck with #protectionisttrump! https://t.co/up5BexC2LP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the capitalist right wing press which lied repeatedly and were never brought to book by… https://t.co/huqudh8Gos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She'll be too busy kowtowing to him. https://t.co/SLqrIlGXBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC now can't report facts in case some moron confuses them with opinion. Get some balls. There was time when y… https://t.co/H5jyp91kna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What rubbish. No ones says she needs to tell the electorate but our representatives, absolutely https://t.co/pBrq0EoewC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your asinine posturing worth the £80 you'll get on #marr as the anti-feminist, pro-trump female? @camillalong #thinkbeforeyoutweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he mention this before the Ref.? https://t.co/NcqaOpJcxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll want to be top of the list https://t.co/cPSOiXTvgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope he stays there https://t.co/zDkck21zuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correct. join Lib Dems only real opposition https://t.co/HdBZjBEhC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, I should think, the majority of the electorate! https://t.co/3wY0VgLy6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make him write it in blood! As we know Tories aren't known for keeping promises! https://t.co/r1slq8QcpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we would we have an NHS in shit creek! https://t.co/MtgaH1tYdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was all a misunderstanding, he's changed his mind ...along with £ 350m promised for NHS? Why would anyone believ… https://t.co/DM1cpbL3ov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My grandkids &amp; me are NOT affected by a US Pres who denies climate change? https://t.co/cIK8usu28k grow up, read some books @camillalong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #Trump means protectionism &amp; #Brexit depends on bilaterals with #USA ...where are we now? @theresa_may @Number10gov #politicalwilderness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may  #Trump"America first, protectionism.."So much for our trade deal and great opportunities!#Remain is our best option by far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may you say electorate"went into ref.with  eyes wide open" they thought NHS would get £350m etc Will you conveniently ignore this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euromove we see  likely ( never mentioned) outcomes of #Brexit we need a vote on options.This is Democracy. Ref bu… https://t.co/t6vzDMzt6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ref  built on lies, misinformation and no information. Reality now hits &amp; likely outcomes clearer.why are you afrai… https://t.co/E3M54eKOJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euromove listening to Michael Roux he predicts 50% of restaurants will close next yr as EU workers leave.Stop #Brexit we know it's madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euromove if we all join we'd make a difference!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MichaelGove if one of those "dole scroungers " did something similar it'd be splattered across ur right wing frien… https://t.co/7aZNeFa56T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But we need to remember "some poor are getting richer" can you believe that's one of their 'excuses" Shameless, but… https://t.co/YSB8YlK6gT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the electorate have been led up the garden path, @UKLabour, decent Torys, @LibDems @theSNP et al need to unite and… https://t.co/duR2gYOY4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's all hope and pray this is the case https://t.co/stVRjmVd3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may  if this happens I will have to wait months to see a doctor and my local A&amp;E would close down! https://t.co/6583VVuX64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So at best majority i.e. 48% want soft /remain 
. Show this to @theresa_may https://t.co/V2jGtj3HpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An utter disgrace . Now listened to billionaires mouthpieces trying to tell us how it's good, some poor r getting r… https://t.co/0ACZnUYnQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the queue at LEAST 48% feel the same https://t.co/euee8O5tPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As my mother used to say" much wants more" Well said Michael https://t.co/BH9XMusUPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurious immoral and something we should be ashamed of Spread the wealth and improve life for those living in misery https://t.co/VaDhmgYLFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may s got Blind Trust, Hunt £m's profit,Gove thousands£ for 8 hours work. Rich elites who've lied to electorate.Stand up to them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Win the Argument - learn to challenge monarchy myths and arguments https://t.co/PiLEHjLxlu #WinningTheArgument]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do we need a head of state? Have your say. #WinningTheArgument https://t.co/x3YrQJadWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cringe thinking of #MichaelGove grovelling at his feet. Who would trust a word either of them say. Two egotistica… https://t.co/rJyhqUkM1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hypocriteHunt,hard#Brexit wouldn't be hard for him. He has no idea how Brexit will harm ordinary( as opposed to ££… https://t.co/p19IX1ok85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Hunt set to make up to £17 million from sale of business as NHS crisis continues https://t.co/tjONYYljE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't. As #Brexit was built on lies disinformation and lack of information it was of itself undemocratic and… https://t.co/ydb2FJKhDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No they didn't If #Brexit are so sure the terms would be agreeable to electorate why are they so afraid of vote on… https://t.co/MqWbi8f8In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the fight to keep Britain in the Single Market - add your name to our petition today: https://t.co/0xJSPNvvC1 #JoinLibDems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just #LibDems all parties have Duty to hold gov to their word Democracy has lost if lies &amp; misinformation are u… https://t.co/lIoSKHSBKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st of many, not what #Brexit promised! https://t.co/5hkplMXiHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ theresa_may Why would 63% give up when as IDCSaid few mins. ago "can't know what Brexit will mean".SNP Wittard is right,"why do it"Fools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IanDSmith admits doesn't know what #Brexit will  mean! He didn't say that in his Ref. Campaign, it was all sunshine and roses. Why leave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IDSNOT incredible he admits we can't know what #Brexit would mean for UK ,wreckless is an understatement!SNP are right, " then why do it"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>