<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildMN34 @theobserver What is going on in that country of yours! Lololol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George is my spirit animal. https://t.co/xQPRi0YUzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fullmetal1986 Better than expected actually. Took it as the joke it was intended to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And getting unmatched in 3 ... 2 ... 1 ... https://t.co/mSvbaTHOON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started off watching videos on whale's evolution. An hour later - Concord crash video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of fun in the sun! https://t.co/IVY0jgZeXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is not to support Trump. Just do your jobs right and not blindly accept what is undoubtedly biased bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hey. Misrepresent reality to further your agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Furthermore, and this is the kicker, it means NOTHING for anyone in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In no way does it prevent women from doing what they wish with their bodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gross generalisation on Trump signing that 'abortion' legislation is everything wrong with modern media coverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 @noreasonspec Enough to reply. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 @noreasonspec All the time? I count twice - and don't get grumpy because I don't agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Electivirus I try to please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My legs aren't the longest, but as they say, girth &gt; length. https://t.co/8a092Es6kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PKaotic We gotta get on that laser treatment yo. I just can't be fucked. Lololol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PKaotic We're both wogs aren't we? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyKat1988_ How about our beaches? They're pretty good I think. Lolol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieinc Its playing into the whole "people are needy and desperate". It's kinda sad really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PKaotic All I can say is, some guys are desperate. That's all I can think of who'd actually support it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PKaotic I'll pay a dollar for that. Hahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieinc And even then, let's use 'legitimise' very loosely. Hahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieinc One person offered a meet at a con and a personalised letter. OH BOY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieinc Each to their own of course, but god it seems desperate to want some of those prizes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach That's not what I implicated - hence not putting words in my mouth. How wasn't that clear?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach "as long as he doesn't affect YOU, fuck everyone else :)"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach 1. Don't put words into my mouth. 2. The news will report what it needs to to further their agenda, and ignore the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach The news has an agenda too. Don't ignore that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach Trump does not affect me. There are issues locally that deserve my attention. I don't wish strangers harm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudbeach Are you wishing him ill because he's personally wronged you, or just for the sake of it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 What would you expect them to say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sort of shit people will put as Patreon prizes ... and then the people who will pay for it. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JaydenPerry Fuck that BMW badge right off! Needs a Ford one! Hahaha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseygambles It symbolizes more than just a bit of fabric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseygambles I know this country isn't perfect - but it's pretty bloody amazing. To burn the flag is such a pathetic thing to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseygambles I don't know to describe it adequately. It's just something I don't agree with at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseygambles Disrespectful to this country and everything it offers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseygambles I've always considered it extremely disrespectful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you burn the flag you're a cunt. Simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a group finished playing Watch Dogs and decided to be heroes. No, you're a pack of fucking losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it was stupid that America voted for Trump, but this rioting is so much worse. What a country full of muppets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caseytxo Pls put Fetty wrap on the menu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How disgusting of Google. To suggest there are only two genders. 2017 and just as regressive. https://t.co/RwaufVW4et]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseSPANNER When I get home, I'm whipping it out for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseSPANNER I fucked up. Sorry mate. Incoming soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaetano_Prestia Mostly old white men*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which deity do I need to pray to for EA to release NFS Underground - Most Wanted on the XB1?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzzfeed posts a video of a woman who's seeing two guys at the same time, and they're both 'cool with it'. What a pair of soft cocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Admiral_Evil He's won the position. People honestly need to move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is your President. Deal with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildMN34 @YahooFinance If Inception taught me anything, its that dreams are real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Electivirus Sorry to let you down. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Electivirus I should have expected that. Hahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fappening v2 is starting, but the nudes are of guys. Where's the fun in that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motownpatty Pretty much, yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to replace the tyres on the RX8 and Rolls. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildMN34 *looks at email for invite* *none found*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bogeh Thanks mate! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliteEffect Thanks a bunch mate! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birthday shenadigans with three of my favourite humans. https://t.co/hDhx0MT7He]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildMN34 *on a first date* "so a little about me ..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birthday breakfast noms with the fam. @ Osteria on Darling https://t.co/4UCmKb32DK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevivor Thanks mate! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motownpatty Just finished watching it. Great recommendation mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RahcleD Not knowing how to use their/there/they're is a dead giveaway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of shit circle do you live in where anti-gay comments are still acceptable and supported? You're a muppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shan Ju Lin is dropped from One Nation. Good. Grow the fuck up you moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildMN34 They don't call it snail mail for nothing! Hahaha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You still need to put in the effort. Someone using gear doesn't just sit back and the muscles come. They're still doing work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone has a goal, and they can get a little push to get there, that's their choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to suggest its cheating or not natural - cheating to who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irrespective of the health implications, it has absolutely nothing to do with anyone but the user.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting aside competitions of course, if someone decides to get on the gear, why would that 'bother' someone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never quite understand why people judge steroid use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received a letter in the mail today from @WildMN34. Shout-out to an absolutely bloody legend. Love you bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnoshArk Started over today. Picked Littern. Regret nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought Dominos for lunch. Kinda regretting it right now, and kinda not. #phet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was thinking of making the Aus Day a long weekend, then I realised it falls during month-end. Fucking hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head game strong. https://t.co/WPk9A5XM8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe you'll stop being a race-baiting cunt? â¤ https://t.co/VcgR160j3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A food fight with grapes just ended with someone pissing themselves. 2017 is off to an epic start!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadekristinee @jesseSPANNER Hahaha! That is epic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseSPANNER I picked grass in X/Y. Just saw Popplio's final form = shithouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fullmetal1986 Can you get them all without trading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4b397158f855429 @RT_com NEWS FLASH! Santa isn't Christian. Moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important question. What's the best starter to pick in Sun/Moon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard the fireworks at Syria were pretty good. They've been going off since last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Year nudes! #2017in3words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B-walking our way into 2017! https://t.co/FShHNvKen3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck, it's hot aye?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Saleh might be the greatest scumbag of 2016. Lower than a snake's arsehole.

https://t.co/AxpztvhgVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RahcleD First thing I noticed when I was there too! Hahaha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to live like a rabbit? Sure. But fuck off spreading bullshit so people can join your miserable cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister asks Mum, "is there pus in milk"? I sit up and say, "did your vegan friend tell you this?" She nods. What a dumb cunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random thought. If you ever start a comment with "dear white people", stop, think about it, and shut the fuck up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieinc Probably because there are idiots out there who continue to support it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at his video history, he looks like the type to do it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because if so, this cunt will have done so much damage to the image of Arabs he should be fucked over for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HOPE that this situation with Adam Saleh turns out that he was deliberately trying to force a reaction. I fucking HOPE so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the shit she said, its people like her that would jump down the throats of others for saying something so absurd. Idiot.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>