<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump pathetic leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Still, confidence doesn’t boost wages or create jobs, and nine of the past 10 recessions began under Republican pr… https://t.co/7DZrbNczcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeepCup hey guys tried using your online checkout from NZ - it keeps on saying all my card numbers are invalid :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha the answer @realDonaldTrump it’s hard to look away from a train wreck https://t.co/2gU60oaNiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roo_winn long haired people can be inherently sketchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jazzica haha its always gin’o’clock somewhere in the world - maybe not Wellington, ha it’s only 8am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on u @FoxMarama your reaction was raw and had integrity. Don’t apologize. Tobacco kills, all for greed. And no one can stop them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And. You. Smell.  https://t.co/RIuC6WKLtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DONALD: Ask the gays #askthegays https://t.co/ucZJUrSkVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our love @Hilary_Barry time to put your feet up for a bit and have a few drinks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A heart-rending read - as a global community what are we doing to help those suffering https://t.co/jAdHhQ91zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clare_barrie don't envy you that one "The Spirit is Dead" "No More Leading Into Truth" ... ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx to @NewshubNZ and @nzherald for sharing our thoughts on #gsthw16 this week - https://t.co/r5DNf1dfwy for my personal thoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord I read this as @paulabennettmp #mostwanted - #prophetic or #dyslexic eek https://t.co/D8pXRQMZ4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hilary_Barry aw thanks Hils that means the world - we adore you and will follow u on your next journey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight ha happy to speak out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s me @Hilary_Barry the Anglican ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slight #breeze sweeping through #Wellington tonight. Even had to bring the flag in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muerk thank you for your kindness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muerk it’s tough yes but Christ walks with the outsider - in my heart I know this is a blessed space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight Christ’s justice is the act of making all whole - this is what we are called to emulate I humbly believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clare_barrie no i know - it is just wrong as so many levels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrBrianD @StPetersWillis that is kind - the Cathedral has never judged us - but the larger Church is hostile and unsafe. Not for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muerk pragmaticaly that is true, but theologically #gsthw16 was wrong to “shelve” us like inanimate objects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnGillespie20 that’s kind thank you John]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archbishops assertions of future way forward hollow &amp; insincere. And they think I will stick around #ugtbkm #gsthw16 https://t.co/iDuehNyPIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Open Letter to the Church #gsthw16
https://t.co/sD26YgVPEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi can we please be honest with words, no ducking for cover, ongoing support for oppression - we cannot sugar coat #gsthw16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrBrianD thanks for being the only one with balls to tell us, I am disgusted and happy to leave my Dio in Wellington to their own devices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clare_barrie thats BS - #Unity does not leave us outside - its violent exclusion - call it by its name #gsthw16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done w Anglican Church - bunch of hypocrites - I will not sit in the pews of the oppressed - I will be outside where my God stands #gsthw16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even conservative Italy knows how to move forward #gsthw16 https://t.co/am5Fmjexyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald yes we saw a UFO flying out of Parliament yesterday - no wait - that was #JohnKey being kicked out #nzqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrBrianD seems to be the never end story of Synod not wanting to share the terrible outcomes. Over this church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#eqnz solid shaking in Wellington City just now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight dont think we are getting anything today since they are off doing blessings (lucky land)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @TeUruroaFlavell sadly Labour does not seem keen on cross-party co-operation these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini absolutely - tactic of the powerful is always to silence - with no real commitment to deeply hearing and changing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini calling out the truth is not being a hater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too funny https://t.co/kSkpJZg1sG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful approach #nzpol https://t.co/pbwQEtHp2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell @gendidwight @squeakycog or we could engage and try to understand we have lots in common in our faith, even in our anger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell @squeakycog sometimes we have to express our anger, even if we dont like what the other says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog @gendidwight F them is an expression of the pain we carry through persistent actions of others, I hold pain and promise together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog @gendidwight salvation is secured by God alone, u know that, u only need stand next to ppl so they know God is near]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog well, isnt it time we find a way love each other for what we DO have in common? And surrender the rest to God to bear for us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog @gendidwight u find it in your heart to love the other, even if we exchange harsh words, we focus on the christ who leads us on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog @gendidwight the threat of being on the outside sux doesnt it Zane, have lived that for decades, y cant there be a common basis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog @gendidwight you accommodate the entire church - dont be a drama queen - we simply need to share the church - no more no less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog you do not know me, I have tolerated and stood by more orthodoxy that you know, if you dont want to engage, walk away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog your ppl can exclude me, I can respond, this does not mean I lack faith/compassion or not desire unity, unity is a 2 way street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog balance of bible is about Christs grace/mercy, not law out of context, the Spirit leads into truth and is not dead in the past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog 2 integrities work when we can still hold a common understanding of Christs redemptive love, if we cannot then there is no unity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog unity here means keeping people out while you come to terms with a gospel of inclusion, that is historical but not truthful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog I am just as much on the journey of transformation through faith in Christ, even if you cant accept that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog fantastic theology Zane - just what we need a faith based on exclusion. Enjoy your shrinking club #gsthw16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHelenJacobi surprised at your comments re Welly - conversations in our Dio suggested a willingness for a way fwd even with differences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dehumanisation marks not only those whose humanity has been stolen, but also those who have stolen it. Paulo Freire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a thought for #gsthw16 https://t.co/YXkK3HCZDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muerk @gendidwight yes of course Teressa - just saying protestant puts the other Catholic sacraments as not so central - no slight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muerk @gendidwight this differentiates us from Catholicism - a reminder that Christ’s life is central, the rest are nice to haves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is interesting to hear those who actively exclude cry foul of being excluded. God has a sense of humour. #gsthw16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight oh dear! How many Anglicans to change a lightbulb? Depends if #gsthw16 can agree, just wait 4 more years, then we will know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini same place where unity was defined as the oppressed accepting the role of the oppressor, rather than radical transformation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog wish i could say it was a tempting offer… the sales pitch is, um, lacking :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog not kidding u. Stand outside the church for decades and tell me how safe it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder, who is #gsthw16 to judge how wide the love of God is. The one Christ gave it fully to all. How simple is that gospel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog if u have 2 LGBT and 98 non - who do u think is making decisions. My point is that LGBT are given no safe voice in this church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squeakycog i dont recall commenting on GS composition. Your choice to read it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight once the thesis havr been nailed to the cathedral door I suspect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The normative experience of church is being a silenced outsider, especially re gender/sexual equality #gsthw16 https://t.co/hShBwc2PhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘I do not accept… history as determinism. I embrace history as a possibility’. Paulo Freire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clare_barrie ty Claire - my prayer is that all will see how wide the love of God truly is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight no I agree it is frustrating. It’s only good intentions wanting to hear what’s happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auckanglican well I’ve been told - sorry for showing interest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am assuming radio silence has been imposed at #gsthw16 given the absence of any tweets or posts - transparency not the order of the day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrBrianD good luck - may it not be a #snorefest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chennoah just discovered vinegar and olive oil removed water stains on wood counter - if that helps :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok people let’s get this #coffeeshow #ontheroad https://t.co/ov0bswal4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clare_barrie just to thank you for your inclusiveness petition &amp; hope that #gsthw16 with have the ears to hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight It really is Gendi - I had the popcorn ready for a fun Saturday night! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtually no #GSTHW16 tweets &amp; 1 news article re tikanga not knowing relationship &amp; talking were important to one another - gripping stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah felt that earthquake - good morning Wellington! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 1 New Followers. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 1 New Followers. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn’t get my support. A PM who runs scared should not be in the job @johnkeypm #nzpol  https://t.co/6rEXZOEXom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 5 New Followers, 1 Mentions. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 5 New Followers. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TastingTable hey there - it seems impossible to create an account on your website - is there something I am missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 3 New Followers. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 5 New Followers. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimDotcom @omegamegan1 I’m sorry Kim but just because you are losing doesn’t mean my country lacks independence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has happened under watch of both @NZNationalParty &amp; @nzlabour govts, what will u do @johnkeypm @AndrewLittleMP  https://t.co/uRzD5ZyElS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My week on Twitter: 2 New Followers, 12 Mentions, 3 Retweets, 1.78K Retweet Reach. How's your audience growing? via https://t.co/is1dZT6Cvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HDPA ha :-) It’s so Mob Wives of Staten Island :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the #goldlame phone case @HDPA :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry guys - think this show is totally rigged - you must be feeling it now :-( @MKRWilliamZoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well thats a joke #mkrnz you judges are nasty - have been throughout - will never eat at one of you restaurants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so much hypocrisy in judging - all the things they demanded were given - then the judges change their minds on what they want #mkrnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[judges comments are not surprising for @MKRWilliamZoe - never happy - dont like simplicity, dont like complexity - yup, classic #mkrnz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>