<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont even need to watch this movie to start crying https://t.co/uBEtSXoIuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oops guilty https://t.co/FZLc8GcNie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoApp ive stopped doing gyms cos the people with multiple accounts are annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so a man jumps two walls and a fence to avoid paying money for himself into a zoo only to get killed by tigers.. yet its the zoos fault? no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNerdist13 you often get thrown into phlegm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNerdist13 i wouldnt want to be thrown on or fall into someones spit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWEChampions hell no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one other good bit was when baron corbin ended braun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[worst bits was when Goldberg spat in the ring - disgusting. and when Dean and Roman got eliminated :( and Orton winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[continued watching and the best bits was when Dean &amp; Roman came out and when Roman chucked Undertaker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[close enough with 12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the stream i was watching randomly stopped when dean smacked braun and now i cant find anywhere else to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT was brilliant. @JohnCena 16x #WWEChampionship #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @JohnCena running down the path thing to the ring before a match. bloody hell if i ran i'd get there and be like 'i need a wee rest' ðŸ˜§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im with @JohnCena on this one. #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHANES FACE LIKE 'DO NOT LAUGH' https://t.co/Fe6XbnOauQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWEChampions i think Dean Ambrose will get after 15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic well it said my card was declined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well i hope braun gets eliminated from the royal rumble in .5 seconds. #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I FOUND SOMEWHERE JUST IN TIME FOR KING ROMANS MATCH YASSS #RoyalRumble https://t.co/g7m0Kg4K5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 month free for the wwe network but they take money off you right away? utter shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yasss time for @NiaJaxWWE to destroy Sasha Banks #RoyalRumbleKickoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH WHATTT no not anderson and gallows #RoyalRumbleKickoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also bout time @NaomiWWE gets the smackdown womens title. @WWEDanielBryan make it happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i watched it again and roman got so mad he spat in his beard ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*ATTEMPTED bloody hell whats with my eyes/fingers today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everything about this is ðŸ˜ dean's attempred betrayal, seths blonde bit and romans hair https://t.co/25bO2SlVSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the olden days wasnt the Queens &amp; Kings allowed to order the beheading of people? imagine the queen now being like 'OFF WITH TRUMPS HEAD']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im going back to sleep ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what the heck was the beginning of this tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knight of at he Realm? is this some Zelda shit or what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night People is out now. we get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after Nakamura losing his title and Rafa losing i swear Dean Ambrose better win the Rumble tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont really care tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic youre the bad guy. we get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic youre not tired. we get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic youre angry. we get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[feel sorry for the next president in (hopefully) 4 years having to undo all of trumps mess. what else can he do in 4 years is scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so best thing about #NXTTakeoverSanantonio was @WWERollins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yay got NXT @TheDeanAmbrose @DeanAmbroseNet #wwechampions https://t.co/CAdlDMRlQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is there cake and a buffet?  #EdSheeranIsOverParty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wanted to drown myself in the bath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOW TF DO YOU LOG OUT OF SNAPCHAT NOW send help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how many horses collapsing and dying will it take for these cunts to realise racing needs to stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i woke up 10 mins ago and read a text and now i feel sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealgokwan is it a proper aberdeen buttery or a lame one from a shop? the proper ones are ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i watched one of that salt creepy meat guys videos and legit felt sick. why dont you go make out with the piece of dead animal creep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when people think theyre so important that they assume my tweets are about them âœ‹ https://t.co/XvwJwJyDae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic who said it was aimed at you? gawd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic wont let me view tweets before xmas day but exhibit 1 2 and 3 https://t.co/ykzrI4XOWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic i do 1 tweet then thats enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RusevBUL you gonna be watching the final?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellaTwins was there a YouTube video uploaded &amp; deleted a while ago? im sure i seen a new Brie video and now its gone ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its funny when jeremy kyle talks about a kid and calls it 'it' then has a rager at someone else when they also call it 'it']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[missing cat posters - DO YOU KNOW THIS CAT? ðŸˆ
me - no but i wish i did ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hear @RafaelNadal is on his way back to the top! #ausopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im actually lost for words after what i just seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['just off to meet Tigger who lives a few streets away to hang out for a few hours' https://t.co/Onfg7xgqWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[laughing internally but worried if one day she might actually do it and i die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[still laughing at how my mum said she'd 'knife' me last night. an oap acting like a wee thug. simmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my cat better stay in my room til i wake up cos ive had the heating on and theres no way im leaving the door open for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a pebble in the water makes a ripple effect. every action in this world will bear a consequence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my flat is so cold with the -5Â° rn im walking about with my jacket on. my room's toasty tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tempted to go make garlic bread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when people lose weight and continue posting before and after pictures. WE GET IT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[part of having a dog is being responsible for picking its ðŸ’© up!! nasty buggers leaving it on the pavements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i heard the branches moving and the cat jumped out and came towards me so of course id try make friends with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[made pals with a wee cat and im sad i didnt have food for it cos it was a bit thin :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mum just said to me 'we're finished' cos i asked to borrow a tenner. finished? whys she acting like shes dumping me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalDivas how will i be entertained until then ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse @TheDeanAmbrose @ReneeYoungWWE cant wait to watch this tomorrow ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RouReynolds i got forced to eat it as a kid and im legit scarred for life. vegetarian now anyway ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wondered why there was hunners of folk about then i looked at them and seen Hearts scarves.. ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanAmbroseNet @ReneeYoungWWE oops never thought about that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanAmbroseNet @ReneeYoungWWE just the mid-season finale! thank god it will be back ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and he was a wee man slag tae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also happy birthday to the number 1 poet, the patriot and a man of the people. #RobertBurns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not eating haggis, neeps and tatties tonight but happy burns night ðŸ”± oh i found a silver crown i like that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that TiK ToK song by Kesha sounds like it could be a 90s cheesey tune like Vengaboys or Whigfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic ok. nae need to throw a strop over it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic if it does explode on you one day i'd feel guilty knowing about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i am a little raincloud of doom â˜ https://t.co/KIVkcjVufN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic just cos i pointed out some issue that may or may not happen? not like im telling you to take it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic theres no articles of my samsung exploding.. i never said every model has problems. just that it happens fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic nah i google'd the  phone and theres articles on it overheating and exploding and that ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic is the s7 the one that sets on fire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic samsung? which one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancingForNic did you sell out and get an iphone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont feel safe in my own home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my cat physically attacked me so now im in a huff and hes no cat of mine until he gets his act together and says sorry in cat terms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i read that as 'Styles of Beyonce' and thought 'yeah the music does sound a bit like Survivor by Destinys Child' ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/PewzJZTQCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[otters have become like, my 3rd favourite animal. the way they can float on water and baby ones eat with their wee pawsies ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[havent seen anything on the Oscars list so i dont care. justin timberlake's song better win tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mum brought my VD calendar and i got Damon for my birthday ðŸ˜ https://t.co/duePs3BAmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've only completed the bottom 2 and some havent started yet but my brain is ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got a good learning thing going on ðŸ˜ŽðŸŽ“ https://t.co/DDgOVF5FKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@O2music dont count me as an entrant but cos MCR are my favourite band.. Welcome To The Black Parade ðŸ˜¢ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me earlier - 3am is a suitable time to go to sleep i think
me at 4am - unacceptable. i will get hardly any sleep what a mess i am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want @ShinsukeN to turn up at the Rumble and put out as many people as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and no its not a cover of Nirvana (incase people dont know this song)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>