<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairenelson 1) I CAN ADD TO THIS JOKE! 2) Oh Yes, that's the joke. 3) OH, I'M MANSPLAINING, TOO! 
Double whammy. Going to bed.
FOREVER!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairenelson I read that quickly and thought "HA! I'M HILARIOUS TOO!!" then realised I probably yes, that's the joked myself...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairenelson she has to cut them off for him because he's not allowed to touch the scissors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloggyDave I've had One Sweet Day by Mariah Carey and Boyz II Men in my head for two looonnnnng days now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews Thanks. If it ever happens, you're invited (I don't eat meat but I'll let my friends know).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews TOP PICKS! I'd go Sparrow, budgie, Pigeon, coote, Canada goose, fucking Swan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews which birds though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews sorry for the bird in a bird in a bird style tweet....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews oooh I'll just stick to goldeneye on the n64 if that's okay?https://t.co/SR7sS2f8Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews did you see the thread with the theory it's a Russian disinformation account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@invictusmaneo83 every year I'm the same. Did have one year where I filed it a couple of weeks early... What a time! ðŸŽ‰ ðŸŽ‰ ðŸŽ‰ ðŸŽ‰ ðŸŽ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rob_sell 9 years the Flappy Bat Brothers have been Facebook Friends (SIX YEARS AS THE FLAPPY BAT BROTHERS)! ðŸ¤¡ðŸ¤¡ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ“ðŸ¥‚ðŸ»ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krussant I asked Stacey about ten years ago to make me a mix... This'll do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairenelson I finished having therapy a few weeks ago after 15 months! It's probably the best thing I ever did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ava_assassin you obviously believed in your fight if they were you're own shoes. If they belong to anyone else you're just a big  bully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ava_assassin whose shoes were they though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent the evening editing photos and briefly forgot about everything going on in the world. Damn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyn79 ha, knowing that jumper exists has made mine! Have a good one, man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyn79 holy balls that's amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyn79  is that a fucking SPACE HARRIER T-SHIRT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMB let's hope not. I'll let you know in the next few months if it happens but I survive...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lules89 ha! Thanks! Don't know why I insist on being super organised for shoots, but anything involving paperwork or workflow I'm a mess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lules89 I did once and I already had the hole punch. It's just awful though. Still a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lules89 I wish it made me more organised, it's had zero effect for five years! Next year will be different though. Yeeeeeeeeahnoitwon't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a bloody great time in the darkroom last night. I look forward to having more bloody great times in the darkroom in future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @pollyth0mas! https://t.co/w9H1OLMepB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dull ache in my side I've had the last two months... If I die, thanks for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaCupLucy I started enjoying it a bit more once I started really sharpening my big knife.  Makes a massive difference.  Still a ballache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what this Jeremy Kyle programme is but it's not my tax return so I'd better keep watching it I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[GIF of Bernard from Black Books doing his tax return]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm brilliant at the internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @jonnyathan @pollyth0mas @Mullane45 better than being dragged into my boy talk...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @jonnyathan @pollyth0mas @Mullane45 Imagine what you can do with your life without someone who can't be arsed though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @jonnyathan @pollyth0mas @Mullane45 send him that John Virgo video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fishplums haven't read these but generally find mirror group awful for multiple shoddy/ heartless clickbait stories and the same content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadinebphoto WHAT?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I see the youth of today saying something is [any word here] af I still get confused that they're not talking about auto focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @jonnyathan @pollyth0mas well now I feel bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan @charmada @pollyth0mas Just got this message in from John Virgo. Good luck. https://t.co/qT0cQdH2sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet too right. I always preferred the little red and white guy with the squarer head. When's THAT magazine out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet and as if you'll be able to find it in the shops after 3 issues. Con bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet have you seen the build your own r2d2 magazine? 2.99 first issue, 8.99 after that. R2D2 complete after 100 issues...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolapop1 Haha, but did it work? It might take a while but stick at it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolapop1 also, I typed DOUBLE SOCKING not double shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolapop1 they're not so bad now. I just wish I'd listened to the physio when I was 16 and rested them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolapop1 I found double shocking seemed to help a bit, keep them warm. Don't know the point at which mine started to get better but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolapop1 my ankles were so bad at one point I could predict a cold snap with them. I had problems after doing ligaments for ~20 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Webbo_init save it for the future though, for when you need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Webbo_init do you follow Pete Souza on here or instagram? If you don't you're missing out on LOADS OF PICS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan I have very much enjoyed my food from Ema Balti at your house near Ema Balti.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan is that Ema?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally watched Whiplash and can't believe nobody told me that one of the two dads off My Two Dads is in it playing a dad. Time wasted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new album "Smothered in VapoRub" available in all good record shops from Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @pollyth0mas @TeaCupLucy @matthew_horwood Variety of textures, variety of flavours and hot and cold mix = perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollyth0mas @TeaCupLucy @charmada @matthew_horwood Noodle sarnies will do if necessary. Sausage roll sandwiches = ultimate comfort food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollyth0mas @TeaCupLucy @charmada you've only had a supernoodles sandwich once? This is much better. More texture. And flavour. And Joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet Just realised I might have already mentioned it to you before, but it's properly opening this week 
https://t.co/X68y7wktrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @TeaCupLucy unless you suffer from really bad heartburn an hour later which definitely isn't happening now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmada @TeaCupLucy as long as there's plenty of butter, the sausage is moist and the pastry is a bit greasy, nothing can go wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaCupLucy @charmada Bread, pastry, melting butter and sausage are all the best, but this is greater than the sum of its parts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet got a new place for us to eat next time you're round these parts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaCupLucy Oh my god it was the best thing I've had for ages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a stinking cold and if you think I'm wrong for eating sausage roll sandwiches with loads of melting butter then you have a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock Oh I don't know, I've heard people mention that but I rarely watch on telly unless it's like bullseye or something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock definitely my style because I can't draw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock well cats never are are they? No sense of urgency! It's not the real cat picture I did by the way... Nobody's seeing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINISHED!  And my old art teacher told me I was rubbish. 23 years later here I am drawing a cat! https://t.co/pKfL0zkoE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ie NOT LIKE A CAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cat looks like it might be a YouTube make up artist/vlogger with 17 million subscribers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone should have filmed this and put it on YouTube it'd be like that guy doing candyfloss like a big flower only really unimpressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell! When did I become so great at drawing?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone have any advice on how to draw a cat in a hurry? I mean I'm in a hurry, not the cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Good Old Days is on BBC4 now. It's my absolute favourite programme on the telly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock absolutely!  Definitely need to look into getting some https://t.co/MVmshL4g4g second hand games!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock I'm fine with that. I actually bought it for my niece then decided she wouldn't use it. Fully intended to use it myself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taffy3rock I bought a 2DS for Â£15 last year and I've never opened it or bought any games for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireandrewz but you don't even like the Silencer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast At Tiffany's or Don't Look Now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, it doesn't matter how much noise there is outside when you've got this inside your head https://t.co/jlP1FR8KJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno why I'm tweeting about it. It doesn't bother me, I'm just putting off reading this self help book for the 5th time in a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like the sound of a generator and someone cutting through metal to soothe you to sleep, I'd imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet everyone in the street is really happy about whatever works are going on at the entrance of Eastern High at 00:15.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews Ah that's a shame! Yes, I'll be the one cowering in a pool of sweat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollyth0mas UNLIKE KARATE KID 2, KARATE KID 3 AND ALL THE CHRISTMAS FILMS I'VE RECORDED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollyth0mas I saw it and didn't get what the fuss was about. I thought it was okay, I probably wouldn't watch it if it was on telly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoesarahandrews does that mean you won't be at the darts? Noooooooooooo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollyth0mas I seem to be the only person in the world absolutely not bothered by this film!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LollyGee Haha! I must have another one!x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LollyGee I went in the middle of a bit of a  breakdown and it is a wonderful place. Happiest of New Years to you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LollyGee that looked amazing!  I want to go back to Berlin. Oh God Oh God Oh God. Hi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't keep watching BBC News if they're going to continue with these mannequin challenge type reports!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally getting in the Christmas spirit.  Woken up with Little Donkey going around in my head. Oh well, time to blow the dust off my camera.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched Pride. Fantastic film. I say that with confidence as today I also watched Inbetweeners 2, which is a steaming pile of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annual watch of Jim Valvano's Cutting Down the Nets finished. Great inspiration and a funny, likeable character. https://t.co/Tg5JyMYoMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My diet the last week has been 94% POM-BEAR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just looked at my goals list for 2016... Made 3 out of 15, which is 3 more than 2015 when I didn't make a list! I'd call that a success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the best 2017 everyone. Be amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet I wonder who ACTUALLY is though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet the one where Mccrirrick anything makes me cross!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalactusHelmet ah balls, last year I watched nearly 8 hours of bullseye straight for new year. Always hated Christmas specials though!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>