<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sooby72 @AlastairBishop_ @PiotrSkut @TasminaSheikh So by your standards I'm Scottish but my born-in-England brother is not. That's silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaleRC75 @solange_lebourg Interesting name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilesBriggsMSP @RuthDavidsonMSP seems like a sensible &amp; decent extension of current care entitlement. Presumably you've costed it properly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddireader @AngusRobertson If the Union was actually any good for Scotland, they wouldn't have to use such arguments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Thanks for the heads up - just signed it :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickWinchester @kezdugdale Gosh.  And there's a lot of competition for that title too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulhutcheon @RuthDavidsonMSP It's a silly question though. Referendums are a pain so responses lean to No, whatever someone would vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@letsdothehuddle @murdo_fraser "Vote No for death by a thousand cuts"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @IJCFilm @Hadi_Alhassani @jimsciutto It's not the cyclists doing the killing though, is it? Nor is it (mostly) deliberate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieKhaleesi His comment has backfired a bit I think with Trump's Muslim ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksguy77 @tparsi  democracy? Freedom of speech? Or are these un-American these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachael_Swindon only in the most mealy mouthed feeble way she could get away with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon Even then, she said it a very mealy mouthed kind of a way. The bare minimum she could get away with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul1Singh Maybe.  Then what? Mike Pence and ... David Davies perhaps?  Not much of an improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosscolquhoun Oh well.  A fleeting possible silver lining of wishful thinking. I guess they were so cosy because they're on the same page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EJKTwit @IJCFilm @rninfl @0utthere @Hadi_Alhassani You'd save many more lives by not allowing lunatics to have guns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IJCFilm @Hadi_Alhassani @jimsciutto Hundreds times more Americans are killed by other Americans with guns than by foreign terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurt_obruny I don't expect that to be a popular view!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kurt_obruny   I do wonder if maybe such a hotbed of competing violent groups needs an unscrupulous strongman to keep it under control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreams_indy @Roadwarrior29 Thought Murray had said he would. Never expect anything from Mundell other than to do as his bosses say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosscolquhoun Well I'll concede this. If by getting cosy with Trump she can curb his worst excesses, she'll have done the world a favour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endless_psych @DouglasDaniel @naebD Ah ok. So they'd prefer to stick with Brexit UK because it's ...  less liberal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harryslaststand  I doubt we'll see the worst of Nazi-ism. But there are real parallels &amp; there's no doubt these are dangerous times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is interesting and worth a read.  https://t.co/yNKjWYCGrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmacwhirter @ericjoyce Ouch! Well it would have been about 10 at first, I thought I'd done well cutting it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter For when 140 characters just aren't enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter -&gt;would have upheld the Sewell convention until it was. I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter -&gt; Saying that, if there had been such legislation in place requiring repeal, the Supreme Court -&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter -&gt; legislation (or even shut it down), and any legislation preventing it could simply be repealed first. -&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter I had always understood that Parliamentary sovereignty meant that WM could legally overturn Holyrood -&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siriuspolitics @JolyonMaugham @guardian If you really believed your cause was right and just, you wouldn't need to suppress understanding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siriuspolitics @JolyonMaugham @guardian Case is about fully understanding the situation before we act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTrefgarne Probably. In one swoop May will have a maj. of ~70 and be rid of only effective opposition. Why would she want us to stay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthDavidsonMSP Wow, you should play cricket with spin like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecrezz @VeroVero777 @maryellenfield @margarance @SLATUKIP Well there's no chance Theresa May will spot that sort if thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heraldscotland Huh, you could just have tweeted that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericjoyce @iainmacwhirter Or rather, confirming that it was ever thus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mazzerooni @AdamBienkov @petertimmins3 @BIUK_Politics I take it that's sarcasm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishlabour Do you seriously still think that Scotland is better sticking with the UK, given all that's happened and is going to happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurt_obruny I hope you're right. But I think you're wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 *hand up*Barf.I despair. Will kissing his arse get a good "trade deal" before the next election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WikiGuido By that token, @RuthDavidsonMSP , I take it you'll vote Yes in #indyref2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faisalislam Bloody hell.  Does she think kissing the arse of that half witted despot will get a favourable 'trade deal' ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcurtiz @LibDems Along with the SNP, you mean?  Or a bit behind them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markrowantree @PeteWishart @wordpressdotcom They don't, so all they can do is blabber about 'once in a lifetime' to try to suppress it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithersJones3 @PeteWishart @wordpressdotcom My Grandfather voted but is no longer with us. My daughter was born since. Good enough for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlasFron @OwenSmith_MP @g_m_hodgson And when the public basically sat on the fence, this is what we get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god ... well its not like no one predicted this.https://t.co/9cwks6OhwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traquir He's got a point though.Independence is a serious business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartHosieSNP @DickWinchester Is that it???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weestie97 They'll change their tune next time around, EU is vast export market for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susannah_cannon @bbclaurak Besides even if that did have a influence it has no bearing on Gina Miller who simply asked for a decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susannah_cannon @bbclaurak Judgements and reasons are written down and will be scrutinised minutely. V hard for personal bias to influence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosscolquhoun I doubt that would gain much traction, in fact with luck it would severely backfire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurt_obruny And Putin, his takeover of Crimea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyndale7 @kennyfarq OK. I was commenting about life in general, not just the EU ref and its fallout. But it could apply equally to both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scotslanguage Those don't say the same thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richprice16 @G4rve @jk_rowling @EddieBarnes23 So? People who choose not to vote are accepting that others will made the decision for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling And by the same token, approx 550,000 voted to leave EU and  1,600,000 voted for independence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling "poorly expressed" is not the same as "completely fabricated".  Disingenuous of you to conflate the two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tyndale7 @KennyFarq Not just about one referendum though. Still, as long as you're happy with your lot, that's nice. Many would disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist What possible benefits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BjCruickshank @Defiaye @muir_belinda @ScotNational I'll have a coffee mug with that on. Or two :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyndale7 @kennyfarq  So you're saying its ok to marginalise us because they bung us a bit of money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimes No shit? We'll be too skint, thanks to Brexit lunacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EleanorFergus18 @dtaylor5633 Been asking myself the same question recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MHRMort @bellshillbaker @DickWinchester Who? Oh that guy. But he's an idiot. (Professor?  Really?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susannah_cannon @bbclaurak If that were the case the judges would have found against her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PartickFeargal yes, which is why we hace to get on with it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brexitannia2017 ... But we're working on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cliodiaspora The last few days were his chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnfmca @bill_macbeth @BjCruickshank That's interesting. Ok not everyone is mr last minute like me. Do you have a link to these studies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheScotsman There's a surprise. I'm increasingly sure the Brexit gov wd be  happy to see Scotland indy. Instant majority o ~70 for a start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bill_macbeth @BjCruickshank Not buying that about postal votes. A late surge is natural as lots of people go 'Oh shit haven't voted yet .."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorcineCarmine @percent48 @lesemasters @theresa_may Well thank God for that, anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheScotsman If the SC rules that Holyrood must be consulted, &amp; they  inevitably vote no, what then? Czechoslovakia style velvet divorce?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingBillyII @MrDavidSteele @heraldscotland Not German. You really are a nasty wee cretin.  #blocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingBillyII @_NatureParadise @lilyallen @thefader Inherited equivalent of about $4bn.  Worth about $2bn now. There's a joke in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingBillyII @MrDavidSteele @heraldscotland "den Papst" is German for "the Pope", for anyone wondering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickWinchester Ah, but think of the journey home :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GAPonsonby Surely the grown ups wouldn't tell him anything anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@margarance He'll be thinking "I did a good job, I saved the Conservative party from self destructing".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout @chalmers_julian @solange_lebourg @g_m_hodgson I'm a lot more interested in my children's future than in Labour's history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swcunningham2 @VeroVero777 For childbirth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout @solange_lebourg @g_m_hodgson I'm an engineer and I agree 100% with her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solange_lebourg LibDems and SNP already oppose it.  If Labour opposed it, I bet there could be enough Tory rebels to stop the madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bellshillbaker most costly and most lethal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acgrayling Except the Americans can get rid of Trump in a few years. Brexit is for life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeroVero777 It's a little hard to read, but seems that even after insurance has paid out, the new parents have to cough up $1800.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent Well done. Now, I take it you're quite wealthy? If not, you've shot yourself in the foot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent I think that's a wee porky pie, since your 1st tweet to me was that my opinion was worthless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent Which you presumably define as people who agree with you? Broad-minded, well done 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent I might be able to string an idea or two together now &amp; then. Thought you were blocking me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeaskyHT @DBanksy @newsundayherald How many of them do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent Let me fix that for you:  "You don't agree with me so I shall ignore you and call you names"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's a point of view.https://t.co/g2G5M38jGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MhairiHunter @kmckenna63 -&gt; For a while after it seemed to be anti -Indy &amp; -SNP.  Took me a while to realise that it was I who had changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MhairiHunter @kmckenna63 During #indyref1 I liked the Herald as, like me, it seemed to sit on the fence and analyse. --&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cal_1979 @AngusMacNeilSNP Good negotiating stance for them. They'll know out-of-her-depth May will have to give concessions to avoid it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tm014d1009 @martinmckee @eyejosh @Independent You're kidding, right? She's well out of her depth and is pandering to bigots and extremists.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>