<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grumpyfck @dizd The 8x10 is a neg,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dizd I only shoot paper in 8x10 so I didn't know this was even possible with film. I assume you still need a backlight for film?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop Sorry to hear that Gordon :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMULSIVEfilm @Givemeabiscuit @andywasley @ILFORDPhoto I'd like to try one of Graflex's gigantic SLRs if I was to try it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geek7 @EMULSIVEfilm @SimonBedwell House painting is amazing there so if you like colour shooting you will have lots of it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geek7 @EMULSIVEfilm @SimonBedwell Not made it to Tirana yet but making my way around the region &amp; it is on my list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit @EMULSIVEfilm @andywasley @ILFORDPhoto Not so easy to do LF on a lunchtime jaunt in central London!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMULSIVEfilm @SimonBedwell As a devotee of bonkers architecture may I suggest the Pyramid? https://t.co/72idM6anoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does sat crying at your desk because you feel at the same time out of your depth and totally unappreciated count as not enjoying your job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit @wordpressdotcom Oh and PanF 50 is lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit @wordpressdotcom It is certainly a good idea to get to the stage of being comfortable with a smaller number of stocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveCommaCarla Absolutely! Star Trek?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incasino_out @JuloPeter I like the sci-fi look a lot, that sort of false colour thing.I tried something with xpro architecture pinhole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incasino_out @JuloPeter For portraits, neon is ideal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incasino_out @JuloPeter I really like this idea, I tried some false colour architecture pinhole (sci fi look) a while ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsShade Ways of seeing is great! Also I am very jealous as we posses no reading nook, dirty or clean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaWriting Now we just all need to make podcasts and it will all become reality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaWriting Of the ppl I have never met on here, I know what you sound like plus @JonWilkening @KristenWACamera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incasino_out The challenge will be replicating this picture in a photograph!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonguetieon @kimmiechem2 Isn't that @incasino_out ? ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdMozmode That would ruin my day too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JT__photography Welcome! I have never adequately managed to convey how depression feels photographically myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is here &amp; now. A cold fresh winter morning, a large camera on my back &amp; endless recursive compositions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is not the BBC news app, my life is not anxiety. My life is not keeping planes in the sky. My life is not fear or paranoia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover That is great! I think we can get that here. Will check...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Oh good, glad you are feeling better! Yeah, it is dark and dim here today, easy to feel glum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Oh no, I'm sorry, I must have missed that :( Hope you are feeling better now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanSmith74 Hope to get some keepers! They are skeletal wooden wrecks, quite large too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some local shipwrecks lined up for pinholing near my home town coast this weekend. Bleak, quiet, near home &amp; near a pub. Perfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westen30 So I have sort of avoided them since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westen30 I don't wish to bash because maybe they came over wrong but I emailed them a couple of years ago abt something &amp; seemed super rude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuloPeter I will check him out thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop In all probability yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding an awful lot of solace perusing Sally Mann's landscapes. https://t.co/PBIT0njEMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stjohnsphoto I love Sally Mann's work,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JT__photography I need one (several) of those! Going to the seaside with my pinhole next weekend will help hopefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awwnuh sending you all the hugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awwnuh Sorry to hear that :((( Hope you are doing ok and the 'kicking in' phase doesn't last too long. I hate that phase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClickErik @HuffPostPol I've actually considered breaking a habit of a lifetime and putting a few Â£ on just this outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice bit of news, I'm going to get to photograph the Dungeness Sound Mirrors in July! Yay! #believeinconcrete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuloPeter @DBloomsday Yes, would love to see. Like I say, this is all a long way off but I find myself more interested in astronomy now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera I'll keep breathing if you will â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuloPeter @mparry1234 I'm years of making this happen, just thinking ahead. Right now I just want a telescope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mparry1234 The cool thing is you need the telescope to move during the exposure or you will get a blur!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mparry1234 I have seen it done though. There was an Episode of Sky at Night last year that showed how to do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mparry1234 Pick a good summer moonless night, a good telescope and cross your fingers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have decided my ultimate photographic aim is to produce a series of wetplate astrophotography images. Several challenges with this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Oh that is fine, I have plenty of other things on the go to eat. Will be doing Toms which crop really well here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Yes a company here sells a variety of tumbling ones. Also Blackberries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Just as an aside, I'm going to buy one of those potted raspberries! Thanks for the tip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaWriting @Frau_Inga @dfdy_ If you are headed to Canada I might just join you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover Plant the jungle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover I cant drive there so will be stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a PhD, my wife a Masters degree. We now work for a pan European company that makes Billions but hey ho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Palaeoboy Home Secretary who decided they would arbitrarily change the rules while we were just trying to live together. Theresa May]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I trusted my government before I married an immigrant, Then I realised how little my rights mattered. I understand. https://t.co/k2VDCo4FjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop Cocoa Beach *SPRING BREAK*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop Whereas in Tehran, I could take all the pictures and meet interesting people.Ea all the good Persian food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop I am going by myself, during spring break. I am going to sit on a beach being a grumpy old man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually don't want to get banned from the U.S because of @DrMarsRover @MarisaWriting @KristenWACamera @JonWilkening and so many others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently wondering if a speedy trip to Tehran will get me out of this work trip to Florida I really don't want to go on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puntofisso I used to think Brave New World was the more realistic dystopia, I'd never seen doublethink in the real world. Now I have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up with a distant view of these forts. One day I will visit them. I wonder how I would pinhole them. https://t.co/yv4ChQ9aXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@achatainfr Thanks! Won't stop trying. It eats away at inspiration though. No significant lens based work in months. So lucky for pinhole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andywasley @JuloPeter @EMULSIVEfilm Hope it brings you lots of joy. I don't own a Holga but I so get why they are addictive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One happy thing this week. I've noticed people associate me so much with pinhole I get tagged in their shots. It is flattering, thanks guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera I know hun, it sucks doesn't it? Hard to see the possibility for recovery in the deep end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrutalHouse 'Because I don't live in Poundbury']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have to find a way to not beat myself up about yet another unproductive weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to self medicate with photography in London today. Then the panic hit and I am back home :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit @Grumpyfck @EMULSIVEfilm I will have some leftover Haggis tomorrow. Might give it a go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera She shoots what she likes on the only camera she has. You are a superb photographer, so shoot what you like, will be great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera One of my favourite photographers is my friend from work, she just posts pics from her phone on holiday. I love them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Givemeabiscuit @Grumpyfck @EMULSIVEfilm Haggis Samosas? Now I know such things exist I cannot be happy until I have had one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera By the way, you own a Hassy right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover @donkittle @EMULSIVEfilm @emmef2 Sky detail...now there is something I seldom get with paper/pinhole!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera You take good photographs. I wouldn't worry. The only reason I tag things as pinhole is to chat to those of a likemind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllThingsEla Yeah, speaking as a big geek of all things Russian, it hasn't gripped me...and that vignetting is bizarre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell the cinematographer of Child 44 that Russian lenses of the 50s were much better than the weird effect their film is mimicking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to someone telling me that my comments on her pictures make her day. Faith in social media restored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarisaWriting I will support this motion so long as you allow me to refer to Pesto as the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big hug to my friends. You all know who you are. I have been through the wringer several times and you come through for me every time â¤ï¸ðŸ’›ðŸ’šðŸ’™ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuloPeter @dsamaddar I got told by a friend on Instagram that my comments on her work make her day. Interesting comments are so important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar @mparry1234 waffle or nuance in inaccurate language.. sometimes that is where joy lays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dizd @ILFORDPhoto @Flickr My Mum and Dad have this on their wall, it;s from near their home. No greater privilege!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dizd @ILFORDPhoto A lovely film... this is it in Rodinal https://t.co/wMDAqE4VlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dizd But I do know I will love Major Kira till my dying breath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mparry1234 @dsamaddar I've tried to force pics during travels that would have been better had I waited or told work I needed more leave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mparry1234 @dsamaddar Even If it wasn't his meaning, getting the feel for places before trying to take pictures is good advice anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recovering by watching more #DS9 In Sisko we trust!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar Incidentally, the foreword to 'The Americans' is my favourite bit of Kerouac writing. Prob because he wasn't allowed to waffle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar Not sure really it means more than a metaphor along those lines. I revealed once I am no scientist but I did a lot of Eng lit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar I guess I'm employing some poetic licence here. A sort of passive looking equating to listening vs active looking meaning looking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar But it could be just a 'deepity', although that sort of thing doesn't sound right out of a cantankerous old sod like Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar At a stretch, learning to absorb the background movements, light and scenes of a place before actively searching for pics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamiraAhmedUK I'm sure there is a reason why this can happen but currently not imaginative to work it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristenWACamera Don't be worried Kristen, I'm not a risk to myself. Just not good to be around at the mot. Lost a lot of friends yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today will be brought to you by the sound of silence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was brought to you by inadequate mental health care, papering over cracks &amp; the reality of chronic depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awwnuh That made me depressed and ill 10 years ago &amp; I can't really cope now.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>