<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald Raurimu is not in Northland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is all by design - but what's the end game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverCarle I wasnt aiming for soothing ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams reservation aside, that's a very nice thing to say. Thank you ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverCarle see the Obama vid for a non seminary ref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler I'm against people punching other people in the face based on their reckons. The state should have a monopoly on violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not really on board with this whole, "it's OK to punch some people in the face" thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sisters - Rise Up and Demand Equality! https://t.co/xNDiDgq0qM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress Getting in early with a WOTY plant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @GraemeEdgeler maybe they just used Colin Craig's photographer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling out bad behaviour - our naming policy ramps up - guest post  | A wake up call for businesses. https://t.co/pszlhbDs4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelcubey @jeremycorbyn his core will be most harmed by a brexit - that is more clear now than was the case before the ref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulapenfold yeah - that was something - was hoping to get my s*%t together during the denouement, &amp; then they threw that in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've got a backup of tears you need getting rid of, I can recommend #lionmovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aschiff @ACLU good on you. I was just saying I'm not going to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 @NZRedCross @ACLU thanks - I was just looking for those links for a follower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mellopuffy I'm all in favour of taking action - protests, tweets etc, but when it comes to spending $$, I'd rather spend mine @ home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mellopuffy true - but the US economy is the biggest in the world - do you really think their need is bigger than our own needy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because what's happening in the US fills our twitter feeds, it doesn't mean their need is greater than our own #rtpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I will not donate to @ACLU - there are plenty in the US to do that. I might donate to NZ refugee resettlement though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf Fake news! Lots of people went dressed  as yellow seats. More people watched these 7's in person or online than any other. Period!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tslumley thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still don't know what this means - ESTA no longer valid for travel from New Zealand? https://t.co/gYmZnCygI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @jimwaterson same thing happened to my Canadian colleagues when I visited the White House- they are very strict about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone heard from Ed Asner? Haven't seen him since Up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MOhlhausenFTC Dear Chairwoman Ohlhausen. Congratulations on your appointment. I look forward to working with you in the ICDPPC and APPA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering Mary Tyler Moore - Husker Du - "Love Is All Around" https://t.co/5Bg0Dvwll4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PogoWasRight @NZPrivacy We don't have any inside info, but very likely the suppression is interim only, to allow him to inform family etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When that joke is really starting to wear thin https://t.co/n1dmLAxI1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So PJ didn't banter. Why should she? Does the lead in Hamlet break out mid performance &amp; say "Hey wellington! What about this weather??"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelBarrowman so great. She brang us her love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sublime tbh- and yes for a minute, I did have to be that guy with the device https://t.co/jIWlQuLHe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for PJ - so excite! https://t.co/vNgHiyicpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could go either way ... https://t.co/UQZncZkILS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-cop charged over police systems https://t.co/rn1eyYolJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensing Murder is despicable exploitation of tragedy and grief by charlatans and their network enablers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis your welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump supporter and champertous businessman Peter Thiel buys up large in NZ https://t.co/TiBDXOJalw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher @plinythemidlkid they're all chins, hair &amp; denim in that pic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid funny thing - I remembered and listened to that track only a couple of weeks ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matarikipax @RichardOSeager the Privacy Act is very often relevant. Have a look at https://t.co/dGqqbwYp4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[give my name and contact details to get action on an abandoned car on yellow lines on a council turnaround.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @WgtnCC your call centre guy was courteous and professional, but was following a wrong and misguided policy. There is no need for me to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From this to this in a few hours (sparing you the in-between bits) https://t.co/QJgMtJCjvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen FWIW, I agree with @OAICgov's position, and am not bound by the Australian High Court decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnityBooks please put one away for me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid thanks - I haven't listened to that version for years (#IggyFTW) - who's on backing vocals? Sounds like Tina Turner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum @anamariecox I'm hoping for "I'm starting with the man in the mirror/I'm asking him to change his ways"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer warning - re Expression Sessions Ltd https://t.co/r2k5LFwsKj @Consumernz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to @jordantcarter from @InternetNZ on privacy, or lack of, in messaging app, and what they're doing about it. https://t.co/VaZLZAWwil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't make it to Sir Bruce Slane's funeral? You can watch the livestream here from 2pm https://t.co/M2Wy1RJtfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" ...a display of hypocrisy so large that it is visible from space." https://t.co/mRRVY6eCuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing my bit for local tourism #WhyWellington https://t.co/akHElErYqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardiannews @guardian get her a ticket to World of Wearable Art show in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Wellington @nickcave - let us know if you need any tips!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamish_keith @LouisMMayo so the cyclists have been effective - doesn't make them whiners does it? What do you think @pippacoom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good story. I wonder if anyone else might have had a useful perspective? https://t.co/QVToidBuqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamish_keith @LouisMMayo but why the need to set 1 against the other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamish_keith "whining cyclists"? A bit unnecessarily provocative doncha think @LouisMMayo? - aren't peds *and* ðŸš´ðŸ¾ entilted 2 safe transit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Ecclestone welcome to the jungle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sturdyAlex I'm not a close follower of and a bit puzzled by UK politics. Could Corbyn surprise pundits a la Brexit and Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheSellout is the best book I've read this year. Satire that gives new meaning to the term black humour. McEwan's Nutshell comes in 2nd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind of tempted to see Guns n Roses. Would make wonky third leg of a stool with PJ Harvey, &amp; Nick Cave. Anyone going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victim wins access to police video footage https://t.co/tIdLhyIrl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Privacy Commissioner rules Corrections breached privacy in refusing to release CCTV footage https://t.co/tStOeAWKYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markcubey I love those things! Weapons of Mass Inundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler until my term expires, or my warrant is revoked by the Governor-General.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA what sort of thing? My 13 yo very into the arduino he go for Xmas - looking for ideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for a swim? https://t.co/rRT2fdzdBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc if it didn't exist it would be necessary to invent it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tributes flow for New Zealand's first Privacy Commissioner Sir Bruce Slane https://t.co/5m3b6pUyzh via @1NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a great self-effacing  sense of humour too - He once described himself as "the only lay person ever to be president of the law society"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secondzeit what? No Vampire's Kiss? His finest hour IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Delwynd1 @ChrisKeall he's really sheeting it home now ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall my partner is a baker - you've proved your point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyer, broadcaster, tweeter @BruceHoulton, campaigner, public servant, devoted grandparent, raconteur, internationalist - friend to many]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President of the NZ Law Society, Chair of Broadcasting Commission, 1st Privacy Commissioner, President of Int'l Bar Assn, @RNZ's panelist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very sad to let you know of the passing of a great and compassionate New Zealander. Mentor, friend, trailblazer RIP Sir Bruce Slane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SofSofSoph solution - tilt your blinds ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkipender @GPFutures interesting piece though - but main feature of ToC = depletion of the resource whereas the online world is expanding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkipender @GPFutures thanks - I don't think the tragedy of the commons is apt, or works very well to help understand the online world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @kaupapa I don't think so. Aren't there zillions of rivers feeding in to Taupo, but only one Waikato coming out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mihi_Forbes @sirmadbutcher @TeKaeaOfficial yep - that's fixed it. Hasn't made it worse at all. Not one bit. NopeðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing as how everyone else is subtweeting, I thought I may as well get in on the act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jesus and Mary Chain #MakeABandReligious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I'm doing #MakeABandReligious right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Paul and Mary #MakeABandReligious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nine Inch Nails #MakeABandReligious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleigh_young think the dream, and the energy you need to realise it will fill your chi, and charge your chakras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslevin that's the first time I've heard/seen it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SRoosegaarde maybe stopping the smog would be a better idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@di_f_w IKR? We'll be rolling it out on https://t.co/vw4CSK5wjT this year to help with queries &amp; complaints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't seen your cat/dog/hopes for a redemptive 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geonet slightly odd that your infographic doesn't have a M7 value?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bored at the bach/beach? Here's my NYE chat with Lynn Freeman on TheWeekend Commisioned: Privacy Commissioner https://t.co/9j4ZjocffT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Predictably, both Twitter &amp; Yahoo make the list. The latter bc of security breaches The Ars 2017 tech co Deathwatch https://t.co/Q7mEO0QuVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eey0re @A_Ecclestone @djhdcj hard to describe scooping up terabytes worth of files on multiple hard drives as anything else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Ecclestone @eey0re @djhdcj pretty specious?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eey0re @A_Ecclestone @djhdcj it's the indiscriminate nature of Snowden's collection&amp; leaking that=the diff btwn him Ellsberg *and* Klein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eey0re @A_Ecclestone @djhdcj# interesting read, and as much as I admire @eff's work, I can't agree.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>