<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Miro â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ðŸ–¤ðŸ’œ ðŸ“¸ by me. Photo shoots done- Home time. ðŸ˜ŽðŸŒ´ https://t.co/VcHz8FVp64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsBiceps @pandsreid I haven't watched it back. I plan to this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobCopsey ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ he's a lovely guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobCopsey Ryan! I'm abroad so can't watch it! Is he doing ok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobCopsey my friend is in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ever awesome @rihanna being iconic #saveOurHens â¤ ðŸ‘‘ https://t.co/DScIaDEcfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMattDowell @all_serena that run was iconic though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise here. May is awful. https://t.co/udYKosYx2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What truly horrible news to start the morning ðŸ’” https://t.co/bARGZ5VEbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MRisingStar18 @rogerfederer @AustralianOpen I'm so so happy and proud of Rogi â¤â¤ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡­ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerfederer well done! You worked so hard for this- so proud ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡­! @AustralianOpen https://t.co/9l219RiIKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerfederer I'm so happy you won! ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ â¤â¤â¤â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ShyamBhatt he's in the cupboard, safe and sound ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the beginning of the week I was worried about Serena and Rog getting past R1! #AusOpen â¤â¤â¤ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so emotional- I can't believe it. #AusOpen @rogerfederer â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually shed a tear, first one in about 10 years! All because of @rogerfederer @AustralianOpen #AusOpen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really good #Netflix #TheExpanse https://t.co/bUtq8NBj2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsungHelpUK it's a Samsung LED UE40K5100-b , it's less than a month old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redelectro7 @SamsungUK yep, i just turned it on, and they're shut until Monday. So frustrating as it's brand new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've only had my @SamsungUK HD tv a few weeks and it has already broken... flashing red light ands blank screen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everyone having a go at Karlie Kloss for being at Serena's win today? They have been friends for ages! ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karliekloss made it to @serenawilliams win! â¤ðŸ‘‘ðŸ’« #AusOpen @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Venuseswilliams @serenawilliams fantastic speeches, shoutouts for Isha and #renasArmy â¤â¤â¤ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Queen. Now hold forever Serena #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena vs Venus ðŸ‘‘â¤ early nerves from Queen S. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROGER â¤ðŸ˜â¤ðŸ˜â¤ so happy @rogerfederer is through to the #ausOpen final! @AustralianOpen https://t.co/BWLdVBxOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redelectro7 it's all getting eaten...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPJGodfrey it's also too early for me to deal deal with him with giant fluffy dogs. ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPJGodfrey I feel like he would be up for it, tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simultaneously super excited and sad that the last season of @girlsHBO is nearly here! @lenadunham https://t.co/pfoslHeOGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mum using a Britney yawning gif to say she was tired the other day ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚@makocharian https://t.co/5ytdjTLmRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix @anorderlymess 'out of order, are we watching.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix @anorderlymess I said do IV but I was overruled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussing with @anorderlymess whether to watch #starWars chronologically from Ep. I or chronologically by release date from Ep. IV ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrProdigy555 she can take out Angie then flop tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_harry91 that went down well then...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandsreid @VishakhaRF @DejnaDM @ChumJetztBAMOS @CaroFederista @Lufedepotro @gothami_de @adi_singh18 @NatyMercury_RF  thanks! ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woken up to Serena &amp; Thiem winning, Roger's tweets &amp; now wide awake at 5am- just in time for Rafa/Sascha @AustralianOpen #sleepisfortheweak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerfederer it's so good to have you back! ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡­â¤ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡­ #AusOpen2017 @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearlescent48 I can usual binge watch something, but there is so much to take in every episode!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thaiguy84 I'm so stressed out by it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching season 1 of #TheManInTheHighCastle and I'm stressed out throughout through the entirety of each episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bigwasp80 it's so awful. Makes me so angry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you and John are ok @chrissyteigen? The behaviour from them is disgusting. https://t.co/DYF1SIFDV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anorderlymess @mrnicklevine here you go. https://t.co/9OEdkWsQVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@footfaulttennis They turned it off by the time I got to a computer :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoePassmore I know they did, you told me last time it happened to me :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaAbbaszadeh It's happened to me twice now :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just iphone stolen by men on mopeds. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borna_coric tough luck and good fight out there Borna! Good to see you back from injury! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bondnickbond and this... very me https://t.co/7K0rrDt7Jt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bondnickbond for some reason no pictures of me (Diedre) come up... but these do... https://t.co/RgF51h9GcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How today is going for me. https://t.co/E8STrzP7AP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @rogerfederer on his @GQMagazine Most Stylish Man of 2016 award in his post match #AusOpen interview 'at least I won something last year']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoying #ANTM with @RitaOra ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandsreid GC is pretty iconic https://t.co/DTjxbXYs7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plavandoski it's Gemma Collins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandsreid it's Gemma Collins on Celebrity Big Brother- she got to have a pony to walk around on her birthday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January has literally been non stop https://t.co/WT2lK9s9Gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, this is still one of my favourite Serena commercials: https://t.co/cba82KHWLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great read about the Queen's journey; @serenawilliams https://t.co/ZAT1a8JhDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanHarkin I am shook! (I also watched an entire episode- what is wrong with me?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dorian_kupo it's such a hot mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Ethel Hallow is now Jyn in Starwars... https://t.co/BeKM7hrXEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix yes! She killed him with an iron I think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix neither do I but she was in it years ago- a Slater Sister!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@footfaulttennis @LadyBellatrix I have no idea why I'm watching this. It's a hot mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix yes! Also Little Mo from Eastenders is in the new one. Brimming with stars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... and Enid is now Nancy in Hollyoaks ... if i used the word Shook, I would... https://t.co/oKYKDzD0O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have remade the Worst Witch with Lyanna Mormont as Mildred Hubble... https://t.co/IDS2a9DAFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usopen  @AustralianOpen aww you guys are so cute ðŸ¤— @Wimbledon and @rolandgarros too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited for @MariaSharapova 's return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started #themaninthehighcastle and I'm obsessed after one episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bigwasp80 hahaha! I forgot about this video!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjc05 of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painted and Deocrated my room for the first time ever and I'm now like... #FifthHarmony #WorkFromHome https://t.co/Ij9IwPYSxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrollandGarros @footfaulttennis haha I have replied accordingly on @vamosBamos ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyBkr she really is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @MichelleObama , what a brilliant, heartfelt and inspirational speech. ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ðŸ‘‘ https://t.co/vNdbIXsiww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week is not the one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TfL just told severe delays on circle line after the person at Aldgate East tannoy advised us to go to there and told of 12 min delay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TfL let's see how long it takes for a circle like to come now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. And told another HC would be in 3 mins-train leaves and told on platforms it will be 9 mins... @TfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many wrong pieces of information given to us by @TfL - got off the train as told the HC train changed into a circle line mid journey...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandsreid @JJlovesTennis I know- she said the tournament had been 'amazing' so silly to fluff this up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mat_the_w86 @joshcharles_21 is it Will?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BelindaBencic and @rogerfederer ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I aboslutely loved this Thiem interview:  thrhttp://www.atpworldtour.com/en/video/thiem-says-off-season-in-tenerife-was-fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newballsplease other twin is over it. Maybe browsing Maria's app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahRapp how come they are so expensive? We got ours for Â£90 (for both shows)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawanda50 @BrisbaneTennis haha! Aw it's Rafa though, it's understandable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawanda50 ha ha! Love this @BrisbaneTennis good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix I feel like he's just turned 23, so it's about what he does in the next two years for me! ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix Thiem is just out of the nextgen cut off to be fair (well he was when they did this time around)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrollandGarros @LadyBellatrix @drop_and_roll it really is, his and Rafa's!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyBellatrix @TrollandGarros @drop_and_roll OMG Yas! I was trying to work out what triggered you remembering this lovely embrace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrollandGarros @LadyBellatrix @drop_and_roll also this is from June!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaroWozniacki great start to the year Caro! ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bondnickbond I feel this is why you love the Eurovision Song Contest so much... https://t.co/ipjqRqXA8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg everyone on my TL with glitchy betting site streams watching the greatest player of all time... https://t.co/Lo6nAmAAgP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>