<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Rain! Thank God!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what kind of trip these would do https://t.co/ilU5ZwCzZn #youwouldbepoisoned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee we can all only dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today too busy and stressful. Muggy weather and periods don't help. Need viscous hate fuck someone #anthatswhyimsingle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grrr rain not comin, plumbers have water off for fixing, lots of shit to do and EDF2 down I feel antsy and annoyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No good. Cool today but I still feel hot and sweaty and gross. Whhhyyy? ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History has shown time and time again; there is always a bigger evil than what you face today. Disagree? You lack imagination, lucky you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleeping on it, I think what irked me was the whole"this person is an ass, no one would voluntarily love them"... NOT TRUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, had dream last night Trump was my CEO, &amp; was being an ass to me smithers from Simpsons. His car was a mess &amp; I stole his laundry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yrs! Yrs! Cold! Clouds! Overcast! Rain! Yes! Yes! Want! ðŸŒðŸŒ‚â˜”â˜”ðŸ’“ðŸ’“ WANT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is more important than what body you're in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope that if Trump was black/female/whatever, you'd hate him just as much as you do now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Obama is alright, but I like him for what he did, not because of what skin colour he has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, fuck Gillard. I didn't even vote for her. Fuck her and fuck her carbon tax. Abbot is my hero for rescuing us from that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact, being the watch-the-world burn sort of sadist myself, that would be just poetic; 1st female president being a Trump who's worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and for those fortunate US folk who think having a leader being female is oh-so great, lucky them; they didn't have Julia Gillard fucking up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know, maybe in several years time there will be another anti-trump campaign, not because of Don, but cause wife is worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[believe it or not there are woman out there who marry asses for whatever reason &amp; aren't slaves but just as much of an ass themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'know what? I agree. Trump is an ass, but doesn't mean his wife is a slave. She chose to marry an ass https://t.co/EBN6OAUmwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish for massage and coffee. I get flat white but I feel entitled to a Vienna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I am like a vampire. Everytime I see the sun I'm like hissing and spitting in loathing of it's burning light, scurrying off into dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too exhausted... Too bloody hot. &amp; yes I can complain as the unairconditioned, non-insulated factory I run around in is in 40's *C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roses are red, violets are blue, Mondays are bullshit and Tuesdays suck too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want protection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh coffee breaks are soooo booorrriiiinnnggg without kiwifarms :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to see the true measure of a man, watch how he treats his interiors, not his equals. - J.K. Rowling aka my desktop calendar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*tien grows extra arms* goku: I've never fought four arms before me: you've fought forearms goku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sea turtle makes tea* Oh no! It's turtle black!!!! #dragonball #dragonballsuper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The fight was anticlimactic and void of any catharses" "I didn't understand a word you said" - perfect response to fanboy whinging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is more try than cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master roshi stands on his cane and channels cologne from ranma 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*tien aims a kamehameha at audience* what is he, Vegeta?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should invite nice guy here ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flat smelt a bit so I brought cheap scent rocks. The place smells nice but it's making me slleeeeeppppyyyyy ðŸ˜«ðŸ’¤ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it after too much TV I feel brain dead and lazy-limbed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never noticed it before. But: no nose. Bald. Krillin can pass for a really short Voldemort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tien: hahaha villafy me, but that doesn't change your friends incompetence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not how you fall down it's how get back up. That's the measure of a man- someone cool online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demon guy: you must either be brave or stupid Goku: I'm not either of those guys I'm goku LOOLLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ED_Retweets your welcome :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["well. He's possessed. That explains it." pilaf, after Goku kamehamehaed Mais robot arm off. No wonder she hates Black.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delicious looking cock https://t.co/x1iPJRJ4KB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee I would, but having a name makes it easier for people who want to get my attention. If I want another name should tell everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee that is your life. In my life labels are a matter of safety. If there are none acid will be drunk and water will not be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee we have language for a reason. An apple has a label. A candle has a name. Why remove that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee if someone called me a self- absorbed wanker they might be right but it's a flaw I enjoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee everything has labels everything has a name other wise it's a ling winded description when a word will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee called attention whores. They're everywhere online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee there are ppl who scream to the void about themselves. Ok. There are ppl who argue. Ok. There are ppl who preach to choir. No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee I meant don't be someone who bans people for differing opinions. What convo you're having is cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee if I called you a pretty person that is a label. Guess you'd hate being called that too. Or if you called someone an idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee what do you think it means?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee don't be a hugbox person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee if you're looking for that on the internet off all places I'd say you lost the battle before you started.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee just vent on twitter and join the club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee I'll believe it's not private when I meet someone who cares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee it's a free internet. Besides their Moms probably on Facebook why not let them soapbox in private]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sosaysrenee this is twitter what do you expect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yamcha vs invisible man. Should have three lasers pointed at him and say its the predator #youareoneuglymotherfucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't even knock paganism or nothing beyond knee jerk reaction to what she starts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's funny is I rarely mentioned Jesus during my Facebook yet she posts stupid and says she doesn't start anything. What bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look fangs is as triggered by Jesus as the Goth girl and half of the danger hairs out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think in one ep in DBZ puar is a vampire that bites piccolo for... Reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puar is now sonic the hedgehog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fangs the vampire is one sparkle away from being as stupid as Edward cullen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey we get to see young master roshi cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think vegeta is the replacement for launch. Or maybe launch is notvegeta. Or femmevegeta. Either way they're both psychos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maxxed out all the GB on my desktop internet. That was dumb *kicks self* that's what I get for streaming all that animu #badaddictions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL Goku fighting black in dragon ball #wrongone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if when a guy says he needs new pants it's more or less disturbing than if a girl says it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching DB red ribbon saga end... No wonder zamasu possessed him to kill everyone. Just look at that scary little shit go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sum of human knowledge is not not contained in any one language- fortune cookie - IMO knowledge can't be gained from just 1 mindset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace is the divine ability to cope with every circumstance - fortune cookie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine &amp; you will never see shadows - fortune cookie. B-bbut I like shadows.. Shadows are nice &amp; cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should ordered red rooster :/ ðŸ”ðŸ®ðŸ®ðŸ®ðŸ¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Chinese new year by marathon watching DB eating dumplings &amp; fortune cookies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my shit!!! Gabby's brother is a minister at my fam's church!!! How did I not see this???? Aaaaahhhh!!!! ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜µðŸ˜µðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then again.... https://t.co/oJ5F0r4orn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either go all the way and be a misanthropist or shut the fuck up everybody sucks the end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about using archeology to find when aborigines first came here &amp; call that invasion day those poor kangaroos getting traumatized by them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this white guilt is condescending nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it invasion when they're all "no. Please stop. We want to go back to England. Oh God we're in some strange country oh God whhhyyy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of which, why call it invasion day? I know my ancestors (1/2 convicts other 1/2 just recent came) didn't want to come here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about that the day started off getting laughed at by kookaburra, to lamb roast &amp; pav with fam, tea then watching stuff then fireworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fireworks!!!! ðŸ’“ðŸ’“ðŸŽ†ðŸŽ†ðŸŽ†ðŸŽ‡ðŸŒŒðŸŒ ðŸŒ  I love my flat it has a good view of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thus my Australia day begins with my laundry sink getting clogged &amp; overflowing while kookaburras laugh their asses off. Brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a platform game for dragon ball? Watching red- ribbon saga makes me think so. That pirate robot looks like something out of rayman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't presume to know your enemy. Learn about your enemy or you enter the fight a fool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manic pixie nightmare calling kiwifarms alt-right. LOL these blinded transtrenders don't know what alt-right is or what kiwifarms were]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I've lost control of my life https://t.co/ekyZjEnnID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoSaysRenee consume at own risk. You have been warned https://t.co/EGiWeIPa7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoSaysRenee uuuhhhhhhhh... maybe not :/ (or if you do, have thick skin and a big sense of humour)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoSaysRenee ever been to the dark recesses of the internet, such as ED? They have many an enemy. They piss everyone off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logical response: WHY ARE YOU TYPING STILL THEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example I have oft seen online, usually vs ED: "I don't care. can't you see I don't care. BTW I don't care. I am not bothered. I don't care"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[complain about is one big scream that you've got some stupid issue your obsessing over. Just grin and admit it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't play pretend &amp; try to be expressionless in an attempt to be badass. you don't fool anyone. From the way you dress to everything you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General blue: sounds frightening. Go check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colour me a bitch but i kinda like general blue]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>