<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seamuscyprien @scrahallia Of course not. But what do you do if lobbying doesn't work in the emerging EU atmosphere. Lobby harder??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seamuscyprien @scrahallia Simply lobbying for support is tactic not strategy especially as EU could be transformed by national elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seamuscyprien @scrahallia None of other 26 have a land border with UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seamuscyprien @scrahallia Standing back and rolling over doesn't work. Remember ECB's bomb in Dublin. Nothing wrong with demanding place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seamuscyprien @scrahallia Trade negotiations is reserved power of Commission but we should be demanding exception for IR on a/c of border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If UK has hard #Brexit &amp; sets min corp tax, one of our key FDI benefits disappears unless we can beat UK rate which EU won't allow. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland should demand place on EC negotiating team. It should also quietly threaten a referendum on outcome &amp; explore #Irexit. #vinb #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump + #Brexit + #CCCTB will squeeze Ireland &amp; we need totally new strategies &amp; leadership to address them. Roll on #GE. #vinb #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only does Denis O'Brien control too much media through #INM etc but he also deploys #dinnybots to other national outlets eg #rte &amp; #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarrieSam @tmccartney12 He already has. Countries where Trump does business are not hit by new travel restrictions. https://t.co/fs5EJaFWbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is a #dinnybot employee chairing #marian when he could be employed by #redacted own radio stations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Molloy: Regulation is a joke in Ireland - look at the banks, energy, prices, water, ODCE, ombudsmen etc. Complete failures.  #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJohndel2 Just watch the Saudi Aramco flotation this year. Billions in fees for US banksters. #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q. Why was Saudi not included in Trump's list of blocked countries? 
A, Oil, $$$$$, banksters.  #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Horgan praised Trump's cabinet on grounds they are exceptionally talented entrepreneurs. Oh yea? Spare us the spin. #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just do it (by mistake and then retract) #liveline https://t.co/Oj9ukEfzfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cblive seems to rotate Varadkar, Harris &amp; Coveney between programmes. Three great spoofers but lousy ministers. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was his €8 mln loan from #Anglo fully repaid or did taxpayer pick up tab? Why weren't those who setup loan before c… https://t.co/dnEB8FNqos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great report by @CaitrionaPerry on deeper, unsettling significance of @realDonaldTrump spin on inauguration attendance. #NoTrust #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on his arguments about inauguration attendance numbers, @realDonaldTrump is either lying, blind, disillusional, bad or mad. #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership of USA is, for next 4 years, in hands of property developers, Goldman Sachs, vultures, climate deniers &amp; right-wingers. #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on the argument about inauguration attendance numbers, @realDonaldTrump is either lying, blind, disillusional or bad. #marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marywallace07 He had better deliver to his "people" or he won't last a full term especially if he only delivers to his family biz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, leadership of USA is in hands of property developers, GoldmanSachs, vultures, climate deniers &amp; right-wingers. Sorry people. #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elpenor_Dignam Yes, And #GoldmanSachs take over the US Presidency along with some #VultureFunds, #climatedeniers and a #propertydeveloper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swans_song Great campaign speech but not statesmanlike. Truely lifted drawbridge on fortress America. He &amp; his GS team had better deliver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swans_song Looking forward to his speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swans_song Pent up demand is such that no need for any specdev so why seek 15% on national radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer requires 15% margin on account of 'huge risks' associated with house building. Unbelievable claptrap. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[€6 mln to cover Expressway loses is a total distraction. #rtebias losing 3+ times more. Just a plaything for Lord Ross to privatise. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamonMelia Agree with your point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamonMelia As I understand it all treaty changes must be agreed in Ireland by means of a referendum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would happen if #Brexit requires EU treaty changes and, therefore, a #referendum in Ireland? Could we hold process to ransom? #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If UK gets hard #Brexit (99% chance) &amp; euro/EU hit big problems after 3 State elections (3x10%), there's a 33% case for a #Irexit. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK looks for almost all EU benefits but without actual membership, immigration or ECJ. Hard to see its #Brexit shopping list been met. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meeple101 I'm not referring to the deal itself. I'm referring to the subsequent treaty changes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinCostell16 At least that number. Can you just see the chaos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would happen if #Brexit requires EU treaty changes and, therefore, a #referendum in Ireland? Could we hold process to ransom? #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If UK gets hard #Brexit (99% chance) &amp; euro/EU hit big problems after 3 State elections (3x10%), there's a 33% case for a #Irexit. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK looking for almost all EU benefits but without actual membership or immigration or ECJ. Hard to see its #Brexit demands been met. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tim_rigby You might need our help as we have most interest amongst 27 in a good #Brexit for UK due to our very close ties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tim_rigby Not really. The comment was as much aimed at Brussels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would happen if #Brexit requires treaty changes and, therefore, a #referendum in Ireland? Could we hold the process to ransom? #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AHAR may be significant to some but we still haven't got to bottom of 2008 #bankingcrisis with its dodgy loans, cooked books etc. #liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theotriangle Understand all that but we could have new Govs in 3 key states during these 2 years. Anything could emerge. Unknown unknowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If UK gets hard #Brexit (80+% chance) &amp; if euro/EU hit big problems after 3 state elections (50%), there's a 40% case for #Irexit. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theotriangle But could UK's future relationship with EU require treaty changes? Not an expert!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would happen if #Brexit requires treaty changes and, therefore, a #referendum in Ireland? Could we hold the process to ransom? #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 politicians on #vinb discussing #Brexit. All heat &amp; no light as we have no say. How about debating #Irexit where we have some control?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks like a massive scandal. Much, much larger than #VultureFunds, incompetent banks, Gardai failures etc. Well done #cblive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do @simoncoveney &amp; #FG keep pushing people to rent rather than buy homes? Is it part of FG's strategy to make rich richer? #cblive #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does @simoncoveney live in the #cblive studio? He'd be better employed by arranging for local authorities to build of more homes. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope @SimonCoveney has learnt difference between "% return on investment" &amp; "% annual increase in rents" since #MorningIreland. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like order" says @realDonaldTrump. I'm swamped by paper so I'll clear the swamp (and maybe buy a PC). https://t.co/Bx5XC3CftP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMHO, News at 6.1, Lee, Tubs, Kenny very biased in favour of #watercharges &amp; ignored huge concerns about #irishwater #redacted. #saturdayrte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So boring - just like watching botox dry with some fillers between the ads. #latelateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swans_song His proposals don't go far enough. Lads can discuss biz with him at meals. Blind trust (very difficult) is the only robust soln.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Priorities for TDs: 1) Re-election 2) Salary 3) Exs 4) Pension 5) Holidays 6) Ministerial car 7) Cronies 8) Constituency 9) Nation. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EndaKennyTD #FF #FG should watch out as #ApolloHouse #homesweethome could be much bigger than #watercharges.#vinb #rtept #rtenews #selloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump did great "snow job" at pressie today with all the folders. He's handing control of empire to 2 sons but keeping profits !! #rtenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump Great "snow job" at pressie today. Seems ur handing "control" of ur empire to the 2 lads but u are keeping the profits !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayjaycafe Maybe he could visit #ApolloHouse or a few E&amp;As.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our dear "leader" @EndaKennyTD has popped up on #rtenews. I thought he'd retired!
#rtept #vinb #cblive #todaysor #MorningIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frankmacc Either way a hard Brexit is bad for Ireland. Anything could happen during 2017 within EU due to national elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If EU deals UK a very hard #Brexit &amp; if euro &amp; EU hit problems following national elections, there's a strong case for #Irexit. #rtept #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No follow up by #rtept to #selloff. No grilling of Kenny/Noonan to explain &amp; apologise for "donating" tens of billions to vultures. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful that #Nama &amp; banks sold homes in bulk at huge discounts to #VultureFunds. Should have been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianFlanagan1 Means that #VultureFunds could clear €20+ bn of profits out of Ireland. Equivalent to a full year's income tax. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianFlanagan1 By comparison, #Nama might make artificial profit of €2-3 bn. Tax take from #VultureFunds should be €2bn. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #VultureFunds seek 20% pa on €80bn Irish assets purchased, profit over 4 yr wind-down could be €24bn with negligible tax due. #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinCostell16 @marywallace07 Yes, investigations are showboating. Would prefer GE with new thinking, real leadership, strong ethics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is going to rise in year or so. Interest rates will follow &amp; put huge additional strain on heavily-borrowed home borrowers.#cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't Noonan in the hot seat to face the music instead of sending his junior minister Murphy? #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #VultureFunds seek 20% pa on €80bn Irish assets purchased, profit over 4 yr wind-down could be €24bn with negligible tax due. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marywallace07 Yes absolutely. Noonan at a stroke of his pen could have stopped the sell off or at least slowed it down #selloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s a great market, we’ve never seen rental increases like this in any jurisdiction that we’re aware of." CEO, Ires REIT. #selloff #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C&amp;AG &amp; #PAC must investigate scandalous bulk sell-off by #Nama #IBRC of mortgages &amp; SME loans to #VultureFunds. #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C&amp;AG &amp; #PAC must investigate scandalous bulk sell-off by #Nama #IBRC of mortgages &amp; SME loans to #VultureFunds. #selloff #vinb #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful of #Nama #FG to have sold homes in bulk to #VultureFunds. Should have been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs. #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful of #Nama #FG to have sold homes in bulk to #VultureFunds. Should have been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs. #selloff #vinb #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#VultureFunds bought assets from #Nama #IBRC #AIB &amp; sell them back at huge markup to Irish banks &amp; funds. #Magicmoney #selloff #vinb #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#VultureFunds bought assets from #Nama #IBRC #AIB &amp; sell them back at huge markup to Irish banks &amp; funds. Magic money. #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame for firesale of #Nama assets lies with board, Noonan, #FG &amp; #DoF. Huge loss to taxpayer + huge social cost. #selloff #vinb #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame for firesale of #Nama assets lies with board, Noonan, #FG &amp; #DoF. Huge loss to taxpayer + huge social cost. #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #VultureFunds seek 20% pa on €200bn assets, profit over 4 yr wind-down would be €80bn. 20 times #Nama's "profit". #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Nama acquired bank loans at huge discounts &amp; sold them to #VultureFunds who sell them on at huge tax-free profits. #selloff #vinb #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Nama acquired bank loans at huge discounts &amp; sold them to #VultureFunds who sell them on at huge tax-free profits. #thegreatirishselloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #VultureFunds seek 20% pa on €200 bn assets, then profit over 4 yr wind-down would be €80 bn. 20 times #Nama's "profit". #selloff #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British health minister in Parliament today answering questions about ED crisis. Where are @SimonHarrisTD &amp; #Dail? #rtenews #cblive #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely wrong for #Nama &amp; #FG to have sold homes in bulk to #VultureFunds. Should have been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely wrong for #Nama &amp; #FG to sell homes in bulk to #VultureFunds. Should have been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs. #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pubinq Yes, deliberate. Easier to sell in bulk even at huge discounts &amp; extra loss to taxpayer. Suited FG ideology to support big biz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moro1968 @countryboy606 Yes, deliberate error. Easier to sell in bulk even at huge discounts &amp; extra loss to taxpayer. Suited FG ideology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCH_74 Partly needing cash quick (allegedly). Easier to sell in bulk even at huge discounts &amp; extra loss to taxpayer. Suited FG ideology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s a great market, we’ve never seen rental increases like this in any jurisdiction that we’re aware of." CEO of Ires REIT. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until Gov reduces cost of renting/buying homes esp in Dublin, there will be no let up in pay demands. Too simple? #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Nama's game is acquire loans at huge discounts &amp; sell them to cover costs to #VultureFunds who sell at huge tax-free profits. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge mistake by #Nama &amp; #FG to sell residential properties in bulk to #VultureFunds. Should been sold singly to tenants &amp; FTBs.#LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATMH1994 Yes, that is a key issue. Why would a doc or nurse stay in Ireland in these circumstances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is funding to fix health service: 
€20 bn bondholders
+€40 bn forgiven bank debts
+€19 bn AppleTax
+€20 bn VultureFund profits
#vinb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>