<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m Shame.I hve 2 hockey playing daughters who crave any media coverage of their sport.Makes a big diff when they see/hear the players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m Girls don't see girls playing sport on tv or in the media. Societal problem as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death of a Superhero. The troubles of teenage life https://t.co/RM1zg5rrkK #lceng #edchatie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LCarley1 You're welcome. Hope it helps. Great film to teach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #RearWindow piece from last weeks #WrittenWord One scene through the twin lenses of Theme+LiteraryGenre https://t.co/1zyIcFfFU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @HobanPat @Sergiofordy Had to be done.... https://t.co/3C1ZQ28xSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My twitter feed is depressing 
How long has he been in power? How much hate has he already fomented? How many families hurt? No laughing now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are are @EndaKennyTD ? Time to stand up and be counted. There are few times in history to be heroic unfortuna… https://t.co/PcvlvmK1vm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher secrets revealed. https://t.co/GCbBr3lw3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HobanPat @levdavidovic @Sergiofordy Beteeen scenes Fonda had his seat back, hopped from one foot to the other, Ford saw it and used it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @Sergiofordy That was one of the joys of the series, how they used themes and images from the great Westerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @ClonlineRadio You'll love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ikiru is just one of the films from the 1950s that I recommend on tonights #TheVideoTrolley at 6 on @ClonlineRadio https://t.co/lrc2I79Jap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruanemedu To place schools in a real league: look at various reports, interviewing Ss asking them their ambitions etc it'd be impossible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruanemedu Easier to go off 3rd level entry, any other 'league' becomes immediately impossible when you take account of all the variables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruanemedu @Twitter Ultimately they are aren't insulting schools but debasing students, parents and professions outside of University ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revolucienary At the moment.  Look, he'll go but he should be made aware of the consequences of his actions. #NoShamrocks4Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Indo is running a headline about the top school in Ireland based on entry into 3rd level. What a narrow and misguided view of education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theapplefarmer @UpliftIRL I presumed he was all bluster but no, he's just dangerous. #NoShamrocks4Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I presume that there is already a campaign to stop #EndaKenny visiting #Trump on St Patrick's day, if not let's start one #NoShamrocks4Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheball You were talking about women's pay in tennis and the related sexism behind the issue. How often do you have female contributers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived and devoured. Great book for those interested in #film ed at primay/second level. #engchat #filmschool https://t.co/3tO8XiPeU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanEvesson @levdavidovic showed 6th yrs that clip a few wks ago (doing All My Sons)+we were trying 2 work out Marty+DeNero's expressions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research before you vote. How will your vote affect LPT's pay, NQT's CIDs, permanent teacher's jobs without redeployment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wiliamwallbook @PittsburghPG Congratulations. Well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanEvesson @ClonlineRadio @YouTube Thanks Eoghan. Very interesting clip. Stand and clap. Sit and clap. Sit without clapping...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissAmor2015 There's always tomorrow's! They might be able to send them anyway?!? No idea really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great spread from @CiaranByrne for my pieces in today's @Independent_ie #WrittenWord supplement #edchatie https://t.co/EpkbrS99u7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the answer is. right in front of you https://t.co/yavjz7vAFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noelahogan @levdavidovic @checian No critical thinking there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @checian Why didn't he use your name?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bcs_historydept Brilliant! Especially the choice of animation. Great series. Hmmmm...I think the new JC is an appropriate place to teach it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EqualPayforNQTs 
We won't win it on our own but....
Check your logic before you tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EqualPayforNQTs @levdavidovic I'll tell them how you feel, i'm sure it'll be a comfort.
By the way, who is this 'we'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EqualPayforNQTs @levdavidovic 
Your replies are ridiculous and are based on sensationalism not debate. I gave my reason but you ignored it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EqualPayforNQTs @levdavidovic I don't think pay equality is achievable on our own. That is why I'm voting yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be voting yes. Time to grow up. https://t.co/RfnusAdr3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leenbre  Let the man in and destroy him so others won't be able to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leenbre But you can use it as examples of poor language use! That's what I'm doing Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed Donald Trump's inauguration speech here it is in full:  https://t.co/73hydUUl2L #DonaldTrump #Inauguration #madmax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine living in a country where people feel the need to make these kinds of assurances. https://t.co/xo3WGXb3ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyDuncan @marygtroche @GalwayMr @levdavidovic @Sharon_Cronin_ @wordsbydan @BuzzFeed Brilliant. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarfern I think there was some scandalous revelations when he was in the list. Hasn't appeared since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m Next week have an item on whether or not you should talk about whether or not you should talk about Donald Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfitzger12 @ClonlineRadio Thanks. On every second week. A softer Irish accent for you to have on in the background.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfitzger12 @ClonlineRadio Hope it doesn't put you back to sleep....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfitzger12 @ClonlineRadio Wow! I've broken America!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on at 5 folks! Set those alarms! #film #huac #filmhistory https://t.co/IDaT4woQx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @Marc362 @A_Fightback @bindibear3 Still a positive but knowing overall numbers wld be helpful as wld asking why pp did leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marc362 @A_Fightback @bindibear3 It is true that ASTI lost members, they just got more than they lost. Still need to ask why pple left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marc362 @astiunion Same in my school. Maybe we're mere aberrations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@de_Bruner Love Bukowski. Use him often in class,  but not his novels...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best ever! @HamillHimself https://t.co/RiK8LA9Hfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colebrax @ScoredtoDeath And mine too. This is one of my prized possessions https://t.co/H26ysbi2Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A history teacher's book of the year list. #lchist #edchatie https://t.co/6TAssT4DCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the Buster Keaton short film boxset for Christmas. Excellent collection with an informative commentary by Josep… https://t.co/fSfCE2wKrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was a good day, watched #Rams and #HuntfortheWilderpeople Both good but in very different ways!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m Great interview. Perfectly destroyed him with carefully structured questioning. Did he even know how silly he came across?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trollhunters a huge hit here! But the joy is laced with pathos when listening to Anton Yelchin's perfect vocal performance @RealGDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crow's Egg is now available on @SkyCinemaUK Highly recommended #CrowsEgg  https://t.co/TIwmo5LgEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@de_Bruner As soon as bleak January is over it'll be purchased. Looking forward to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing new, just a commercial twist on Scorcese rewatching The Searchers when making Taxi Driver, or Welles watchi… https://t.co/TWX7a46kxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movies of 2017 or 2007? https://t.co/lkWcu3gWih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is his problem, he sees films as a series of comic book panels. Should plan 'em and hand them to a film direct… https://t.co/CRIj1zVA6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@de_Bruner Understanding Comics better be good, just added to Amazon basket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissAmor2015 @irishtimesvideo Thanks!  La La Land is being not-so-patiently waited for in this house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic Thanks Fintan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't #Batman wear a gumshield?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@de_Bruner @JamesTheo 64, but a good few were Graphic Novels, you know, comic books....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barb287 See them as Christmas gifts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People love a 'pathetically wholesome' Christmas. Another great blog from the Cancer Drama Queen. https://t.co/5xFtvUf6D8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deckerharr @2000AD Sounds perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I have to 'do' New Years? Can I not just read this? @2000AD https://t.co/7h3llWfUlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems I read a lot of Graphic Novels this year. https://t.co/qN2p5aWONe via @goodreads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie Stars close to extinction. Only two left on the planet. If only they could get married have children. https://t.co/oGxyBmUDf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, so lists are subjective, fine, and this is designed to be subjective, grand, but where's Some Like It Hot?Not o… https://t.co/bNPz5NUOyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the few quotes I'd have on my classroom wall. Must make one. #edchatie #lceng https://t.co/HSdCEgQ1m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hispanista @levdavidovic @C_Hendrick @tombennett71 @EllenKMetcalf @Karl_Kitching @carlobrien @de_Bruner @GregmFoley Use #IEResearchEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie Fisher was not just an Actor but also one of the great screenwriters/script doctors #RIPCarrie #CarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any student's of mine that still follow me: See, I bloody well told you! https://t.co/WgDlebmlSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Krampus Made in 2015, an evil Santa destroys a modern, white, gun totting, greedy family, he was last seen in Nazi Germany. #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfitzger12 I hope you left it there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@languagesdude I presume you visit the shrine everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking through #Waterford I find this! The rest of the family weren't as impressed, no matter how much I talked ab… https://t.co/YCjfGiYorj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneOSullivan5 @levdavidovic @OnePerfectShot Love the Fifth Element. He has another crazy scifi film coming out soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @JaneOSullivan5 @OnePerfectShot Nah, you need a French film director for that, aliens need that touch of chic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @JaneOSullivan5 @OnePerfectShot 
'It's a good movie, not a great movie.'
Any more and I'll throw my pen across twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @EoghanEvesson You have the voice down. Perfect imitation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanEvesson @levdavidovic Careful lads, my thesis was on scifi films, including 2001. You really don't want me to dig that out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levdavidovic @shanehegarty Thanks Fintan,  this is brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leenbre My students understand bribery, a very important life lesson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorsmurf 3rd years staged a comeback today, up into first place! https://t.co/iMy9UJbvQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ss often ask which class is my fave. Answer is simple, the one that gives me the most chocolate. 5th yrs are winnin… https://t.co/G9N7jsCNmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorSlattery No problem. He's a great kid, made even better by the cake his mother dropped into the staffroom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd year attempting the sample JC Exam simply said 'I prefer being creative' #JCreform  #edchatie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatKennyNT Answer :Virtual Reality #pknt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie I'm looking forward to it but worried that it might answer some of the questions from the original. I love the ambiguity of the 1st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is, the trailer for the sequel we're all worried about   #Bladerunner2049      https://t.co/wc0pAtlaEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starts at 1.15 every day this week. https://t.co/Iene1gt0o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the great noir films, #DoubleIndemnity is another recommendation in today's show on @ClonlineRadio  https://t.co/vBqkEPbCkU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>