<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MountainMole @jurylady5 @dailykos Thank you....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieraGorden @BuzzFeedNews Outrageous! Amd the far right demoises our freedom of leftie speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noisywoman Thank you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teakingw WTF fuck are you on about? From Australia :s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statue Liberty cries - On Behalf of America, An Apology | The Resistance with Keith Olbermann | GQ https://t.co/doM4I2MJxp via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Second Week Is as Chaotic as His First: A Closer Look https://t.co/WNcX55pGyL via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: "Blunder Down Under" - The Young Turks on Trump's ... https://t.co/U0mSP5u7BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Gays blamed for illegal immigrants - christians https://t.co/Ro0X8TUFPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Australian "alliance shock" with the US https://t.co/uGcDJyrrbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about the hair-loss drug Trump takes https://t.co/QkA3d3o0rP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: White-House gets out PM's name wrong - twice https://t.co/B6NicPUv5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's favourite movie right now https://t.co/zg8iPhKI8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ravensreyas Trump inflated that. It's actually only about 1,250]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Warns Usa Of Nuclear War If Trump's Camp Doesn't Back Off! https://t.co/0H7g5zObok via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked Draft of Trump’s Religious Freedom Order Reveals Sweeping Plans to Legalize Discrimination via @thenation https://t.co/rJdybDilNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump accuses Australia of trying to export the next 'Boston bomb... https://t.co/zpLs77NYXE via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Not-A-Muslim-Ban Muslim Ban | Full Frontal with Samantha Bee | TBS https://t.co/OK02GcRbca via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madbum456 @MarkHertling @HawaiiDelilah @lawsciencelogic @CNN Bill Shorten is Labor leader in opposition. We've had this gov 4yrs already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoofed Grindr Accounts Turned One Man’s Life Into a ‘Living Hell’ https://t.co/o9jgRKvgfd via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: 88 mystery deaths to be reviewed as possible gay h... https://t.co/SIza8tPbOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telstra just launched a mobile network 10 times faster than the NBN https://t.co/psDY3LxKG5 via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal Donor Insists He Has No Influence On Party Policy https://t.co/67vyCsZTDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Trump blasts Aussie Prime Minister https://t.co/6uoCj2vpkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink unable to track how many overpayments caused by error https://t.co/zk2AO9l3y9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US healthcare in jeopardy after Trump's Muslim ban https://t.co/kNsgkwKYpE via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Protest Centrelink robodebt - Melbourne https://t.co/PoF5UEZLZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Travel Ban Sparks Global Backlash: A Closer Look https://t.co/UbAacSpLat via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Pastor Forced to Flee Naked After Parishioner Finds Him in Bed With Wife https://t.co/ppz3sZfnVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Taiwan could be 1st Asian nation to get marriage e... https://t.co/o8NQ5pHeUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Silent As Quebec Mosque Terrorist Is White Christian Pro-Trump Fanatic - https://t.co/W8NCcWr2lY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US could resettle zero refugees from Manus and Nauru and still 'honour' deal https://t.co/A7pinuepo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House considers reversing LGBT protections for federal workers https://t.co/y135lwrDyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A refugee for 25 years, he was days away from a move to America https://t.co/6k2P3motnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trial Balloon for a Coup?” by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/Q2c80UU7un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump’s Rush to Enact an Immigration Ban Unleashed Global Chaos https://t.co/WjYLdBDS70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's advisors: condemn his Muslim ban now. This is immoral. https://t.co/zmJj7aNzCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Australian dual citizen denied entry to US https://t.co/VQ7U4aQve0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s refugee ban triggers wide condemnation in Europe https://t.co/IO3yQYycMT via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monologue: WTF Is Going On? | Real Time with Bill Maher (HBO) https://t.co/hmIpBqFuBS via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Spineless Turnbull silent on Trump anti-Muslim ord... https://t.co/6kxNjBn5Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merkel 'explained' convention to Trump in phone call https://t.co/RDm0DReHPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public service bosses missing on Centrelink's robo-debt #notmydebt https://t.co/3xkS3hqkYa via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Muslim Ban Is Cowardly and Dangerous https://t.co/ceMBk33rzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ScottMorrisonMP we support a Google tax. Don't let big business water it down. https://t.co/J5TbYQGCkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/B6EMyJw4nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins’ Top Psychotherapist Releases Terrifying Diagnosis Of President Trump https://t.co/Qd5hxU813h via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: The US Trump disaster.... Jan 29th, 2017 https://t.co/R0XDx6O5wV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo debt: Centrelink staff write protest material in response to debt recovery program https://t.co/bXcIKDdSyr via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: ScoMo spending like 10 Labor drunken sailors - thr... https://t.co/0sQopjbgof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-KGB chief who helped compile Trump dossier is found dead in car https://t.co/v4ZKV2nQ3P via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Uncovers Al-Qaeda Plot To Just Sit Back And Enjoy Collapse Of United States https://t.co/FPAKll5hSM via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan rejects Malcolm Turnbull's push to salvage Trans-Pacific Partnership: report https://t.co/zOZ0s7TLBA via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concerned Americans Unites Over Trump’s Executive Order: #MuslimBan https://t.co/VRJgQNHGZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Immigration Ban Is Illegal https://t.co/78WEgfuHNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These LGBT Refugees May Be Trapped By Donald Trump’s Immigration Plan https://t.co/wy4NA6wT3D via @jlfeder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franco could be deported because Sweden says he couldn’t "prove" he's gay. Here's how you can help:  https://t.co/7lS5Co2bPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Trump's first fucked up week - Angry Aussie video ... https://t.co/q20Z8D46iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@violencehurts @abcnews @HarassNoMore What assholes! Using our sexuality or even our status against us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA live stream - Earth From Space LIVE Feed | Incredible ISS live stre... https://t.co/PppoUBQPjg via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shep Smith: 'The list of falsehoods is growing' https://t.co/0Hh1T6rIe6 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Andrew Wilkie presents a mum with a robodebt story... https://t.co/L96qgNVVJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussies panicking over Centrelink demands to pay up to avoid debt collec... https://t.co/Bp4jgdrbnG via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: The christians like being pissed on by Trump? - au... https://t.co/BXTXfiPGLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: The Doomsday Clock Is Reset: Closest To Midnight Since The 1950s https://t.co/6YnlLZJvwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims about inauguration crowd https://t.co/jna9mlG3Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: LGBT life around the world - TedTalk :) https://t.co/a8VJDWrf7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPP Poll: President Donald Trump's Base Deluded By False Facts | Rachel ... https://t.co/KxX1LkQ7sV via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Trump considering US taxpayers pay for the wall :s... https://t.co/PSgMM1uRYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHON candidate for Joondalup Brian Brightman sacked by Pauline Hanson https://t.co/SNQpKQhOAu via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Anti Trump protest song - Lily Allen (video) https://t.co/cczRDpTAI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Samantha Bee shreds the inauguration - video :) https://t.co/sfJhO22LSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top foreign banks make $9b revenue but no taxable income  https://t.co/B6RZKdjhTX via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In his first major TV interview as president, Trump is endlessly obsessed with his popularity https://t.co/jxeLdMHixo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The State Department's entire senior administrative team just resigned https://t.co/Za1yvHVp2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Elijah Cummings: President Donald Trump Needs To Avoid The Trivial ... https://t.co/op4etwbDct via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drama Downunder: Northern Territory — Behind the Scenes with Casey Conway https://t.co/xHBRwi1vJr via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuff your boss says in a heatwave https://t.co/UFIu0kWXfD via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operation Nemesis: Sea Shepherd Finds Factory Whaling Vessel https://t.co/lSDlVdupxr via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink threatened to cut pensions to elderly couple unless they paid... https://t.co/D3gXw6vSQT via @YouTube #notmydebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia: ‘No pride in genocide’ – 50,000 march in Melbourne for ‘Invas... https://t.co/I74kzRR6OO via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punching nazis - why it's always good https://t.co/RYaQB87Vez via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swamp Dwellers | Full Frontal with Samantha Bee | TBS https://t.co/cDNsDTaegt via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: The best US piss take of Trump I've seen lately (v... https://t.co/FXkhWH5FV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Only 25% of Australia thinks Trump will be good pr... https://t.co/Jm89xVSUj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaker at group supported by Betsy DeVos says Hitler was good at reaching children https://t.co/kVFpg7PgBI via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkiPoss   a belief is not a fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Barnyard goes bananas at Australian Aboriginals - ... https://t.co/Kh4i9Nkjjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linda Burney: Barnaby Joyce's comments on Australia Day show 'complete lack of empathy' https://t.co/jTvzkGK4ab via @DailyLifeAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Owns Stake In Hotly Disputed $3.8 Billion Oil Pipeline, Conflict Of Interest Looms via @forbes https://t.co/SsrjjzoPMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Aides Leak Embarrassing Story About How He Can’t Handle Embarrassment https://t.co/Lx7D9QyvbF via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HivPeter And shut down Pine Gap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump "America 1st"? We'll have to think about Australia being the first. The next time US wants to take us into war with their latest enemy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump official forced to admit White House was wrong about inauguration attendance https://t.co/qzHsviSNAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life with HIV: Viral video -"The Netherlands welcomes Trump in hi... https://t.co/bOTy2gvrrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realmikedoughty "Thank you Trump for being a running of the free world crazy narcissist with nukes" *pfffft* Dead set moron u r - Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Just Issued a Nuclear Warning to Donald Trump and the United States https://t.co/RPTNYtE04O via @antimedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters clash with police at inauguration – video https://t.co/Px6LTAZ08R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four more journalists get felony charges after covering inauguration unrest https://t.co/ql5qmgmEmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably the very funniest photo I've seen in some time https://t.co/rzqxePdhxS https://t.co/NojxeEhUiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dead set your so bloody stupid. From Australia.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>