<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcatwindsor I love pugs!  Thank you for making my day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrLDC I saw that too! I can't believe how much damage can be done in so little time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're officially in 2017 ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FedeBaArcheo We're doing better thank you, just dealing with some big aftershocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcatwindsor We're okay! Central Wellington got the worst of it, luckily we avoided a lot of the damage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeca_dlc yes thank you! Just dealing with the aftershocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncleDynamite Thanks Uncle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe Thanks! A lot of aftershocks are happening, we've been issued a tsunami warning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinlovesyou thank you! Really shaken, will be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinlovesyou get in a doorway or under a table, put your chin to your chest and cover the back of your neck. Avoid all windows. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julee_princess_ No word from Christchurch but it hit the top of the South Island so I think they should be okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyEliStew the top of the South Island]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge 7.5 earthquake just hit NZ. Is everyone okay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recommend reading this letter Aaron Sorkin wrote to his 15 year old daughter after Trump was elected: https://t.co/WHnDn5LJ5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcatwindsor and how does hate win at the end of the day?Its baffling. Just know the good people will rally together &amp;stand against the hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcatwindsor totally- I am heartbroken for them because I know they fought really hard and this is their worst nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this election really hurts because the only reason a bigot was voted president was because millions of people share his views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leithmcp @Aaron_Morgan Leith make sure you send your kids Trump memes like the ones my mum sends me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan @EricVespe Might have to settle for less. I think couch surfing here is better than staying where you are right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe its beautiful and summer. Time for a 4 year visit I think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's one lesson learned it's that we need to stop laughing about Kanye in 2020.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JVen50 I agree Bernie would've been a way better candidate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElvenBallerina I don't judge you! I'm feeling so sad for my friends in the US right now who put up a good fight against this asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JVen50 I love Bernie and wanted him to win. It's just scary where the election is right now, I can't imagine the US in Trumps hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan I can't bring myself to go there yet, I need to hold out hope even though I'm sure you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadjdaly yeah! All of my friends in the US felt the same. No idea there were so many Trump supporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spencerkate thank you for voting against him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wondering how a narcissistic, racist, homophobic, misogynistic lunatic who brags about sexual assault can be this close to winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calm down everyone, there's plenty of room for you in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudaciousKili Please please please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan @pauljeremiah we also have the actual Shire so....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan This is too scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljeremiah Thank you this is great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljeremiah true. I wasn't in Florida too long ago and I spoke to some people who told me how amazing Trump is so idk whats gonna happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan Hello you two! Remember if the results are bad, you can always move to NZ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljeremiah but what about this https://t.co/PWWalCmypY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljeremiah the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan I understand, that whole episode was really hard to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ever going to get over that Walking Dead episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LifeAtBagEnd that's the difference 12 years will make!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wowinthedetails very cute!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrownAds haha I'm in the uk. Is this what you're all like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese whispers with two people doesn't work. It just means you're whispering back and fourth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple sitting next to me is on some serious drugs. The guy injected the girl with something and now they're playing Chinese whispers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarterNixon when they actually had it right in the first sentence. https://t.co/PgBKydYfwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elenaal30847596 Thank you so much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrophyJed you're right, no one wants to take responsibility for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jechevr Aw I love that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrophyJed Something needs to be done about it. There's too many Internet trolls spreading hate without suffering consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fear we're going to become desensitised to the hate we see so often on the Internet. We're forgetting the impact words have on some people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at what people sent Leslie Jones on Twitter makes me lose hope in humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julee_princess_ Yeah I'm nervous to see what the future holds for everyone over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_lindsell I think that would be a good idea right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe I miss him so much. He was the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theoneringnet I would've been keen but unfortunately I'm leaving tonight! Next time though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theoneringnet I am! It's so inspiring!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe yes! Exciting things are happening soon. You should definitely visit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe and I'm still waiting for you to reply...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatCoffeeBrat Yeah I don't think he had bad intentions. It's just a shame my dad is now being called "brutal" for something he never said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnSant87 Maybe he has his facts mixed up. All i know is that defiantly wasn't the audition scrip they used, and my dad has never met him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsIvs that thought has crossed my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apema85 Who knows, maybe he was trying to make a bad joke. All i know is that none of it happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolmarshall exactly! not sure why Jake felt the need to make up that story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pabst1994 Hi! Sadly The Silmarillion will never be adapted into a film because the Tolkien estate owns the rights and will never sell them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isiodith it has a great script and proves you don't need a huge budget to make a good movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordiHimself I'm working on other projects right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leemitage sadly not right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe I was playing with Gizmo the other day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweats_wine exactly ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serial killer documentaries and chill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe Agreed! I loved  Jareth and his goblins. I would replay the Magic Dance over and over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labyrinth was my all time favourite movie as a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the worst news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarFdzL happy new year from the future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2016! Happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe haha I'm very interested to hear what she says about it! I think she's just as confused as everyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe that's what dad said! He's really into it and keeps yelling at the tv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billiejruck Um can you please get up here ASAP? I miss you and we have serial killer shows to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe episode 4! My parents just finished binge watching the whole thing and now they want to re-watch it with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe it's so insane!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronansik nothing is confirmed right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Em_H94 next time come and say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't know real pain until you've stepped on a Lego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EJ_kiyokian 0 chance right now unfortunately!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was fun https://t.co/W9fxpVsSgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mia_Cluer Nothing is confirmed right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweats_wine absolutely terrifying. Sending my love to everyone over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Shia LaBeouf #allmymovies live stream is the most entertaining thing I've seen all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Walking Dead episode was too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the future Marty https://t.co/vMvfkruQv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lijeyeshaveit Where did we plan to go? Somewhere good i hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncleDynamite Started from the bottom now we're here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love love love this new video by @artyfilms and @PhoebeGittins for @lontalius https://t.co/v0h9Z4zRtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/zL0LYiBOor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celebrimbored nope, nothing to do with dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helena99Hc thank you!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know why Fox News is tweeting me? https://t.co/bZjyQf7Y3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow I almost didn't see you there http://t.co/hG8ibGzN0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I highly recommend watching The End of the Tour]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>