<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigfhloinn Absolutely. Can't wait to lose in Letteknnny again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle Pity it was only the league v Laois. One of the best performances in a Donegal jersey I've seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should probably just start the match at 0-07 to 1-04. https://t.co/CJqP8J59gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really nice tribute to him. And a few words from the man himself. https://t.co/TgJq1h9vMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @dcr22B I'm sure a wee piece of silverware today would make your day if not your entire year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere Paul Kimmage is thinking "there's something not right about this". 

#AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setanta provide Dublin games previously unavailable free to air. https://t.co/4rhX6woFkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad bastards hi. https://t.co/DVyhst40ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Mahoney retired from football long ago. Glad to see he's now retired from being a good looking Ryan McMenamin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Mayo have learned how to score goals into the opposition's net again. Bless. X https://t.co/vG6HT5k5xS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year's #DesignatedSurvivor for the #Inauguration https://t.co/xVi1U4HF6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say Richie Boyd Barret is as hard as a rock watching this. 

#generationfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far it's only Dublin that's fucked. The rest of the country is tickety-boo. That's a relief. 

#generationfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that's that then. https://t.co/zROQLBRMnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these facts and figures are well and good but a wee citation wouldn't go amiss. #generationfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Donegal, there's still time. 🤓 https://t.co/4iEPBNr8sK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one of those fair play shootings then. #Limerick https://t.co/rL2HOyyvEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Snood, THE accessory for every diving bastard wanting to protect their face. https://t.co/bVkRFJ6fMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A frank discussion will be needed post-haste, to be frank. https://t.co/Ur5sY0nOBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Liberalolz https://t.co/fC7By9dGtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good thing is that mouth-for-hire pundits will have to retire the lazy "plenty of miles on legs" line. https://t.co/O3EOFxg5ho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopping at a Monaghan petrol station at 07.30 on a Wednesday serves purely to remind me that everyone in Monaghan looks like a murderer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shonda Rhimes 100% wrote 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin would be going for 5-in-a-row were it not for Christy Toye. No doubt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So aggressive was the evolution of Donegal football since 2011 these players are prob upset at retiring with only 1 All Ireland &amp; 3 Ulsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word from @KCsixtyseven is that Christy Toye is to spend his retirement from football fist-passing the ball from Creeslough to Malin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, a friend of mine just rang to see if I was OK. #christytoye

Good man @frank0ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigfhloinn Well sure at least he has his health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigfhloinn It is yes. Niall from Lifford, sat behind you at league final last year with the family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigfhloinn Ultan's mammy!!! Who is he supporting this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah fuck off Kevin*. You could have left this till tomorrow. https://t.co/9TOkLQROAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the combined 349 years of service.

@CdToye @123kav

Ye made a county breath again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Christy Toye,whose injuries forced his role into that of a cameo - but what a series of cameos they were. Armagh, Kildare, Dublin, Kerry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pride of Creeslough. Love of my life. 

Maith thú, Christy Toye. https://t.co/krMphxxEpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my short time as a Donegal fan I can't recall many better individual performances from a player than Christy Toye in Portlaois in 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCsixtyseven @ev_mc As equally good as Cassidy's point. In my biased opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the day job now...

#martinmcguinness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always thought Arlene Foster was a good lad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankCraig13 Thanks for the coverage today Frank. Top notch. Can't imagine you were prepared to livetweet a Donegal match with 39 scores.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a while since we've been called economic. https://t.co/vdgwcxJtX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Snapchat's new Glenda Gilson filter. https://t.co/GyYT9TIIdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcr22B @CiaranMcMonagle Oh my Daithi. I thought about going there myself... Didn't have the balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle Don't know, one of those sports round up articles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has Training Centre been apostrophised? Isn't it real? https://t.co/rkiZZcGJSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCoyNiall @frank0ryan No Niall, it's 100% a tip. And on your head be it now. Frank always says there's easy money to be made in January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frank0ryan decent tip there now. https://t.co/a9IuEd4RNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The popular redtop, @Independent_ie, also reports that Anthony Thompson's future remains unclear. 

Down with this sort of thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point it begs the question... Is Christy taking the fuckin piss? https://t.co/MudnYBp630]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most stylish footballers in the county. May his break serve him well and should he come back he'll be gl… https://t.co/Hu2LcfhZLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're 72 hours into 2017. That's the same number in years this man has lined out for Donegal. Here's to one more. https://t.co/gjOLPqLPtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buseireann is the no33 from Derry running today? Waiting on the 13:00 in Strabane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle @dcr22B *aside from handing Dublin a replay then gifting them said replay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle @dcr22B I can't believe that Mayo have done fuck all* yet again but somehow they're the story as we close 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spare a thought for those who have successfully navigated 2016 but are now in Vicar Street watching Aslan. Poor bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted for him personally. 

But as a Donegal fan, it's a break he needs. https://t.co/6QKj2FraD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. A few game changing cameos this year. 

A lesson in shitty man management. Suits perfectly the football we pla… https://t.co/RykzQg0j22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on... My Son. #soutot https://t.co/kogdG9nuu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Walsh must have taken the soup. 

#offtheball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonlikesjumpers I'd say they all had hitches too for towing taigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ but GAA interviews are turgid. I've had more enjoyable dumps than this muck with Jim Gavin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big year for Hulk Hogan. He gets a big payout from Gawker and was ringside to see his beloved Dubs lift Sam.… https://t.co/tUgBjz62a1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had #Saara won her winner's single was to be called "Article 50". Well done to the white man for winning. Very 2016 of him. #XFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could listen to George Hamilton all night. He could read the Dublin GAA Annual Report and he'd have me captivated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know very little about association football but I'm very confident I'd be a decent addition to the Man City defence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this mean we can start buying our final tickets now and pay in installments? https://t.co/Bi0DFCW6lB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCsixtyseven @offtheball If you're going to be reviewing 2016's Best Sports fiction writing give a nod to the Dublin GAA Annual Report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dublin Annual GAA report reads as if it was written by that lunatic Barry from @Hill16Army 

Whingy bastard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Costello seems like he'd be great craic on a night out. https://t.co/vEiMnKGib3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to win The Shelbourne Overnight and The Saddle Room Dinner @thetaste_ie @theshelbourne #WinTheShelbourneXmasStay #TheTaste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcr22B @CiaranMcMonagle I've nothing but respect for thon shower of cheating bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vogue fucking Williams. #CuttingEdge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took a pink water bottle to spinning tonight.If only Eric Bristow hadn't died such a public death y'day he could tell me his thoughts on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frank0ryan saves me from more work down the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin and Tyrone in MacCumhaill park. You'd get the feeling one or both of those games will end our unbeaten home… https://t.co/aBfn0T6TDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the GAA Master Fixture list for 2017 hurts my eyes. Here is a link to the Football Division 1 fixtures. 

https://t.co/dzXS0owSzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the GAA Masters Fixture list for 2017 hurts my eyes. Here is a link to the Football Division 1 fixtures. 

https://t.co/dzXS0oOtqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's a bigger shower of gypsies than Monaghan it's the All Blacks. #irlvnzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle I'm going to remain calm. Best not to gloat until I here more about Christy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those protestants. Up to no good as usual.  https://t.co/et0VfAO8BN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This note to the Irish Times on the death of Leonard Cohen. Wonderful.

I bought my first 3 albums circa 2001 - his… https://t.co/cH2Ah5cQoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRollingDonut you got me there. I managed to get in early today.... https://t.co/wkXTmWBSMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gave me a good chuckle. 

@EamonMcGee in yesterday's @IrishStarSport 

Never liked that Michael fella. https://t.co/hUZihwSNTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle You seem to know a lot about where these churches are Ciaran. 

Up to no good as usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle Yes. But only to the church on the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaranMcMonagle There's a fine cricket club in Strabane too. Wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCsixtyseven I was literally going to tweet that back to Harbo. But I'll have to settle for retweeting you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland Association Football.
Ireland Rugby. 
Conor McGregor in the MMA. 

I'd still rather Donegal win the McKenna Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are there no late night donuteries? A la Chippers, Chinese's and Kebaberies etc. 

@revolutionbake @TheRollingDonut @DubDoughnutCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO'S YOUR SEXY TAOISEACH? https://t.co/6jYChcvEgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm hoping we all get an email from Morpheus on Jan 1 2017 saying that 2016 was just a test &amp; we all passed...except for America and the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And says I to Donald "grab all the pussy you like but keep your hands off my choc-ice" 

The wee rascal. https://t.co/E3ghrAPpgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My personal highlight is his last act in a Monaghan jersey. A poor pass led to a Christy Toye point. Majestic. https://t.co/BiEmowiukn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stayed up in 2008. 
I stayed up in 2016. 

Hope.
Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please please please let Trump's Irish ancestors be from Monagahan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind Black Mirror. South Park got it bang on. #ElectionDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "I'd like to thank all these old white men and Dr Token Carson who helped me bigly these last few months" #ElectionDay #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside millions of white Americans there lies a scared racist who all think it's OK to grab women by the pussy. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only she could turn back time. #ElectionNight https://t.co/R8UIJx2MwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet you're all feeling pretty smug you've Enda right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I ever have kids who opt for Leaving Cert History I'm going to be "away with work" the week they need help with 2016. What a shithouse.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>