<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[World no longer sees China as a cheap outsourcing destination: Survey https://t.co/rh98jbaoVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms crystallised ginger sometimes helps. I found a dry digestive biscuit straight away in the morning worked well too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinner_b I believe they do under the new Omnibus Bill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop it. https://t.co/CpNxM0LloL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthealeyrn I could teach you but it'd have to charge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthealeyrn Google has the answers you seek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop waiting for someone else to given you the secret signal and listen to your own conscience instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthealeyrn it's a book about Phasmids and Phasmids are awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you become still and listen for your moral compass, you'll figure out what's right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to put it out there that lots more ppl don't need to suffer for you to take action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a question: are ppl waiting around for some unspoken signal for when it's ok to pop up like the badasses in Inglorious Basterds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 50% of child support payments are made in full or on time https://t.co/rIpDEk9XwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so cool https://t.co/uDo4EL4W1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When men start equally shouldering work &amp; cost child-rearing, then I'm willing to discuss your plans to remove gvt support for single women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving women with the option to stick with abusers, or... what exactly? Win the lottery? Get a sugar daddy? Be the exception to the rule?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... you then can't afford childcare to work and you won't be able to get any gvt support for raising the child while being unable to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The same One Nation asshole who wants to cut gvt support to single parents also wants to remove childcare benefits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...then butt out with your opinions on single women's appearances, worth, values and your ridiculous demands for them to partner up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And your kid's school lunch as well... https://t.co/J9ldsvypn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And unless you've cut your lunch for work tomorrow already... https://t.co/81oq9LbRIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe a decent society shouldn't require women with children to nab a partner to survive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird late night snacks in bed with awesome books https://t.co/Gw7tD8kLYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellaFlokarti @RichardDiNatale @guardian @australian the @greens all voted against removal of statutory time limitation on debt collection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens leader Richard Di Natale says debt recovery program is ‘epitome of a system stacked against ordinary people’ https://t.co/sI85kKz0BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink unable to track how many overpayments caused by error https://t.co/bhdvPm5NpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data retention delays release of key telco interception report https://t.co/Yn9nPPmBo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picked up Kiddlette from first day of grade 2, paid bills, went to the library to get readers for Kiddlette, made dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nobby15 where is this from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Association for Computing Machinery Expresses Concern About New Executive Order Suspending Visas https://t.co/wwi7P22xYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*scrabbles for a pool of dialup modems and a bunch of memes* https://t.co/NYaOTiQ1zo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Constitution hasn't ceased to exist. The Trump regime's actions are extra-legal https://t.co/z29xZWLrd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lanesainty many many ppl will be in this category]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd gathering at Melbourne State Library for @AusUnemployment's rally again Centrelink robo-debts (pic via… https://t.co/SiEeFFjo37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Turnbull is a publicly elected leader. He should put his advice on the record. https://t.co/xzYrddwYap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rally today at 12:30pm, Melbourne against Centrelink robo-debts. #NotMyDebt https://t.co/Pho06o0Ff8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks Responds to Trump Immigration Order With Pledge to Hire 10,000 Refugees https://t.co/lTelNvPrzG via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's immigration ban triggers panic at universities
https://t.co/Sn9MZqW7fP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ebswearspink both native, harmless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ebswearspink either that or an antechinus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ebswearspink Spinifex Hopping Mouse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the point at which you send them to school in a hessian sackcloth https://t.co/QvTOdtoBfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siobhanheanue somehow the pep talk I gave earlier on the importance of first impressions didn't get the response I was hoping for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Pls put your school clothes and socks out for the morning.
Me 4hrs later checking to see what clothes Kiddlette… https://t.co/jheMYSi6mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntDanceParty it was all for you and you alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baeoflight naaaaw. we'll get coffees together sometime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjdavoren it's a public school for students with high marks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should probably say this more often, but for the most part, I'm fond of the ppl who follow me on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ebswearspink a feminist will set it all on fire and take what she's owed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jplonie oh, that's *my* lunch. His has no pumpkin seeds and an apple spice muffin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S&amp;P Just Demolished One Big Distinction Between Emerging and Developed Markets https://t.co/9c0iPUFo5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms you're going to be a great parent because you're a great person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms you say this, and yet the three a.m. trip to E.R. with a wheezing toddler...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms @expectproblems ok, but the really freaky part is after pregnancy another person has made us never quite exactly the same again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms right up to the point where you have to get an X-ray of BubGerms to search for a missing piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls these are the same ppl who verified Nazis, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls (got locked out from here a while back bc of a 2FA stuff up and used a second phone with account already installed to disable it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls if you can do that perhaps you can (a) disable 2FA (b) change the email and THEN the password]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls nope, need an app which already had it installed so you can change the settings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls do you have an old/second phone with the twitter app installed with that account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academic banned from returning to US after Iran trip following Donald Trump's executive order https://t.co/OBNXt43uVb via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbstractCode no. no it does not. and maybe never again https://t.co/n6p9mILjMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melbourne High is a selective entry school. U.S. is banning an incredibly bright person from attending space camp https://t.co/eVinlSsQdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I let him disassemble the vacuum cleaner as a way to relax. I regret it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiddlette is very excited about starting grade two tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinrileyau sending all the hugs because damn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is precisely why insurers are swivelling to investments in ride-sharing https://t.co/BCV4nejcjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dignity Not Debt: End The Centrelink Robo-Debt Debacle! Rally tomorrow, 12:30pm at State Library https://t.co/kIoT0pzJlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/cn66vuu8K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tqft9999 excellent :) my boss is awesome and so are all her staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyayres that's for the past year https://t.co/TJ5n5CUDbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google searches for "bomb shelters" spiked in October 2016 https://t.co/KvmCs3larq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trial Balloon for a Coup?” by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/At9m0mPNbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread. https://t.co/LWE9nKT0Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worked. Vacuum cleaned. Changed the vacuum filter. Put an apple spice cake in the oven]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because someone is wrong on the Internet https://t.co/Nb8bdhvoGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlgerms CONGRATULATIONS!!! This is the best news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houses prices in Melbourne are so insane ppl are living in taxi boxes and car parking spaces https://t.co/fY8bVQS7my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice that MP Porter has been sent out to counter Abbott's attack on Turnbull? https://t.co/dMeHt2tyO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull wanted to be agile &amp; innovative. Now's his chance: offer Aussie citizenship to all the green card holders… https://t.co/FnE8Dc5UXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia should follow Canada's lead and offer asylum to green card holders trapped outside the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian gvt must ensure that U.S. green card holders in Australia aren't sent to Manus or Nauru or refouled to unsafe places &amp; war zones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Australian government send U.S. green card holders trapped in Australia to Manus or Nauru, or refoule them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan my advice is block him, report it and anyone associated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessFluffy @laureningram @carolduncan it's not him. They're just using his pics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan it's not the rapper. He's just a straight up anon troll &amp; he's using the rapper's pics for his multiple accounts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan same guy. Note the facial marking over the upper right eye brow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan could you send me the handles of the other accounts ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan so, either he's that loser. Or he's some guy pretending to be that loser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan and the bail sheet also mentions Fort Lauderdale https://t.co/fvij66k9Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan no I can't say for certain it's the same guy, but in his bio he says he's from Fort Lauderdale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan in this case we can do a reverse image search using his avatar :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram @carolduncan the avatar he's using belongs to XXXTENTACION (Jahseh Onfroy.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner. Harissa tofu with yoghurt to take the edge off the spice, and veg https://t.co/yDXAc53URg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ClaireConnelly don't really know either, but calling might get somewhere. if it doesn't work, let me know and I'll look for more resources]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordyPls really?!!! Please share. Because I am walking around with multiple cordless battery chargers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any U.S. green card holders are stuck in Brisbane, message @morgancroberts. https://t.co/qqmQE9SZGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know someone trapped in Sydney because of the U.S. green card situation? DM me. A friend wants to offer people a place to stay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fem_Kat use Whois to search for domain registration details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krispythehuman thank you :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>