<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahsmacdonald who was trying to take your photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live reviews (&amp; amazing photos c/o @kamaramorozuk) of @unblondelife, @LidoPimienta @New_Swears &amp; more up now https://t.co/LyobHR94Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pansytwistmusic I threw up in my mouth a little bit when she said "this is my frontier"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is called "Pioneer woman" and she's making jerk chicken lolololololol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get the food network at home so any time I can watch it is a treat but all I've seen in the past 3 days is white women on ranches?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrimKim all runstatetapes releases are 25% off w/ the code "fucktrump" https://t.co/tJUF7oSVWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mandatory coat checks: dumb!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrimKim the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahNEmerson yup that nose looks dry. feel better bruna!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriayoung @samsthrlnd @johnsemley3000 i definitely did not get doubled invoices but you wrote there a lot more than i did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnsemley3000 @samsthrlnd i only heard the part about skimming $$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[best one yet https://t.co/WOSWdYE7oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's one of the favourite things" https://t.co/vP8CHyXJtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@varadmehta15 OK let's do Monday.  I'm headed out of town right now but will be back then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@varadmehta15 hey! I'd be glad to. when were you hoping to do the interview?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scaachi he's just doing his part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Canada is committed to refugees, just not *those* refugees"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the news you can use https://t.co/ROGHgM7IZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBoothGallery cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals being extra spineless during this Emergency Debate, focusing on what they've done and not what they can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahNEmerson you're doing really great work, sarah 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tianafeng yeah but now they're working on the kitchen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the rivoli is set to close
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
for a month
https://t.co/vjXJX17T53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't forget this https://t.co/LAl7Do7Vdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great piece by @amuredda for @nowtoronto about the awkward, alienating experience of accessible seating in cinemas https://t.co/WAD7CgvF4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thread https://t.co/4JmufyqXdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkOkanagan the shooter was white and christian https://t.co/S5vwMqqLDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lbourgon that's fair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lbourgon half the entire Muslim population in Canada is located in Ontario, it's surprising that the first mosque was established in YEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[here's how Al-Rashid Mosque looks now. every mosque built in Canada since is the result of the love and cooperation… https://t.co/bSZ5ZghApl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslims have always been a part of our Canadian identity and Canadian history, and it's important to not lose sight of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[though it was nearly lost, people were able to realize what an important building it is, &amp; its place in Edmontonian and Canadian history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamdon's granddaughter Karen and friends raised the necessary $75,000 to have the mosque moved to its current location in Fort Edmonton Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the mosque would need that communal support again in 1988 when it was nearly demolished for a hospital expansion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it was a community project, designed in the style of an Orthodox church by a Ukrainian-Canadian builder, with funds raised across the city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Fry agreed to provide the land for a mosque if Hamdon could raise the funds. the $5000 sum needed was raised by going door to door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edmonton just named a school after Hamdon (it opened just this fall). this is her story, told by her granddaughter: https://t.co/vyUxEAYqCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it was a Lebanese-Canadian woman, Hilwie Hamdon, who first brought the idea of a mosque to Edmonton's mayor, John Fry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Muslim community in Edmonton was 20 families strong. many were Syrians, having fled from conscription into the Ottoman army.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the first mosque in Canada was built in 1938, in Edmonton of all places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psych_death right! hatred has been masquerading as opinion for far too long now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilymkeeler yes! happy people are deleting the app, but it was a trash company before yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just donated to the ACLU. I was glued to my phone all day… https://t.co/OmhNSXC6XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i finally met the legend @mariasherm yesterday after following each other since the 2012 Popcon in NYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehivesy would read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_parris do you have a license? @car2go is great and usually costs me less than an uber or taxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norm you should be using your platform to help people not profit off of them you hack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i didn't ask you what you've *done* i asked to speak out against the Muslim Ban. tell us what you're going to do. https://t.co/cloDdDAszi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you need your spirits lifted for a bit, may i suggest some soca https://t.co/p0HZhazxmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a horrible decision, please don't be silent. We need your voices. @JustinTrudeau @TOAdamVaughan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's also the Parliamentary Secretary to @JustinTrudeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to hear my MP @TOAdamVaughan speak out against the shocking and disgraceful Muslim Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@futuristicall but that's still money earned from taxes is it not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all of their responses were v. generous + thoughtful but i esp. liked @K_ALICEGREER calling out the lopsided way mu… https://t.co/qTSL5e7VaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had the pleasure of interviewing @PRIESTS_TWEET about their excellent debut record, which is out today https://t.co/mZ73gnW7cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is it me or does Amy Goodman sound more *alarmed* while reading the news than usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristelJax ah! those eyes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristelJax not sure I'm that invested in getting this point across]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for the record I think it's ok to punch Zizek https://t.co/BycHVKTJ6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[about to start an AltParliamentHill twitter! everyone follow me, I'm the real deal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jenniferhollett it's meaningless until they're verified https://t.co/ARH6o3CKsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briandstdenis North American Pond Scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what the hell? if not us, where is the money going to come from then? https://t.co/4sixIa1nd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love when the dancers take the Nestea plunge https://t.co/ou0Ju38847]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i guess no one at @thefader liked "Pep Rally" https://t.co/6XzJpWfjxY https://t.co/MrgEkC0HRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new Missy is here to save the humans https://t.co/WfeZlfcmcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what a shitheel https://t.co/dcY7iaMinr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brofromanother ah! i'm a bad Wain/Sho fan and keep forgetting to watch this, going to have to remedy that soon. thanks for the reminder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariasherm stop by Faith/Void if you're looking for punk rcds! https://t.co/CYeIABGMmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariasherm see you at @katekillet's birth celebration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your nose is the punctuation in the sentence that is your face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza i wasn't a huge fan but then i went to new orleans and it was in everything delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelseyChapstick wow, yes, two tracks in so far and this is pretty great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's really sinking in that this man is a child https://t.co/Lozdff0l9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the best news https://t.co/27vLwXKJcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnsemley3000 I never knew he was funny until I saw him on Letterman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just seeing this now.... so your body shaking wildly from being tased is considered to be "resisting arrest" now? https://t.co/LnbPk2W3pP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curlybecs it's a good spot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[though maybe it's no coincidence he left Marilyn Manson right before things got bad, and also plays on the better A Perfect Circle record...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the new Emptiness record manages to be good even though it's produced by Twiggy Ramirez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobalAgencyTV shouldn't it be "our first lady is waiting *for* you at Washington"??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mega Carpenters vibes from the title track off the new You'll Never Get To Heaven album, Images https://t.co/aW6jRCniHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[an unexpected but brilliant collaboration https://t.co/75Cus4sV7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met this lady 10 years ago and we've been embarrassing ourselves at formal events ever since. https://t.co/6EaXsBvZsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnsemley3000 @sarahkendzior calls him a "kleptocrat," which accounts for that discrepancy you're noticing btwn his politics and fascism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this was the sketch of the night if not the whole season. more Melissa Villaseñor please. https://t.co/4p6twFUCDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently you're only a woman if you've got the parts to match https://t.co/dY8jSNBwAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not going to tweet much today, but my thoughts are with all of my friends who live in the states]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i knew there was a reason i preferred my eggs scrambled 😈 https://t.co/NRo0rwrejw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliacomedy not even inauguration day and america is already showing signs that it's falling apart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jzcamp finally saw Firewalker at NDY this year and i was so glad i did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@austratalks are making the future desirable again. my review of the excellent Future Politics for @exclaimdotca https://t.co/sMUWoS6Vvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you gave them the same benefit of doubt you're giving me you wouldn't be spending your Wed night searching &amp; responding to pro-BLM tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White ppl in my mentions, think long &amp; hard about why you're more willing to listen to me explain BLM/Pride than hear BLM in their own words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Streetsbag I purposefully click them like mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@an_feilding also Sammy Yatim, but that one was higher profile so you might have heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@an_feilding since you're so good at searching for opinions you disagree w/ can I recommend that you use that skill to Google Jermaine Carby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manfeelings90 @38percentsure do yourself a favour and google "project marie" then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manfeelings90 @38percentsure lol what work, this was THIS SUMMER https://t.co/bxJ7YK9DwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manfeelings90 @38percentsure Pride in Toronto literally started as a march against police brutality, a problem that's only getting worse]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>