<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[had the worst chicken nuggets. mcdonalds wtf is going on? undercooked slimey nuggets?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo i was at work. felt like i did a double shift by the end of my real shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today i will do pilates!!! lol #fatty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe cos i was dreaming that my brain was working all night+!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't know why but i am.sooo goddamn tired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont know why but i feel so damn exhausted today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sending the boyfriend out the door and watching him drive away to work feels like im sending my child away on his first day of school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lols i think i should have doubled the pancake batch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hate waking up before my alarm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[passenger shaming makes me laugh so much @PassengerShame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why is there a creepy man standing in the carpark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreetz19 i know i woke 30 mins before my alarm coz it was hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont want to go to work.. i actually wish i had all of february off..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so i have been sleeping all day today and i feel like i can sleep some more till i have work tomorrow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my boyfriend is so handsome today ðŸ˜ his hairrrrrrrrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want to go drive in moviesssssssss ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yayerr no work today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[catchin up on some jknews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[slavery in the kitchen part 1. over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is the worst waking up before an alarm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoDamnTrue oh my god yes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[goddamn it is sooo easy to type when i have short nails!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidsocomedy omgosh i cant wait to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bubzbeauty happy chinese new year bubz!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it feels so weird sleeping in my own bed, what happens when i get use to sleeping on the boyfriends bed for a while..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why the fuck is there so many families buying trollys fool of stuff and less cashiersssssss at woolies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is it strange that i am literally happy when i am not at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mean girls is the most hilarious movie i have ever seen, can watch this over and overr!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need to go back to the gym. #fatty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mad cravings for chocolateeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the most easiest check in so far today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had the best coffeee !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh my gaahh its soo cold right now.. im lovin it!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[okay so... when i get home today after my shift... i am going straight to bed for a nap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh man.. my stomach is feeling bubbly. ðŸ˜£ this cannot be a good sign..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we all have that one friend who forbids you from leaving work early so she is not alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo true story. https://t.co/bbPzNc18lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_TRIX im excited for 11th feb too! it's the start of my annual leave from work!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i loved going to the drive in cinemas last night. I really want to go again!! screw going to the normal cinemas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shimmycocopuffs arrghh i wish i could go back to bed too!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rofl.. i cant wait to get out of here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[argh slept soo early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[argh i think i am about to be sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is it weird that when i get a little bored, i start cleaning a little? #HouseWifeInTraining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[baby has landedd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not even on shift and i know the rules and procedure!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol just watched how staff in veloce handle  unattended bag. u guys suck..lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omfg i wear shorts today and its freaking cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today is the day!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gotta love flight radar. @Alanbngo comes home to me in 15hrs! ðŸ˜ can't wait to see him! #boyffiiee #givememymassage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissGinaDarling  cheers to that! ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes that is proof why its a good idea. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyGraceffa aww i can't wait to watch joey!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bleh.. some of these people do my head in! i am not excited to be here looking at the line up. #WhenYourTeamPicksFavorites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hope to pass today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe i should create a gronk list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when i go through the list of 'friends' on my facebook page.. GRONK...GRONK..GRONK...BIGGEST GRONK.. 
why do i even have these ppl on here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol dumbass gronk that yelled at a newbie on her first day of check in. how dare you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dear god.. please give me the will to get through full flights today! and I am going to take my time on the counters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo because i have to survive another week!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wish it was winter!! fucksake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i feel like i am comin down with the flu...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its 0830 and its 30 degrees already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i am sitting in the shade....and sweating my ass off.. its soooooo bloody hot today!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hate getting mosquito bites on my fingers ðŸ˜£ it hurts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ahh today is the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol what a dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[such a beautiful day today ðŸ˜â˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dear day.. please hurry the hell up and pass already! i want today....actually this week to be over!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i miss my baby ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[looking a destinations to travel to next month made me sleepy.. i think ill just go be a fatty &amp; eat oreos in bed &amp; fall asleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo totes should go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omg niall horan ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to go to greece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things to do today, find a new adventure for my annual leave next month. It sucks that I wont be in Thailand but its for the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo lmao anddd i am always on it! omg like the MSN BEBO DAYYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanbngo too much people stalkin and wanting to know my buisness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need my boyfriend back...come back @Alanbngo  I misssss yoooouuuu!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to get mexican food or not to get mexican food? i bloody cant decide!!! ðŸ˜£ ohh maybe maccas... haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i am getting sick of people lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tomorrow im getting a burrito after my shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rosterr where the fuck are you?@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got some cleaning to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omfg i hate when im about to shower and a cockroach is there to greet you. just wasted a lot of insect spray killing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just realized i havnt caught up with youtube in a little while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pitch perfect makes me laugh sooo much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i am feeling sad because you are leaving me soon ðŸ˜£ i have no idea what i'm going to do whilst you are gone. Going to miss you so much ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why does it have to be so hot for?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if only we can tell passengers to shut the fuck up. why are they sooo demanding the kients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its interesting to know that when u dont say anything bout wat goes on in ur private life, others assume &amp; make shit up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ahhh im so damn happy right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜ so it had to happen officially on christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol that awkward moment.. lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i will remember what you told me yesterday. lol ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where to apply?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[farrkk why do i have to be working today?! it's christmas eve ðŸ˜£ 
i need to have a new job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 more to gooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shopping! #therapy  just kidding.. i have a lot of xmas shopping to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol i need to start my xmas shopping.. last minute stuff!!! i have no idea what to get. shitballs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just drank coffeee... and its 21:06..i am BUZZING.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>