<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmoncur freak of nature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier league darts is back tonightðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robyn_Hutton yaasðŸ‘ŒðŸ» was gonna text u later when I got home, might have had spare ones cause I'm sure my brother got some extra but no needðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robyn_Hutton did you not get oneðŸ˜­? Wish I knew I would have got my brother to get you tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirstmccallx @paulmoncur I'll do enough drinking for the two of us if he doesn't buckleðŸ¤™ðŸ» mon the HibeesðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to my big bro for his 14 hour shift at Easter road last night to make sure we got ticketsðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ» @paulmoncur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my ticketðŸ˜¬ðŸ’š hearts away laaaavvv it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmoncur got them ayeðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atRosco cause it's so pointless, had one in work today that had all the political parties on it does my tits in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atRosco gives me the fear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are these people who write on Â£10/Â£20 notes????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry I've just got it done or I would haveðŸ˜• defo next haircut I would #fundrazor https://t.co/XpS3BYCfAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh haircut for the weekendðŸ’ðŸ¼âœ‚ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are working on #DeadlineDay ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get me up there with a half bottle pronto https://t.co/kAM12p2xjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 can't waitðŸ˜ wee bit of the 2 stepðŸ’ƒðŸ¼ I'll need to give you a phone or a text nearer the time to make the plans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February is the month for seshingðŸ‘€ so many nights outðŸ’ƒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you always more tired after you've had a sleepðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to getting steaming tomorrow after workðŸ¤™ðŸ»ðŸ’ƒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too pub crawl again for my birthday in a couple of weeksðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go 2 in a rowðŸ†ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robyn_Hutton aye kenðŸ˜© I've phoned my auntie she's been to every home game. Gonna try get one with her ticket fingers crossedðŸ¤žðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robyn_Hutton I'm already on the phone to people about getting a ticketðŸ˜‚ works getting telt tomorrow that I'm out with the hibs that dayðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 can't help it when it's hearts pish ehhhhhðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robyn_Hutton see you outside the roseburn at the crack of dawnðŸ¤™ðŸ»ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than getting out your dish at 8am on your way to camp outside the Roseburn. Hearts away laaav itðŸ’šðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BRING ON THE HEEERTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 your a loveable cunt tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your Scottish and not having haggis then your part of the 55% cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking love burns night! Get the haggis ooootðŸ‘€ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does every random person you play against on 8 ball pool look sexually aggressive??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove money lender in CraigLang https://t.co/6uFcrR0ATV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove not copying me with watching still game are youðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that old cunt pal will probably be Hanzo guaranteed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be like jack&amp;victor when I'm that age. steaming with ma old cunt pals  in the galleon at half 11 in the morning bed for 8pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still game in bed is 100% tidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hair of the dug I think laaaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 it was a pain in the arse but got there in the endðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 I am the sameðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ what even happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of me wants to get ready for the pub, half of me wants to jump in the bath with a toaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vikki_01 either need to get a venom or get back in my bedðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[vvvvv tempted to sesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HFCTransferNews @Leighgriff09 Ross Caldwell got the winnerðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed to do something last night that I have never done before. Said I'd go to the pub for a couple and I only had a couple and went homeðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Saturday plz hurry upðŸ™ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks mum, love you too https://t.co/qubPPJNaUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First weekend of staying in of 2017âœ”ï¸ thank you illnessðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GiroudðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ some boyðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran what did I do? Here you remember your up for work soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran I wouldn't let hanzo away with it so you don't either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran right hanzo needs to give you a crash course on comebacks laaaaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran why? I am a delight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran just banter the fuck out of her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confront jedward for not texting her back https://t.co/i4vii2Wby8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need Utd to get a goal to win my other betðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤žðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atRosco me and my brother haven't, embracing the Gaelic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still better commentators than Michael Owen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a bet on @Jasoncummings35 to score 2 or more, some boyðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brothers being a raj and getting a vindaloo with no milk in the houseðŸ˜¬ @paulmoncur #ringsting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait till pay day, spent a bomb over this Christmas/new year periodðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolinebrown_x one hundred and eightttttyyyyyyyðŸŽ¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canni wait for the darts ðŸŽ¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With her magic hat https://t.co/6HFt81lzAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 9-5 on Hogmanay isn't what your wantingðŸ˜´ plz fly in I want to get steaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran calm down hanzo will go mental at you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanzodoran @samicosgrove there he isðŸŒš]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran and if the can handle a venom or a wild turkeyðŸ¦ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Samoa joe is Hanzo's back up if she's still single at 30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove @hanzodoran aye it is the flag of Samoa ya cheeky devil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanzodoran @samicosgrove mate your not even the queen of 7 joppa grove never mind joppa #Kazza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for tomorrow laaaaksðŸŒš #cockeyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See these cunts in greggs who give you a cold sausage roll without a lick of sympathy! How do they sleep at night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank fuck I'm in my bedðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove I'm not mad with it yet but hanzo defo spiked me cause she's a wee rascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove I've had 3 vodka and cokes, and I'm mad way it. Hanzo spiked my drink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove phone just took the cunt out me, but like yourselfðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove likes that siBsy Christmas ment thoðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove aw glad you eventually got back to me. Thought you misunderstood da bantaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove I'm not that aggressive really but, balls in your court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove all the better for speaking to you! For future reference when you want to speak to me it's only the one b in sibsy doll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmoncur @jdwscott10 least I'm attempting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdwscott10 @paulmoncur thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmoncur tell me about it, could easily get oot my dishðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samicosgrove hello you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a start to this match btwðŸ˜³ðŸ‘ŒðŸ» come on GaryðŸŽ¯#WorldDartsChampionship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShannonPickenxx I can tag you in it on Facebook, pure topperðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dodgy soupðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜· stomach is telling me I need to shite out the eye of a needle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to watch time for heroesðŸ’šðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atRosco @jdwscott10 @paulmoncur merry Christmas boysðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right get me to the pub prontoðŸ˜³ choking on a vbl laaaaaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work till 5 then meet the team for a couple for Christmas EveðŸŽ„ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday mateðŸ‘ðŸ» @DarylMills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First weekend in a very long time I'm staying in and no bothered in the slightestðŸ¤” #WorldDartsChampionship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibs are playing terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a signing from the hibees btwðŸ‘ŒðŸ»ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next thing u ken Amy is getting chatted up fi hagrid xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's my dancing partener normally but, she's the midweek seah queen partner alsoðŸ‘¸ðŸ¼@28Amy94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 half of me says be good and rest, other half says you do enough resting when your deedðŸ™„ðŸ’ƒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 nah I'm working Friday and I'm going to the panto tomorrow nightðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@28Amy94 I am off tomorrowðŸ™„ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>