<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having an internal freak out on the bus over these qotsa teasers. SO HAPPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm getting old, my walk to the shop for the week's bits in my hungover state has exhausted me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the actual...? When you see who made the video though.. https://t.co/Dp029rQ1mP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The takeaway I have the mother of all cravings for doesn't open til 5. Gonna be a long two and a half hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenOC92_ ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ and one of them sorta looks like merlin! https://t.co/0cj6pg3AH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone is gonna have to explain to me why people are getting excited over a celeb, no matter how big a fan they may be, being pregnant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ @thebodyshopirl I'd love this! I never win anything ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can hear a couple in a neighbouring house having a full blown argument... aren't thin walls great lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without the tennis to engross myself in to escape what the world is coming to, I've decided to sort out my room. Regretting my decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was 100% worth sacrificing my Sunday morning lie in for ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been saying for a while now that Fed doesn't have another slam in him. I'm DELIGHTED to be proven wrong. â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS AINT THE TIME FOR YOUR FIRST SERVE TO GO WALKABOUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four aces please roger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any of ye are wondering why I love tennis so much turn on Eurosport now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not able for this!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh lord I really want Fed to win. I'm getting nervy and shouty at the telly like I get with Novak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just stunning from Federer. I hope he keeps it up because Rafa won't just lie down and give up #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being on holidays from school and watching every minute of Wimbledon and the US Open - those were the days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just rare that I actually get a chance to watch a whole match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone who may be thinking "since when does Rebecca know anything about tennis" - I've been a fan for years and years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know how the tennis wives cope ðŸ˜‚ #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent hold, the relief!!! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed needs to find his first set form again quickly or I think Nadal could run away with it... #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly the start Federer wants yessssss. Not that I dislike Rafa, not at all, but I really want Fed to win! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I wouldn't give to be at the #AusOpen right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What eyeliner is Venus using? It has some staying power ðŸ˜‚ #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous interesting. I only got into them cause of that album! I think I can see where you're coming from as an older fan alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the weirdest dream where I was at a qotsa gig, and Mikey and Dean started fighting and I told them to calm down and then they apologised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous did you not like once more round the sun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio asking kids what they'd do if they won the lotto. One answer: "I'd go on holidays to Wexford." ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having withdrawals from the White Moose Cafe on Snapchat ðŸ˜“ #bringbackpaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenOC92_ have you listened to similarities yet I need to fangirl over it it's so good prioritise it! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ a whole lot of people have lost any respect I may have had for them, and @RosemaryMacCabe has gained a fan. Whole thing: mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've been in denial about Trump this whole time. Cause seeing these pictures and these quotes... I'm just a bit speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I see it. Dear lord above, do I see it. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to wonder why women swoon over Ryan gosling. Then I went to see la la land tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least Kyrgios is out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 1:10am why is there a bird outside singing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ain't crying, you are ....
ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸ https://t.co/Z3LSJArP8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but the fella queuing since Friday afternoon for u2 tickets going on sale today is cracked. I wouldn't even do that for QOTSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only got round to watching #thelyingdetective now - holeeeeeee shiiiiiit that was good. Like, "swear at the television after" good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been home about 24 hours now and the only communication I've had from home is dad replying "yeeeeah" to my text saying I'd landed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've decided that I'm gonna be one of those crazy people for QOTSA's next tour and go to as many shows as the bank account will allow me to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another thing: I only started properly listening to Nine Inch Nails last month ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How am I only now discovering Ozzy Man Reviews?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must. Concentrate. On. Walking  tour!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting in Copenhagen having an internal freak out about a new QOTSA album this year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it that good hair days fall on days where you're doing feck all? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous actually yes that's true. I abhor them ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's January 8th. It is beyond time to take those stupid reindeer horns and noses off of your cars ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pure sickened I missed the avenged sevenfold gig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know when you need to sneeze but it won't come and there's no light to look at to make you sneeze? So irritating! #ijustwannasneeze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to start the 1st wheel of time book again cause it's been so long since I read it, there'd be no point starting the second ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcd_productions @TheOfficialA7X @Disturbed @3arenadublin pretty please I've the deathbat tattooed on me but couldn't afford a ticket!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billyjojo_ ah Christ ðŸ˜‘ðŸ™„ id bet money on him being a really preachy one too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo a blogger I follow is a vegetarian but she works at MAC. kinda cancelling out the vegetarianism there no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fell asleep on the couch for about two hours earlier and now it's nearly 2am. So much for trying to fix my sleeping pattern!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen an ad for an accountancy exam prep course or something like that. Except it was spelled "acowtancy". ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved the new #sherlock episode!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@El_Cheesio Okies! I'll listen to em on train tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every so often I just look through all of the @NoContextLouis tweets and just skit laughing at all of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@El_Cheesio oh I forgot! I will soon ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to cuddle my two some more right this second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY HAS THIS MADE ME CRY https://t.co/sPYQkvKzv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin 10th January :) exactly!! Be a long time before I have this much time off again ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless you sky scanner and bless you Ryanair! Nice wee trip to Copenhagen to look forward to now before I start the new job :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few things irk me more than people on The Chase who take a minus offer!!! This twat got 5K and has taken a -4K offer??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@El_Cheesio I won't tell you what date I'm baxk to work so ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember reading it in the book and I had to put the book down for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Wedding episode of Game of Thrones still gives me all the feels. ALL OF THEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officially in that phase between Christmas and new year where you're like "what day is it? What's going on?" and your body clock is a mess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraceyOConnell I've become very cynical lately but dear lord that warms my cold dead heart right up â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sean25b can't believe you'd say such a thing. https://t.co/MvIUHjA0Ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Home Alone! https://t.co/KMaLmzOY8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin aw shite mine is in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin what time are you doing your hair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin mine too I haven't had them done in about two months ðŸ˜¨ haircut tomorrow too. So excite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin I'm going to her tomorrow so I'd imagine she's open today yeah :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AileenLavin I'm on way home now we should bring him for a walk!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two posts in a row on my FB timeline about golden retrievers and they're so damn adorable I'm a tiny bit emotional even thinking about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous well you and @SeanDMRooney are prob the only friends I'll have on it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous will do, won't be for another couple of weeks though!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous thank you! Don't think I'll bother with the pro and save the few bob ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous and if I go with PS4 should I get the pro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous PS4 or Xbox one? I'm getting one and leaning towards PS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous it was unreal! Probably the roughest gig I've been to though ðŸ˜‚ I'm still a bit fucked after it tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous nooooo! glad I got them though because I'm starting a new job in new year that I'll need to commute to so will def need themðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday evenings are going to suck now without Planet Earth to watch :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous they're wireless too I'm in music heaven!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got myself a pair of half decent headphones and I don't know how I ever put up with iPhone headphones now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamA0208 Chris Pratt looking at her the whole time like "please stop"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gon' have to get to the barrier so ðŸ˜Ž https://t.co/hfYKQ9a1S8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm genuinely like a child in a sweet shop when I'm in a Tiger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Culinary" is a bit of a stretch but ye get my drift..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Terry's chocolate orange mcflurry is a culinary masterpiece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpusEponymous hahaha ðŸ˜ƒ I'd get over it though I mean it's crash bandicoot!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crash Bandicoot is coming back, that's it, I'm buying a PlayStation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just rewound the telly to listen to a Welsh man talk again â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ best accent ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#glassesproblems when you're lying on the couch in such a way that your breath ends up fogging them up ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cisuMaria thanks bbz appreciate it!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>