<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It pisses me off that I really start getting into bands after I've seen them. Would give anything to see Disturbed again ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieJBullock SIGURDSSON SCORED SOPHIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALFIE FUCKING MAWSON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lloyd_Jacques The irony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetingTommy32 In a heartbeat mate. You have no idea what you're in for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 2 hour lecture on sociolinguistics isn't something that I need at 9am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last 3 months have been so perfect for gigs. I'd cut off my arm to do it all again. Especially with my brother @Connor_B04 â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just dawned on me that the back end of last week was quite possibly the best week I will ever have. I've peaked. Sad times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You look like a proper catfish at the moment Ben'

Cheers Mase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning an entire module in 24 hours isn't the easiest thing I'll ever do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@97JDB_ Honestly, I'd love to be able to tell you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP That guy has a lot of heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP Remember this? ðŸ‘€ https://t.co/QnclcfjzdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've written an entire essay on face theory. Still have absolutely no clue about the subject whatsoever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olliebask I've been telling everyone this for years ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll only be happy with a Batshuayi for Llorente deal if Batshuayi dabs when he scores. Otherwise we need to keep Fernando]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 50th @ffi0nlewis â¤ï¸ https://t.co/NywWBWI3k4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Bring on the 19th ðŸ˜ @ConnorFP https://t.co/xTtSIK7Bdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My skills at taking photos of photos quite clearly need some work but my parents are the cutest https://t.co/15RgoXDQxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only been listening to them because they're supporting Avenged in a few weeks, but In Flames are quickly becoming one of my favourite bands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In need of the biggest Moos sesh ever known to man. Friday night can't come quick enough â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unis fun and all, but nothing will ever be able to beat a night out with my team #MyDargs #Easy3Points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a worse defender than Jordi Amat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People moaning about working Christmas Eve. I'm on my last day of 7 straight 12 hour shifts. Quit your complaining ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strongly feeling the urge to learn every guitar part in Hotel California]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone doesn't have enough battery for 12 hour shifts ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the most interesting life anyone has ever lived https://t.co/xgYeybZG8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 8 years since his last game for Barcelona but I still can't get over how entertaining Ronaldinho was ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY LOVE FOR SLASH KNOWS NO BOUNDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP the Motorpoint is gonna be a bit crammed ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/8bag8uCg21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never encountered more disrespect than witnessing @SophieJBullock dab along to Fat Lip by Sum 41 ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being a second year English Language student and not being able to distinguish between a hypernym and a hyponym ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lloyd_Jacques @FourFourTweet I saw him do that in a match once. The man is a legend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay team, Guns N Roses have announced a U.K. date in June. Someone has to come with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rolling Stones truly are the greatest musicians to ever walk the planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entire band puts everyone else to complete and utter shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's undergone absolutely no change other than the fact that he now looks like a walking testicle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger was born in 1943. It is 2016. The man can still sing as though it's the fucking 60's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So blessed to have seen my two favourite songs played live by my two favourite bands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alter Bridge were incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieJBullock Yeah but it melted in my mouth ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah I reckon you are actually https://t.co/08A4a9CQ90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we just take a moment to appreciate that Leroy Fer has scored more goals this season than Pogba, De Bruyne and and Rooney combined?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP @DONBROCO @ENTERSHIKARI @BLAXUK Yeah just get the train up lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odds on the Swansea match still being last on @BBCMOTD? @GaryLineker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily the most stressful game of football I have ever witnessed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT EVEN IS FOOTBALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if its 5:43am and I'm still awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has killed me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/dfIWYzQNaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swear Rob Damiani's voice is the only thing getting me through life atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine a tumble dryer taking 5 hours to dry your clothes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Joel Dommett dick pic' google searches have just gone through the roof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just brilliant. https://t.co/pzf5VGHTD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffi0nlewis @EllieJerman @BBCBreaking Yeah I think it was actually ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never impress myself more than when I seem to be able to just shit out an essay out of the blue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the bright side though, last time someone as unqualified as Trump won the election, his name was Ronald Reagan and he ended the Cold War]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just amazes me how America is so integral to so much of this planet's affairs, yet so dumb and fucking juvenile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if Lord Sugar ran for Prime Minister, promised to rebuild Hadrian's wall, and everyone absolutely loved it and voted him in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP Try and spot us ðŸ‘€ https://t.co/DNhK3x5UfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman @CostaCoffee @georgiaavanp Nah that's bent af where the real cups @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You don't strike me as the kind of person who listens to heavy metal'  Story of my fucking life ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman About half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman pls donate them to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman That's my coursework sorted https://t.co/Gyv95THDVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DONBROCO @ENTERSHIKARI and @bmthofficial absolutely smashed it tonight. Bravo chaps ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay I'm drinking wine and watching Strictly. Is this what being a middle aged woman feels like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the fuck do people think it's acceptable to speak really fucking loudly on the phone on a train?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine having the bollocks to make a 15  minute song that features a monologue from Neil deGrasse Tyson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Stage is such a fucking bold album. Whatever Avenged seem to do just works every time ðŸ¤˜ðŸ» #A7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love sitting in Costa for an hour listening to Alex and Ellie droning on about fucking coursework ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a better build up to a song than Enter Sandman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Fire by Black Tide is such a fucking tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fuck am I a second year English student that still can't wrap his fucking head around positive and negative face?! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem ones when you're halfway through typing up a 9 minute transcript and your computer restarts itself ðŸ™ƒðŸ™‚ðŸ™ƒðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial call - The Stage may be my favourite @TheOfficialA7X song ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've still not come to terms with how well Synyster Gates absolutely slays it in the Stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ngl I've had better days than this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP HOENSTLY MATE IM SO HARD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorFP ITS FUCKING MAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine @DONBROCO having the cheek to retweet me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had my ticket for months but I'm still not over the fact that I'm seeing @bmthofficial @DONBROCO and @ENTERSHIKARI all in one night ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fucking love this city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, there is no better night out than Cardiff â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if Glam has actually produced a decent night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alter Bridge have absolutely smashed it with The Last Hero. Roll on 28th of November ðŸ¤˜ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of my brother's cover photo on Facebook https://t.co/aqlg256aZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learned a very valuable life lesson today: Don't do anything to do with my course unless I have @EllieJerman there to hold my hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieJBullock Good for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss my boys ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambsya Why do you do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whose dick do I have to suck in order for Giggs to replace Guidolin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman You best get round ours as soon as you can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieJerman Thanks Eliza, you're back tomorrow right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetingTommy32 Too right I am ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip to all freshers. When you're making food after a night out, use your flat mates plates and cutlery so you don't have to wash it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had such a great night out tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alishadanielss ...That was Ffi ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffi0nlewis There's a fucking pizza bar near our flat Ffi. We're moving up in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffi0nlewis Oi nah that's dinner on Tuesday you snake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to get back to uni just so I can stop working ðŸ˜’]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>