<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eddie_At_Skaro IIRC, JNT 'fessed up at a con in the '80s to suggesting Tom say it cause it would get huge publicity. A very JNT thing to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're using these flashes as practice drills for staff &amp; to get ppl used to constant news flashes when WW3 kicks… https://t.co/ZBHMAlaHeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...now I can only think about how it may be possible to hack the software to give diff answers. "See? He left every… https://t.co/lUgGt01K80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As someone who moved to Australia in '77 &amp; found issues there were about 3 months behind, it really did feel like a… https://t.co/r4LwkCUK3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this where I say "I told you so"?
https://t.co/8u5Go1AWpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hence the brain melting thread I saw the other day claiming 1984 is a right wing attack on the "lefties" cause the… https://t.co/ttW5NHQvoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't keep up. Which edition of the Newspeak dictionary are we on now? I'm still on the 9th but the inner circle mu… https://t.co/VliE41stXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great. Seems the gov has picked which side of history to be on in WW3. At least our trains should run on time... https://t.co/Is4M6DhQLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If true, this rogue Twitter account is the scariest of them all. [for obv reasons they can't prove who they are so… https://t.co/nF3MtTtWgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a certain irony in being a committed atheist and realising my values are more Christian than many committed Christians right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of binary logic is this? Caring for 1 group means hating others? If only there were a good book that expl… https://t.co/zRUHb8PAKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, this is going to be a rough year! https://t.co/qtu5LP2oTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Bannon forget his password to the Google Docs account? https://t.co/1X0SvSwxct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I just gained a smidge of respect for this man. That's twice in just a few months! (First was when he refus… https://t.co/ZYC8AoGywj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franksting Oh yeah... he got well and truly owned for that. I think I just loved every scene Toby was in, which usually also involved Sam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why it's not a violation of free speech to want to censor nazis (morally or legally). Their rhetoric means… https://t.co/ze7qqeCHHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franksting Yeah, I'm hearing that. But it's Sam! I prefer the fiction to the reality in this case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you hit Don't Play on a news site's irritating autoplay video and ten seconds later when you've scrolled past it plays anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franksting Enjoyed the burn but hated finding out Sam Seaborn is a dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will leaders like May &amp; Turnbull quit their Chamberlain-like appeasement? What are they waiting for? Trump to invade Poland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does that even mean? https://t.co/MiJpUWqSKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemme guess, is it also Bannon? https://t.co/1gv5LChH4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There will be no loyalty, except loyalty towards the Party. There will be no love, except the love of Big Brother." https://t.co/DzZDnVRJSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Caring about people because they are people shouldn't be political". Slogan. T-shirts. Go! https://t.co/tUWkghrtwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what happens when certain pollies then argue for us to do the same as Trump? This gov really knows how to paint… https://t.co/Iicbwsb2xj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["World is catching up to Australia... " in a race to the bottom it would seem. https://t.co/oGuKnA2Qon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lazenby wasn't that bad. Didn't kill the franchise. It's more like casting Kenneth Williams as a Bond allied w/ Blo… https://t.co/B5q9rP15B4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 @MarkDiStef That's why I can't believe it's that simple. If it was, why didn't the original press release mention it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least we can recognise the warnings from history in relation to political rhetoric like this. Gives us more time… https://t.co/qJE6JdaGyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he's going for a "better by comparison" kinda deal then. "Hey, at least we're not those poor fuckers! We should… https://t.co/4dxOv6MeAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant cover https://t.co/IxPFkKGsXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on some of the stories I'm seeing of transit visas being revoked, it already is affecting Britons.... so, you… https://t.co/gy7rMGebBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, Turnbull really let him have it, sticking up for people' rights and... oh, wait... https://t.co/qlEXFVWRfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Trump cares about the Oscars. He'd just say "good, no acceptance speeches attacking like at the Golden Globes" https://t.co/zTxOpdssgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're tying to come up with more appropriate language for "clusterfuck". Turnbull was deluded to think Trump woul… https://t.co/rTkBidGCcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Hatch @lush_digital My brain clearly editing for me cause I had to look twice to see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wavenode @Andr3wSmith @nimbos while set in history, I don't think The Highlander's features any historical figures, only mentions them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PRisUs Doesn't matter. Whatever you call him, in his own mind he will always be Grom the Exterminator!!! (Yes, spelled with 3 exclamations)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Australian Woman's Weekly has been a monthly mag for decades &amp; has never felt the need to change the name... https://t.co/BMskXlNHw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: "Are these onions picked by exploited foreign labour"

Auto-Checkout Screen: "Please place the item in the bagg… https://t.co/MhUx8XbihS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealEdDawson Oh yes, a classic. Pretty sure I've also seen him perform it live at least once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is readying to attack voter rights based on nothing more than a misremembered rumour. Trump also has the nucl… https://t.co/CsEGoDKhm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu "tango down"? Well Tango is a bright orange and very fizzy, unhealthy soft drink in UK so it sorta fits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and ANZAC Day is to celebrate the Aussie love of oatmeal biscuits while Boxing Day is to recognize Mundine's ach… https://t.co/QVr1WQsXyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So on Australia Day, a newspaper publishes an editorial arguing that Australia Day should apparently be "Aborigine-… https://t.co/ETQzmnFoOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if 2017 is already bad enough https://t.co/Qx0QcxBIEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garystark hmmm. I suspect that, in a few generations, Trump's role in a modern society will be as a cautionary tale - or a new Godwin's Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital punishishment also works in preventing criminals reoffending. Still primitive, barbaric and with no place i… https://t.co/JpGiaNOQ2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer (on #alternativefacts): "You can watch 2 different stations &amp; get 2 different weather reports."

Meanwhile,… https://t.co/dP3ag2GqxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. As in judo, the best defence often isn't to resist but to use the opponent's own strength &amp; momentum to… https://t.co/MGss46PfSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayacunzo pretty much my response to everything right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best argument for why punching a nazi is morally the right thing to do comes from... Richard Spencer https://t.co/0as5IJisgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a fascinating and convincing analysis. https://t.co/kab5M2g4VL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcarruthers oh I didn't even realize my tv preferences were a factor... Excuse me while I cull that Netflix list...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The coward who takes the center... when the 2 sides are “Genocide” &amp; "Opposing Genocide” is as dangerous as the si… https://t.co/xZViSdVf4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A president who apparently can't type &amp; send an email yet tweets all the time? It's anomalies like this that prove… https://t.co/gkAxFZejOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spencer laments rise of "European-style anti-fascism" in the US - as in they don't just protest but fight back. Gee… https://t.co/tB8st0uYkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The phrase #alternativefacts sounds a lot like politically correct language for "blatant lie" &amp; we know how much Trump hates PC #OhWait...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best and most persuasive thread yet on the dilemma of punching nazis. Absolutely essential reading. https://t.co/ZoET9G3Nb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People don't "want" him to fail. But because they fear he will fail, they're desperate to replace the pilot before… https://t.co/xVBmw6J9jP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Hatch 2/2 but my social has always been all of me, not just the carefully curated professional bits. And this stuff is me right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Hatch this is my dilemma too. Ppl following me for tweets about marketing &amp; writing seeing me tweet more on politics than ever. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well it WAS 100% rhetoric, even if it was more Sophist than Aristotelean. #ProbablyNotHelping https://t.co/3CmgDDgxiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the next 4 years, every time the news comes on I'm gonna put on an ep of The West Wing until I'm convinced Bartlett, not Trump, is Pres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, we know what it has become a symbol of... that's why you go hit! https://t.co/3TcBT6xqnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This so reads like a pitch for a satirical sketch, but... no. "And then he announces Mar-A-Lago will be the Winter… https://t.co/bDbbA83RYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is typical "my dog has four legs, therefore it's a cat" logic. You can prove anything by skipping details, lik… https://t.co/luQJLOn6zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably death of Elvis in '77 although I have the vaguest memory  of John Craven's Newsround reporting Jimmy Carte… https://t.co/5KhPKM3NHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the old "guns don't kill people, people kill people" chestnut. Don't give them guns then! (Such a nonsensical a… https://t.co/F0JkxdPgYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGProctor Then they're not writer IMHO. Every writer uses drafts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGProctor but I agree the lazy and quick first draft is increasingly common and can only be stamped out if everyone is willing to pay more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGProctor plus content agencies that have a long publishing history (eg: pre digital mags) can be more focused on quality than quantity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGProctor Well, there's always reaching out to those whose writing on other blogs/publications you already like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Expressions #692: writing the shopping list &amp; trying to remember whether he's out of milk without having to c… https://t.co/rYBaTScq5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I agree wholeheartedly that this applies to perceptions of POC issues, it's also pretty true of almost everyo… https://t.co/zmTHJtVaa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrivateEyeNews Lord Gnome is probably off on a yacht somewhere, but didn't he leave anyone shackled to desks? No response to emails re: sub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@servantofchaos You calling your audience ugly? Just because we don't look like "excessively happy woman cheering with laptop #629"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably the single TV cancellation that angered/disappointed me the most since Deadwood. https://t.co/JmjBXQxeqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owned. Just brilliant https://t.co/Oxr1Xevzva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...in which I join the Brand Newsroom team to rant about overcomplicated and fancy writing. #ContentMarketing
https://t.co/rcR8eWXqMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghost Busting: Is Your Content Haunted by These Scary Ghostwriter Myths? https://t.co/WClY3TdIsI #contentmarketing https://t.co/ad8kKIywbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lauracarrie I'm working with a client in their office all day. Think they'll notice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmortoncopy As I'm working from a client's office today, I don't think that would go down very well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night of 27 degree heat and a 5am start, I'm not so sure I'm going to be very coherent after lunch today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lauracarrie I.... I don't know were to begin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you passing off a ghostwriter's ideas as your own? https://t.co/WClY3TdIsI #CMWorld #writing https://t.co/Dw6cjmItfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brand_Newsroom Not sure I'd have quite characterised plain/clear language as "vanilla".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...if poking the grumpy bear with a stick known to aggravate him can be called fun... ;-) https://t.co/GGI5VNOlAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason good writers are paid by the word is because we often spend ages selecting the right one! I live in the Thesaurus! #AmWriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TFW you're the only person in a lift and the 'Car is overloaded' warning comes up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If true, then I must be near-immortal! Though I'm gonna need a lot more Mylanta to get through the millennia! https://t.co/NIOygDGxiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 It may be serious overkill but the Ripley Strategy sure seems the safest. https://t.co/MVtZcJfvHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Hatch Watching it tonight, but the glimmers of hope from last week that the series was getting back on track have been dashed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayacunzo you may have a point... though instead of a curiosity gap, it exploits a hope gap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, if true, he should be able to show us expenses for visiting every other town in his electorate too. Or w… https://t.co/Acfkx4V2zT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you see transparent scrutiny as "the opposition", then it means you already know how bad your policies look.  https://t.co/xLHQwq1FqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a court to say this? https://t.co/tA9DIwdFqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusannahBirch That's a contradiction in terms in my book... ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He does know that as Pres, the intelligence services are "his people", right? What, he's got his own spy network no… https://t.co/2qXmMbJjRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rare, exceptional content demands an exceptionally rare kind of writer." https://t.co/b1rX9HZ5xI #CMWorld https://t.co/fJbbBWFw2l]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>