<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Oiche Mhaith Coladh Samh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNews @pascalmeier74 Trumps paranoia has no bounds-Blame game his main pastime .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly only likely solution Dem+ GOP initiative impeachment-it will come to that or God forbid military coup within the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly Hmm I think very measured -softly softly does not register with Trump-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly 49% is not a reason for supporting something that is morally &amp; likely legally wrong-Discrimination should never be upheld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very proud of Irish president speech to diplomatic corp-world leaders take note. https://t.co/otZFTfguUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US - as stated in previous tweets-US in an administrative coup-only solution impeachment-beware military in wings-… https://t.co/319AEk1ZbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US Yes-I hope Constitution is robust enough with broad interpretation to -bringing office of presidency into dispu… https://t.co/hIsfLkgYb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US yes-in his final press con he covertly referred to challenge to democracy &amp; constitution -said he would speak o… https://t.co/Co3sU25ZDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Trump attacks Pope for questioning his  Christianity-Trump is so irascible he will be persona non gratis in eve… https://t.co/IDXAwpzj1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/JttWAeuIEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree-Consultants give 24 hrs cover 365 days-pts will attest to this -crisis is due to lack of funding-2 many chief… https://t.co/4w3g6l65sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree-a crazy &amp; dangerous position-splitting military &amp; intel a prescription for disaster-divide &amp; conquer seems to… https://t.co/UKAHJJFDjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulstpancras we will have to shut down tweeter a/c before going to US -free speech a misnomer in Trumps US= dictatorship-walk like duck...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredwalton216 @space_menagerie agree bar set very low-Hitler was also elected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul if that happens 90% of people will be excluded including myself-Erdogan template. https://t.co/IwVznM9GeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredwalton216 @space_menagerie Fred I hope any doubts you had of Trumps unfit presidency answered I was not OTT re: Trump worse to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Trumps regime destroyed all underpinnings of democracy-Abrogated all US support for Int HR org.UN Gen Conv NATO etc-= Dictatorship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-very interesting the write down Deutsche got on its debt -Trumps total debt to Deutsche  250 billion? https://t.co/iHlp2DQmIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-look at  Erdogan's  Turkey-1st free press than professionals etc-hallmark of a dictatorship-Trumps Orwellian em… https://t.co/WTtVymwbad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU EZ Humpty Dumpy status-only viable solution rnt to Rome Treaty-i.e. EEC rnt power to sov states in fiscal moneta… https://t.co/PTgOTLf9lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vitolaterza09 Cts need to move fast to declare it unconstitutional &amp; illegal-delays dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-WH  HQ for white supremacist- US citizens wake up or anarchy will prevail-impeach now https://t.co/shaQ5O4aS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree-May seems to have Stockholm syndrome after meeting Trump-remember Chamberlains appeasement- https://t.co/UkshrNvKEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 21 new followers from USA, and more last week. See https://t.co/TCPFiCb0VJ https://t.co/qkg62drQlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump does not recognise law -He is the supreme leader-the state is synonymous with Trump ergo his dictates are the… https://t.co/RiBqpdJg97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Wow-Trump moving fast to Orwellian evil empire-US wake up to this tyrant before you are comatose . https://t.co/vlH82FFj8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Maire Very accurate but very scary- https://t.co/tg1SrVkiPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GTCost @qualann @EricRWeinstein mindset of holocaust revisited-scary precursor to war?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stratosathens @nytimes #US citizens get a copy of 1984 Orwell before Trump bans it as terrorist book with fake writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US -Trump creating an Orwellian empire-setting US foreign policy on path to war -arrogance &amp; ignorance of geopolitical environ-limitless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG-1st to war-next trade embargo than nuclear agreement abolished-than WAR over a trivial incident- https://t.co/uivZiyKQfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May &amp; Erdogan laugh at the notion of Trumps Muslim ban-did not condemn it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kevin_Maguire @chezmik methinks birds of a feather flock together-or else she suffers from Stockholm syndrome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes very impressed with  his definition of Intelligence-Seeing the similarities in things that are diff &amp; diff in t… https://t.co/3hQijsjcac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-a loose cannon that can fire at anytime over nothing-he uses a cannon to kill a fly-scary &amp; dangerous to the wo… https://t.co/pOjrC88JaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Trump more right wing than Marine Le Pen-that is some achievement - https://t.co/2od1AeUGwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US- Agree-tip of iceberg in Trumps regime -thousands of innocent people treated like a deadly virus in Trumps Orwe… https://t.co/Q0CLD5OBT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent_ie Kenny'sonly agenda to stay in power -FG to share power w/ S/F death ofF/G-Kenny way past sale by date-be honourable step Dow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[90% of the western world believed no way US would elect an unfit person as president-rationality lost out to to irr… https://t.co/IUdGJKve3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bombshell yes but no real surprise-writing on the wall for some time. https://t.co/5zPiFzdbWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-nothing new there-profit for 1% takes priority over Human Rights for 99%-money makes world go round mantra-Absu… https://t.co/dbudjnb7mM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stratosathens @nytimes Great hope people will see the parallel with the Trump movement-Stop it before it takes root.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-Trump is a loose cannon-very dangerous- https://t.co/sqv7xh1DVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps Wall is analogous to the former Berlin Wall-bridges not walls required. https://t.co/OzWdH3IdIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly @cathyby yes-Trump recently called the Irish stupid re: wall in Doonbeg his covert reference at News Con -blamesEU -Trump rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN-Trump denies knowing Putin?-hope for good relationship .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN-Theresa May congratulates Trump outstanding victory-Trump facial expression the Cat who got the cream-May extended an invite from Queen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary -loophole open to abuse of power-freedom of thought eroded by Trump -Orwellian https://t.co/Dtp3qTxUqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/JttWAeuIEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree-Trumps rule becoming more totalitarian by the day-NATO &amp; now UN being put on notice -only Trumps way to preva… https://t.co/csEowzxMlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN- Bannon Trumps  senior adviser told NYT-Press an opposition party &amp; should keep their mouths shut-Democracy or Dictatorship ?-Scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stiNgo100 you're welcome Dorothy-I like you're tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US Trumps bullying behaviour to Mexico-demonstrates his total ignorance of geopolitics-try that with a superpower - taste of things to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to US State Department entire senior management-hope other departments follow-show support for demo… https://t.co/PP4o0hhblU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on all fronts very very dangerous-GOP &amp; Democrats all US citizens must stop him-faith of world in his hands-s… https://t.co/AnlbpucYNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps speak these are alternative facts-Trumps belief =truth &amp; nothing but the truth-welcome to authoritarianism https://t.co/pr7gbc9l4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US - to stop Trumps path to dictatorship-GOP must wake up &amp; withdraw unconditional support-with democrats must initiate empeachment proceed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astroehlein @MartinaGrey1 yes-the speed of Trumps violation of HR alarming &amp; scary-vigilance required &amp; reported by HR agencies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-very scary slippery slope to conceal truth-1st jurnos EPA &amp; scientists-Orwellian Erdogan template-US Bec Author… https://t.co/SnshZk3voU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-demonstrates his complete ignorance of medical science &amp; lack of human empathy -Absurd-CDC watch out next for c… https://t.co/RaE8ZuLogl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianklaas @washingtonpost yes-1st step in Trumps Orwellian society-denial of truth with alternate facts very scary-Absurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcj66 @thetimes Mans inhumanity to man seems limitless-Absurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US -Trumps flawed democracy slipping rapidly into a totalitarian state-power house of W democracy-Scary https://t.co/JE0QlrNJju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump self praise analogous to N Korean president. https://t.co/BjPPRpF1Kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US Yes-Trump using Orwellian words-alternate facts-Trumpspeak 1st step in totalitarian regime-World according to T… https://t.co/4jIzT21nUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US Trumps Orwellian society rapid advancement -Trump speak  alternative facts propaganda taking root-Trumps belief… https://t.co/w64mTEmIqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulFedayn @MaryTCon Great-what a relief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Trump following in Erdogan steps &amp; adopted his template-#jurno #Fed agencies#next academics teachers etc-wake u… https://t.co/YVWW8kydEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US Trumps presidency indistinguishable from Erdogan Turkey -very scary slippery slope to dictatorship. https://t.co/xSvWTlsXEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US pub funded body EPA under new Trump dictate acc to Trump not the people-next CDC will be stopped issuing health… https://t.co/nMlpO1SY2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBs acting beyond remit-CB function set monetary policy&amp; regulators for commercial banks. https://t.co/CqJ5sBLxar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 people followed me and 10 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/JttWAeuIEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacfarlaneRobin only hope rnt to Rome Treaty i.e. EEC-reinvest all pol soc econ power in sovereign states-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gian_TCatt @guardian for profit-HS is not a luxury service but basic HR  outsourcing starve NHS of funds transfer to profit providers-Absur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsourcing to priv cont who's agenda is profit= reduced service at &gt;cost-health service outsourcing = basic human… https://t.co/0Tv0oT5QNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinGiovannoni yes-big pharma cartel earning SNP must be stoped-pts are held at ransom by big pharma-Absurd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlfletcher15 @economytweets @SheriHerman10 yes-the 99% fodder for the 1%- Davos mantra .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump attacking the very fundamentals of democracy-free press-press accountable to him not vice versa-hallmark of a… https://t.co/aGyr6rMbtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katherinemiller @Nildam85 #Davos -True colour of elites i.e. Cream of society Richest &amp; Thickest -agenda&gt; profits of 1% with fodder of 99%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lars9596 Lars let's hope head of viperous snake cut off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-the speed of his take over -abolishing all democratic procedures &amp; conventions unreal-must be stoped. https://t.co/Tv5DWirKBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple answer yes in a covert way. https://t.co/NyiUOUXb5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes-hallmark of a dictator-do as I say not as I do-Absurd https://t.co/znvnGSm11k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US #kellyanne&amp;sean spicer the public face of Trump says it all-laughable if not so serious. https://t.co/UELX6h343Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei @pdacosta #US  alternative facts to become buzzword of Trumps administration-Trump speak akin to N Korea -leader knows truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-scary most powerful leader in the world-annihilating democracy &amp; freedom of the press-geopolitics in a v dangerous place global hazard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller @GLOBALECOM1 @nycjim @nytimes A trivial announcement one would expect re:N Korean leader-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly @DonaldClarke63 Trump Orwellian in tone with #SeanSpicer as squealer-ducks lined up for a totalitarian state-must be stopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-scary Trumps behaviour looks v like a legislative coup-Press acc to Trump not vide versa-Democracy on a slipper… https://t.co/XfXrCDzxTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Halsrethink @ektrit agree-input garbage output garbage-economic models can be biased with input data-get the and before Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffPostUK #SeanSpicer -role of squealer for Trump-Orwell would very proud of his performance-1984 template]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GTCost @ScrapCrokePark1 @moiracathleen @maddow EU rnt to Rome Treaty-rnt all other policies to sovereign state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 16 new followers from Canada, and more last week. See https://t.co/TCPFiCb0VJ https://t.co/qp9IIO2lml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sallycopper @TIMGOLDFINCH @MiddleEastMnt -maybe it's a warning to her -persona non gratis -not to turn up? -Int to see what will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lonestarmomcom @GLOBALECOM1 @marikatogo @CNN #US -hope woman of US save democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Kellyannes military outfit Fox News presenter in military outfit-is something sinister on horizon?Trumps behaviour that of a take over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#US-Trump moving with such speed dismantling Obamas legacy-hallmark of a legislative coup-US democracy on a slippery slope-impeachment now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/JttWAeuIEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump absolutist policy + isolation policy hitting the ground-Erdogan template-Trump must be impeached quickly https://t.co/gFqsWOjIHR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>