<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM @neilturitz Now I'm even more bummed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmachota What they've done in the salary cap era is amazing. They win with guys who probably couldn't start elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NFLCharean Not for Falcons and Patriots fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm Where's "Major Boobage?"  Where's "The Coon Trilogy?"  Where's "The Mystery of the Urinal Deuce?"  ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM Yep. Small comfort for those guys who emptied their buckets onto the field Sunday and still saw their season end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyIckes @mlombardiNFL I don't know whether to laugh or cry. I'm just speechless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlombardiNFL @BATMANONFILM You see this yet, Jett?  ðŸ˜¯ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜–ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyIckes ðŸ¤”okay now why did I think he was in TB before AZ?  Man you turn 40 and your mind just goes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Great season but a shame to waste such a golden opportunity with home field advantage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHQ_Jordan I'm sure that's what Dan Marino thought in 1984 and Tony Romo thought in 2007.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Birddog26 @SonnyKoufax10 @PaulThrows Attemped piggy back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Birddog26 @SonnyKoufax10 @PaulThrows If what Doug Free did was holding, what the hell do you call that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelmanDC Home field advantage is rare. Can't afford to blow a great chance for the Super Bowl. Might not ever get back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus It's because we all want to know your take on things.  ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 This X1,000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptainFrugal Lately I'm itching to replay Castlevania: Symphony of the Night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptainFrugal I love Halo. Some of the games are masterpieces and others are meh.  But I love the whole franchise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptainFrugal Me either. I've always thought it looked cartoonish. I stuck with Halo and COD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TxTechGooner @SportsSturm @LifeTexas I've got iHeartRadio and could get tunein. I might give it a listen or visit some NYG message boards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @LifeTexas After the wringer Romo was put thru in 2007 I'd love to hear those fans rip OBJ and his Miami crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @LifeTexas Wouldn't you love to listen to New York sports talk radio for next few weeks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 How was that not holding or PI on Sensabaugh on the TD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat @starwars Just made no sense. There was no heroic purpose or honor in it. Just "Whatevs. I'll just die here."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat @starwars I wondered why he just said, "Screw it. I'll just die here."  Made no sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Timothy_Barrett Lol. I can't figure it out. Seahawks are a dirty team but refs were much harder on the Lions last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Timothy_Barrett Fair is fair. Lions got hosed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geofbar Unbelievable that pass interference was not called.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksonclyde27 @makecomicsgreat @Lauren_Southern Suuposed to be @AnnCoulter I'd guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat Marvel:  I don't get it!  Why are sales tanking?  I guess we aren't putting out enough socially conscious books!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 Oh i was just talking about ice cream. I'd rather rewatch the 2007 playoff game against the Giants than any ESPN show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 Asparagus for me, please.  ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doyle_pj @BryanBroaddus @robphillips3 I might sneak in a little HALO late on an occasional Friday night  but work and family makes it hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doyle_pj @BryanBroaddus @robphillips3 My stepson plays. I haven't played Madden in 14 years or so. Too many responsibilities now. ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TjRuLz6298 @BryanBroaddus @robphillips3 ðŸ™„ And some think that could happen for reals. Mostly listeners who call sports talk radio shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus @robphillips3 It's just my theory, Mr. B. Hate to just think they're a bunch of dummies who know nothing about the NFL.ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus @robphillips3 The Madden games give lots of people bad expectations for NFL trades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He thinks MC Hammer's music was too hardcore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He's been parasailing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite His favorite band is The Moody Blues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He tips his servers at restaurants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He orders his steaks rarer than well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He thinks those Tyler Perry Madea movies are pretty good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He's seen every episode of Friends but never watched Living Single.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He thinks Wayne Brady needs to dial it back a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite His drivers license has never been suspended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He unironically rocked a mullet in grade school. (Not a joke. This actually happened. Google it.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He's never been fingerprinted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite If he gets cut, he bleeds milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He had to score at least a 28 on his ACT to get into a decent college.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShaunKingSoWhite He actually knows how to swim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@getongab Awesome!  But I'm still waiting on my invite...  Been like a month...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gil_Brandt @Tony_Dorsett My dad made me go to bed before this play...ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayderMan @thisisalexreyes @Eric_Edholm @JC1053 His statement is accurate But I think he's delusional for thinking he knows what he's doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisalexreyes @Eric_Edholm @JC1053 York's statement is some Jerry Jones circa 1996 level of self delusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisalexreyes @Eric_Edholm @JC1053 Trying is good but I couldn't forgive him allowing Baalke to run off Jim Harbaugh if I were a 49er fan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eric_Edholm @JC1053 That noise you hear is cheering from Los Angeles, Seattle and Arizona and laughing from the rest of the NFC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa @richeisen I just remember it still being daylight when the game ended. Man, we were so close to going to the NFC Title Game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa @richeisen I think we were the early game that day in Green Bay, RJ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 @SInow @thefootballgirl I knew the 49ers were dysfunctional when they fired Harbaugh for the flimsiest of reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa Glad we won't see them in the playoffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa @Tixpunched I think it's pretty good. It was a dream job for a 16 year old Cowboy fan. A magical time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Glad we won't see the Skins in the playoffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa @Tixpunched I worked at a football/baseball cards and comics shop in high school from 92 to 94. Collected a bunch of stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1970Bing @SportsSturm I fear the Redskins more than the Giants this year but don't relish playing either of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa @Tixpunched I still have that issue of Beckett's somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 @drewdavison In other words we can forget about seeing Gregory in the playoffs or in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa Let's hope for a different result with Daks team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Because they're the Browns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus Don't call timeout. Just let it run and get out of town. SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Randall Williams for the Cowboys against the Ragles in 2003.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyIckes @CHQ_Jordan I'm sure now the league will take notice and suspend him for the playoffs and all of 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YumaCactus Graham hit him in the face while swiping at the ball earlier. No call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Except when I'm playing for the fantasy championship last week and he produced nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Atlanta962 This X1,000,000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 Hopefully Jaylon Smith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EltdPodcast I'd follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inoxum1 @CowboysNation1 That game pretty well ruined Pozderac's career I remember we started 6-2 and finished 7-9 after Whites injury in NY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p0is0n0uz @CHQ_Jordan Could be taken that way I suppose. Dang it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHQ_Jordan It's insulting to the NFL that he's won 2 Super Bowls with teams that were not even close to being the best in the league.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer The Melting of the Snowflakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat @DailyMail What a tolerant little fascist asshole to berate a woman and her family over politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat I've been watching from the 1st ep. It's pretty good. It's been a little PC at times but not too terribly annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tarheel_Paul Very telling what Troy thought of Jerry the GM. "But Jerry wasn't having any fun with Jimmy Johnson coaching!!!" Lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@getongab Hello, I've been on the waiting list for a few weeks. Any ETA on getting the invite after applying?  Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, @BryanBroaddus !!  You are the man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @patthinx But Jerry loves him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm This!  This!  This!  X1,000,000,000!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa This!  X1,000,000,000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmachota He might need to start warming up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offense is wasting a great game by this undermanned defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now would be a good time for Dak to start playing well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjochoa Dunbar takes your biggest weapon off the field. I don't care how much Jerry Jones likes him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys can't do a damn thing without holding but apparently the giants o-line never does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation1 Wishbi could favorite that X1,000,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BEBolly71 @jrstuit @RapSheet Save some for me. Got any hot sauce to go with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edwerderespn @JasonRomano I've thought exactly that for 20 years, Mr. Werder. Totally agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabblerousr @JC1053 I think Marinelli would curse...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NFLCharean Dumb players do dumb things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makecomicsgreat @vox_independens Didn't Jackman audition for Bond but lost out to Craig? IIRC producers said Jackman's audition was too fey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dixonverse That's only because your a conservative, Chuck. It wouldn't say that to Dan Slott.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>