<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to be at Danish Intensive Care Symposium in Hindsgavl.  Looking forward to talking about #REACTORtrial #TEAMtrial and other stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CCR17 is the best continuing medical education meeting there is.  Next year it will sell out even faster @CritCareReviews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna @kellumja may be right about 0.9% saline.  Patients in #PLUStrial will receive an average of 10L+ of fluid so we will soon see...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna @precordialthump most of the time it is easy to see the larynx with DL; how is this result surprising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #SMACC talk with @FlaviaSepsis on the top 10 ICU trials of the recent past now up on @I_C_N https://t.co/PxOLAfuY3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennethbaillie @geoghep @iwashyna @icuresearch ...except that there is no truth in clinical trials (just degrees of probability)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An amazing 100 @WellingtonICU patients now enrolled in the #TARGETtrial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[important work from @dfmcauley https://t.co/Ndl8aLUzEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geoghep @iwashyna @icuresearch it's not that physiology isn't important just that making the physiology better sometimes kills the patient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial from @ANZICS_CTG has 875 of 4000 enrolled including 402 in NZ and 99 from @WellingtonICU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All health professionals should read this one and think about what it says https://t.co/5YxAsUhodr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 834 of 4000 but the big news is that we expect to enrol patient 4000 in 2017 @ANZICS_CTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another nice piece making the case for the #PLUStrialhttps://t.co/Jri5uKYza4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 21st Century Cures Act will be a disaster for healthcare throughout the developed world.  Anecdote over evidencehttps://t.co/ttp6RfMUJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hswapnil @JeremyCohen14 not confirmed but I was thinking: The evidence base is fatally flawed.  Pro: Ioannidis; Con: Me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG what was I thinking.  Debating EBM against John Ioannidis is going to be like arguing the existence of God with… https://t.co/zd2cBSK0fO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The background work supporting the #TAMEtrial is one of the most highly cited papers in Resuscitation https://t.co/64SzobHBiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The death of science &amp; the rise of bias and anecdote.  Link from @icuresearch https://t.co/clo6UheQ1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TEAMtrial has been funded by the NHMRC.  Another great @ANZICS_CTG trial will happen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#icssoa2017 I'll be there 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianOwenEM @jlvincen if there is shock then either saline or a balanced crystalloid would be equally acceptable (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianOwenEM @jlvincen unless hypotension/shock, I'll stick with my earlier answer.  Low Na is hard data; clinically dry is not (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianOwenEM @jlvincen Can I choose no fluid plus urgent dialysis? Low Na suggests water overload already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#REACTORtrial protocol manuscript accepted today; same day as we enrolled our 1st patient]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First patient in the world enrolled in the #REACTORtrial @WellingtonICU https://t.co/jwwLAXKM9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agordonICU @royalsocietynz @HRCNewZealand @ANZICS_CTG thanks Tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan thanks peter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karnikicu thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ed_litton thanks Ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdsoni111 thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuicyMango1 thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anzic_rc thanks Carol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevemathieu75 thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaomiHammond thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adintheICU thanks Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch thanks Simon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I received an award from @royalsocietynz @HRCNewZealand https://t.co/5gMS1txQ1wIt was only possible because of the @ANZICS_CTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICUROXtrial all the background information there is on O2 in critical illness from @precordialthump https://t.co/stqwHs22Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, in response to my previous tweet, someone unfollowed me so now I only have 1999 followers.  Phew, now the pressure is off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2000 followers and, yet, I often can't think of anything to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna proper pre-publication peer review is, to quote @KathMaitland , a 'kind of dipstick for shit']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#REACTORtrial start up NZ meeting done.  We are officially on the starting line @ANZICS_CTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch I read it but, I suppose, NZ is another country...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horstie well ahead.  Most sites come on line early 2017 &amp; we now expect to be finished late 2017. #TARGETtrial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 623 out of 4000 enrolled @ANZICS_CTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's not important, remember don't let perfect be the enemy of done.  That way, you have time to make important stuff perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#REACTORtrial start-up meeting in Wellington next week.  Hoping to enrol the first patient very soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great review that tells you all we know about paracetamol in critical illness https://t.co/lM27E7aNAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[front page of Wellington's paper
https://t.co/dk72MY5zLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellomoRinaldo not random so much as pointless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 550 of 4000 enrolled; 75 from @WellingtonICU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple message:If the treatment effect is not biologically plausible, don't believe the result of the trialhttps://t.co/G6xH8pfQOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not surprised that trials with very large treatment effects are usually bollocks https://t.co/G6xH8pfQOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently I said hello to a patient on a ward round &amp; they said "ROODLE ROODLE ROOOOOOOO...DLE!". #lifeimitatesart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ercowboy nice one. We are a very powerful group of witches and wizards though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#dasSMACC if you are interested in research the Dark Arts Workshop is a unique opportunity.  Limited to 30.  https://t.co/XW4NVSlWtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riding a bike from one side of Australia to the other is nuts but @ed_litton is a legend for doing it &amp; I am enjoying his progress tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@medevidenceblog: @DogICUma prediction markets to predict replicability of trials. In Nature https://t.co/fGLuBDZgCe" interesting idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sg_anzics won't be finished by then so no secrets to share...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500th #TARGETtrial patient enrolled @WellingtonICU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curatorius @precordialthump by writing you learn to write &amp; build track record; once you have track record, your imagination is the limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@precordialthump depends which journal you write for ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 491 of 4000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamyourgasman @nitramsg @JAMA_current @WelshICS #ICUROXtrial being done by @ANZICS_CTG 100 of 1000 enrolled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasumback targeting a 'sick' group where it is reasonable to postulate cost of pyrexia outweighs benefit.  Protocol manuscript coming soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will we afford all these new cancer drugs @nejm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 'mab' drugs for cancer that sort of work https://t.co/Tkaqwg8fO5https://t.co/O0z8kr1Ztghttps://t.co/IuaOpVcLCghttps://t.co/L0XTsyx35E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the hypotheses outlined in this paper are true the #REACTORtrial is going to be big news.https://t.co/9hFGJMZ1BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horstie the ICU should be a place where dogma is broken down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horstie @CritCareReviews @JAMA_current expect to publish mid 2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@dbootland: @DogICUma @stemlyns @JAMA_current 'a larger multi-centre trial is needed'.....sigh" #ICUROXtrial already recruiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna @anzic_rc @ANZICS_CTG @BellomoRinaldo we should hear about whether our funding application was successful very soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geoghep 10% of #ICUROXtrial recruitment done (n=1000). Expect last patient in by end of 2017 and results published in 2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XERrgKyyTH
"We stopped early as suggested by a statistical reviewer after an interim analysis not defined a priori." Seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest evidence on O2 in ICU https://t.co/iFc3wbFRvk1.  1 centre; 2.  Early stopping without stopping rulesBetter data coming #ICUROXtrial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedCrisis contact @oliflower he will sort it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 430 of 4000 enrolled including 205 from NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pyrexia in the ICU.  Nice series of articles in @Crit_Care https://t.co/is5pXOxGmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TARGETtrial 400 out of 4000 enrolled in our @ANZICS_CTG trial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Brain Trauma Foundation Guidelines.  Summary=we know (almost) nothing but these are some things we made up https://t.co/TQt7T9XzsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More data supporting the need to conduct the #PLUStrial https://t.co/pSRYvZUYe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed to sneak a reference to #fragilityindex into @JAMA_current https://t.co/HO12JFimmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some comments on timing of RRT study from JAMA and why @akistarrt is a high priority https://t.co/HO12JFimmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have now enrolled 100 patients in the #ADRENALtrial in @WellingtonICU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMerrynz @kaye_rolls @psirides mine was also a joke but I think I could put it off ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaye_rolls @EmmaMerrynz @psirides maybe not if the Dr said started by saying I have made a list of things we need to talk about today, OK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk of unacceptable badness needs to be part of the conversation when deciding whether to do a decompressive crani.
https://t.co/24TbhEFJbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I print this out and take it with me to the meeting? https://t.co/Ztt8Ezk8JK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great commentary on @RESCUEicp trial from @EMNerd_ https://t.co/VptsNmwhfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@precordialthump the statement is true.  It's just not the point...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMinFocus for every 100 treated with surg intent, 22 more survive ( 23% are vegetative, 18% are dependent; 59% are better than this)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Menon_Cambridge do you have data on organ donor rates for the 2 groups.  Seems to me very important to deciding 'best' Rx at societal level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Menon_Cambridge totally agree that whether upper severe disability is a good outcome is complex and likely to depend on the individual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scimedic I agree; people who need a minder to leave the house may still have good quality of life &amp; this group is key to interpretation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JAMyburgh totally agree. The Rescue-ICP paper is beautifully written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...plus Rx with medical intent likely to result in increased organ donor numbers &amp; hence net societal benefit #RESCUEICP (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RESCUEICP in refractory high ICP 2ndry to trauma Rx with medical intent gives same no. of truly independent survivors as decomp (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Menon_Cambridge ...and assuming that you buy into the notion that being unable leave home without a minder is a good outcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rescueicp trial results are out and decompressive craniectomy for refractory ICP sucks https://t.co/czqbnHrudG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilkinsonjonny not for this one, sorry.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>