<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueLifeOfBrian no, Russell Crowe/ Kenneth Branaugh, I am not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to ask the guy at work who looks like Ben Stiller to do Blue Steel and let me put a photo of it on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryanne thank you! I promise we'll do better. ðŸ¤“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But we have!! Two eps up and more coming...eventually! https://t.co/1B7HBbcPiN https://t.co/LKiW7DcWQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When our little community radio station @2XXFM fires back up please tune in #Canberra.  https://t.co/1eRfrpFYNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like it funny, but if you like it clean too, go see this #Canberra https://t.co/ZlWK4SnF9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We made it ourselves with wire, duct tape and a hampster wheel, but the second #thebrightside podcast is up! https://t.co/va6lnL0Vwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryanne Thanks! You were literally the first to know - I cut it today but didn't know if it worked.ðŸ¤“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 @2XXFM that is the best, Lord Wes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for The Bright Side on @2XXFM now! ðŸ˜„ 98.3fm #Canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewBensley Totally. It must have been hard having more than one son because she could never say 'Who's my favourite boy?!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle-aged Mum literally dancing to the song 'It's just a little crush' in Coles Back to School aisle made my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not all doom &amp; gloom, Ramshackle Fiasco (Tom Gibson, Emo Parsonson @hamishhudson and I) are back at Uni Pub! https://t.co/XVVNOF2VsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VarshaBhargavi @codie__bell @whyloiter @WomensMarchCBR Good on you women! I grew up in Hyderabad - great to see this activism for women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 We were there, I promise! #technicaldifficulties at the station. On the bright side, we're getting podcast ready :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for a swim. https://t.co/L464SbIGiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 I recommend you continue to drink while listening to us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lishfejer @666Canberra @Dan_Bourchier Lish really tackled it head on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuskelson @wapple15 @2XXFM yep, understood. Thanks ;:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuskelson @wapple15 @2XXFM Overachiever! Do you ever tune in? We'd welcome your tips on how we can improve our Weds 7-8.30am brekky show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuskelson @wapple15 @2XXFM what was your show called?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 Weblink to come when art is done but 24 Feb Uni Pub https://t.co/JqtZ4laZoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 @marcuskelson Yes, it's a real shame. Hoping for many tech improvements for ol' 2xx in 2017. Also, come see our show in Feb, Wes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 @2XXFM I know you've got our backs, Lord Wes :) Thanks for listening and we love your tweets ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 Now, now, I'll hear nothing bad about Tom and Emo. Literally, have you seen the @2XXFM website?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only time I'd be glad about a JetSkier nearby. https://t.co/mVSvAg7ivx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed visiting #Geelong where even public art supports the footy team. https://t.co/H3bSktFR0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 I fear I miss #TheBrightSide more than it misses me, but bless you Sir Wes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bright Side is on this morning on @2XXFM with new tracks including one from #Canberra's @mondecreen. Streaming broken so tune to 98.3fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeheggie @ABC2 @abciview  what a brilliant, hilarious dissection of Australia that was!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamishhudson @2XXFM you're the best H. Bring a guitar next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 Yeah that's the pits, sorry. @2XXFM is working to fix its technical problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bright Side Podcast isÂ up https://t.co/UrLpyKADFV https://t.co/pfBEDtyByY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wapple15 Thanks Lord Ws! Is it streaming online or do you tune in on fm radio?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Araluen hippy @hamishhudson joins Tom and I on The Bright Side @2XXFM tomorrow 7-8.30am while Emo enjoys his cruise ship honeymoon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryanne @comedyactcbr Hey thanks!  @Rumwillis was on there too but Tom has no Twitter game (that we know of).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you win best comedy release @lukeheggie at the ARIAs! #best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 yeah. And office farewells/ congratulations/ happy birthdays also mean I have to balance out 5 introverts with lunacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 I know this. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester @WgtnCC @radionz @SusieFergusonNZ They were complete professionals. Gave such comfort to this inexperienced Canberran!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elias_Hallaj thanks. Listening to @rnz_news and feel informed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHindle29 thanks mate. I think it's all ok :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just felt my first earthquake - 6.6 magnitude. Really scary. In Wellington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe female Trump voters could have googled internalised misogyny first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@visitcanberra @Wellington_NZ @WgtnPhoenixFC Rightly so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wellington_NZ @visitcanberra @WgtnPhoenixFC Sisters always bicker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think most fundraisers would benefit from rethinking silent auction footy jerseys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 @iamcameronjames when someone is condescending to you and overtalks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canberra's own @Mondecreen bringing the gold to New Zealand.
#WellyCan Concert. https://t.co/XWJ1CPapFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's happy hour. https://t.co/dvHyu7HLKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what all the guests do after they've been on @2XXFM  https://t.co/10v6uzLNCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We left space on the left to photoshop in a comedian more famous than @damiancallinan https://t.co/7utOxkFTZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaTheGlass well jeez, Josh. What even does all that MEAN?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read your post about how successful you are. It made me look like an old man. https://t.co/QGx5hYW1jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe fish are just whistling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WtfRenaissance @EricTrump It even grew EARS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And scowling in different places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivor seems to be about growing a moustache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEndrey but you made between one ferns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussing the big issues like lemon squash in the @666canberra green room, Mr @ChrisEndrey https://t.co/Q2gbNKVzSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEndrey what were you going to be doing? Music or comedy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think the clown bit was a d!ckmove #Canberra ? Join The Bright Side tomorrow on @2XXFM 7-8.30am for funny local radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevKillick @canberracomedy @GregKimball but the payoff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevKillick @canberracomedy @GregKimball at least you gave him a hug goodbye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevKillick destroyed the Bunker for @canberracomedy last night! Thanks @GregKimball for making this room great! https://t.co/KNWPqdulFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddsampsonOz @channelten Was so looking forward to last week's ep but Canberra had a bad storm &amp;  we couldn't get the channel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how worked up arewe about the Council elections #canberra?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgot there was a band called Wet Wet Wet until I stayed at Mum and Dad's. #paytv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum rang a chip company to 'let them know their chips were stuck together' &amp; got a voucher for another bag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 I don't know about that I just wanted to compliment you on the rat emojis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elias_Hallaj @2XXFM Ha! I am listening too - it was great until the armchair commentators started up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 @gregmlarsen Well done! Can't stand that show and now I know why!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what happened to my landfill?!
#kindersurprise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @jvyver on another brilliant radio doco! https://t.co/fqMx0FVXNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have family that wouldn't bother, so you're a hero in my book Lord Wes. https://t.co/EcZkZ3cHD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will chat to fashion warrior Nathan from @threesixtyfm tomorrow in @2XXFM about his favourite 'weapons'. Tune in #Canberra #upcycle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MFiskMenslink Want to chat on the little brekkie show we have on @2XXFM  of a Weds am?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Menslink @MFiskMenslink Sorry about the typos, I'm just reeeeally busy ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the @Menslink ads during Survivor @MFiskMenslink 
Told tge kids all aboutyo &amp; your work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're not watching [insert tv show title] you're missing it!"

- Shit TV show testimonial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamcameronjames you look like AustenTayshus in these.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I empathize too much to enjoy watching the models do Fashion parades in Westfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish crap life experiences were tax deductions for comedians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewBensley also true of open mic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's immature, but I want to abuse my ISP on social media because Internet won't let us download Dirty Dancing &amp; I paid $4 already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FQ_Window @SBS2 You're right. It's compelling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please stop letting contestants sing and dance on #ifyouaretheone @SBS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarzEdraki @lishfejer #bounceyheadvibratto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig_Harvey Such. Relax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig_Harvey I took 4 minutes to get that !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm off to have a spa against my better judgement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewiss50 This photo of your teeth is hilarious Stephen R. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez, if giggling on air's a crime lock me up! https://t.co/zCTyVAdDmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's that?! Wake up on The Bright Side from 7am tomorrow with me, Emo and his bro on 98.3fm @2XXFM #Canberra https://t.co/s35vRbpSRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 not a shitty act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, have they just given all the gymnasts joints and said 'Have at it! We'll sell tickets']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Horse Leaping at the Olympics wondering if ol' Lintea Tequila agreed with its name, let alone all the leaping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becky_Lucas89 You sell yourself short Becky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want an outfit that says: "I can't even!" https://t.co/YoYkaICw6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune in to @2XXFM now for The Brifht Side chatting to @themoodyjuliet about @fearlessgala]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>