<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The sun baker (with apologies to Max Dupain). https://t.co/pub62fZbti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from Powers Lookout, named after the old bushranger who lived nearby and taught young Ned how to bail-up. https://t.co/Q2veO615lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here comes Mike Munro; I strode into shot, shook his surprised hand, and thanked him for all his work for AA. C… https://t.co/porwL0EFlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crew wait around the corner as the drone operator controls the action. https://t.co/b7ufEADlxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The serenity is invaded by a drone following the star through the forest. https://t.co/BSegFf4uiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sacred Groud at Stringbark Creek is not out of bounds to a film crew who have taken over the place. https://t.co/beX9vDECKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The actual site of the Stringbark Creek bail-up. https://t.co/FfdDEj7Apk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bizarrely, a stringybark grows over a plaque to the three murdered police at Stringybark Creek. https://t.co/Hj3eUomfsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the romance about Ned, we must remember he was a cop killer. Bad tactic; fundamentally flawed strategy. https://t.co/osIMQiXRfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As against the re-enactments in the tourist traps on the main drag. https://t.co/XzvL7GfoZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glenrowan has completely out-manoeuvred graffiti by using pebblecrete walls. https://t.co/3ovDUZnHn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lock-up where Ned served a prison sentence when aged 16. https://t.co/ZFaiyx0eMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wounded, Ned sent away the armed supporters who wanted to fight and declare the Republic of North East Victoria. Pi… https://t.co/4ComGAxKtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The site to the side of the pub where Ned was shot down. Sponsored by Hume Pipes. https://t.co/ZHdl1Td5J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crowd gathered to watch the show. https://t.co/fwf26iIZZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The black trackers were placed right out the front of the pub while the white cops stayed well back and to the side… https://t.co/HlLIUg6aYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eye slits hide reflectors which wink at you from peculiar angles. https://t.co/5vGjQ3ODsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some stylised Augmented Reality poles suggest the action...but, really, how about the people who were burnt alive? https://t.co/ennERBmwt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, the site of the siege is a suburban sheep paddock. https://t.co/vk4B2fS2vR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Glenrowan Inn starts to smoulder. Rather anti-climactic ACTUAL PHOTO. https://t.co/P4uhoyXM4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having avoided visiting Kelly Country all my life, it seemed churlish to drive right past. https://t.co/CtgCC0BSjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open fireplaces (yes, plural) in the camp kitchen makes one suspect winters in Wangaratta may be chilly. https://t.co/COfYxvHbY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Short pitch and conduit wickets: no wonder the Indians beat us if this is all we can dish up for our kids. https://t.co/lewNYTwA1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back for the second test: yep, world famous certified milkshakes. https://t.co/8q18WIPFQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detail of Everton Bus Shelter facilities. Note that someone moved Pandy. https://t.co/JFE65P7Im8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everton Bus Shelter without smell today. https://t.co/RD6KML3dJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better than Cooktown Bakery, the previous record holder. https://t.co/8dgEt1ac4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wangaratta accessibility map: parking; toilets; transport; pay phones; ATMs; charge points; hearing loops. Fantasti… https://t.co/xHCQMKnYza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Everton Toilet, so signed in case you think you've slipped into another dimension. https://t.co/66L54hGLVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Everton Bus Shelter. Go there, Gladys. Lounges AND a panda bear, even for economy class passengers. https://t.co/Zv7CZliOYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Everton Hotel, from whence the boys no doubt went to war and no doubt some returned to build the monument. https://t.co/181dRjtGwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you missed the flagship store, there is another on the corner one block away complete with flapping bees in the… https://t.co/Brj7tDMoAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, however, IS a painto. Zoom in for correct spelling on the window. https://t.co/wJxbczTuWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it's not a painto. There were live bees; top that Apple! https://t.co/nZFiCV54Jx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there is the flagship store for Beechworth Honey. Think Apple Store only sweeter. https://t.co/jKi94GmcEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spiritual home of the franchise. Not sure why is does so well; think hundreds and thousands. https://t.co/00rF2p7Qza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's a picnic table setting in Beechworth Park. https://t.co/HX85WZv4dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can still send a telegram for $2 to anywhere in Australia. I remember them fondly but couldn't think what to say https://t.co/bv1P6L6XMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazingly, the Beechworth Post Office building is still a Post Office. https://t.co/EXlcehEL29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More gas lamps converted to low energy bulbs. Sad for historical Beechworth. https://t.co/xjpoQ1vHUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The looooongest gum leaf ever rested momentarily on my bonnet. https://t.co/uloAbY9Xfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everton gave 8 of its sons to the Great War (3 from one family) but only 3 to WWII. Smart. https://t.co/YxxcEzGmHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, it could do with some more upmarket context. But first, move the power lines. https://t.co/MCrVKLvcU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious, this charity tin made me go searching. https://t.co/SlFovJCrYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The same doll used in the Kyabram window display about the evils of alcohol was sulking in a corner of Everton Stor… https://t.co/vLrzDlTRPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, it deserves to be world famous. $5.20 for malted. Don't drive past Everton General Store. https://t.co/PENWQbMeze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the senior staff get to make the milkshakes, and the boss yells out "Better make it good." https://t.co/ChXbbRbBm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, how could you drive past that inducement. https://t.co/PrHzdzUGtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bark home detox watched jealously by a more primitive Xanthorrea. https://t.co/XF0MIjkw9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outlook from Ryan's Lookout in Warby-Ovens NP. In winter, you can see snow on them there hills. https://t.co/8Z0lnsuKA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rod for your own back. https://t.co/udfnw1rRC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No photo from Pangarang Lookout because I turned back here. No sign telling me how far the walk would be and BORING. https://t.co/XKzLfkLGf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since the superphosphate bounty ended, the Nationals have been looking for a new cargo cult; now, hopes are up for… https://t.co/l0akz8leD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here I am, just having devoured a peanut butter roll and a nice plum for dessert all washed down with hot water. https://t.co/dFAzzX2e18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you noticed that passionfruit is sweeter than when you were young? Or am I just more bitter? https://t.co/i64ctADKnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This mid-Murray island is claimed by both NSW and Victoria. Must be good fishing. https://t.co/XXpu40DWym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody else can walk the Murray mud so no bath today. https://t.co/IgSYFedSqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am delighted to report that the Haversack is alive and well. First sighting in decades and still only $9.90. https://t.co/9TpsXK1NCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm seriously fucked up by being captive and on display in the main street. https://t.co/96k3TeuxGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is the sex shop in Echuca; part of a bridal boutique and fancy dress hire!!! OK, back to the toy shop. https://t.co/2bAIMES9OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a toy shop for men. Play, not sex. In Echuca. https://t.co/n7XQcByHob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What has NH3 ever done to them? https://t.co/SF3tz9Hz0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Euphemisms around the other side. https://t.co/3zKyFghn6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A huge philosophical issue in the 1970s was Free Will and Determinism. There was never any debate in the Bloom fami… https://t.co/lJblnbF7ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One passage to adulthood is to work out the difference between needs and wants. Retail seeks to blur the distinctio… https://t.co/j6DFuDkWgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The speed of 19th C architectural styles. 1883: Gaudi's Casa Vincens in Barcelona. 1901: Uniting Church in Echuca. https://t.co/yYuxrnpwNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plain speaking is not a new phenomena. https://t.co/J6xvNVlPyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Shackell bought the building in 1865 and added a new section at the back featuring the Star of David. So there. https://t.co/nluYYkVDR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One must credit the Christmas trees for their originality. But it's February. https://t.co/71IUykaJvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A timber jinker sports cross-section-of-a-tree wheels: that's like asking someone to dig their own grave. https://t.co/N4lRVDu3Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Echuca has managed to retain a street in the historical precinct with a real dirt road. https://t.co/ntQ4cdGZJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but how did she get there without getting wet. https://t.co/ZFe6OfvcmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing so pathetic as a maggie with a beak full of nesting but undecided what to do with it. https://t.co/irGmDxVRRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First recorded sighting of the Indigenous letter Nj on a building. (Renovated 1988). https://t.co/EeM5D8loOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely it is against the Trade Practices Act for the Holden Museum to fly the Aussie Flag these days. https://t.co/nydcHuiS5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The local artists have even taken to dot painting the chooks. https://t.co/qKPcUFqS5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spa has washed down this far with the recent floods. https://t.co/OLkG4JEfJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CWA chose a brutalist design rather than some effete welcoming style of front door that would let just anyone i… https://t.co/LtZexPvKGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The body pick-up van is hidden behind a hedge but no one is fooled. https://t.co/aQZn9KbgKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A failure to kern made me think on first glance that the funeral parlour was named 'To Bin' (...or not to bin?) https://t.co/TA0LQTRYED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming Soon: What the Painter Saw! 3D from Big Blonds in Sweden Productions. https://t.co/0OX2wPMkMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was also a time when temperance was fashionable. We could do with a repeat of that in this alcohol-soaked age. https://t.co/nn47wQiv7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was an earlier time when coffee was popular, but the men, despite looking like hipsters, did not barist. https://t.co/rDk1nAjIKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign for the slower tourists who may not catch on so quickly, or just can't find the correct words for Facebook. https://t.co/WfsKmQegVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Port of Echuca is guarded by the Thong Gates. https://t.co/5KbOuge97R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just for you vexillologists, here is the river boats' ensign. https://t.co/Y2vpPzpDNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one boasts 'Genuine Steam': one would never want to be out on the water with ingenuine steam. https://t.co/MIevsRSQsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paddle steamers do a nice trade in tourists these days. https://t.co/YbWTdmv00M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snags come from trees which just can't seem to resist the temptation to fall in, much to the bemusement of cockies. https://t.co/Z8zZwH1pi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Murray is also full of snags. https://t.co/4S2e5eNQA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Murray does repeated hairpin bends; in fact, it's recidivist. https://t.co/6jE1VOfDGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunset on the Murray. https://t.co/WadEgj2YQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leunig's 1990s entry for a new Aussie flag featured a speedboat. When I'm dictator, they will be outlawed as moroni… https://t.co/VoCREUfRGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lopped gum was traduced into service as a lost thong monument but, Phoenix-like, it objects with a new shoot. https://t.co/ddPszXdWFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[River Red Gums proudly flutter the flag over the Murray River for Australia Day. That's NSW on yonder bank. https://t.co/4gr8ziERcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Terrick Terrick is covered in moss and lichen, even on the north side. One suspects winters are bleak. https://t.co/Mtg9T30Wlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrick Terrick NP is really about remnant Cyprus Pines and native grasslands. The rock is just a lure. https://t.co/D8dULBhIDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat silos used to be a status symbol in country towns; a big blue bag of wheat on the ground is not as grand. https://t.co/f137WoIL7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flatness from whence they shoot. https://t.co/F0j2DUKUum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the local boys are good shots and the Trig Station is an irresistible target. https://t.co/BHmBZSEuHt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>