<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Serial Creators Announce New Podcast Series https://t.co/DXkFeLFNYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most govts don’t bother teaching citizenship education properly &amp; polls show the young are losing faith in democracy https://t.co/Z7DoJ2UN6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meredithmartin @jm_mcgrath Check out Trump Draws @TrumpDraws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Tory won’t rule out future work with ‘friend’ Nick Kouvalis  https://t.co/t9liRLTLBO #topoli #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A-list finding it harder to be apolitical https://t.co/OCLFeBgh3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Ivison: Anti-O’Leary faction struggles to mount serious challenge in Tory leadership race https://t.co/Y1AB0pZ6Rj #cdnpoli #cpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nordstrom Drops Ivanka Trump Brand From Its Stores https://t.co/O9ei7j2YJB #GrabYourWallet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwoodgett I would think he's become too much of a circus side-show and a risk. It would be disappointing to see Tory work with him again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Kouvalis, controversial campaign manager for Kellie Leitch, resigns  https://t.co/j2tSBvxoWt #cdnpoli #topoli #cpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Tonight's @TheAgenda episode on The Patient Experience: https://t.co/lezZIQmFXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burn Harry Potter books? Have people lost their minds? #LoveNotHate #LiteracyNotIdiocy #ToleranceNotIntolerance https://t.co/4wG2JGUUL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheAgenda @8 w/ @PatientsCanada's Denyse Lynch @OttawaHospital's Dr. V. Roth @RNAO's Doris Grinspun @judithhjohn &amp; Gary Froude of @nsmlhin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've ever been a #patient in our #healthcare #ONhealth system, &amp; had either a good/bad experience, tonite's @TheAgenda is 4 you. @8/11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser Super Bowl ad pays tribute to brewery’s immigrant roots https://t.co/UWKvYeuO1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. John McCain, again the maverick, challenges President Trump  https://t.co/ym9ptWSMP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingrid Schumacher out at CHUM FM after 40 years https://t.co/49CSG1YQbd #cdnmedia #sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bell Media cites CRTC Super Bowl ad policy as a factor in latest round of layoffs https://t.co/mUZSqKlFXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw @tvo's ad for #TheMissing, starting next Monday at 9pm. OMG...it is an amazing series! Not to be missed! https://t.co/uTM6FxHPML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In light of events in Quebec CIty &amp; Washington, @TheAgenda will instead cover the #stefoymosque attack &amp; the U.S. #MuslimBan tonight. 8/11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that much info provided by police briefing of Quebec CIty mosque shooting other than how suspects were apprehended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frum: Should a patriotic American work for Donald Trump? Assessing the risks of service https://t.co/X4YQ7R8WM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors’ vote to oust Ontario Medical Association leadership fails https://t.co/im8Ia1NboL #onhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks to hire 10,000 refugees over next 5 years https://t.co/W77oKukClv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads Up: @realDonaldTrump will soon slag @OfficialJLD aka Julia Louis-Dreyfus, calling out her lack of talent. She just won a #SAGAward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors set to vote on ousting Ontario Medical Association leaders  https://t.co/wrKytQXUQo #onhealth #onpoli #oma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Blocks Part of Trump’s Immigration Order https://t.co/F1sVAQTu5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump immigration ban ‘a boon' for Canadian tech industry, say executives https://t.co/VX2ajsq89L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish photographer Lennart Nilsson behind spectacular photos of fetus developing in womb dies at 94… https://t.co/srW31AQAMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmanuelle Riva, Star of ‘Amour,’ ‘Hiroshima Mon Amour,’ Dies at 89 https://t.co/XW68jQQf4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt, Oscar-Nominated Star of 'The Elephant Man,' Dies at 77 (Report) https://t.co/aP8iYw34Wv via @thr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmy winner Barbara Hale, who played Perry Mason's secretary, has died at 94 https://t.co/OYB2cqTsql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Councillors blast 'short-sighted' decision to block tolls on Gardiner, DVP https://t.co/6XxYJaz3iF #topoli #onpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Connors, Glass-Jawed Star of ‘Mannix,’ Dies at 91 https://t.co/XH9t8QcF9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doomsday Clock ticks closer to apocalypse and 1 person is to blame https://t.co/mBOOLKMNNH #150SecondstoMidnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WaPo: The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned https://t.co/PYaZqKRuQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On again right now... #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/vMeWLDJ38c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to watch part of this today. I urge you all to take a look. Imp to share mental health stories like this abt pe… https://t.co/HcmRuXpPPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made this. And it was a thrill to meet @clarahughes. A great inspiration to all Canadians #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/iLJM0Khies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hotels, Amid Calls to Divest, Instead Plans U.S. Expansion https://t.co/eNrUJ2Jv8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my fave Mary Tyler Moore scenes from her show: "Laugh for Chuckles." https://t.co/ZbTDfkMaqy #LovedHer #KindaFitting #RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: .@TMZ reports Mary Tyler Moore has died at 80 https://t.co/H0Ia4Ekpbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Meyers Confronts the Trump Era on ‘Late Night’ https://t.co/0xQglDrouW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Butch Trucks, Allman Brothers Band co-founder and drummer, dead at 69 https://t.co/33WgByRxh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of @TheAgenda's coverage of #Depression: https://t.co/ITU6ajBGo2 plus https://t.co/ARhRriJeHm &amp; https://t.co/zYbMEIjJnX #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of @TheAgenda's coverage around #Anxiety: https://t.co/qektmZsQlu plus https://t.co/ZbrSlThzyS &amp; https://t.co/E2kra8h0eB #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheAgenda joins the #BellLetsTalk effort today with an in-depth interview with Canada's greatest Olympian, Clara Hughes. At 8 &amp; 11!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has backed out of the Trans-Pacific Partnership. Now what? Watch @TheAgenda's TPP &amp; Canada's Trade Future: https://t.co/OQOQunzEUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JATetro I will take a look. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreschel: A reality check on #Hamilton’s renaissance https://t.co/RiEi47lb6v  #Ontario]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump signs executive order officially pulling U.S. out of #TPP https://t.co/mW73A6U7Vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rural #Ontario school closings hit communities hard  https://t.co/ler0HJaHGH  #onted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's Trudeau, ministers to discuss Trump plans for NAFTA including a meeting w/ Jared Kushner on Tuesday https://t.co/fUsJaZAdXK  #trade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats off to the women: A look at the knitted pink headpieces that helped make protest history https://t.co/DUDRGgm2kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to #Ontario...Paikin: Some bumps in the road for Wynne and Trudeau’s friendship? https://t.co/HsOokHyLbH #onpoli #cdnpoli #olp #lpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U of T’s student newspaper @TheVarsity appoints a public editor https://t.co/WdB3D4TNTV #cdnmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CNN would rather see the protests and the riot police. Not a parade. Stop apologizing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN  covering the protests in DC...getting very heated, Looks scary right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islamic State blows up famous #Palmyra monuments in fresh assault on Unesco city https://t.co/kRn2c8GoxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth following @davidfrum today. He's on fire. I will retweet some of his stuff... #StayStrong David!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto's restaurant icons spill their secrets https://t.co/UWwo1b9Z9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The End of History? Not a chance....tune in at 8/11. Live on Twitter in minutes. https://t.co/UXJmmzus1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the eve of the Trump inauguration... at 8/11. Live on Twitter in 14 minutes... https://t.co/RXuHGj3A1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Barrett, Fierce Muckraker at The Village Voice, Dies at 71 https://t.co/Crqclyr0YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, we're trending on Twitter! Ask Steve anything. Twitter Q &amp; A on now #TVOTheAgenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a TVjourno, author &amp; Uni Chancellor. If you could, what would you rather be: crooner, baseball player or hockey player? #TVOTheAgenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good one ...Twitter Q &amp; A with Steve right now... https://t.co/W36I58I29x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one flaw Steve Paikin has...WATCH: https://t.co/NPAucA21zp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We dare to bore you to death," says Steve Paikin. Yeah, he said it. Paikin's live Twitter Q &amp; A now on. @spaikin https://t.co/hjsO9x4yTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot air: The truth about Kevin O’Leary’s business history https://t.co/O4bp68v2gD #cdpoli #cpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary enters Conservative race, won’t yet seek Parliament seat https://t.co/TdlQiOGO12 #cdnpoli #cpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govts must take action on Great Lakes farm runoff: report https://t.co/m7WhN1KiyC @TheAgenda/@tvo on #GreatLakes: https://t.co/sIL2BWaFup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto doctor's sex abuse penalty ‘clearly unfit,’ court rules https://t.co/Kbddx9SfER Watch @TheAgenda on this: https://t.co/6cIctPO7XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanJasonWebb Amazing the election results didn't kill him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George H.W. Bush, Barbara Bush both hospitalized  https://t.co/Jab1JDsyx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask away folks! @TheAgenda #onpoli #Ontario https://t.co/wJuncmp2fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NYMag is featuring Pants Week. #Love Those who know me know the Pantless Public is one of my biggest pet peeves! https://t.co/kmyiIHCY2C 🙂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TVO, Twitter to live stream ‘The Agenda with Steve Paikin’ in first Canadian media deal for social network https://t.co/Yqo0jo5vcm #cdnmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I produced this with the amazing Brenda Waudby &amp; writer John Chipman who wrote incredible book abt this dark chapte… https://t.co/3AqFRjZEo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other shoe drops: Kevin O'Leary to enter Conservative leadership race tomorrow https://t.co/UtP8c8Ai1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saskatchewan and Ottawa reach deal on health care https://t.co/ZY0N0doQcG #cdnhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fmr ethics counsels for Presidents Bush &amp; Obama: You thought the Trump ethics disaster couldn’t get worse...it did https://t.co/ftADGRaEVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outage knocks Air Canada's airport check-in software offline https://t.co/En5OtqMMPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative leadership candidate Kellie Leitch is dead wrong about Toronto: Keenan https://t.co/ioIpL49V2H #WorthReading!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump praises wrong Ivanka on Twitter — and she has a message for him  https://t.co/IWYYzZIOZK #PleaseMakeItStop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Cernan, last astronaut on the moon, dies at 82 https://t.co/PGkBR9kAic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're in the news again: TVO's @TheAgenda takes to Twitter https://t.co/1rMGbsW1eo via @torontostar #cdnmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @VP_Fuentes for all you've done for @bloorci. You will be missed!! @tdsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Canadians killed in nightclub shooting at Playa del Carmen resort https://t.co/ncNFDPjBBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two richest Canadians now have as much wealth as the poorest 30% combined, report finds https://t.co/pXR2fZJpU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upstart Roman Baber trounces Joe Oliver in Ontario PC battle https://t.co/h8Cf3U4nHi #onpoli #opcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIG NEWS: We're Periscope streaming! @TheAgenda is now available to watch on Twitter every evening at 8 p.m. EST, Monday-Friday. @tvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s hockey star Hayley Wickenheiser announces retirement https://t.co/pvhSeTQ9xR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#Ontario economy growing at 2.6 per cent https://t.co/R6C3V2xdck #econ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s the Year of the (Giant Inflatable Trump) Rooster at one Chinese factory https://t.co/krBIpYBdgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Christie sees future job w/ Trump WH: 'It’s Game of Thrones, the Apprentice, and Survivor all mixed into one' https://t.co/NTMM0vDtGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Supreme Court judge Rosalie Abella named Global Jurist of the Year https://t.co/A5gqvK1qva #cool #scoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[William Peter Blatty, Author of ‘The Exorcist,’ Dies at 89 https://t.co/Ds2LhP7YyU #books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Snowdon, ex-husband of Princess Margaret, dies at 86  https://t.co/Kzo0RfZQHD #royals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Patrick Brown’s biggest electoral problem may be his own party | TVO https://t.co/wUVPbeV8yB #onpoli #opcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodstock, #Ontario nurse Elizabeth Wettlaufer accused of killing seniors faces six new charges https://t.co/hOH3M4WMiB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>