<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[High end drinks for a high end gal! #cheers #cocktailcrazed #showeringsaturday https://t.co/hKzcaqZIxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mykines, Faroe Islands | Photo Credit: @cosmokoala https://t.co/xQq1vDreOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE FAROE ISLANDS – Iceland // A photo series by NORTHLANDSCAPES, @JanWaider – Landscape &amp; Travel Ph https://t.co/QSoS8236Hd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strolling through the charming villages of the Faroes. https://t.co/Xhtg484SoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faroe Islands https://t.co/nLjje2Qfob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how to spend 5 scenic and serene days in the stunning Faroe Islands with this 5 day Faroe I https://t.co/QlEltKK77X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s also one of the most spectacular and underrated places on Earth. | 29 Reasons Why The Faroe Isl https://t.co/apdG6a8R35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful Nature on Instagram: “Faroe Island Photo by @paulzizkaphoto check out his feed for more” https://t.co/hNwYtg7GPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Emma, Forever Ago - banshy:   Faroe Islands // Johannes H https://t.co/Dpu1zrWU8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smallest destinations often boast the largest variety of things to do, places to explore and exp https://t.co/aNWu9fRR88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secrets to making a wedding cake. https://t.co/7xjTJHOiQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very useful information about the wedding cake. https://t.co/9vi3TrrWem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video is about How to make edible gems. It is a demo on how I made my light blue edible gems fr https://t.co/a0lp4FoeaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rhubarb + raspberry tart with almond praline. @thecoveteur https://t.co/aZJXdgOyWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's to new friends! #atlantafalcons #superbowlbound @ The Blaguard https://t.co/EA7ghuohWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IPAtlanta Falcons. #hotlanta #atlantaflacons #nfcchampionship @ The Blaguard https://t.co/rpWUpstKWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[malaysian peanut cookies for raya. eid. chinese new year. soft cookies https://t.co/B45EaEstI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Joy Factory: Best Melt-in-the-Mouth Pineapple Tarts (Sonia's Recipe) https://t.co/2dlCFsHMdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pineapple Cream Meringue tarts have a smooth and luscious filling that sits in a buttery flakey crus https://t.co/RRr5T9FNY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best-ever pineapple cookies or pineapple tarts - buttery, crumbly and melt-in-your-mouth pastry with https://t.co/4tPJVayZ4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish Pineapple Tarts - Finally found a recipe that is close to my favorite dessert! https://t.co/i8wdP9ZsYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[{Malaysia} How to make pineapple cookies - learn the step-by-step and make the BEST and easiest Asia https://t.co/bNWhRfARm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To buy or not to buy.... #godirtybirds #hotlanta #atlantaflacons #falconsindc #nfcchampionship https://t.co/Y6PjxKzqkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Almond Wedding Cake Recipe ~ Says: So Simple Yet Full of Flavor.... Truly The BEST White Cake  https://t.co/IWQ7YjYG6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almond Cream Cake ~ Light, moist and velvety, this cake has a homemade cooked, whipped frosting that https://t.co/p4piSnG3A1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rich, fudgy brownie you can make with just 6 ingredients in under 10 minutes! It's the perfect ski https://t.co/Elb823fguD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almond Cupcakes with Whipped Almond Buttercream Frosting. A delicious dessert treat recipe that's pe https://t.co/G7dfond97y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hazelnut crunch cake https://t.co/3pKKAGop6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One word defining the next few days and into the next few years: curious. #curiouscat #myhood… https://t.co/i9xgzdHfjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to return to the writing... #rsvpconfessions #blogginit #extracredit #operationlizzi… https://t.co/H7vY5D7iVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joy of car trouble...#neveradullmoment #hotwheels #notyouraveragemonday https://t.co/jqB33WISqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The design for the covers of the new passports is bold and striking. https://t.co/B35cwEalMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius!!! Cupcakes for TWO - for when you just don't need a bunch of sweets laying around - 1 egg wh https://t.co/NZJnO91Djx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Cream Pie Cupcakes ~ They are to die for... A moist vanilla cupcake, pastry cream filling and https://t.co/FNmvJU6A3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One-Bowl Chocolate Cake (For Two) | A Cozy Kitchen https://t.co/XAHae5KudW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Pink Champagne Cake is the perfect way to celebrate any occasion or holiday! A champagne infuse https://t.co/MKHf7xMW0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make Lemon Curd. This stuff is just awesome: creamy and tangy! So good mixed into yogurt. Mmh https://t.co/cDfYssK2fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful picture! https://t.co/3RvGn4x4eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milk Bread – Japanese-inspired milk bread that is cotton soft, sweet and delicious. Using roux metho https://t.co/dZJUsuir2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sparkly beauty can be decorated in under 2 HOURS!! https://t.co/Kzvbs4sXhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swooning over the pretty pearl detailing on this traditional wedding cake https://t.co/X6PFpyFO78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chocolate roses made with Tootsie Rolls and strawberries. Delicious! https://t.co/jkjOlLu9C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will absolutely be doing this, or cupcakes. No way I can pay a lot of money for a cake that no one e https://t.co/Di01UbV6LG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this dessert decorating tutorial to learn how to make a fondant-free Naked Wedding Cake. https://t.co/Oxi5Fv4jUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Super Simple Guide to Designing Your Wedding Cake, from Top to Bottom. https://t.co/shabv0Bi7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a Bakery Quality White Cake with Buttercream Frosting ~ It is delicious, the frosting is awes https://t.co/6wu1j4GzXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make a wedding cake in advance. Tips for getting started so you don't have to do everything at the l https://t.co/iyStx5hIN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DIY Rustic Wedding by Michael Meeks Photography – KnotsVilla https://t.co/umbJho6dug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Make Your Own Scratch Off Cards! DIY TIME! | Wonder Forest: Style, Design, Life. https://t.co/X4mdhBvOle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make scratch-off save-the-dates with just a few tools | https://t.co/HJXDFzXWj7 https://t.co/ydxzXI6C7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bric's Black Crocodile-Embossed Cargo Duffel on https://t.co/aSNBkLZ7id https://t.co/QiMLcDB5jO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sided #booklet and #brochure design with marbled cover and gold foil: https://t.co/dsb5a9aFeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate travel duffel featuring a bottom zippered section for shoes. Also perfect as a gym or h https://t.co/B1L7HpwVRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funfetti Angel Food Cupcakes - love these cupcakes! Homemade funfetti is so much better than a box m https://t.co/pKRzC9xeR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S'mores Bites - a twist on the classic dessert, make these little S'mores Bites in the oven! https://t.co/JusvYIIaK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you tried these Homemade Pop Tarts yet?! They're INSANELY good!! https://t.co/bWXRRNWH4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its about time  https://t.co/ZYXQAH3cE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S'mores Chocolate Chip Cookies are thick, chewy, and loaded with so much gooey goodness! https://t.co/I6mYDgs9vJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patioset: Simple Outdoor Furniture with Modern Comfort https://t.co/kU1cKV1GPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for easy, no-bake desserts? Try this Easy Lemon Truffle Recipe- This is an easy cake mix tru https://t.co/YuG4dFeNPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Layer upon layer of light, buttery flaky pastry filled with rich chocolate and drizzled with more ch https://t.co/iUDDXwGCV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copycat Girl Scout Tagalong Cookies https://t.co/P0RnJkn7NU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized how much pepper is going to be in this chili... #whitechickenchili #oops… https://t.co/kJyG8uaGaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moments where you can look back on your first blog post in a kitchen of a Michelin starred… https://t.co/RuPPkkduYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s A Wine Amusement Park And It Sounds Amazing https://t.co/z9JbtOuL9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year! #bringiton #2017 #nevergrowup #operationlizzi @ Adams Morgan https://t.co/PgDMVJaDWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Source: mrslindsaypavy #humpdaymotivation #humpday #2017 #operationlizzi https://t.co/GiImGaOlLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom. #bullseye #takethat @ The Passenger https://t.co/dtHjEpWYnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you tell I'm ready for #2017 yet? #champagnecocktail #tgif #chambord https://t.co/mcj7a56tai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So nice to have this around again... #chambord #champagnecocktail #tgif https://t.co/2EutcMGc4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting off lebowski style... #tgif #cocktailcrazed #whiterussian #biglebowski https://t.co/7ojxcETqEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These No-Bake Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough Brownie Bombs are the ultimate treat! Egg-free cookie doug https://t.co/eRY1MtGzjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White Russian Cocktail is The Dude’s favorite. What else do you need to know? https://t.co/eplrV1pSKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raspberry Butter Cookies - Erren's Kitchen - This Simple linzer style sandwich cookie recipe is just https://t.co/oOmAa2FT6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spice up your famous batch of chocolate chip cookies with our Eggnog Chocolate Chip Butter Cookies r https://t.co/Ftw2g1aGX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pistachio Lime Cake with Vanilla Buttercream https://t.co/pqQQDBYk5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tunnel of Lights, Ireland https://t.co/mYq3B70RUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These no-bake Chocolate Chip Cookie Dough Ice Cream Sandwiches are egg-free and delicious! https://t.co/GoW0nGFYmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[River House at Morukuru Lodge in Madikwe, South Africa. A romantic retreat perched on the banks of M https://t.co/0NE8fSeaCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painkiller (2 oz. Dark Rum 1 oz. Cream of Coconut 4 oz. Pineapple Juice 1 oz. Orange Juice Cherry fo https://t.co/FgcrfnDxZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grapefruit Moscow mules are the perfect refreshing + citrusy summer cocktail to try this weekend! https://t.co/BKx2HH51bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Steps to Make A Beautiful Edible Centerpiece https://t.co/I84s7v9wvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This eggnog truffles recipe makes for the perfect Christmas party dessert. Or, package the truffles  https://t.co/TadJvnFCwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Red Queen cocktail is perfect for the festive season https://t.co/h2SU1dwdaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balloon backdrop https://t.co/EvOQQMxTPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackberry bourbon smash cocktail drink recipe, /waitingonmartha/ https://t.co/oe9qTc2VBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[ad] Create your registry with #ZolaRegistry, you and your guests will love it https://t.co/s5tOdXDLpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you actually can make a mixed drink out of a lager or IPA. https://t.co/ziUvRatoe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Panna Cotta with berry sauce is AMAZING! A quick and easy recipe that can be made in advance (p https://t.co/NKuiJdNkrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Brick Street Chocolate Cake. Everything you dream of in a rich, dense chocolate cake. Secret  https://t.co/lR9wPqB1IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homemade chocolate truffles are so easy to make! These chocolate truffles have a cream cheese base a https://t.co/cO9go0kstW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thumbprint Cookies – Best, buttery and sweet cookies filled with raspberry jam. Easy recipe that any https://t.co/950HSK7qbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently smelly doesn't want us to bake cookies... #smellycat #catsofinstagram #unproductive… https://t.co/udlHKlkdVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT Cooking: What these cinnamon rolls lack in bells and whistles, they make up for in butter and br https://t.co/35ZciDrkZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn how to make big giant cinnamon rolls-- almost double the size of your typical and covered with https://t.co/JAG67ps7l3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost-Famous Cinnamon Buns recipe from Food Network Kitchen via Food Network https://t.co/vrkyFvywIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is how you make friends on a flight #atlbound #toomuchfun https://t.co/RmALcytODk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Turtle knows how to pour at BWI... #atlbound #headinsouth @ BWI International Airport https://t.co/Av9Td88o8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is Not a Drill: Champagne Marshmallows Are Real https://t.co/vPdLNkwlBF via @VinePair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to see this silly guy #panther #pantherofthehouse https://t.co/zxj2SoVJpX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>