<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When is a pork chop not just a 'pork chop'? When it's from @proudsow #brockley #foodporn #localbusiness https://t.co/tfl1Tr4idO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome article on job sharing in @standardnews tonight - embracing new ways of working brings better brains into b… https://t.co/7WRAtPaSY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#r4today *head in hands* over handling of the debate on gender led dress codes. Tragedy this important debate sidelined by design of shoes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a phenomenal piece of reporting and a truly chilling story #journalismmatters https://t.co/e1PAvQDVJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has to be THE BEST #christmasadvert of the season including #christmasjumperday and #MannequinChallenge https://t.co/nO9jXs2nJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunLintern @pressgazette @HSJEditor congratulations - well earned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NHS Twitter a quieter place today as @RoyLilley quietened by a mouthful of humble pie https://t.co/hmm2QqvzA6 @VirginiaMason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msclews @Fortnums glad it got there okay :) xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V impressed at @LiamByrneMP ability to explain failures of liberalism. See that line going down = real term earning… https://t.co/xfiQU6Y1IV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a Steady Eddie or a Rising Star? Recognising the pipeline of SME growth at #smallbizbritain2016… https://t.co/SbmGWtP1ls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_MES noooo! Not a patch on the lion king!! Where's the sound track?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_MES beautiful. Great not to see a Disney character in sight! The Incredibles theme was a poor year :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliciakearns @PRCAIngham @DJKSaunders yes you did. Im sorry. Shortly after I was 1 of 1st signs @PRCA_UK campaign for proper paid interns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliciakearns @PRCAIngham @DJKSaunders @JournalistaLtd I think #londonlivingwage should be the basic standard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are unpaid internships still legal? One of biggest barriers to social mobility as only possible for parent fund… https://t.co/7B7szezFzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a track record to be proud of @IBM - spend with diverse suppliers over 3% of revenue #weconnecteurope https://t.co/lLvmh0knkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[November reading sorted thanks to @MindyGK #weconnecteurope https://t.co/X93YQIG0ig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring view to match the @WEConnectEurope conference generously hosted by @IBM https://t.co/V0PtrSDI3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sutton_eileen hope you have a winning day :) xx https://t.co/FARv30aNh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to my mum winner of #UKITAWARDS Cloud Computing for leading #nhs #111 - irony free call to me at 2am to as… https://t.co/dWDgInMjNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone has the time to shine, even when their chance only comes round every 60+ years. Poor #hilary . Poor ol… https://t.co/QhljaI0dCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to get top spot on @GdnHealthcare for this great story on a very important topic #NHS #NHScomms… https://t.co/ELAtQ4cNLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was Belstaff I'd be asking for my media spend back for the juxtaposition of this ad with the story! The wordin… https://t.co/6P7KiRoLRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May is 'totally nailing' the middle ground...more like lost, stranded and broken down at hard right. https://t.co/IAScrkuLrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is increasing feeling like we're in Black Mirror - the pig voters won, next up foreign worker detectors in our… https://t.co/0V90IOvywv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @KateSwaffer making my mouth water! Delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @fredds_flowers for this week's beautiful bunch! My favourite so far #ecobusiness #sme #ukbusiness https://t.co/Kke5fzUYi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Points 1-2 the most complicated and even non-sensical (see end of Pt.2) way of making mash I've ever seen #prfail… https://t.co/5NtyjIa0BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Boards must make decisions with patients, not for them" #NHScomms #patientengagement #accountability https://t.co/Ce8j6M9EVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely - see @_ukactive calculations on #turningthetide reports https://t.co/BZ69JsJZ0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @BBCr4today yours have more bling though :) great look! I feel 16 again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_shibley @BBCr4today they're Bose - never has music sounded so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but these are just too good for @BBCr4today sauntering along to De La Soul instead - much better start to day! https://t.co/2aRJAUSadI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSJnews the link on the HSJ Awards shortlist announcement takes you to where to book a table, not the shortlist https://t.co/hXruTBaTdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blown away by size of @johnlewis in Birmingham Central...question is will there be time for shopping post pitch? https://t.co/CF37tT1Xi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly season still strong - hedgehog sanctuary on garden bridge called for &amp; GP claims ownership of Mars courtesy of @thetimes  #prtips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother and daughter reunited at #nhs16expo any other random family meet ups here? https://t.co/J70dK53wb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V brave woman speaks out on transformative treatment received for BPD power of patients' voices at #nhs16expo is what makes it so special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[111 announcement: algorithm currently led by phone call - now also on line. Better than webmd where all symptoms=brain cancer #Expo16NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only one london trust named as a global exemplar of #namethepaperlessby2020agenda #Expo16NHS https://t.co/QGjCEyCePF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No UK hospital IT systems are world class - trusts will need to go at different speeds." #Expo16NHS #namethepaperlessby2020agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindless #nhs16expo musings... Is Lord Darzi the best dressed man in healthcare? https://t.co/4j7sl258Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple effective #prtips David Halpern @B_I_Tweets 'what are the existing comms channels you've got?' Uses eg. Of HMRC for SMEs #Expo16NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPIAndyCowper further evidence you no longer need a physical product for @HSJnews ! You'll all be able relocate to sunnier climes soon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sutton_eileen your moment of fame #nhs16expo https://t.co/uFS0jVOGLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Hunt getting down with the real folk queuing at #nhs16expo hope doesn't escalate to Corbyn-esq train selfies https://t.co/jjxMjt09Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning tweet so far #nhs16expo  https://t.co/ibZeAYaY7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteThomond @ExpoNHS it's okay you can follow our tweets - we'll capture all best bits on @JournalistaLtd and maybe see you tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In 30 years of being in service 1st time I've been able to do justice to people's opinions" #AHPsmandate using @clever_together #Expo16NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visit the tallest stand @ExpoNHS today to find out about a. Why the Eiffel Tower changes height &amp; b. New products https://t.co/9QA3rT04MN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the transformations required to deliver the changes called for @ExpoNHS? #NHS innovators give their insight https://t.co/BKrFeQCafR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteThomond watching your work with AHPs @ExpoNHS but can't see you...are you in Manchester?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting behind the scenes insight - thank @whazell  https://t.co/eImVAJSvIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteThomond Jaffa cakes aren't technically biscuits...see you're on the slope to cake already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteThomond it starts at biscuits, it graduates to M&amp;S flapjacks and before you know it everyone's a stone heavier...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone had a bad 'back to work' Monday, here's to a better Tuesday... #prfail #JuniorDoctorsStrike  https://t.co/iQ7OTpeeaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #eco #startup outside Hammersmith tube today - looking forward to my Lincolnshire fresh flowers next Monday! https://t.co/cBUbZvr1nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah those restful mornings when you dream you've had a c-section in the morning and pitching in the afternoon #mondaymotivation #workingmum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question that's driving everyone crazy today - how did #KeithVaz find a central London flat for less than £400k? https://t.co/tTbuLJoaZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kentpolicedart our carbon monoxide alarm just went off in the Dartford Tunnel. Bit of a worry. https://t.co/rSMOr8LCxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msclews @LewesAC wow - that's absolutely breath taking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@proudsow did we do your short rib proud? Tasted absolutely delicious 😋 https://t.co/wpe5lAz8WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aesopskincare think you might want to check out Coppa Three Quays they're using ur branded dispensers in their bathrooms but not ur product]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st stop with 'lil sister the awesome @MarySeacoleHA statue. Remarkably 1st statue of a black named woman in UK https://t.co/p5HAVTDhnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dysology oh no! That bacteria loves you :( get on the probiotics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the #70things campaign - this is my contribution photography made into art via the great Prism app! https://t.co/DuEd9sOH0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will STPs replace CCGs? And other predictions for the #NHS from soothsayer @HSJEditor https://t.co/c89858hbeI https://t.co/p7n3nSAxQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dysology I'll screen shot and email to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rum affair as botanist’s Ice Age fraud finally proven @Dysology  https://t.co/0Z7VJPC6r9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Something is happening here/ But you don't know what it is.."Bob Dylan #//post #Brexit @frontlinepbs @WildernessHQ https://t.co/6m91OvUfTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye bye clogged M40 - hello West Country #Wilderness2016 nearly there! https://t.co/Q4iGUWQSws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hssood advises new tech tariff launched by @NHSEngland today, no official release as yet. Anti-holiday deadline of 16th August! #healthtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/wXreba3INm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/70dnWASjcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful call to leadership in @RoyLilley blog this morning - as applicable to anyone doing #NHScomms as a #NHS CEO https://t.co/faupFmZcz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having bit of a clear out...that's a LOT of crap #email #Google https://t.co/CLl18qBQ3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets have arrived! #wilderness2016 is first festival with the little chap #wilderrides can't wait https://t.co/tAJ1zJ4An0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msclews ah really?! Can't you recreate the couples one with Mr Clews and the kids? Ha ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brass Eye or Sky News? You decide... https://t.co/uCPxjN6mHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PRCA_UK launches its gender equality survey today - get involved people! 
https://t.co/4QOvq5aLtR
 #PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markbritnell 's healthcare buzzword bingo - play it on your #healthcare document now https://t.co/9BNFgI5N0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In summary, @markbritnell summarises the best bits of the world's health system #nhs #healthcare #NHScomms https://t.co/zVY8ETs8Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eminent @markbritnell endorses #PR "At your best you're unbeatable" talking at our @PRCA_UK healthcare group. https://t.co/8YiCT9j6xG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Id rather a leader that felt comfortable being her true self and cared enough to cry!  https://t.co/iQ9yEJVoBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more than one way to be a leader. Most sense I've heard on @BBCr4today for a long time. Thank you @angelaeagle you've got my vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theipaper they're all joining so they can have a say on who replaces him! Think he's missing the point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to engage? Process, process, process - great step by step diagram by @JessLonsdale1 @VirginCare #c2020health https://t.co/igU5avsUuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently away from desk feeding my son fruit from cocktails. Will check emails - can't guarantee reply. Back 3/07. https://t.co/VNmdXd0C0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hate the haters. Be wowed by  resilience and fortitude. Proud to be a citizen of this great world. #JoCox  https://t.co/rrdWc1lqnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite outfit of #confed2016 so far @lynda_thomas - the NHS' very own Jenna Lyons https://t.co/VJ3ISOq129]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 to dos when using IT &amp; digital to transform patient care from @Bob_Wachter #confed2016 report due Sept '16 https://t.co/OrTc82U52U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality, quality, quality - that's what @Jeremy_Hunt wants the 10s decade to be remembered for #confed2016 https://t.co/x3IIIkdMqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram friendly freebies? A rare treat #confed2016 kudos to @allocateS for breathing healthcare into their brand https://t.co/B5BgErw3tS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sort out a narrative, get people engaged and show progress in hard facts and figures to deliver #devolution // all PR campaigns #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling reminder from Stephen Dalton that 20 years ago today a bomb went off here in Manchester: solidarity #orlando #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White, heterosexual men your place in the queue is not as secure as it used to be for CEO" Awesome msg to kick-off with. #confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPIAndyCowper and @ShaunLintern get good humoured  dressing down at start of Stephen Dalton's speech to kick off #Confed2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big topic -centralisation- to coincide with day 1 of a big event #confed2016 from @DrFosterIntel on @GdnHealthcare https://t.co/eg5KhH4mZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 on site journalists at #confed2016 inc. @BBCNews awaiting @nhsconfed view on #Brexit today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-harmers gain celebrity on web app via @thetimes @oscarholland  https://t.co/fDQPVFHWKi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>