<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@terryjstamp @_chriskohler It should be recognised that it has always been hard for young house buyers to make ends meet. No new phenomenon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terryjstamp @_chriskohler No. Earlier tweet was relating single wages with house prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terryjstamp @_chriskohler She had a partner who shared repayments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anto1503 @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Backbone of the nation. https://t.co/Of8FZi9rjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anto1503 @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Trades need career planning. Pathways for progression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anto1503 @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Yes. Team job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terryjstamp @PuntPal @_chriskohler Whoever said Karratha &amp; Port Hedland was kidding themselves. Perth metro will come back soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anto1503 @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Overtime money is good. Lucrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anto1503 @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian They are on a pretty good wicket already. Very expensive hourly rates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam @guardian Use Google to check my facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @petegordon4sir @_chriskohler @australian @illchangethis Compared to what? Australia is still the lucky country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam @guardian Household income is very different to two average incomes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinVirant @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Yes. Tradies are the new Dentists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @Graham1Sam Try Google. It's all there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illchangethis @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian They would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @illchangethis @_chriskohler @australian Yes. Banks believe more in increased value of houses than your ability to pay back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petegordon4sir @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian @illchangethis So defeatist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkPlackett1 @cponzi @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil That's credit cards. No one likes to talk about credit card debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illchangethis @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Incredibly banks will still give you a 30 year loan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler That's always the benchmark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @MarkPlackett1 @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil Most people's biggest purchase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian It affects everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian Yes. House prices are like a clock etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam  Not according to official statistics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian Mmmm. It's more complicated. We do need investment to build rentals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @MarkPlackett1 @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil Pretending there is no dosh in Sydney is naive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam  Wages are matching CPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian 15% increase is not guaranteed or an annual thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil @Graham1Sam Two 'average' incomes are $150,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @MarkPlackett1 @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil Demand. When people lose interest in living in Sydney, prices will fall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam  That's arguable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian It has been sustained. Nay sayers have been proven wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam @BoomersAreEvil @MarkPlackett1 State government has become dependent on stamp duty revenue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham1Sam @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris Needing two full time incomes to pay off your mortgage, to me, means you bought the wrong house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkPlackett1 @Graham1Sam @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris Now THATS a scandal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham1Sam @MarkPlackett1 @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris Achieves nothing but years in the wilderness for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgesStPaul1 @MarkPlackett1 @Graham1Sam Problem is the 'good of the nation' is second to most people's individual struggles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @MarkPlackett1 Do we really want endless cheap houses further &amp; further out from cities? Is that progress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @stoicsnake @_chriskohler @australian Yeah that's what many red faced economists have been saying for years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam  Low (it's not nothing) wage growth ignores fact people get promoted &amp; then earn more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @MdmAbsentMinded @_chriskohler @australian @linzcom You can with negative gearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham1Sam @BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @MarkPlackett1 I'm less of a fan of that. People do need to have some benefit from saving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil @Graham1Sam @MarkPlackett1 It will make a big difference. #IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @MarkPlackett1 @BoomersAreEvil Yes. Currently population growth is exceeding demand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian Actually the Labor Party has announced a perfectly practical policy. Change is coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam @MarkPlackett1 Just change the tax laws. #endnegativegearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MdmAbsentMinded @BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler @australian Rents are tied to property values.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @MarkPlackett1 @BoomersAreEvil Demand. Prices can't fall in popular cities with limited space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham1Sam @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil @MarkPlackett1 Even Albo has a second house in Canberra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham1Sam @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil @MarkPlackett1 Yes. Dutton has a reported $10 million portfolio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stoicsnake @43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler @australian As long as people think they can't, they won't. Think positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @peterfraserbris @Graham1Sam @MarkPlackett1 Higher stamp duty for investors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfraserbris @MarkPlackett1 @BoomersAreEvil Catch 22. The longer you wait the higher the buy in price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkPlackett1 @peterfraserbris @BoomersAreEvil They keep saying the Sydney market will turn. It just keeps going up &amp; up. #demand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian I get out a lot. You'd be surprised who the entrepreneurs are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkPlackett1 @BoomersAreEvil @CENTUM Well their houses are now worth a fortune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler Or talk to a financial advisor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @vaughanhealey @_chriskohler Its not really ingrained. Will change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughanhealey @lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler Not in a limited house market. Demand is always growing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler Yes. Home ownership is decreasing with population growth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil Yes. People are now using their superannuation to pay off their house debt &amp; then go on the pension. That's not ideal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @BoomersAreEvil Yelling doesn't get you a house either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler X. We who came after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler That's a good point. That's an extra impost on young house buyers now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebGroarke Yes. Negative Gearing tax cuts are out of control. Need to be be removed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler True. Wage growth is a real issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuntPal @_chriskohler House prices are never going to lower in Sydney. Too much demand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler Median house cost in Sydney is now over a million I believe? https://t.co/mNm2e2bSXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler Old suburbs see little new building.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler It's a politically unpopular tax. Another impost for people struggling with a mortgage. Two sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil No one was ever handed a house. Saving is a bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler Not really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil No obligation to buy a house. Europe has a very low level of home ownership. Australia has an unusually high level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil 18 is too young. See world, be crazy but then allow three years of hard savings to get deposit. It's worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler No. People get ahead by using the leverage from the increased value of their homes. Salaries aren't everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cponzi @BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler First home owners should buy dog box then a few years later renovate or upgrade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler Each to their own. I prefer to get advice from people who have done it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler House prices traditionally double every seven years. That's not new. #oldsaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebGroarke @_chriskohler She had to put up a third deposit. Borrowed $40,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuntPal @_chriskohler Talking to people is a better way to find your way into home ownership. Practical advice based on experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler Yes that is certainly on the cards. They do that in ACT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler This may shock you but the notion houses are impossibly expensive is not new. At 25 it always is a mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler No, understanding that finding a way into the house market IS hard, requires sacrifices but is worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler Yep city prices are much higher &amp; they grow in value much quicker. Much more competitive market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lapuntadelfin @_chriskohler That's a great plan. #not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler @australian Not really. Point is to make your rent your income. Getting that deposit is everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler No. I know hardly anyone who built a house from scratch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil Seems you are just on a Blame hunt rather than a solutions hunt. #nothelping @_chriskohler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuntPal Example was demonstrating house v salary prices from the past. #importantdistinction @_chriskohler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler Personal anecdote, lived experience, the media &amp; government statistics are all we got.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler That's a different discussion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil @_chriskohler @australian No, youth of today ARE buying houses. That's what I'm seeing. It's tough, sure but it's happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler Average salary is now over $80,000 a year. #OfficialStatistics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @_chriskohler @australian What 'average' tradie is on a grand a week? Please advise. #needsomeworkdone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holder_glen Damn real life examples. Talking to people is SO last century right? Back to compliant anonymous statistics.  #comforting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmydownawell Packer ads looks like this: https://t.co/8hARjyWVri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmydownawell Ha - no. Not even sure what ad is selling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_grante @_chriskohler Have another friend's example. In 1989 Petersham house was bought for $197,000. Salary $20,000. Same, same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PolitiScopeOz It went REALLY well! The time did zip along. Congratulations to all. #itworks #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plebiscite is old Latin for 'no political backbone'. #auspol https://t.co/WZFZV35rfz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>