<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexcanroar just marched in Edinburgh. What a brilliant atmosphere https://t.co/PJpWu4Um2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are marching against trump #edinburghprotest #fucktrump https://t.co/9UrolcLljk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABFalecbaldwin currently protesting Trump in Edinburgh. We stand united. https://t.co/IccpG0BIJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my essay that I started four hours before the deadline got a "this is generally good work" along with a B grade. Bless u Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe 2017 is our season 4 of Community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andy_pee_tho I've still to watch it, but I'm looking forward to that and the music. Was the film good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar fuck off that's amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar I like to refer to them as Charlie jobs to make myself feel just that tiny bit better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got an A for my photography project at uni. https://t.co/nU9p5CTsJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryOnTour can you retweet please. I am selling my Edinburgh ticket for your show. I can't make the re-scheduled date. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like what the actual fuck haha https://t.co/FmnwGrST27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who needs to watch @T2Trainspotting when you live in it? https://t.co/N6bvdm78sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar or that howl when you die. Gets me every time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar still making my way through 4 with my wee dog companion. It's all I want in real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose working until 6 on a Sunday. Choose missing the #trainspotting2 premiere. Choose to prentend you actually had a choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World premiere of trainspotting 2 is at my local cinema in Edinburgh and I'm working all day. Fuck sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natashaax I'm surprised you've not had a heart attack with all those takeaways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to the gym for the first time in six months and proceeded to congratulate myself with a chippy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was the one that said "so help me God" which is the only time I've ever agreed with him #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC news presenter just said it's the "beginning of the end (pause) of obama's presidency" we get you #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here @JoeBiden gonnae punch trump in the face at lunch. You'd make my day. Cheers pal xoxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roryharper genuinely any religion is better than the mental evangelicals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you bring the rabbi back and like get rid of this evangelical weirdo. Thanks xoxox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well at least we have a cracking episode of @nbcsnl to look forward to... #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can never use the 'ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½' emoji again cause it reminds me of Donald trump :////]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC news presenter was going through trump's children and forgot Tiffany even though she's standing beside the rest of them ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually went into uni today and there are a group of girls in the row behind us that just won't shut the fuck up ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first day back at uni went very well as I managed to sleep until 2pm missing the only lecture I had ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHazelHayes @nbcsnl I catch up on Sundays evenings accompanied by a chippy. Keeping it classy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@n0rmanbates that's like the optimum tipsy level. You won't get a hangover, but feel fucking chill and happy for like half an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to make a cameo in some randoms snapchat story displaying my first class patient care, holding a sick bowl to their pal's face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natashaax haha but it's also great doing fuck all too xox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natashaax samez. Haven't left the flat in days. Just as well I'm working all weekend ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexcanroar just watched your video. I am also thinking about saving so I can buy the flat and get a wee old cat. Priorities, right?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexcanroar do you mean like actually buying property? Because wow there, that's a grown up thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only labour can deliver a successful brexit" or you could just let the tories deal with it and not fuck the Labour Party even more xoxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Hamill Is Dubbing Drumpf's Tweets as the Joker https://t.co/AV5nKawUsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you really have a cold if you don't sniff and say "fuck my life" every 15 seconds????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerchvais I look like such a loner xoxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating alone at a restaurant for the first time. My craving for sushi overpowered me. There's only me and a couple in the whole place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryOnTour gutted I can't make the rescheduled date. Is there anyway I can get a refund?  Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@on_lothianbuses thanks. It's just annoying how I have to then get the 30 back up to my uni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for the first time I managed to use a tram to get to the airport. I also had the joy of passing my work and not having to go in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leither94 @on_lothianbuses haha I'm going to go by my uni and then get a bus back up. Thanks for letting me know :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cstevenson1968 @on_lothianbuses thanks for letting me know. I'm going to pass my uni to then go back haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@on_lothianbuses does it actually stop at queen Margaret? Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@on_lothianbuses the 44 going east re-route stops at QMU? Just planning for going back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellaloubateman @JackHoward and that's perfectly fine. You are allowed to like the show, but accept that others will critique it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellaloubateman @JackHoward they had a great storyline in season two and then absolutely shat on it in season 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that my eyebrows are meant to be sisters not twins, but I think mines are more like second cousins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who went through 20 different emotions in 5 seconds to finally realise it was chocolate. https://t.co/B81NaZrDEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar ah yes! It wouldn't be right if that didn't happen. It's like a tester for the week ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBR988 Such a wonderful video. It highlights the broader point of the article and sums up everything so articulately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLikeTheCar and being in a tense state for roughly two weeks of the month, then a week of the period. Then one week of feeling safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBR988 and they want you to be afraid. Don't let them win and enjoy yourself. You're right, I'd much rather go out enjoying my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece about travelling around europe with all the shit that has been going down as of late. https://t.co/8uBgx2zolu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whathayleydid wow, that will be awesome. I hope you enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whathayleydid when and where? That's hopefully my next move after uni. I'm so excited for you ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas bitches. Same jumper, different year. @LeahJayex https://t.co/rhbl42TW2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izzyinkpen Berlin is my fave. Going back in a couple of weeks â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nothing quite says you're back in livingston like bumping into susan boyle down the centre xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHazelHayes most relatable tweet of the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just realised I have become a hipster. I am drinking a latte out of a mason jar. Not in a fancy shop, but in my own home. I'm ashamed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBR988 I'll give you some of mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexcanroar I learnt my lesson when a can of cider did the same thing. Can't believe I was betrayed by my one true love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 I hate it when my parents would get cards addressed to "Tom, Susan, and family" like fuck sake I'm an only child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jlogzzy haha I forgot about that. I'll text ya ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jlogzzy haha I'm considering re-downloading it. Need a spooning partner ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after all this essay writing you would think i would be able to spell 'synonyms' first time, but naw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBR988 Only if you are prepared to fail miserably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My lecturer just appeared on the news. They are clearly going to new levels to remind me to stop procrastinating and do my essay...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing says Christmas in retail like customers moaning that you don't have contactless but they are spending &gt;Â£100 ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roryharper here Liberace had a limit, and it was way before that monstrosity of an outfit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerchvais he backed into a parked car. Even I haven't done that yet. He had to walk me to my hostel. He rated me 5 stars though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerchvais oh my god he got lost and crashed his car. I still had to walk for five minutes at the end. Fucking hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerchvais his driving is fine though and he seems nice but 40 minutes of awkwardness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently in what can only be described as the worst uber ride of my life. 40 minutes and neither of us speak the same language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy and trying to find specific readings online without spending Â£40 or trying to share a book between 60 people ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy I feel you bro. That's what I spent a couple of hours doing yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me right now https://t.co/mRYno9axg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rushed lots of uni work this morning so I could meet up with her. It's love. https://t.co/mKj2iyHSAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wrote a 1500 essay in three and a half hours and it's a load of shite, but it's my load of finished and ready to send shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHazelHayes honestly I am always up for watching woman create comedy and I wasn't disappointed. I loved it and hope it gets commissioned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updating my uni pal on the progress of my essay xoxo https://t.co/YAFKXYtr3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a teenager and got stressed I used to comfort eat. Now I forget to eat and drink 30 coffees an hour. I can't win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't started my essay yet and it's due for 4pm. This will be a fun day of stress crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy is he still there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy haha I wish I was there right now! You never know, he might come out with the whole "well trump actually isn't that bad" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy has the girl said anything more/actually engaged in conversation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy oh my god, wait until he saves that he is pro israel and then pounce ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy are white guys that oblivious or so self centred that they don't realise people aren't interested??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kibbyboyy haha I can't even imagine what she was thinking whilst he was saying it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izzyinkpen it's what always happens to me. I rush something trying to get to the imaginary deadline I made up and regret it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izzyinkpen then it will always eat away at you :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izzyinkpen will you regret putting that version up? will you be like "I could have done it better?" don't make extra stress for yourself...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 haha I just assumed you worked in princes street or something. We have probably passed out each at the tram stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 wait do you work in the gyle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 yip, it is a nightmare, but thankfully now that I am at uni im only there on weekends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 the lovely diy shop with all the orange and OAPs :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidB1996 and my work is just on the left ðŸ˜­]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>