<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover How This Ex-Musician Kicked $400,000 In Debt &amp; Has Taught Thousands People To Live The 'Laptop Lifestyle'… https://t.co/JZZg3IJtzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet my new friend Jeff Lerner. He has just released Laptop Lifestyle for your online business &gt;… https://t.co/toIVB5Zbdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If fear is the great enemy of intimacy, love is its true friend." Henri Nouwen
Read more at: https://t.co/jvSY4CU3M1 #quote #inspiration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you fancy a Laptop Lifestyle? Work anywhere you can take your laptop! If you do take a look at this &gt;… https://t.co/3792yWhp97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To respond is positive, to react is negative"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some people who listen to you when you talk and there's other people who just wait for their turn.- Bryan Kramer #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connect enthusiastically. Give relentlessly. And lead bravely. Do that, and the future is yours! – Ted Coine #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas are easy. Implementation is hard. – Guy Kawasaki #quote #entrepreneur #startup #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Laptop Lifestyle" is here! Check it out here &gt;https://t.co/ssK9vrF4JU&lt; We launched today! New &amp; fresh!… https://t.co/THzZ4YmQuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We gotter done! We launched today, Lifestyle Design International (LDI)! Take a look right here &gt;… https://t.co/haA3olbUdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The athlete who says that something cannot be done should
never interrupt the one who is doing it."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like photography. You need the negatives to develop. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Learn to help people with more than just their jobs; help
them with their lives”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-Esteem begins and ends with you. The more you know about yourself, the less moved you'll be by the opinions of others. - B. Dilley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you share a good idea long enough, it will eventually fall
on good people"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not anticipate trouble or worry about what may never
happen. Keep in the sunlight."
- Benjamin Franklin #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is CBD? Cannabidiol, also known as CBD! Here is an article that explains it really well &gt;… https://t.co/77UMYAg37V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Can Benefit from Pure CBD Products? Everyone can! &gt;https://t.co/xLN6WrSIki&lt; Great article about THC free CBD! #CBD #hempoil #hemp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaKendriick_ You are very creative. Keep after it, you bring out the emotions of the emotions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last call for Lifestyle Design International's "Backdoor Access"! Check it out here &gt;https://t.co/ssK9vrWG8u&lt; We go… https://t.co/hyoaNQaIfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from. - Cormac McCarthy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. - Albert Einstein #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IS BĬBONG? I love that word! Click here to see what it's all about &gt;https://t.co/3qrZIQPkKw&lt; #cbdoil #hemp… https://t.co/rTaJIuCAae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth obtained by fraud will dwindle, but whoever earns it through labor will multiply it" Proverbs 13:11 (HCSB). #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Only 3% of the population writes down their goals, the rest of
society works for these people” — Brian Tracey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Don’t set your goals too low. If you don’t need much, you won’t
become much.” — JimRohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Dream no small dreams for they have no power to move the
hearts of men.” — Johann von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private “Back Door Access” to LDI, closes very soon &gt;https://t.co/ssK9vrF4JU&lt; for more information! Closes as soon… https://t.co/EaMy5AwVdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kannaway’s Hemp Oil is derived from 100% legal non-GMO European industrial hemp! To learn more click here &gt;… https://t.co/hhSt2djYBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13
"Leadership is the challenge to be something more than
average”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you in a constant process of change in your life? Do you embrace change in your life? #johnbdeleo https://t.co/udhgqVm0Ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest mistake you can make is listening to people who've given up on their dreams telling you to give up on yours. - Umair Hague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actions are remembered long after words are forgotten. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Marketing Leads Generation Platform https://t.co/Q60jIiJRLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @hanaemorishita Thank you for following me! Keep calm and tweet on! via https://t.co/BYAcaTekB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @OnlyFollowTeam Thank you for following me! Keep calm and tweet on! via https://t.co/BYAcaTekB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @TechGenYZ Thank you for following me! Keep calm and tweet on! via https://t.co/BYAcaTekB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @madaboutcompute Thank you for following me! Keep calm and tweet on! via https://t.co/BYAcaTekB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @SaifurRSohag Thank you for following me! Keep calm and tweet on! via https://t.co/BYAcaTekB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we have no identity apart from our jobs, we are truly vulnerable. - Dan Miller #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MJNA Statement Re DEA, this is not only the video from Dr. Stuart Titus but a statement from Medical Marijuana Inc:… https://t.co/YmsBmzzclu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want the LDI Freedom “Back Door Access”? The Laptop Lifestyle will soon be here! Find access at… https://t.co/29bLoXBNyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you working on you? Personal development is key to your growth as a person! My latest blog &gt;… https://t.co/1hNylxrgsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at what the DEA said about our CBD &gt;https://t.co/qUFmitidjE&lt; #hempoil #RSHO #randyschroeder https://t.co/aNuehn7Esb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people dream of success... while others wake up and
work hard at it."
-Author Unknown #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What books are you reading for your personal development? One book has surprised me. Don't judge a book by its cove… https://t.co/juV5UsP3l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just read this about Kannaway's THC free CBD (cannabidiol) &gt;https://t.co/vd65XXinrJ&lt; Take a look! It is helping p… https://t.co/1ChjKk1QiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't make the world go round; love is what makes the ride worthwhile. - Elizabeth Barrett Browning #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have courage. It clears the way for things that need to be. - Laura Fitton #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise men speak because they have something to say; fools because they have to say something. - Plato  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Can Benefit from Pure CBD Products? Everyone! Our CBD products are a THC-free way to get CBD into your diet. &gt;… https://t.co/JeZL96PJCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laptop Lifestyle is almost here! Take a peek here &gt;https://t.co/19kwPbbNTm&lt; Meet my Jeff Lerner, as shared with by… https://t.co/bMgfc1ZtMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you treat yourself sets the standard for how others will treat you. - Steve Maraboli #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to a podcast about Cannabinoids &gt;https://t.co/EtX4N9ZGDW&lt; An interview with Dr. Stuart Titus. #cbd #hemp… https://t.co/QSVUwfLp0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard of the Endocannabinoid System in your body? Check it out here &gt;&gt;https://t.co/qjmleDMyjw&lt;&lt; It is fasc… https://t.co/5dpobU1EKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in CBD? I have seen many testimonies about how CBD has helped people with their health! First look=&gt;… https://t.co/veZMWZu5rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most practical, beautiful, workable philosophy in the
world won't work - if you won’t"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tre amici this morning! 

#racoon #friends #family #wildlife #winter @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/UvYLupTDkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three raccoons came for a visit today! A serendipitous moment this morning!

#serendipity… https://t.co/vj5uF2tQ57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @recurpost @hotshower @DebraDebramitch @jheltz27 via https://t.co/g9O0oSPjeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is devoid of the power to forgive is devoid of the
power to love."
- Martin Luther King #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look for ideas to confirm your thinking, rather look for trends that will disrupt your thinking. - Rich Simmonds #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @chomper_ebooks @badsmellingbot @Mindinfusions @MariusIluca via https://t.co/g9O0oSPjeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening, not imitation, may be the sincerest form of flattery. - Dr. Joyce Brothers #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success without honor is an unseasoned dish; it will satisfy
your hunger, but it won't taste good."
- Joe Paterno #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know your why? I believe it is an important first step in your business venture! My latest blog &gt;… https://t.co/PJu4IJACWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may be asking yourself, "Self what is CBD?" Well here is a great article about:https://t.co/QNkOxJBeFC #CBD… https://t.co/vGQvZeAXAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A webinar on a quick product training on our 3 hemp oil supplement categories- Premium Hemp Oil, Pure CBD and Reviv… https://t.co/ZWbEJOYZo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First we form habits, then they form us. Conquer your bad
habits or they will conquer you."
- Rob Gilbert #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Greatness is a road leading towards the unknown."
- Charles de Gaulle #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none. - Shakespeare #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything from your past does not belong in your present. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We launch tomorrow, wow I may not sleep tonight! Check out what me and @AdamChandler will be starting tomorrow &gt;&gt;… https://t.co/wE1PD7I8Eb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Big dreams create the magic that stir men's souls to
greatness."
- Bill McCartney #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever felt like a kid on Christmas Eve, excited for the next day to come. Well that is how I am about this… https://t.co/DHs6siC1jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How he paid off 400K worth of debt in only his first year online! This is a message from a good friend. My blog &gt;&gt;… https://t.co/veTFRe2dn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard the saying: "Don't judge a book by it's cover". Well I did with this one, not… https://t.co/pWeHHRer9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went on a bit of a rant about CBD in my latest blog! &gt;https://t.co/jIsSBObF45&lt; Read with an open mind! #cbd… https://t.co/FslnvWOB70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big launch tomorrow! Do you want to take a look at what me and #AdamChandler are up to? &gt;&gt;https://t.co/ssK9vrF4JU&lt;&lt;… https://t.co/bt9j5LNMfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Marketing Leads Generation Platform &gt;&gt; https://t.co/TqyEyGqPJe&lt;&lt; #networking #mlm #teambuilding #workfromhome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom begins with owning your flaws and disowning your fears. - Umair Hague #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of success is constancy of purpose."
- Benjamin Disraeli #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The miracle is this, the more we share, the more we have. - Leonard Nimoy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others. - Gandhi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The soil says, "Don’t bring me your need. Bring me your
seed."
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flash Sale on Our Favorite Value Packs Running Now in the Kannaway Store! Take a look right here &gt;&gt;https://t.co/H3KxCXksqF&lt;&lt; #hemp #hempoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow awesome article about THC free CBD! &gt; https://t.co/JgdAm1Rb5e&lt; The stigma needs to go! #RSHO #hemp PM me for mo… https://t.co/xcjySuN8aU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The athlete who says that something cannot be done should
never interrupt the one who is doing it."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13
"Leadership is the challenge to be something more than
average”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving is important. Thriving is elegant. - Maya Angelou #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is much easier kept than recovered. - Thomas Paine #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you share a good idea long enough, it will eventually fall
on good people"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LDI is like a steaming locomotive! We haven’t even fully left the station yet &amp; already paid out $60K in commission… https://t.co/Sj3fTLf55N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey all meet Adam Chandler in my latest blog. I am honored to be on his front line of our new launch! &gt;&gt;… https://t.co/EbzTzMGDGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @randyschroeder in a Facebook Live training event tonight! More details in my latest blog &gt;… https://t.co/kYrgOOnAfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just uploaded “Untitled” to #Vimeo: https://t.co/fpIBAoC6BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious. - Albert Einstein #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream big dreams! Imagine that you have no limitations,
and then decide what's right before you decide what's
possible"
- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not always tell you how they feel about you, but they will always show you. Pay attention. - Kim Garst #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not anticipate trouble or worry about what may never
happen. Keep in the sunlight."
- Benjamin Franklin #johnbdeleo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>