<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanJAQuinn @I_stand_for  particular social group or political opinion. Don't see anything about financial status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanJAQuinn @I_stand_for  a well-founded fear  of being persecuted because of their:racereligionnationalitymembership of a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanJAQuinn @I_stand_for a refugee is a person who is outside their own  country and is unable or unwilling to return due to a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanJAQuinn @I_stand_for you appear to be confusing poor people with refugees. Though if they spend all money to get out often poor now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanJAQuinn @I_stand_for I'm sorry but does having money prevent your house from being bombed? Or your family seized and tortured?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MG177 @I_stand_for so you admit you and lnp are xenophobic people with no empathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happy_dingo @I_stand_for they haven't , we just don't get told about them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogMofo @I_stand_for seeking asylum is not fucking illegal no matter how they come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @KellyannePolls so she's claiming to be incompetent rather than malicious. My bet is both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teasleyj @Jimryan015 no, because her life was saved he parents will praise the American doctors that did it. This is how you make friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arcticz28 @Slate after all what has knowing stuff ever got you except tv, internet, improved agriculture, wifi, gps.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Omnibus101 @Slate look, just because you don't have the math to understand the physics is no reason to disparage those who do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@desponder @ApeFroBoogie @Slate would you travel somewhere you didn't feel safe if you didn't have to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JefferyMay13 @AidanKingVT @billygendell @AjitPaiFCC @washingtonpost what the libraries that are now closed or being closed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CbolttttLeibold @MrChuckD such as? What is it exactly that you want to happen apart from 1% getting richer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamSykesSwears Given that he doesn't *really* seem to be enjoying his presidency, perhaps he's in the wrong job and should retire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paleocinema you have been doing non English movies. Did you ever see Vidocq?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealsirge @DaemonAAc @rachelheldevans to increase the ability to live in clean and healthy world, to make life fairer for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealsirge @DaemonAAc @rachelheldevans the reason for rules and laws is to optimise survival and happiness of communities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrblutoski @palmerstevej @Slate perhaps the idea of an equal relationship never crossed your mind. I wonder why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaRealNews @Slate are you talking about iran's own money that was returned to them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesternInsurgnt @donaltjrump @Slate @andreastonez how do you know? He won't release tax returns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scott_salzberg @chuckmcatee @beecat911_moore @GeorgeTakei so why is he stuffing it up so monumentally?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scott_salzberg @chuckmcatee @beecat911_moore @GeorgeTakei obvious typo for good. Though reviews of his restaurants bad too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wheels3314john @bandmanli @eNTyDF @LexnSydney @Nic133 @GeorgeTakei and no tax returns so can't tell how much they are in hock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans oh fuck I'm not wasting anymore time on ignorant douchebag with 2 followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans unique potential. Not same as being independent human being. An acorn is not an oak tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans so you would not be unhappy if someone illegally forced you to be a blood filter for someone else 4 months?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans dipshit men of all faiths and not kidnap children to get back at ex-partners who have defied them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans I was not if you remember that far back arguing for mandatory burqa wearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans oh I see argument by anecdote. White Trump supporter killed 6 adult Muslims in Canada. Bad ppl exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans so can long sleeved jumpers and skirts/pants. Abusers know where to leave bruises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans oh fuck you. Abortion is a woman choosing for whatever reason not to bear a foetus to term. Nothing pagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParszywyZyd @cbcnewsbc a shooting by a Trump fan yes. And choosing not to go where they feel not safe is their business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorKarl in any case enough mass to be significant can't just 'appear' out of nowhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fuller_Si @DoctorKarl mass increases towards infinity as goes towards c, why impossible for particles with rest mass to reach c.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans banning them would be just as much deprivation of choice as mandating them. Best would be for it to be choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans perhaps you should stop associating an article of women's clothing with that sort of thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans human sacrifice is illegal because murder is illegal. Acts can be illegal. Beliefs not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @rachelheldevans I am offended by antiabortion laws, dominionists and having 'under god' on currency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonKnaeble @YaYaCass @rachelheldevans I think Jon maybe doesn't realise prior tweet was already talking about Christians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealsirge @DaemonAAc @rachelheldevans there are many reasons to do good for others without authority figure dictating it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@margare79163346 @Joannechocolat 'S math sin !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneMoore1987 @Milothicc @CouldntBRighter ah so the USA doesn't have to improve itself until *everybody* else has. So much 4 world leaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joannechocolat @old_pyjamas lots of keyboards make it easier now. Less common from lead type because of space limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyDangerOz truly the temptation can be strong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real @danharmon at least the attempt should be made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real @danharmon the opinion here being that all people should be treated equally. False equivalency they are not =bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InnerPartisan @SallyStrange I must admit, I still haven't got around to finding out who George Soros is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catpyre @Rory__Walker @amos_true @scottsurette @meakoopa unfortunately it may be only thing they understand given their actions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I'm in cargo pants and a t-shirt #dresslikeawoman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po But I've got stuff to do, so going to give up on arguing with someone wilfully ignorant. Bye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po Why just about every other developed country has health care for all citizens, of better quality, and for less cost per capita.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po Not currently. But it should be. Fundamental human needs work better when dealt with by institution NOT focussed on profit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po @gofundme Oh, because EVERYONE has rich friends who can contribute money for health care? Why not just have single payer, saves time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delNick54 @LudwigTheJust @LauraJSilverman @arthur_affect So nothing he says means anything. So why did you vote for him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hood_Biologist Isn't it interesting that the same people who value women only for their appearance also don't like them charging for access]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA and no snowflakes here. They don't stand the 40°C plus days. But can see you're stuck so bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA because of all the articles he's posted on Breibart showing that. Being a wife beater also bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA I respect kangaroos as I would any creature mostly made of muscle that can disembowel u in secs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA well Bannon is. You I don't know about. But so far not impressed .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA making him the terrorist in my eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA because at the moment Bannon scares me more and is more dangerous than any refugee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA not internal threat from white nationalists basically staging coup on your country Glad not mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA I notice you *didn't* answer my question. I'll take that as a 'I only care about external threat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA does that include the white supremacists or do you only fight PoC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA and in this country we don't do either. In fact haven't most bombings in USA been domestic ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotPride80 @LibyaLiberty @YOSOYCORDOVA certainly no more likely to shoot anyone than average USA citizen probably less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodfreyOfBoulli @dernjg @LibyaLiberty you have asserted without evidence, that is not showing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobinAtlanta @paulkrugman actually I saw many liberals criticising some of Obamas policies. Based on whether policies were bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@t_raf29 @paulkrugman @nytimes is that all you know how to say? Must be bot. Not worth seeing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@partythree @paulkrugman @nytimes if you think the council had any tempering effect on trump and cronies I have bridge to sell you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobinAtlanta @paulkrugman isn't that free speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajplus @toriKh well obviously yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foucault_45 might as well leave me out, got tired of arguing with bad faith deplorable and muted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po system works better if more people get to pay in, spreads the load, reduces bankruptcies. If you got really sick, wld you be bankrupt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po if you don't actually understand that a healthy populace is more productive and cheaper long term.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po so what happens when you or someone you love (if you love anyone) and you can't get health care bc no company will give insurance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Octalthorpe @nkjemisin unless you're a lefty/liberal protestor in which case they go "la-la-la- can't hear you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 and the idea that killing someone unarmed is self defence is one of the saddest things. But predictable. Goodbye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po he's already acting in that way, regulations against polluting water near coal mines - going. ACA - repealing. Says will invade Mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 ok, I'll agree the destruction of property was bad if you agree Milo's supporter shooting a peaceful protester was bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 in which case the antifascists are named wrong and are probably anarchists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bombonattim @jonathanweisman was government arresting him for speech? No? Then no violation of free speech. He is not owed a platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 and to be honest I only see them being talked about by RW people so never seen any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po @MilaTequila10 @a_free_america @SheWhoVotes lack of medical care, pollution in air or water, drafted for a war he starts, all possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po @MilaTequila10 @a_free_america @SheWhoVotes I don't know who you are so I don't know which way you're going to suffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 give him time. He's only getting started. He's already moving faster than Hitler did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkieOG420 @Karnythia @SabrinaM_ agree property damage not good but his supporter shot someone which is worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a_free_america sorry, I think I got confused about who I was replying to. Meant to indicate I can tweet about Cheetos bc he affects world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po @MilaTequila10 @a_free_america @SheWhoVotes or to point out that you are going to suffer. He just hasn't got to you or yours yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlososuna86 @GooieGreen @skyboundpilot11 so you're admitting trump is a fascist? Otherwise why would antifa be against?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkieOG420 @Karnythia @SabrinaM_ if government not arresting him not being censored. He is not owed a platform any more than anyone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZippyYeti @Karnythia @fatneckbeardguy no it was his fan earlier (day spencer got punched) that shot an unarmed peaceful protestor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heather_never @wilw well I hope no one with a gun has a psychotic attack near you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryudo9 @wilw I think they are making it easier for people with mental illness to buy guns not harder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@16po @MilaTequila10 @a_free_america @SheWhoVotes because unless USA tiny he affects whole world so I have right to complain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pieballs @FarrellLawCA @AllenFrancesMD does he suffer from narcissistic tendencies himself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davethebinman @DoctorKarl increased heat trapping but not visible light scattering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davethebinman @DoctorKarl the scattering isn't primarily caused by CO2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>