<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely epic. Sporting contests don't come much better than this #FedererNadal #AusOpen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here I was thinking we were in 2017. Obviously forgot to put my clock back 30 years last night.

 https://t.co/WoOXbEnwVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shame, but it's felt that way for the past couple of years. https://t.co/Z4t9OFbk4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality start to 2017 with a lovely drop of @TwoPaddocks https://t.co/SFtoOW9DTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really are beautiful New Zealand #aorakimountcook #lakepukaki https://t.co/0qTESLmhU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resignations in NZ are just like buses. Two come along at once #merrick #key]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nice aftershock to liven up a Sunday afternoon! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sevens from Heaven. Wonderful.

https://t.co/RE2dK1OMCu via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knowlesie Welcome! Last night's  was much more violent shaking so you've had a nice gentle introduction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welly has the wobbles again. Biggest aftershock since last night #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaLStoney That should have read Hamner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And another one! Long night ahead. Hope those in Hamer / Christchurch are ok #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's got the adrenalin flowing. Biggest shake I've felt in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dread to think what state the world - let alone America - is going to be in in four years' time. #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnificent Ireland. What a Test. What a huge sporting week in Chicago! #IREvNZL #Chicago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice of Wellington to break out the fireworks to celebrate @A_Dura22 #250 and Vince Lia #200 #WELvNEW https://t.co/gyqPgTzDWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithQuinn88 @fijirugby Absolutely. A proper heart-warmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a brilliant watch about Jerry Tuwai and @fijirugby Can't recommend it highly enough.  #gold https://t.co/MOJE1MNhWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following on from Cheika, here's @nzheraldrugby on Gatland clowning around.
 https://t.co/UicX4ueJxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all interviews are done face to face. What happens when recording fails? https://t.co/LqAnFlhrh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad you enjoyed it Scotty   @sumostevenson @nytimes @WgtnRugby @Prop3baumann @MartyVeale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if Wayne Barnes has  just been added to the list of northern hemisphere referees Michael Cheika doesn't like #yellow #AUSvARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sense All Blacks can go up another gear in the second half, wonder if the Boks can #NZLvRSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Blacks really are just light years ahead of other teams at the moment. They flick the switch and it's game over #NZLvARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking half of rugby. All Blacks being put under real pressure. Some great footwork and offloading from Pumas #NZLvARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titch retires. 4 Com Games golds, 12 World Series titles, 2 7s World Cups and helping 40-odd players become All Blacks. An incredible career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyLiebenberg @AllBlacks @qantaswallabies 
Springboks and Pumas will certainly fancy their chances against the Aussies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bledisloe wrapped up for another year by @AllBlacks. Had to work a bit harder tonight but too much class for  @qantaswallabies #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show time! https://t.co/JBdz4Bn6o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farah utterly brilliant. An outstanding run by the champion #Gold #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big news out of Glasgow. Dave Rennie will be the Warriors coach from 2017/18. https://t.co/S5f6FF4x3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was awesome from Mo Farah. What an incredible race #Rio2016 #Gold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GBR thoroughly outplayed in the final but worthy #Silver medalists. Beat some very good teams to get to final #Rio2016 #Rugby7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An absolute masterclass from #FIJ Just brilliant to see @benjaminryan and @fijirugby win the #Gold #Rugby7s #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ My broadband internet is down. Are you having system-wide problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnPhoenixFC's new centre-back Marco Rossi https://t.co/nmx7fduakq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hurricanesrugby prove defence wins championships. Amazing effort not to concede a single try in the play-offs. #HURvLIO #champs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's guide on 'How not to run a major sporting event' comes to you courtesy of the IOC. Updates available over the next 2 weeks #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's a second successive home Super Rugby final for the Hurricanes. Will it finally be their year? #HURvCHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Lowe's error sums up Chiefs' night really. #HURvCHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barrett has surely earned himself the All Blacks No.10 jersey for the Bledisloe Cup. Cruden has been very quiet. #HURvCHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing Rennie's HT message to the Chiefs will be "take the points on offer". Boyd's is likely to be "more of the same boys" #HURvCHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 It took me more than an hour, scanners were shut and latecomers got priority! That's plain wrong. https://t.co/XeRZikprig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people who give themselves plenty of time to clear security shouldn't suffer because of your poor system. 1/2 https://t.co/XeRZikprig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manairport Any reason half the security scanners aren't being used when it's so busy in T1. And latecomers keep getting priority!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manairport What an absolute shambles at security. Been here nearly an hour and still waiting to go through while latecomers get priority!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussies have a bit to do before they face the All Blacks in the Bledisloe. Looked much better with Toomua at 12 #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking series. Lot to like about this England side already, but plenty more to come from them. #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots to like in that 1st half. England missing Haskell till Itoje switched to the flank. Toomua made a big difference for Aussies #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Wales keep playing the expansive style they've shown this series. Reckon Liam Williams will be back in NZ as a Lion next year #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too much poor kicking from a very tired-looking Wales side tonight. Paid the price with Dagg, Barrett and B Smith carving it up. #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong finish from Wales, but four tries in 14 minutes shows the class / relentlessness of the All Blacks. FT 36-22 #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big score for Wales on the stroke of HT. All Blacks won't be happy about that. 10-10. Big second half to come #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminryan Hi Ben. Would you mind giving me a follow please so I can DM you re Olympics. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be a ripper series #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a great win for England but Wallabies gave them a big helping hand with the penalties they coughed up. #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haskell has been a human missile tonight and has rarely missed his target #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wallabies indiscipline killed them in that first half. Farrell made them pay. Itoje been impressive #AUSvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big final 20 mins from ABs. Bench did its job. Great to see Wales play with such ambition. Roll on Wellington #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st half over in the blink of an eye. Liam Williams excellent. Wales deserve HT 18-15 lead #NZLvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling comment from Steve Hansen - we're not rebuilding we're re-establishing #AllBlacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jarryd Hayne in Fiji 7s squad for London

 https://t.co/phcAgDMzLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible story

 https://t.co/ixmVtuvn4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goucsb @ProRugbyUSA @nytimes  
Thanks. Glad you liked it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianDennison and @TwoPaddocks absolutely superb in Hunt for the @wilderpeople. A brilliant movie #haiku #gangsta #skuxlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting comments on Sam Burgess too.

 https://t.co/a25g6750jt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Cup failure hasn't scarred Stuart Lancaster too much. He is keen on a Super Rugby coaching job.
https://t.co/GdAWYClR4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise @Siggy2010 spilt some blood for @WgtnPhoenixFC today. Competitive to the end. Enjoy your retirement. #WELvWSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a long time between drinks but England finally have another Grand Slam. #FRAvENG #grandslam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive from the Brumbies. Hurricanes will struggle to put a highlight reel together but plenty for the 'work-ons' video #BRUvHUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think the ref has left his yellow card in his changing room #BRUvHUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see @A_Dura22 get a win in his 200th game #WELvMCY #ALeague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How cricket is helping Rwanda heal.  This really is well worth a read. Beautifully written by @NHoultCricket https://t.co/qVVFoiYAHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's fair to say New Zealand Football has not had the best 12 months. The eligibility scandal and now Jones' botched transfer. #shambles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hopdaddy27 @USASevensRugby @nytimes @Carlin_Isles  Sadly I won't be coming to Las Vegas. Should be a great tournament though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mab8663Panto It will be a GB team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hurricanes also have some injury worries two weeks out from the start of Super Rugby. Not sure how serious but disruptive all the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricanes have a bit of work to do before they meet the Brumbies in round one. Lost 40-12 to the Blues in a hot Eketahuna #summerrugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't envy the players having to play in this heat. #summerrugby #hurricanes #blues https://t.co/6KvUUchZAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food for thought.

https://t.co/PZLOnSyBvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well worth a read.

The Making of Eddie Jones https://t.co/8TmaGBI7Ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Mitchell is the new head coach of USA Eagles. The ex-All Blacks coach has signed a 4-year deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas. ðŸŽ…ðŸ» Wishing you a fun-filled festive season with family and friends. Cheers! https://t.co/rqDo4Zudiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing young lad.     BBC Sport - Sports Personality: Bailey Matthews wins the Helen Rollason award https://t.co/HC1QRRoj8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina Super Rugby team Los Jaguares confirm Raul Perez as coach, Agustin Creevy as captain. Felipe Contepomi one of 3 assistant coaches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another city, another code. Catching my first NBA game #bostonceltics https://t.co/yOXeMJrWrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An impressive set of numbers to end with, but Richie McCaw was so much more than that. A true icon of the game https://t.co/OhfexPpBfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such sad news. New Zealand, rugby, and the sporting world in general, has lost a legend #RIPJonah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying a different brand of football today #Redskins https://t.co/OzFxp61dak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllBlacks deserved champions. Carter was a class above. #RWC2015 #RWCFinal2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are some impressive numbers.
 https://t.co/FWrHf0MJ9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to take something special to beat these All Blacks. The French certainly didn't have it, and haven't for a while #RWC2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotjane Absolutely. It's had everything. Power, pace and precision. Cardiff will be lively tonight! #RWC2015 #NZvFRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Blacks have flicked the switch. Some sublime skills and finishing in the first half. Picamoles has been France's best by far #RWC15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia look in ominous form. Cheika has got them humming. #ENGvAUS #RWC2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England totally out-played and out-thought. 'Poopered' at the breakdown, smacked in the scrums and woeful on attack. World Cup over #RWC15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Western Mail's front page!  http://t.co/lEyBjUXP3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Blacks seriously underwhelming but hats off to Georgia, a sterling performance from them #NZLvGEO #RWC2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanWalthew @markscott82 Appreciate the interest. I'm not sure who made the decision. I'm contributing to RWC coverage, just not from UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A genius way to explain the new Super Rugby draw. Well played @Hurricanesrugby ðŸ‘https://t.co/wQ6PDy1bgL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>