<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcbbags He wasn't very happy about it! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llymlrs @emmablackery https://t.co/uaXYXpvZwP This is my literal favourite ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to work out how I can fund a degree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcbbags I went for a picnic date once and my dog ate his sandwich ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joy can be shared with others, but grief can only be endured alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cox_tom Your tweets this evening are my favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhiannonPeaches Oh! I'm not sure. I remember walking passed it thinking "oh that's moved" but never been in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhiannonPeaches It's where miss selfridge used to be! Further up ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llymlrs @EvanEdinger That death glare that A is giving you though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all bad people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had the most obnoxious bath ever. Bath bombs and bubbles. Nice mid-week pick me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDoughtyMP well done. Proud of you for standing up for what you believe in and your constituents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've surprised myself so much over the last month, in the best way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin This looks so good! Delicious/10?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not bad for a Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling so much more content than I have in a while. Being kinder to myself and giving myself more credit for the good things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhiandavey90 No no. The breasts are fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhiandavey90 It wasn't what you did, it was the way you did it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know when you feel so tired it makes you feel nauseous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fridays are such long days for me at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really need to get out of bed. But I can't. Send help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin You look cute as hell though girl! ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forever being disappointed by people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that really matters about humans is their minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonoread that was just so awful. I actually cried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday was a bit crap, but I'm ready to boss the shit out of today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FallenShadows82 I always find this kinda thing weird because I live in Cardiff and buses won't give change here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a good game tonight! @steelershockey win in Cardiff! Yasss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selfie. The first time I've worn make up for ages. https://t.co/6o3usCqJTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jack_TheJobber #content #cutethough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SumoScott Really well thanks! How're you getting on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SumoScott Happy birthday! ðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhiandavey90 You the best kid! My favourite ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally don't know what I would do without @rhiandavey90 and her pep talks. ðŸ’œ https://t.co/RL38RD8jJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up for my NUS card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The suffocating constancy of my own self, that numb and desperate company."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things change and friends leave. Life doesn't stop for anybody."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Makebelieve_ "But as with everything in life, I get to assign meaning."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Like a dandelion up through the pavement, I persist. Anyway. Still. Despite."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also is #cumberbae a thing?! I want it to be a thing. #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fucking Sherlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sineadl69 I miss you too! Still adjusting to life without young members! How is everything with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin I've obviously been doing conferences wrong! Although I did turn someone down at one young members thing...!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin After the recent sucker punch to my feelings I'm giving dating one final chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin It's like my fifth picture in, so 92% of the tinder population won't even see it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin @jeremycorbyn haha! No. You're in the middle ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @jeremycorbyn actively assists with your love life... https://t.co/IYkPq1rrIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life can get so lonely sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've started using my Goodreads account properly again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hi anxious chest pains, it's been a while...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@llymlrs I'm excited! Your moving vlogs are when I subscribed and they just gave me life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngreen That's all anyone can ask of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Forever21 Is there any way you can find an order via my address? I think I entered email incorrectly at checkout ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin I literally had to ram it in there because I didn't have a bigger one ðŸ™Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin Yasss! Glad it got there safely! Sorry about the awful wrapping!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually wearing gloves at my desk today because it's so cold and selfish people keep setting the air to cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've literally only just discovered The 1975. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re reading conversations too though. Which is not awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re watching Black Mirror and it is just so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sound of rain on the window, though. It helps get the thoughts in order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one more day to get through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin if only I were joking! If only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin His friend added me on Facebook to see if we could maybe "chat and hang out". I was livid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Witness For The Prosecution on iplayer is so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin That's not even the end of the story. It gets so much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin He's ignored my previous messages though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin Damn girl! Looks like I'm going to have to write you an angsty letter about how shit my life is! Enjoy though! ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awful sex stories on the adult nerdfighters thread is giving me life right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Makebelieve_ Would it be acceptable to ask for it back?! I love that book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Makebelieve_ I don't know if I'm more upset with him or about the book. I've had it since I was eighteen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin When are you back?! I really need some Kim time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out he was just pretending... #humiliated #tinder #onlinedatingisshit https://t.co/Vqf9NbeK1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin one of the worst wrapped parcels ever is on its way to you! ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhiandavey90 Wow. That's some doing though. You have to admire the level of skill involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't punch anyone in the face. Don't punch anyone in the face. Don't punch anyone in the face. Say it with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having to resist the urge to leave passive aggressive notes everywhere, in work today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I do these days is roll my eyes at life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in serious need of a holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's so much tv that I actually want to watch on at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I go on too many dates but I can't make them stay..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for The Undateables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not ready to be back in work tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things never change...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watching the new Sherlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went on a first date the other day. I gave him "dogs" by Elliott Erwitt. Luckily he loved it. Or at least pretended to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017. The year I only make time for the ones who make time for me. Simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 feels the most like a new start ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin 2013 is the first Kim I met. I was a massive fan ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin But Kim's 2013-2016 have been great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying up until 2am was not the best idea I've ever had...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Paul &amp; Mary wake up in bed together on #gbboxmas and all your fan girl dreams come true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steelers is trending and I genuinely thought it was about @steelershockey !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitzyG28 Merry Christmas to you and your family!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cox_tom He was so beautiful ðŸ’œðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had to pause the wrapping because I've run out of sellotape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Makebelieve_ It's too early to have a beer though, isn't it?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas films and wrapping presents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart just feels so full today. There's so many lovely people in my life ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimorwin You'll be alright pet! Let me know your plans! One day I'm going to work myself up to actually driving up to you! One day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone finds my will to live please return it to me.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>