<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin I have supper every night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EE yes please who do I contact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EE it said problems yesterday would be fixed in 16 hrs but it's still says this?? And I still have no network]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EE it says there's problems in my area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EE I have no service all afternoon in Cardiff CF5 area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a morning run in sunny Lisbon! https://t.co/mXNEXikuDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jej6150 oh yes and got a champagne surprise! Annabel was looking gorgeous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bearshead thankyou so much for the champagne! ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're taking up running have your posture checked first! #injuryprevention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankyou for all your support in making my first year as Virginia Williams physiotherapy a success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NenDavies are you watching through a Bt box?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diverap2 and a good physio!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clinic is busy in the run up to Christmas! Have a pain free one by booking early!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clinic is open until 23 rd December!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessGlynne  and thankyou Giles for the tickets !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessGlynne great Cardiff concert last night! Thankyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get set it's the missing final episode!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin say hi to my brother!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales where's your creativity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejongriff thankyou ! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good night for @StFagansCricket https://t.co/ikHLbSTC9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clinic is now registered with vitality health as well as BUPA and Nuffield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be wet outside but the clinic is warm and dry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyoleary1 well done I hear that course is really tough! Congratulations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin indeed getting on my nerves now !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 firework displays going on around my house! I feel under siege!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Andy Murray world number 1!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember xrays won't help diagnose back pain but a physiotherapist WILL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people will do anything to avoid strictly! @imw60 https://t.co/Nb7qaxHZMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Poor Posture Causing Your Back Pain? This is a big cause of low back pain! https://t.co/L0LhOyewJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feet up and Ryder cup for the night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bearshead when's the party so I can try it out!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowds getting on my nerves already in the Ryder cup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Cardiff half marathon week! Rest those legs !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7xWM7jMjnP @CantonSeals I am a local physiotherapy clinic and I offer good discounts to sports Clubs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - 'No proof' fitness trackers promote weight loss https://t.co/ixTgndjSK3  But at least people are trying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dshglam20 ask your boss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you suffer from neck or back pain at work? Ask for a work station assessment to improve your POSTURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrapTri Physiotherapy discounts for club members! Virginia williams Physiotherapy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyoleary1 is there a Luke Jackson out there with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahbell1983 wow congratulations both!! â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 happy st fagans boys after their win today! https://t.co/wnmzC4R6nK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zacs rugby team Llandaff U10's looking for a sponsor for some shirts! Only Â£250 for a sleeve logo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandyallen3 you Teachers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cardiff_Chiro love the expression !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Williams Physiotherapy accepts referrals from BUPA and Nuffield health. Appointments available Monday to Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Golfers have unusual hips, study suggests https://t.co/kuMpcstPRq    Something for physios to be aware when examining golfers .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StFagansCricket zacs so tired he's gone back to bed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guvnorcousty watching the hockey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin no I want that job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandyallen3 love it there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops think Fiji have this oneðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeparkerjames shame about the result!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Short, Top tips to get fit at your desk https://t.co/B3DWO1V3cy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Rio is inspiring you get out there and get exercising ! #cycling #diving #physiosupportteam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to tonight ! Good luck @GlamCricket @Jacques_Rudolph @MarkWallace18 ! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJShapewell no I don't so would be good to refer people to you for massage . Inbox me your number!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJShapewell thankyou that would be great I'm in llandaff north!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethanAmyJames and we need ideas from you ðŸŽ‚ðŸ’„ðŸ‘ ðŸ”’ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWallace18 @Jacques_Rudolph @CAIngram41 looking forward to the 11th ! ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling after the climb https://t.co/OwIi9wGLDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hubby doing well on the climbing! https://t.co/rKGZC9OZXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not often speechless but Boris?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jongrifff we never saw that coming !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic Andy Murray !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin @imw60 @abbey_glass bullet proof apparently !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PonthirHoggy @CardiffValeCric @gwentcricket @CardiffCC teas are prepared by parents  and never a previous complaint!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PonthirHoggy @CardiffValeCric @gwentcricket @CardiffCC teas are prepared  for players umpires and coaches . https://t.co/tzolmAUbZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Julieyapp2 i did that eventually ']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray or wales ? Who to watch !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't be bad just been given free hospitality !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow wales that's brilliant !ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin exactly boring get on with itðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin why are they talking about England in the middle of the wales game! I'm English but this is nuts. We are out get a grip ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fulthorpe still younger than me !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandyallen3 nasty poor you ! Feet up for the footie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandyallen3 need a Physio ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fulthorpe wow have fun Abby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethanAmyJames have a great holiday!âœˆï¸ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpencerVignes enjoyed coco on centre just now !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpencerVignes how's it going ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin we are always like this overpaid and under achievers ! Clueless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sun is out and Wimbledon starts today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy now leavers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefatkin apparently the leavers feel more British!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jongrifff zac is worried he said Farage is mad! 51% of us are as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jongrifff too small minded I'm afraid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad that the scots feel more European than British]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick Walsh's In memory of Patrick Walsh on BT MyDonate https://t.co/Z6ucucMwKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethanAmyJames what a great day for you !! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NenDavies looks peaceful !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petermeades I'll be round later!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carinawrites @CaroWild happy to help I'm based in llandaff north . https://t.co/skYCzZvPyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StFagansCricket @TennisCardiff Discounts for club members at Virginia Williams Physiotherapy Clinic !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartfelt tributes paid to firefighter who died this weekend - Wales Online So very sad he was just a lovely man https://t.co/k1WxL6OPIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TennisCardiff A tight loss today but some great tennis and a few 3 setters! Well done all. https://t.co/cIohHmLTa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulSussex2 bad behaviour whatever it was for no player should heckle the ref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandyallen3 never mind it's England B don't worry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clinic is finally BUPA and Nuffield Health registered! @TennisCardiff @StFagansCricket @Jej6150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wales velothon is nearly here! Make sure you stretch your back before and after the ride!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>