<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris @GamejunkieNZ @agentK I stopped contributing regularly aaaaaaaages ago. Last thing was Aug 2015: https://t.co/hXUIdryzSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBurman I would die. It's 19.4 in Wellington and my air con is on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hi, I'm here to get [giant heavy thing/couch/fridge/aircraft]. Hope it fits in my car." -every @TradeMe buyer arriving solo in Honda Civic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careful on Happy Valley Rd this morn #Wellington. Duck w 6-8 ducklings doing multiple rd Xings. So far all drivers respecting space. #cuteas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack let me see your re-placed hips SWING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll never see me happier than on a summer's day with a southerly looming. Come at me. https://t.co/EzdxSIjjJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was a bit of an SNL fan before, but Poehler's book shows the real graft in sketches. Even more appreciation for seeing the creative process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the news re Key's distinguished career and the hallowed nod to English, Bill gets referred to by @DomPost as a "craggy Dipton farmer."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien I never did catch that sonofabitch Hylian Loach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate @Gimletmedia for ditching @MysteryShow but have to love them for Homecoming. First episode was great. Dammit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What the Hell Just Happened?” by @davepell https://t.co/lcRcWGPfSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajeevfilm why would you bungee your blanket to the front of your hog where it can get all full of bugs and stuff while you shred miles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The very best piece of writing about this wretched saga yet. https://t.co/oUzk0VKD31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best yet. This album is going to be amazing. https://t.co/Zu8I2KqHe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hells yeah. While I always lament the approach of the Kiwi summer, it's a cool time for bleak thinkpieces from the… https://t.co/btgJfdYUKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drawing a loooong bow for Halloween. They're called "lives". He's alive. Nice shot at playing the #context game tho… https://t.co/kY7w7ILSpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Raglan all the time. #raglanroast far outstrips any local brand. #badwellingtonian #coffee https://t.co/R7bE64EWGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@garyvee must have said "always make me look like a fighter/athlete emerging from the tunnel to do battle" Slick as https://t.co/cPnHQ7lgUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just made the #RedDeadRedemption2 trailer appointment viewing. Going to hold off watching until @_MarySylvia and I can Chromecast it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lame. Without @MysteryShow the @Gimletmedia empire is just @replyall. Shortsighted. Nothing else like it. Was going to become a member too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got to Hunt for the Wilderpeople. Rad movie; got bummed out reading about the Huia after though. #skuxlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spotify this is maddening! Pulsing dots of death but no videos. I watched chapter 1 on YouTube and now need the rest! Help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanKeoghNZ Black Mages is always a winner. But this (classical adjacent) piece of music is my absolute fave: https://t.co/8lEvkg5UDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajeevfilm @Wright_Now I can't believe you fell for that trap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, when did TV credits get so good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien I think the neighbours have the impression I was trying to take a photo into their living room just now. #zubat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien "tell me about US politics!" and "What bank is good!?" Who even are you anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now if you're not gonna be a dad then you've just been snapped hunting biscuits (opposite side of the aisle).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now @rajeevfilm @chrisjtse  Move to Norway is a cool name for a punk band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien likely to be my first ever launch day buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found new cure for common cold: American ads. All those polo shirts and sensible shoes and family fun. Makes me feel warm again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearthstone eating me alive. Should've amped up the irreverence, though. Too earnest. Characters, genre ripe for irreverence. Irreverence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohsarahrose I so get this. I. So. Get. This. Keep them coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien Rad. I will watch out for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien just finished listening to a superb @replyall podcast about it. "The Cathedral". If you're reviewing, could be good context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have already creatively named 11 kiosks and you are just so done naming kiosks. https://t.co/IMLk6KAxEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outwitted. Outplayed. Outlasted. You lose, 2015. https://t.co/tmjnxidV9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorbLund Alberta is saying hello.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Dictionary access upswing directly proportional to the cold March of time, so I can stay woke. The last thing I looked up was "woke".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Forget https://t.co/5mh7my4BgB via @imgur. RIP indeed. All I do is try to forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did Adobe's terribly vanilla tech "predictions" for 2016 make WaPo? (re Internet of Things) "Google will continue to see success". Um.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How did that goat get there?" @replyall with a genius recap of all their best bits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been holding on to this Windows95 disc for years. Favourite RTS ever. Bought the whole kit on @GoodOldGames for $15! https://t.co/kINXx17yKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you pause Blanka half way through a spin it looks like he's going through the worst break up ever. https://t.co/DGveGsANSM via @imgur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now yes. Smart. Lay that base of evidence down before Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjtse don't give up. Next week: rap battles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is not your oyster. You are the world's oyster. One in a long procession of oysters, being endlessly shucked. Think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SydneyAirport thanks for your response; http://t.co/xF0HEeVZpB timetable says no action in SYD tomorrow - is that right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SydneyAirport do you have info about actual delay time from yesterday &amp; this morning as a result of strike? Is 90 min accurate as reported?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On hold listening to DD's Loyal but with intermittent &amp; inexplicable &amp; utterly terrifying wailing like my phone has trapped a wayward spirit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now I think it's you who deserves a reward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now love that you didn't even back yourself to be successful. "Tries" to join.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, my sister swears this is a picture of her dogs. These are cats right? I guess I might also concede foxes. http://t.co/v5OAec00dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things no one tells you about building a house: literally everyone who exists/has existed/will ever exist tries to sell you a used heatpump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjtse and what a name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuminatorNZ that ceramics expert who is the happiest guy on earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I returned to Animal Crossing after, like, ages and this is what happened: http://t.co/8Zg9PxbsVd http://t.co/AhRBEcGyI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys: @MysteryShow so worth a listen. Also @replyall. Also "Juliet, Naked" by Nick Hornby is nearly as good as High Fidelity. #revelation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjtse spoiler alert for the one on the top of the pile: https://t.co/jPFJ5nH843]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ follow me and I'll DM my account number / ph number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Internet outage. Suspicious as I called re a relocate/new build hookup earlier in the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@vodafoneNZ this is a joke. 15 mins on hold to be told there is a special ex-Telstra team. 34 mins on hold since. http://t.co/ZE8rwbbtwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjtse that doesn't even look that bad. http://t.co/iq1mWUztnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic chess champion game from the early 90s. 72k memory. Pretty sweet  tech. http://t.co/fAlHAm5o6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going out at 12am following Good Friday for 4 hours seems desperate. Town is packed. #apartmentliving  #picofmydog http://t.co/XxpcqiHSto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ nope, gave up. Broadband started working again in wee smalls. Who do I talk to about mobile data rebate for 3 days hotspotting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Autumn you cold and beautiful sonofabitch. Here's a sunset on the 2nd to last day of summer to celebrate. http://t.co/aVGahNde0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kernston's Rubber Nipples has the same clout in #Pawnee that Peach Teats (calves love em) has in the Horowhenua/Manawatu. #ParksandRec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the good with the bad on the ferry today: great coffee; cabin smells like a woolshed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @nextdraft #saveahorse http://t.co/LMiYK14hoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite thing about Parks &amp; Rec is that Andy's band is called Mouse Rat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ a housing bubble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseM_Wallace looks delicious. Proves nothing. (But wow that really looks delicious).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseM_Wallace there is no button for "I don't believe that exists" so I just hit fav.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien your tweets are stupidly good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to play Majora's on the 3DS. Such a strange and dark game; loved the 64 version and have only heard good things about updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blasting Don't Fear the Reaper (while sitting in a suburban car wash in my Ford Focus).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@_MarySylvia *drops teaspoon in waste disposal* "I hate reaching in here to get stuff. I always think it's going to Final Destination me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country music has me wondering what county officials are doing with public funds in the US. Why are there so many unpaved roads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Molly Malone's closed, the owners of Kitty's and JJ Murphy's met on neutral ground did a jig of triumph, then glared at each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuminatorNZ blog schmog. Where are our grandchildren?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleigh_young I wish I'd had this cautionary tale when I tried to explain to my parents that cleaning my room was a waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleigh_young what is the answer is this on Kindle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leggetron Yea, son! Who can we get to pen the rap interlude?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leggetron "when I got the time and I got the money, Google won't find me the right pic of Ryan Gosling..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleigh_young I bought a $15.97 watermelon the other day but it's ok because I craved that mineral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No bites yet but who cares? #paekak http://t.co/dgSgpElN9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*moves furniture to make it difficult for Roomba to manoeuvre* - are you doing your part to quell the robot uprising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wright_Now do you do jokes? Bae is a good name for a b-boy posse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone out there score any good novelty tees this Christmas? Pobody's Nerfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseM_Wallace if they complain you have to give them a free taco it's the law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate: ol', ole (old). 'Uns (ones). But worst of all is Lil (little). I mean, come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a pheasant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yates Garden Guide starts off with a 7 page history of NZ gardening. #contextisking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any other Sons fans finding every scene more depressing than the last these days? Can't look away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leggetron I cannot tell you how much it means that you remember it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leggetron it's different from when you were a kid, man. Responsibilities. Other hobbies. And don't you just hurt all the time? I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christ_Monkey THAT'S BETWEEN ME AND THE RACK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got in lift and this was in there with its arms up like it was waiting for a hug. No one else in there. http://t.co/ZEFeXH8D0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verslibre @LouiseM_Wallace @chrisjtse now I can confidently update my LinkedIn profile. "Poet". Ha.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>