<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“Some guys feel the weight of a contract. Some guys actually get freed by not having to worry about a contract." https://t.co/LxUenOYCJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote about Marcus Johansson quietly having a strong season, freed by contract security for a change https://t.co/LxUenOYCJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NHL's compressed schedule has been a pain for many around the league this season. But it's benefitted Grubauer. https://t.co/9YmeO4CoqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericfingerhut why i've always been skeptical of how a pro team would do there. people have allegiances elsewhere when they get to norfolk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericfingerhut as someone who's lived in norfolk briefly, it's a varied fandom because of the navy presence there. lots of people moving in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin gets another golden stick. https://t.co/BNqX9iLXsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what an exit. https://t.co/5iWD7EBnaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Alex Ovechkin head on a stick was taped to the wall right beside Alex Ovechkin's locker room stall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenT6 so about that jinx? Oh, right, jinxes aren't real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lars, this team likes to pour it on, eh? Eller: “It’s definitely not something I’ve experienced before playing on any other teams."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I think everybody, once they’re on the ice, they think they can score a goal right now,” Lars Eller said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lars Eller on Caps: "It just speaks to how everybody wants more. We want more all of the time. You want to score another goal."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trotz joked that Johansson has "obviously" been lifting weights because he snapped his stick on that shot in the first period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philipp Grubauer said the new pants are like "skinny European jeans." Which he wears often. Didn't feel much of a difference in them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Williams against his old team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is already the most saves Grubauer has made in a game this season. 37 at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaCooper @helenenothelen @dougherty_jesse it was really just @alex_prewitt and I bobbing heads and playing an imaginary fiddle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmhopmayer might be a top five song for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenenothelen @dougherty_jesse psh, I'm the nicest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just jamming to some "Devil Went Down to Georgia" at Verizon Center.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two losses were both to the Blue Jackets. https://t.co/uPs5plZ6E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeccaH_JR the Kings fan base that follows me on twitter is my favorite. they're so nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps up, 4-0, after two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might be the best I've seen Grubauer play all season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that's a priority. https://t.co/xlmHcckyMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oshie goal. Water bottle. Caps up, 4-0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philipp Grubauer wasn't thrilled with switching to thinner pants halfway through the season. He might love them now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oshie for cross-checking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Caps look like they're playing video game hockey with all of the cheat codes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder: Brett Connolly was a really good signing for the Caps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connolly goal. His 10th of the season. Caps up, 3-0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martinez for hooking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering both teams played less than 24 hours ago, think this is a pretty entertaining game with good pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That snapped a seven-game goal drought for Marcus Johansson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps up, 2-0, after two periods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muneebalamcu against the blues. off the draw. second period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slowly, quietly Marcus Johansson is having a heckuva season. 16 goals and 17 assists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dowd for interference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grubauer has been sharp early on. Just made a pair of point-blank stops on Brown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johansson had a good look, and then his stick snapped in half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps' PK had a good day yesterday, limiting third-ranked Montreal PP to just two shots in three opportunities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delayed penalty on Caps/Winnik for goalie interference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third line nearly just scored again. Eller has 10 points in 13 games. That trio is feeling good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eller was all alone in front of Budaj for a while. https://t.co/G14e21FqZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's Eller's sixth goal in 13 games. He's feeling it finally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eller goal right in front. Caps up, 1-0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings stayed in the locker room for the ceremony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Williams shrugs on Ovi celebration video. "Pretty good."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give @dougherty_jesse a follow as he covers his last Kings game before joining Team WaPo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps starting their third line of Connolly-Eller-Burakovsky and Carlzner pair. https://t.co/WyhYN3sbNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Budaj goes for the Kings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grubauer leads the Caps out and will start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeccaH_JR in fairness, every team plays soccer there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T2Va haven't tried. Not a big snapchatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ovechkin heads everywhere. https://t.co/QPzXuFkux8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trotz said Kings' Drew Doughty has some "junkyard" in him. Has "bite" to his game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trotz said "a goalie" will play. Wouldn't commit to which one. Smart money is on Grubauer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg what is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always watching. https://t.co/Q8xRQLUk6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Capitals have returned Jakub Vrana to Hershey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swisschris19 nope. fourth line was good tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamVingan you're really on brand about all of this today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Braden Holtby's review of his new tight pants: https://t.co/8cJsWcnMdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sickunbelievabl it was funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sup, Nicklas? (Screenshot from @CSNCapitals video) https://t.co/M43mlCQCkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, and I made it to the Montreal airport with time to spare. #blessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bottom-six snipes put the Capitals up and a "muffin" from Backstrom kept them ahead in a 3-2 win at Bell Centre https://t.co/4m7zqRZFUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[btw, Beagle said his eyes were closed on his goal. "And then top shelf." Said it was a "pretty nice" shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holtby on pants: "Going post to post while down was tricky, mainly because they're new, I think."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarification on this: Holtby said the pants were "a little strange," not weird. https://t.co/AlNDP4DHZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holtby said he was the one to alert the officials of the hole in the boards. "I've never seen that before."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holtby joked that it was probably a Shea Weber shot that created the hole in the dasher board. (Believe it was actually Niskanen).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArshoffFred they did wear them in practices. but there hasn't been many practices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holtby said the new, thinner pants were "weird," but added that it could just be because they're new (as in not completely broken in).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstrom said Burakovsky and Beagle's goals were "snipes." "And a muffin by me," he added.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps win, 3-2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Holtby fellow is good, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habs have an empty net.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tight pants didn't keep Holtby from going into a split to stop that Galchenyuk shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how the game isn't tied, but it's not. Yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thadmoore @jdawsey1 @cmcampbell6 @StephenGarcia ha, we all know how I felt about it at the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps PK had a rough last game. Perfect tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burakovsky for high sticking. Caps clinging to a 3-2 lead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacioretty makes it 3-2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @barrysvrluga's column on the underrated Nicklas Backstrom https://t.co/MPMKv5yOie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstrom goal. Someone wrote a really good column about him recently. Caps up, 3-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radulov for hooking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps have twice as many shots as Habs through two periods. Canadiens have just 12. Feels like they'd have more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of two periods: Caps have a 2-1 lead over the Canadiens. Eller looked a bit jostled by that last shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenCarroll15 how interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandon__alter or it's just a typo. because i'm a human being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a stop by Hotlby on Radulov, who is clearly feeling it tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orpik for tripping. Caps going to a PK for a SECOND time this period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goaltender interference on Pacioretty. But before that, the Radulov celly was epic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radulov's goal immediately waved off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Eller gets a point against his former team. He started the whole sequence with a pass to Connolly on the breakout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shot by Andre Burakovsky. Wow. Caps up, 2-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until that penalty, Carlson was one of three NHLers with 40-plus games who hadn't taken a penalty. Johnny Gaudreau hasn't either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carlson for interference. AND THAT IS HIS FIRST PENALTY OF THE SEASON.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first period is over. Hot dog time. Teams are tied, 1-1.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>