<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sir_cornflake @HullCity asking for too much I would have thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydtidder @JessRoebuck end of summer I reckon top gun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessRoebuck @lloydtidder always got to follow it up with a cheeky smack of.the arse now though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder why I bother sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a guy https://t.co/w0O02QFMuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first son is going to be called Eldin #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uzzell01 totally agree! Feel like Liverpool are there for the taking at the minute too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobIves597 probably should have won it at the end, Markovic incredibly unlucky and Hernandez should have done better mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huddlestone and Maguire were different gravy #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Jakupovic save from Mata though #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking result that is, unbelievable performance from the boys #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck sake, in said we would sign no one else #hcafc https://t.co/XwsYg9w4NJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the odds on us signing no one else? Cause I can see it happening #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish him nothing but luck though, been a great servant to us!!! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't make a whole lot of sense letting Bruce leave, type of player we could do with as well absolute fighter #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like a terrible performance, shows our lack of depth in the squad and how badly we need more signings! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Nani rumours have got to be a joke right? #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Hurt, what a sad sad loss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real shame the way Snodgrass left, not wanting to play or train! Thought he was better than that, onwards and upwards #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take it Snodgrass refused to play for us then? Fit enough to pass a medical! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickSutton I think he's one of them for me but each to their own :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJonny so do I but snods obviously didn't wanna play for us anymore so no good to us! Hopefully he gets to reinvest it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus his heart wasn't in it anymore, can't afford to carry players in our situation #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snodgrass is one of the best players I've seen in a city shirt but we've proved we can play without him #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine how much of a hero snodgrass would be if he decided to stay? No chance of it happening like #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cry mate cause we ended your unbeaten run with a barely fit squad #hcafc https://t.co/osPvE4MR2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted to be out but the lads have done themselves proud again plus nice confidence boost going into the next #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davey_bennett @AwayDaysVideos haha yeah that would help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't you love to see this at the kc? #hcafc https://t.co/uTA8NjHDjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still get the feeling the allams are doing this out of spite, to get one over on us #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Were not a selling club' sells two of the best players the club has for way less than what they should have #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maguire will be next no doubt after his recent performances! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davey_bennett maybe I cursed us!!!! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulashby3 heard it was the other way round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulashby3 yeah I know but they pulled out which says everything you need to know, don't remember him been good there either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Burnley #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulashby3 says something if Sunderland don't want him and can't get into there team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't buy into the Yann M'Vila rumours #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something feels off at the minute, the city Twitter page seem to be listening and engaging with fans #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissaa_lauren give the gouch a good clean and tickle as well, I know he likes that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissaa_lauren say hi to Scott for me please while your tonguing his arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissaa_lauren Melissa Scott's got his own phone, tell him to stop been so controlling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gone Baby Gone is tonight's film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahWragby @TomosHefin @KatieLouise_8 don't get her hopes up kids, live halfway round the world now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobIves597 @HullCity probably asking for too much there mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like another Ben Arfa or Ramirez but will support the man and give him a chance! #hcafc https://t.co/xPXCJjhMFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how I feel a about this #hcafc https://t.co/uii1n4szTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank god mason is in a stable condition, now lets just pray and hope he makes a speedy recovery! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hope @RyanMason pulls through, thoughts and prayers are with him! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You feel like performances like that will see us pick up more points then drop, especially with plenty of teams to play around us #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like a very good performance from us, shock the referee sticking by the big club! Onto the next one lads #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that's Snodgrass gone then? #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetoogood91 Manchester by the sea is a cracking film mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The week when the allams could have tried to build bridges, they burn even more utterly fucking clueless morons! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly would not surprise me if this was the allams way of 'getting back' at the fans, cause that's what it feels like #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when we were all building some optimism up the allams have well and truly crushed it this week, absolute arseholes! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devastated about Livermore leaving, stuck by each other through thick and thin, been a wonderful asset! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Â£10 million for Livermore is a joke and so much for us not being a selling club Ehab?! Fucking Wanker #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: Phil Jevons has just passed a medical and is going to pen a 3 year deal, fee undisclosed #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Id take Ulloa in a heartbeat #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we sell Snodgrass to Burnley then I give up #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cera in This is the End fucking kills me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it rains it pours here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful player #hcafc https://t.co/IhNeOzfbz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This doesn't fill you with hope does it #hcafc https://t.co/4RqSzY6Q6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think its imperative that we do everything possible to keep Livermore at the club, hugely influential player #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skiing was class and I didn't die, so all round top day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just out of curiosity, with us not having a RB in our squad, who would we rather signed ? #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Will Hunting never gets old, outstanding film!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to go snowboarding tomorrow, probably gonna result in my death though so been nice knowing you folks ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that we've come from behind too, shows we've still got plenty of character and determination, much much more positive now #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robbo's cross for the first goal by the way, just fucking sexy want it! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely goal Abel's 2nd, shows what he's capable of when he turns up and got good support around him! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking get in there city, what a massive 3 points that is! Sounds like a good 2nd half, good to See Abel back in the goals #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Silva's positive attitude, no doubt its given the fans a boost and created some optimism #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a sneaky feeling Evandro could turn out to be Geovani esc... #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom! Nice boost ahead of tomorrow's game #hcafc https://t.co/F8vcIJgXsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydtidder just waiting on 57 to pick me up mate, taking the piss as usual! First round on you ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Graham Taylor, what a sad loss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor strange was meh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking ridiculous stats them https://t.co/TT1URZ6uqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyCart1994 hella goal that mate, loved Ashton top striker in his day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piss off ya Bellends worth at least 3 times more than that #hcafc https://t.co/dkGzalw0iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetoogood91 @Tigertully @sir_cornflake I agree think they would be uproar if snoddy went and rightly so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The End of the Tour is a cracking film, Jason Segel is bloody brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetoogood91 @Tigertully @sir_cornflake wouldn't surprise me if he sells snoddy and settles for 2 maybe 3 loan signings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that the players seem to be behind Silva straight away, wish we had owners that would give him and us a fighting chance #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetoogood91 @Tigertully @sir_cornflake 6 minimum for me, hard done by with injuries but need depth and some quality desperately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proper striker Dean Ashton, talent ruined by injury unfortunately https://t.co/8JIHbcU24O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tigertully @sir_cornflake apparently we only need '2 or 3' signings...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kierbrady99 catchy number https://t.co/vRtgTD4KtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotQuiteNoel with how tight that twat ehab is, can't see this been true! Then again you never know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like we picked a few knocks up? Christ we need fresh faces and quick!!! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of the effort the players put in, sounds like they gave it a right good go! #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captain Fantastic is a phenomenal film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world full of Kardashians, be a Meryl Streep!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattworman he was very inconsistent in his early days with us, shame he hasn't kicked on if so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattworman that's a shame, one of the most talented players I've seen play for city, very consistent in our relegation season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niasse seems a weird one, feel like the club lined him up before Silva joined #hcafc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring him home Silva #hcafc https://t.co/nVX39bxsy5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>