<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexandraFox5DC @fox5dc Trump is waaaay over your head lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews It should be a federal crime with jail the way she politicized and damaged the Department of Homeland Security. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks Tells U.S. Veterans Why Company Will Hire Refugees Instead - Breitbart https://t.co/lKLDaohThh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are Democrats with Islamists or are they with America? Either you're with us or you're against us. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkeley doesn't stand for free speech. It stands for radical leftist politics and nothing else is welcome. #MAGA  https://t.co/ftkf7MBHLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we need a LONG pause and extreme vetting of migrants and so-called refugees. #MAGA  https://t.co/DR8C8zkHW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefanLoeffler @Chess__News Prepare for 1. g4 2. f3? Dude, you're funny!! #Comedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT @theheraldsun Aussies played Obama for the sucker he is. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chess24com @MagnusCarlsen @PHChess @gmjlh Wild guess: dishonest organizers?
#GreatestOpenChessTournament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Glad this woman spoke up and asked Pelosi that question. People need to hear her. #MAGA #BuildTheWall  https://t.co/2nDuRtnDfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with Rush Limbaugh. It was a mistake by #Trump not to fire all the Obama holdovers immediately. #MAGA https://t.co/SXBZCIp2Q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK Petition demanding Trump make UK visit over 130,000 and rising fast. #MAGA #MakeBritainGreatAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media gives 57 times more coverage to Trump immigration order than Obama ending Cuban refugee program #MAGA https://t.co/3Cnr0IZo9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT Really, nutritionists need to make up their minds. Breakfast or not, eggs or not, low fat or not. #ImSoConfused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT Only billionaires like #Trump elected by the people get to be president. Nobody elected Howard Schultz to anything.  #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT @nytimes More #FakeNews alternate reality from the failing New York Times. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE – Islamic State Supporters React Angrily to Trump’s Temporary Refugee Halt #MAGA https://t.co/PtVcb8NMJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ To the 100+ jokers signing this: best wishes in all your future endeavors. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Times Journo Calls for Assassination of President Trump #MAGA https://t.co/HUlWFngOJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FLASHBACK: Obama Suspended Iraq Refugee Program for Six Months Over Terrorism Fears in 2011 #MAGA https://t.co/Dhxiptge5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't they ever play @Megadeth or Metallica in @Starbucks? 🤔
#amwriting https://t.co/2OONhVKGz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton received 800,000 votes from noncitizens, bolsters Trump argument, study finds  https://t.co/or9qGbsUxr #BuildTheWall #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing to see how many unfollow me after years bc they're Trump haters. The ignorance is breathtaking. I unfollow and block. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxBusiness To be on the safe side, fire them all. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOE Employees Scrubbed ‘Climate Change’ From Agency Files To Fool Trump https://t.co/3YI42PvkEm via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAKE NEWS: Washington Post Uses Tweets from 0.006% of UK MPs to Blast Theresa May over Trump Meeting https://t.co/dBwEc7hdW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: Media Doesn’t Cover Large Crowds During March for Life - Breitbart https://t.co/7IHmWWtgjT via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Sanctuary Cities Face Billions in Funding Cuts Under Trump #maga #buildthewall  https://t.co/p62YkntYz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six shot during vigil for gunshot victim in Chicago after Trump warned he'll send in the feds #maga  https://t.co/Xtwhbf9RFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Voters liked Trump’s ‘America first’ address https://t.co/y2lBW3sI6g #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theworldchess I expect prescriptions for Ritalin for chessplayers will explode. Many will try these drugs after doctor shopping. #chess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanPolgar @websteru That's great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yazidi Girls Sold as Sex Slaves while Women March against Trump: https://t.co/WFKXxxsnNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Brennan is yet another ex-CIA chief with emotional issues #maga https://t.co/6tMJJNTpRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Effect: Grocery Giant Kroger to Add 10,000 New Employees in Trump Era https://t.co/6KwFSjIoK9 via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: George Soros Tied to More Than 50 ‘Partners’ of Anti-Trump Women’s March https://t.co/qoCvtGExOj via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump Marchers ‘Mostly White’ Women Who Need ‘Therapy’ After Clinton Loss https://t.co/IJwa92qPYx via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need term limits on TV pundits. George Will, many others long past their expiration dates. #maga https://t.co/cpvGURNdHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @greggutfeld The rioters are people who would've held Cabinet positions in Hillary's administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writers Vote Politics, Not Baseball, in Rejecting Curt Schilling for Hall of Fame - Breitbart https://t.co/QEthBi3AAO via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great song! And so true.

Trump's first dance as president will be to Sinatra's 'My Way' #maga https://t.co/57p3zTUEgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ Clueless. Totally unsuited for their roles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top German Paper: We Need To Be 'More Gay, More Multicultural' To Oppose Trump #maga https://t.co/F82dLqVgXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump Gonna be funny when conservative media sit in the few chairs and liberals are standing on the sides!! #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump is SOLELY responsible for all these jobs coming back to the US all of a sudden. Who believes #FakeNews media?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartLondon Trump is the only one who can move NATO forward, certainly not the sad europeans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltClassicRock Offended snowflakes gonna sing about the evils of democracy and fair elections. #flush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limbaugh on Trump Falling Approval Rating: 'Fake News, Fake Polls' - Breitbart https://t.co/EfY4FCUFLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many twitter accounts posing as pro-Trump yet post nothing but anti-Trump garbage. So many losers in Obama's America. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tweeted at the time the #NeverTrump signers wouldnt get jobs with #Trump. The dummies thought otherwise? #maga  https://t.co/6eHltPxkbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody who signed that #NeverTrump letter is an expert in nothing but stupidity. #maga  https://t.co/6eHltPxkbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SURPRISE! John Lewis Didn't Attend George W. Bush's Inauguration Either https://t.co/hYVlG7iXc8 via @seanhannity #Trump #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If European nations believe in NATO, why are the vast majority, including Germany, NOT paying their share? #Trump https://t.co/ey2UwUT0EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe feigns 'shock' at Trump over 'obsolete' NATO comments  https://t.co/ey2UwUT0EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind of  teenager.
Refugee: Obama Ended ‘Wet Foot, Dry Foot’ to Punish Cubans for Supporting Trump https://t.co/XIy4aGSpYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant idea: drug testing for White House press. Imagine the meltdown they would have if anyone found out! #MAGA https://t.co/kScbF72qn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK @MailOnline No one can be surprised at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MailOnline Because many of the criminals are now illegals in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4Chan Claims To Have Fabricated Anti-Trump Report As A Hoax  https://t.co/sTwhTwRqpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why California’s Silly Secession Scheme Can’t Succeed https://t.co/epPJvIhrmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News Media Go To War With Trump #maga https://t.co/50N24k1WT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics Gotta say the Dems have the Thug vote locked up for decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxBusiness 2018 looking more Republican all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters Think U.S. Intelligence Agencies Play Politics - Rasmussen Reports™ https://t.co/TLNuaqYl3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's see if the @Drudge_Report attacks magically disappear once Obama is gone--which seems highly probable https://t.co/czeiGeD5Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News Plus Fascism: New York Times Urges Boycott of Breitbart https://t.co/4dJOvWReYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Intelligence Committee chair: Russia report leak was a 'political rollout' https://t.co/4SOWmW28in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Trump’s Dismissal of Obama’s Ambassadors Is Not an Unprecedented Crisis.

Obama did it, too.

 https://t.co/8mgaH7f3Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the grindstone. #amwriting #2017 #Starbucks #cafes #coffee https://t.co/wOQuHust4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The report quoted a Russian official as saying Ed Snowden shared intelligence with the Russian government." https://t.co/Up2OXXoFLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coworkers said Ed Snowden voiced few political views but voiced sympathies for China. #cia #nsa  https://t.co/Up2OXXoFLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of traitor Edward Snowden's disclosures have nothing to do with privacy #nsa #cia https://t.co/Up2OXXoFLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA, NSA Missed Warning Signs of Traitor Edward Snowden's Betrayal https://t.co/Up2OXXoFLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merkel Ally: Christmas Market Attack Suspect 'Should Not Have Been in Germany in the First Place'  https://t.co/mHzXiGTrb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blundering German police thought Muslim terrorist Anis Amri was still in Berlin https://t.co/ItmaeVoHbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berlin Christmas terrorist Muslim Anis Amri fled through 3 countries thanks to EU open borders https://t.co/ItmaeVoHbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed Police at Christmas Hotspots as Britain Braces for Possible Islamic Terror Attack #WarOnChristians  https://t.co/gfrvx7uqg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German police arrest two men in struggle at Islamic terrorist Anis Amri's Berlin mosque  https://t.co/Ck1gUGmyzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian police gun down fugitive Berlin killer Anis Amri in Milan as he screamed 'Allahu Akbar' during gunfight https://t.co/WIvvbLb8qJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowden is still in contact with Russian intelligence, House report charges #treason #spying #nsa  https://t.co/LtZHdGqtNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psycho liberal haters

Passenger thrown off flight after confronting Ivanka Trump #maga  https://t.co/hb0RiTHZ4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Permits Will Allow Wind Farms to Kill More Bald Eagles https://t.co/6tGOGng3Bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-CIA Director: Migrant Crisis Has Germany ‘Massively Overextended’ https://t.co/BfZksuxhcS #terrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to imagine the mentality of a New York Times subscriber. Brainwash me, please!
#LameStreamMedia #DemocratPRDepartment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Trump's win, the news media and Democrats still tricked millions into thinking they work for citizens' best interests. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German privacy laws blurring the eyes of Berlin massacre suspect clearly favor terrorists Insane that Merkel hasn't been hounded from office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany has pictures of Islamic truck massacre terrorist with his eyes BLURRED while the world searches for him https://t.co/eWPQnJhwUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First picture of Berlin massacre suspect: Anis Amri, 23, of Tunisia #Islamic #Terrorism  https://t.co/eWPQnJhwUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton is an 'angry white male' #KellyanneConway #maga  https://t.co/DbcEffktQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times Gives Valuable Publicity to White Nationalism  https://t.co/rn4aLUwwjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany has been rocked by seven terror attacks in 2016 leaving 22 dead https://t.co/JshXAemesl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 3 in 10 Americans believe Russia was behind election-year hacking https://t.co/HohMNgywM5 But the media says only Trump dissents!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in Berlin terror truck attack is released for lack of evidence https://t.co/QCfHuZ400Y #MamaMerkel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrant Youths, Locals Brawl at Christmas Market in Germany https://t.co/4aFpnPu7RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Light Orchestra, Journey, Yes, Pearl Jam To Be Inducted Into Rock And Roll Hall Of Fame  https://t.co/stlSiKdr8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berlin terror attack: Wrong man arrested https://t.co/Yxio3QALXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Fires Back After Bill Clinton Says He Only Appeals To ‘Angry White Men’ #maga  https://t.co/yPJbTsK9gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Angela Merkel hasn't been hounded from office by millions of outraged Germans. Probably gets reelected. #MamaMerkel #WarOnCitizens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump calls out Bill Clinton for the liar he is. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German right, security experts blame Angela Merkel's migrant policy for Berlin truck attack by refugee #MamaMerkel https://t.co/g2dvTcyfVp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>