<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HattieJo18 I love that you keep track - thank you for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey I think a lot of them have buyers remorse....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/BjcRpCbeGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This scares the sh*t out of me (and I'm in the country they all want to bolt to when everything hits the fan).… https://t.co/k9qk5jgXsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey Toddlers with guns kill more people. #BanToddlers 
I can't believe this is happening to you all. Wish I could do something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated The world is with you... https://t.co/NHIYGn1SiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@straczynski I met my husband because of this show. Changed my life in so many ways. Still my all time favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey This is a theory I posted a few weeks ago. From all the reactions, I might have been right.
https://t.co/2OYXrmP5Sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated I feel for you all - so many good people in the US, but your politicians...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey They change Felicity's clothes all the time now. I think designers are begging to get stuff on her -… https://t.co/QhPsCcRG9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated But it will take the fight out of a lot of people (who think getting rid of the orange one is the a… https://t.co/Nh6Y9xiCav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated I wonder if this is to make everyone sigh in relief when they replace him with either Pence or Ryan… https://t.co/Bq2rhz7nEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sapphire_Queen_ Surely they should hate Diggle as well (he's not comic book)....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UndercoverMenna @HuffPostArts This fandom introduced me to Hamilton and Lin and for that I'll always be grateful,… https://t.co/sOi20SJX7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UndercoverMenna @HuffPostArts He will, maybe not this time (though he should as the Moana soundtrack was brilliant).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UndercoverMenna It's actually a MacPEGOT - which is even rarer.
https://t.co/6m74LSUgaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I think it will be better than a lot of stuff out there. Remember some of the biggest books in the la… https://t.co/elh0aZ1ezP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf Can't wait to read your original stuff. https://t.co/sU2D2N0c9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated Fix one thing, then another, then another. That's how you gain momentum and show it can be done. It… https://t.co/WVCX3EVtRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated How about "This is bad, how do we help you fix it?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I loved when he told her she was right - all women love it when their man says that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UndercoverMenna She's building a very loyal fanbase. We'll follow her anywhere
(So glad again I only did Aisha's kickstarter)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf That's a good one, but there's been so many nice little moments (I'm doing a 5A rewatch) I can't pick a favourite, just yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UndercoverMenna I also love that she let us know she was there, but didn't promote herself (like others).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've found me out.... https://t.co/crzrUKZre6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf that's what she does. I wonder when she was there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But so much more to learn. https://t.co/rvPKoll9E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnottedYarn This is why he's my fav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheFutureisFemale https://t.co/oR6ZKEBC8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He he he he he 

He's not going to like this.... https://t.co/D0Zz1z48hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then I read twitter and realise we're all doomed. 
#ThankYouObama - not American but you're a good guy https://t.co/Bvk2c5s0nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That elation you feel when your home broadband finally works after 4 days. https://t.co/qR3D69g1Jd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey @rhodesmoak @mguggenheim @antonionegret respectfully disagree. Antonio needs to direct the angry make-up sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @NetflixANZ for #OneDayAtATime great show. Need more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Narelle_NZ poor you. 
Try ginger beer and ginger tea. Worked when I had food poisoning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey I would leave and never return. Screaming. Snakes are my phobia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlicityDreams my friends, who are casual viewers, can see the rebuild. It's just slow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey I'm allergic to lots of things and that's not an allergy attack - it's bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not live there anymore, but I'm proud to be Scottish today. https://t.co/murVC2gf5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SpiceMeg I know people who are working on it...there will be 3 sequels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FanMomMer I saw it talked about as soon as he went onto the ticket. I think that's the endgame, either pence or ryan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SpiceMeg I know. Can't wait to read. Love this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scu11y22 Want to know a secret - he's even better looking in the flesh....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotsforolicity @StephenAmell @EmilyBett @mguggenheim Beautiful - that you for sharing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey They must have been told to really push his character - don't know why though, audience doesn't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Srishti369 I hope it's more he realises what it's like to be lied to, Oliver needs to learn that lesson. AND APOLOGISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romancebooknerd please do - I need more tshirts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@magsdoleman @jamesdoleman You guys need to watch this movie #HuntForTheWilderPeople on Netflix - you'll love it. https://t.co/moCC6vNubu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbuffyangel @OlicityDreams don't forget one of the best ships - 7 years we waited. https://t.co/zABGqUsr7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I loved the lost finale. It was saying goodbye to friends who'd been with me for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Armageddonexpo anyone from Arrow but especially @EmilyBett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanCarchedi  so sorry to hear that. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredGulian I, at least, have a few more weeks off, so hopefully I'll get some sun... After the rest of you all go back to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredGulian Currently wet from having to rush to bring the washing in... Where is summer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf see this thread. 
https://t.co/cJEoFYvJEh
Also Love will win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnottedYarn or everything was filmed at the same time and is being rolled out slowly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf can only send love and hugs. I hope things get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 has just been born. Tonga, first on the international date line has passed into the new year. 
In NZ we pass i… https://t.co/ybIDqtClUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey @MyFutureQueen I'm all in too. 
Let's get this terrible year gone, and do something positive in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just so sad
#RIPCarrie 
#RIPDebbie
#Fuck2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdoleman @NewsBud_ actually it's more like this. https://t.co/zRp0VEWjq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdoleman @NewsBud_ kiwi reaction https://t.co/gBjRZw6jQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FanMomMer they're declaring war on New Zealand, and we don't care. Probably don't even know where we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HattieJo18 @ThatEricAlper me too. I was so happy when I got a cassette radio and didn't need the mic anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey  I think it would freak anyone out.  Might be worth it. https://t.co/QPFYnfys4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey only for cockblocking purposes. Good mood killer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey that's great news. Something positive for 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Nathan_W_ she was the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tread....
Perfect. #ripcarriefisher https://t.co/FFiAviOaZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one hurts. #RIPCarrie 
2016 can fuck off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too. https://t.co/xCVAN78ySt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awful. Such a huge part of my teenage years. So much great music. https://t.co/6MTqSyPH3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf what a nice Christmas present, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bindy_417 great stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone from New Zealand. I hope santa was good to you and you have a great day. https://t.co/pqKvSOIPfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf @DolbowMaria @scu11y22 They probably just forgot about it (again). LOT promo is out.... How do these people still have jobs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdoleman Cool. https://t.co/mCdDp3eUy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 can fuck off. You don't get Carrie, she's ours. She was my first badass role model, and has been one of my heroes for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey  I now have a month off. After Christmas I think we should sort out the website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf 
https://t.co/Q0XP59tL2D asked readers to list their fav 3 fics of the year.  It might still be open, it was only last week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I might have voted for that in the tumblr poll of 3 fav fics of the year.... https://t.co/3cuF2qH8py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey That sounds disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf Me too - we should start a fan club (I just re-read Felicity's Revenge the other week).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I love Tina's writing (btw I do the same for your stuff as well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I'm saving it to read at bedtime - so excited....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are few things more satisfying than setting up my out-of-office on work email, Especially as I have a month off...
#ItsSummerHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I stay in my hope bubble, I know there's good things coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf Unless...
Please show the punch, please show the punch. That would keep us in gifs forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyricalarrow It's definitely the fandom line of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepperDempsey I'd only put 4, the other would be your kindness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf I can't believe you want to win an argument with facts and logic. https://t.co/IMathRozds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChooseLove86 @callistawolf Even my husband, who's a casual viewer, has no doubt they'll get back together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf Their evidence is "but comics"....
Ours is watching the show....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated I threw something at my TV.  We do not speak of it. Back to Joss and Donna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callistawolf They'll still be telling us the rebuild is coming in the series finale (even though O&amp;F will have tri… https://t.co/X7AUB6ZmEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated I fell out with BSG after the last episode. But yes Kara/Lee was heartbreaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated I waited 7 years for those 2 to kiss - 7 years. And let's not forget Buffy/Angel. Olicity is easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_caffeinated It's actually really dark (very good - seen it twice already) but it's PG-13 for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK. Let's do this #RogueOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SweetzCupcake he'll be lurking the entire time.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>