<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just recently Tesla installed its first Grid Sized Battery installation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember Coal kills
Nuclear kills
Gas maimed and kills!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As of March 2017 Tesla will be installing Battery Systems on Homes! #Richo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All major energy providers are transitioning from Fossil Fuels to Renewable Energy!#Richo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cant put in Coal Plants when Banks and Energy providers will no long back Coal Fired Power! #Richo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs Worldwide show that Renewables can now provide Base Load Power!#Richo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frydenberg lying thru his teeth,
Banks will now No Long Fund Coal Plants and recent studies show Coal Plants now drive up prices #Richo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Second Week Is as Chaotic as His First: A Closer Look https://t.co/lhBk2gZbNx via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Donald Trump Backlash Outpacing Tea Party | Rachel Maddow | MSNBC https://t.co/ihcSTDnrbM via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's First Military Disaster https://t.co/W4Z3ctUxG8 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Call With Australia: Total Disaster https://t.co/687tNV8aBv via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia has its own war!
War on the stupidity of the the current Government and its Anti Climate Policies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember we really are at WAR!
War on Trump
War on Trumps policy's
War on Trumps Lies
War on Trumps racism, sexism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull supporting a mad man whose ready to knife him and Australia in back! https://t.co/OIGmwKnBh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Whooping telling the Truth as it really is! https://t.co/XnxjdJwGbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whilst they pocket Tax Cuts? https://t.co/Qeh7ockf1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News Flash!
Mad Man Trump screws up again
Or and again
Or wait a minute Trump  a permanent mistake!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump allows Whitesupremists https://t.co/MC4pHGXEvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shorten pushes integrity inquiry but says political corruption isn't widespread https://t.co/nFVcSCX4zN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA election: Labor strengthens lead as One Nation vote surges – poll https://t.co/8D7Yv9QuJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNP Australia and Trump an example of when Politicians Go MAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trumps treatment of Australia's PM, Australia needs to suspend all use of Pine Gap until Trump is out of Office!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ill wind is blowing in energy and climate policy debate https://t.co/6MUUjU3fqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new level of resistance to Donald Trump that is less visible and potentially more troublesome https://t.co/Z5l3zGc6wK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump to focus counter-extremism program solely on Islam: sources https://t.co/zsyCLS3lVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists blast lack of NHMRC funding on climate https://t.co/vMomB2gUpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US media, congressmen stunned Donald Trump has picked a fight with Australia https://t.co/GSnBK1R0Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's some reality for Donald Trump: the US needs Australia, not just the other way around https://t.co/nCSooek1wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Train Passengers Sing Over the Rainbow! https://t.co/Xa9Gyrubpa via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Will crash the system | Billions will be lost https://t.co/qxsJnPRxpO via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FactCheck: Turnbull’s Speech on Australia’s #Energy Future https://t.co/z7G0MyNGC0 #auspol #climate #coal #renewables via @climatecouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Supremacists Are Taking Over Police Departments Across America https://t.co/0mwAy9zzK6 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Bernstein Calls Kellyanne Conway A "Propaganda Minister" https://t.co/Nu4niEHUzP via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tamaralynn212 
Under the Obama agreement you took our 1200 and we were meant to take some of yours from South America somewhere I think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trunbulss lying about Clean Coal and Renewable Energy so can we really trust him on what was said on a phone call?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's time Australia formed an Alliance with China we have some American bases they can use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump supporting White Supremacists are the real Terrorist threat to America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring back Keating as PM at least he would go Toe to Toe with Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should suspend the ANZUS treaty whilst we still can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again total lack of any Economic Sense on Energy! https://t.co/SJr9t8sKoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only fake thing is anything coming out the mouth of Right Wing Propagandists! https://t.co/RneGUKwZ4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about Iran, the World has Offically put Trump on Notice!
Pull your head in or bugger off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool that has No Knowledge on how wrong he is! https://t.co/0BcGpXyP1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fossil fuels are no match for wind and solar as clean energy investment breaks records https://t.co/Mvfqwm9IBI via @financialpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind and Solar Are Crushing Fossil Fuels https://t.co/9HASqaVosd via @business 
#pmlive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not cost effective compared to the price of Renewable Energy https://t.co/yVirQhvWHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Message For All Of Humanity  -  Charlie Chaplin https://t.co/GUQmCRjqim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean Coal about as likely as a Clean LNP/Conservative Politician?
And just as expensive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and the Republicans putting Americans out of work as fast as they can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britons THeresa May ignores the voter when it comes to sucking up to Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Federal Governt won't and can't step up to save Cheap Renewable Energy than the States Must!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airline stocks lose $US4.9 billion as investors weigh Donald Trump's immigration order https://t.co/1tQkbHPzcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally Yates in spotlight after defying Donald Trump's order https://t.co/2u5koBrKjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republicans' deal with the devil https://t.co/nSYZD7IOws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons of WW2 'in danger of being forgotten' warns Prince Charles amid controversy over Trump state visit https://t.co/rRwsvLQCcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec mosque attack: Canadian Muslims point to anti-immigrant 'trash radio' https://t.co/cfXpHK6flT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May says Donald Trump's UK visit will go ahead, but no word on Parliament address https://t.co/Q3Azqgov7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud over $5.5b Western Distributor with Coalition, Greens set to block toll plan https://t.co/udIHZPjxft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parakeelia generates a record $900,000 for the Liberal Party https://t.co/4gNRkif0Mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One night in a motel, then back on the streets for Flinders Street Station rough sleepers https://t.co/HL4rfx43mL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats face 'nuclear option' on Neil Gorsuch nomination to US Supreme Court https://t.co/LW3T6Wtqcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coal could get clean-energy subsidy under new Turnbull focus https://t.co/NzKJHqI2PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its amazing how màny on the right believe the con that the coal industry is running that it is cheaper than renewables, its a lie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Aides Say Trump Acting Like Spoiled, Clueless Child https://t.co/vvLJzC1lOi via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hits 50% Disapproval in Record Low 8 Days https://t.co/0La0FLIWcs via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/Sm6osrfELJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian companies wouldn't picket the money at the Top and run?
nah? https://t.co/d859P3U5fJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia really does have a dis functional, dillsionary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fools on a fools errand!
Facts are Renewable are now cheaper to run and install! https://t.co/9jtAtIysMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an f###wit! https://t.co/C8E0K02ckc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems she really does live in a fools paradise! https://t.co/25UPVGELyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is the reason why the Second Amendment exists,
The Right to Bear Arms to stop a Hostile Takeover of America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to suspend the ANZUS treaty whilst Dictator in Charge of the USA is still their!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote LNP get higher Electricity prices via Espensive Coal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Turnbull and the LNP are learning from Trump, if you can't get it right Lie, Lie, Lie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull supporting higher Electricity prices via exspensive Coal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull really wants us to believe he is going to look after us after gutting Welfare and Medicare and stealing from the poor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump forgets you are looking at Britians future King! https://t.co/nuQVP9Ijzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting yesterday's technology with tomorrow's future! https://t.co/2gtcquRNuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How wrong our prime Minister can be!
Wrong on Renewables,
Wrong on Climechange
And definitely Wrong on Trump! https://t.co/J0tjgtPwWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and his Henchmen are the Biggest threat to Democracy since Hitler and Stalin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASX tumbles after largest US sell-off since election https://t.co/C9BEvtEDbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's ban puts Turnbull in a bind over refugees https://t.co/GhAdnfg83x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four ways they can get rid of Donald Trump sooner rather than later https://t.co/duzzNfTeMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's refugee policy sparks US diplomat dissent memo https://t.co/dzGhpIFjs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting US Attorney-General Sally Yates fired by Donald Trump over immigration order https://t.co/WVJVYDCmYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump to withdraw from Paris agreement, 'change course' on climate change, says adviser https://t.co/f52xAUZMSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition rejecting Trump state visit to the United Kingdom gains more than a million signatures https://t.co/TYzIjo0tJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loophole will allow donations made in dying days of federal election to stay secret https://t.co/ED5C7t6gjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My toddler had his first taste of racism on Australia Day https://t.co/yHLT5tJaMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What sort of government is too cowardly to stand up to naked fascism? Ours https://t.co/AeUpqGKyiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope your Right, Censorship is that he thin edge of the web! https://t.co/tv8o19RzGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump signs an Executive Order to Silence/ Sensor Social Media and the Internet then it's time he was Removed by any Means!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's time to march on Canberra and sort out the LNP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump your Fired! https://t.co/KyomusALz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet he's tries to silence  Social Media! https://t.co/AMaCMYEV5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeh complete chaos and total collapse of America!
Thanks for nothing! https://t.co/6m23HUnqf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump taking his life in his own hand if he turns up in UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delusional Conway Brags About Trump’s ‘extraordinary Accomplishments’ In... https://t.co/DKgtDyvViI via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former CIA deputy director says travel ban will make America "less safe" https://t.co/x4MXPg8xg9 via @YouTube]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>