<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["The mana of everyone who attends and takes part in the festival is important to us" https://t.co/GnaroYK0UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verbscape lol did you hear the interview this morning? i was in such a rage on the way to work i almost crashed #weakling #notracistbut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English: up to others to decide whether ethnic cleansing is wrong, but ‘certainly not the direction we plan to take’ https://t.co/dzprORIwkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking (and by extension, nz constitutionalism)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking click! it's a classic of commonwealth legal thinking and British constitutionalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[relevant post-Trump, post-institutional break down: "the political constitution" https://t.co/jXiKormBAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[coming up on @CheckpointRNZ, "a wonderful hedge in waikanae"

never change nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewPaulWood i thought I'd blocked this ballsack. Thanks for the reminder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonder what stormfront et. al. are saying about Glorious General steve bannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hold on, is that @farmgeek in the front row? hello!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[optics 

*shivers* https://t.co/4KewaUn7gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik oh it's still totally useless! (though, to be fair... to myself... i do try and avoid "savvy" commentary)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in non-gang and way less interesting news, i was on @RNZSunday talking politics etc this morning https://t.co/UCewktCFJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and yes, "former mob member warwick godfery" is my old man so i know a little bit about this eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that has nothing to do with more cops and more prisons (and yes, this message is for you, Stuart Nash, you epic fool).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and you can't "smash the gangs" - these are people, not objects you can take a hammer to

instead you can make gangs unnecessary, BUT...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gangs emerge in gaps - places without work, community support, and whakapapa https://t.co/jRUOjw4u7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[without internet what the hell am i meant to do today 

no way im not going outside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there an internet outage, @SparkNZ? Wifi router and 4G are down.

Currently tweeting from Vodafone's 4G network...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating talks from @AnthonyByrt and, right now, @hangipants78 on @SaturdayRNZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @mfyfyr was this the time Trotter tried to school you - was it you? - on continental philosophy and the enlightenment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HORansome @LI_politico though the "humanitarian and *other*" part is so wide you could fit Trump Tower in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HORansome @LI_politico (refugee and asylum seeker status is hard to obtain so in some ways it's good to have a discretionary power)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HORansome @LI_politico it's a power usually reserved for "humanitarian" cases, like asylum seekers etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[arrived at the airport, the koru lounge is full, it smells like someone left their duty free calvin klein in the midday sun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenThomasNZ i was asking for this wasn't i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please send comforting pictures of wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stuck in auckland traffic "chaos", was nice knowing you fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdnharris Great analysis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when i say "pretty big deal" i mean massive career-defining deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[campbell mcLachlan is already a professor and a QC so i guess all that's left is to knight him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[though, seriously, it's a pretty big deal - for academics and lawyers - to be approvingly cited in the UK Supreme Court twice IN ONE MONTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how long before the media realises a new zealander was mentioned in this pretty important thing happening OVERSEAS https://t.co/UZtYFMED5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bjjanssen @keith_ng @LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack it's too late to delete the tweet too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying "Labour did it first" is ridic

Residency = some nameless bureaucrat processed a form;
Citizenship = the Miniser actually granted it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryteatowel @LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack the time you must spend here is dramatically reduced under the investor categories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, Thiel gaining citizenship appears to have involved the use of a discretionary power (a ministerial power). They're different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thiel gaining residency is a threshold question - did he meet the points requirement? There's no need for the use o… https://t.co/NY1zoE4JZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack criticising use of discretionary powers is exactly what a good opposition should do!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack Thiel's citizenship appears to have been ranted under a discretionary - i.e ministerial - power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack so granting residence is merely a threshold decision - bureaucrats make the call. However...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostArcNZ @avancenz @therealgregjack That's right. The relevant categories for Thiel were probably "investor 1" or "investor plus"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[come listen to comrades Rodgers, Munro and godfery this evening https://t.co/QL0lgM7NC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking you conservative you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thiel is kind of right and new zealand is a free market paradise, for example i'm now registering my 27th shell company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how long before we can add brexit to england's long list of half-finished revolutions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mary, a saudi-based ewe, formerly of a south canterbury flock, disputed transparency international's finding https://t.co/XnjtG1BvXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[price gouging: the great kiwi tradition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[luv the free market https://t.co/tfM3jIbxIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this year my diet will consist solely of big ben pies, l&amp;p cans, and grass clippings from a quarter acre i'll never afford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we're getting "uncle tom" and it's only january fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pray for the discourse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the discourse is fucked, already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the indispensable @tzemingdynasty https://t.co/GRN3lI2Khi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relevant to #NikisEviction cc. @defendGI, @defend_Niki https://t.co/qObjHiF0Hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Procurement policy": welfare for wealthy contractors https://t.co/Kj57nmsSMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presenting noted tikanga expert, Wiremu Pakeha, formerly known as Bill English. https://t.co/kRjKYVsImV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NikisEviction isn't for her benefit. Developers are converting public housing into private homes. Niki will be priced out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the best way to deal with nazis is non-violence"

this is some weird virtue signalling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP your work is important and if some leftists can't handle that, well, it's probably a sign of conservatism on their part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if jimi jackson was from te teko his kuia would be giving him a rap on the knuckles rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come and listen to @bootstheory, Stephen Mills and I talk about election year stuff. It'll probably be fun. https://t.co/LaDsqgQHLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhenaOwen true that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solidarity with long-time Glen Innes resident Niki Rauti https://t.co/dqNfZsSN7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps @CitizenBomber i wish the herald didn't report on it, then it never would have gold further than s couple minutes on ZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP lol half a million wut https://t.co/Qd7UyvoaU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP and for all the progress made on representation, they're still just doing it to profit. witness their sole attempt to give back...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP but the overall point is about power: disney is a massive media conglomerate with the power to shape how people encounter maui etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP it's the race hucksterism you hate :) 

but seriously, it's not a materialist analysis per se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DennyPaoa @PPNetwork16 @PPInternational @TheHuiTV3 Good to see such a big community turnout for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps fair point. i should have linked to https://t.co/9NmaS7uq9d, https://t.co/x9jlo9XeXd etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToaFraser Thanks! And yeah... I wonder how it would have gone if they went with Taika's original script?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps for sure! (being a dude in his 20s definitely means my stake in this is reduced)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps that tweet was shit stirring - went overboard! - but the medium post goes into more detail. like i say i like moana the character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps that i think has largely gone unnoticed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps this isn't to say the progress made on representation isn't important - or to enforce authenticity - it's just a critique]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps sure, but genre doesn't alter my primary point. this is a question of power. disney will shape how many peeps encounter maui etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauliolo for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alice_tps no, other than in a hypnotic way - there's something primal about the music/animation (in a "why am i still watching this" way)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I wrote this journal article on citizenship. https://t.co/sUv87Piks5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[follow me for the thermonuclear takes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[further to this: some reasons https://t.co/6bZEfyR7hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ban "fat homeless maori" and bob's your uncle https://t.co/Y9fMRPNQZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm on medium dot com watch out fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliasvonhelios chur, have changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney's Moana isn't as progressive as you might think. 

Hear me out... https://t.co/We2MZcvzYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipsTane @PouTepou shocking eh. Feels like there've been heaps of tangi this month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ indeed - encouraging to see the likes of Deborah Russell having a go, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[greens are getting all of the talent, tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dvd_john on post-liberalism, or what comes next. https://t.co/SAWGe273SL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe @Taroaroa @AndrewLittleMP what a champ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe @Taroaroa @AndrewLittleMP as inspiration: "do one for the country robert... one for the country!" https://t.co/8blgvaq7UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mokai77 lol that's pretty menacing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bekathrills nice. they should give this facebook page a like lol https://t.co/9NmaS7uq9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmc_21 cool for the kids - moana the character is great - but other aspects (Maui, misuse of Poly iconography, Pele, the haka etc)... na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMakereti @nzgirlemd Disney has the power to shape how the rest of the world encounters/understands Maui, thus displacing Poly stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMakereti @nzgirlemd true, but of course this is Disney we're talking about so playing with the myth becomes a question of power...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMakereti @nzgirlemd but what about Maui...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewPaulWood true, i'm really not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sure, moana the character is great, but i'm not sure how you can praise a film that displaces actual polynesian histories and mythologies]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>