<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a Subway pro, may as well work there but yesterday instead of a footlong meatball I straight up asked for a football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleThings_LB @BreadMeatsBread send me pics next time you go pls. Miss that place so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnybrownbaby hahaha yasss.    What about people who love meat substitutes...  Quornhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A website for people that are really into square sausage. 

Lornehub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegetarian haggis should be called haggish and the fact it isn't is a PR disaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not his biggest fan but how much does that mean to Rafa Nadal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer, Nadal, Venus and Serena...  This is very 2005]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe Trump cancelled T in the Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Campbell18 @seonaanderson time to unfollow Baz aswell it seems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drank 5 coffees at work and now it's 6am and I'm buzzing out my nut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to unfollow potus and flotus on here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible what happened in Melbourne today, really makes you stop and think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class week spent watching the tennis capped off by watching Sir Andy bossing the court.… https://t.co/SitkdGG0UE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizkhamilton oh you aren't gonna enjoy today then, seeing the man himself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the number one tennis player in all of 
Kazakhstan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely Novak hasn't gone and lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen @JudyMurray at the Australian Open. About to watch Jamie play aswell #lifegoals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsure if these Japanese people are massive fans of Kei Nishikori or just white supremacists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a fucking boo son https://t.co/gCARC4r4b3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizardharry69 aye hoping to catch a few good ones, Saw Novak last night at some event he did, turns out he's not bad at basketball eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizardharry69 Don't even know about the final.. sold out already. I'm gonna get a ground pass so I can see all the random games tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartBroad8 Nervous on that last ball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Murray gets to the final of the Aus Open i'll be taking out a loan to get myself a ticket #arisesirshaggerandy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see the stadium from my bedroom window and I decided to watch this one on TV instead... https://t.co/94pA9jHuUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many job adverts on gumtree here for barristers that can do latte art, strange skill for a lawyer to have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoulder is sunburnt so bad that the packet of chips i've got on it is not just defrosted it's actually about cooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up four months i've been in Australia and I honestly didn't think i'd miss Strongbow dark fruits as much as I do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whale will be a meme by the time I wake up I can feel it #Tilikum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See how there's a bar on A380's, how does one go about getting that gig? Asking for a friend...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad had an afro in the 80's but as far as i'm aware is yet to post a #frobackthursday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleThings_LB is this ultimate Bisbee or just regular?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_dontbehasty I was actually telling people I was gonna miss seeing in Christmas with the Betts! Hope somebody got you a cone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Eastern European pal said he was away to get some dinner, asked him if he was off to Iraq... he didn't get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EuanCampbell1 Gonna have to skype my way in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleThings_LB not bad! I'm looking at 37 on Christmas day though!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[29 degrees today, chilled on the beach. Don't have a phone so no snapchat but just imagine it looked like that Daniel Craig beach scene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dabbed at someone while working today, should have seen the look I got back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PC_Plod_35 It only went up this year because @jonnybrownbaby came back from China!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and fuck it, back to buzzfeed quizzes about how well I remember about early 2000's chocolate bars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the North Korean people gained access to the internet, the North Korean government wouldn't last more than a couple of months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a theory, it's a strange thing to be tweeting about at 2:17am after work but hey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__Hannah_King__ i'll have no doubt fucked it again by that point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__Hannah_King__ It was 50 on mine i'm sure! Must be because i'm in the future. Sometime next February we can get back there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__Hannah_King__ I was genuinely gutted about this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__Hannah_King__ I wasn't sure how to break the news to you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phones fucked, if anyone I don't really care about is on a night out can they DM some blurry pics of them with some people I don't know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus v NZ ODI at the MCG tomorrow thought get in!  @RhysDenby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I first got to Melbourne if I was working at 6 i'd try and fit in as much as i could before work, now I just sleep in till 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EuanCampbell1 hahaha 
Me *sees tree*
"... When I was trekking the Amazon.. "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When i'm back home everyone has permission to punch me if I start a story with 'When I was travelling..." #dontbethatguy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a bit wet getting there but worth it for the 'gram
#greatoceanroad #zeroexcess @ Great Ocean… https://t.co/QSGmeCTQh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnybrownbaby could have bought 8 burgas with that tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserrMac one day i'll be in my 50's with kids of my own and she'll be sending me advent calendars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely my mum's not spent £8.55 posting me an advent calendar to Australia... https://t.co/mnPGM6e1ea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a male only salami festival in the town Melania Trump is from in Slovenia...  #sausagefestatasausagefest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is worse than Brexit and Trump together. T in The Park is an institution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedy that Justin Beiber punched a fan, tbf if a guy sticks his face in your car window you should be allowed to punch him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIFA: "We should investigate all those deaths in Qatar..."
Also FIFA: "No, some Brits wore flowers, they must be pu… https://t.co/8Ew3HCGUaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KP24 Sammy was on top form today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen Brian Lara eating a pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook: "Snapchat won't sell out to us" 
Inner Facebook: "Copy their entire app" https://t.co/snbDUHnjhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supposed to be 38°c tonight and I'm playing Frisbee... Once played in -2,not sure what's worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to explain 'here we fucking go" to Aussies, didn't go well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kanyewest what do you think? Worth a punt? @FLOTUS https://t.co/1FI3cTCTJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWUltimate honestly reckon I could have made all the difference. #whenwillthisjokegetold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucked it https://t.co/VA1tqxuSQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WorldCupGolf Is there a line up for the pro am on Wednesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleThings_LB couple of these https://t.co/sMVOT2pTCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surreal being in a country where people haven't heard of Frankie Boyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cute little fella sleeps 16 hours a day and has a top speed of 0.3mph.... Anyway that's… https://t.co/fzybhqwfwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not what I had in mind when I heard Shot tower.... @ Shot Tower Melbourne Central https://t.co/DgXiMXc8nF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders wants free healthcare, free uni, no guns, minority rights, cheap prescriptions..Scottish, Bernie Sanders wants to be Scottish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWUltimate ps what team is Baby G on? I'm supporting them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWUltimate WE ALL DREAM OF A TEAM OF ANDY B, A TEAM OF ANDY B, A TEAM OF ANDY B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 320000/1 this is worth a punt with the way things are going right now https://t.co/T6eg8iiZJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ladbrokes make it the other way round, can't see Kanye accepting the vice president role]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway, what odds can I get on Michelle Obama and Kanye West being the winning ticket for the presidency in 2020? @Ladbrokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could also read: "One person searches Shay Given on bing" https://t.co/kBpLrRASkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1000000% goes to Edinburgh uni #fty https://t.co/CYi42YHgSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No excuses people. Anyone still saying this wrong can get in the fucking sea with those yo-gurt cretins https://t.co/POZDL0prl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's not the only one on the far right is she... @example https://t.co/3fuuQcG6xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this for real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When all you wanted to do was lower the Gini Coefficient #Feelthebern https://t.co/qfEWHUuemt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I got food poisoning from a Subway, given the amount I've had I'd say your chances of getting food poisoning from Subway are 1/1000000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Andy you've just become the world number one how do you feel?" #Murray https://t.co/wQwCkLLFqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying on the grass in sunny Melbourne, it's 28 degrees and I've just found out I'm 10,500 miles away from a Strongbow Dark Fruits. Fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, I didn't have a subway today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway fuck it i'm in Australia trying to avoid this shitstorm, but here we fucking are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sorry this tweet wasn't true, i'm an atheist*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but as a fucking scumbag proddy, queen loving, union jack wearing and england supporting No voter, i'm kinda against second referendums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only democratic way to avoid brexit would be to have another vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that we are in the right economically and morally etc we need to remember that most people in our country who voted, voted to leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not saying that's what this ruling means but people saying that we should scrap brexit asap need to remember that no matter how much we feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While i'm a big fan of the EU, i'm also a big fan of democracy and we can't start throwing democracy under a bus when it doesn't go our way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Cool. Almost makes it worth the 1000's of slave workers dying in the process doesn't it? https://t.co/rBFSxSo6hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was in bed by 9 (hardcore I know) when the flatmates came in, guilted me into going in and then bailed! Solid hour of sleep lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordanjhamilton that too, funnily enough a pizza sorted them both out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought I was in a rager of a mood after work, turns out... Just hungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Bernie Sanders be in charge of the world pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The building I live in skips floors 4 and 14 and there's no flat 4 because Asian people are afraid of it (https://t.co/90PUfX723j)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>