<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn thanks that would be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn and another one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @metlinkwgtn what's with n#1 driving straight past supreme court stop on Lambton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long to rebuild chch? 6 years?   #nzqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did bill just pull a shaw pun?  #nzqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigFossMP @StatisticsNZ pharmaceutical products &amp; therapeutic appliances and equipment increased to $9 and $5, respectively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile that didn't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile that I know of. Okay trying now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four bills from two ballots, great way to end 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @2degreesmobile any ideas why you blocking my sisters txts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome experience for those kids! #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does the vote work for @NZNationalParty leader? Is it a run-off? STV? or just a FPP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @TeamSnapper then you wear the penalty... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rarahsobson tough on crime or decriminalization?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic backed up from Newtown shops all way to basin at least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sstewart_nz for those after more detailed instructions... :) https://t.co/5vGZNeM2ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington - Confused by tsunami map evac zones earlier today? Now's perfect time check out you house on… https://t.co/vVxz2w14Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin @radionz impressively quick transcribing + summarising of what was on the radio :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixmarwick any news about Bowen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixmarwick makes all those evening bike rides up the hill worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamGoodallYes @jamespeshaw assuming we get all clear to get back into bowen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was behaviour ethical... (Apparently yes) #nzqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZGreens this one's cooler! https://t.co/UrohS6fupb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @FedFarmers re that camera -  I do not have many [secret's] so I am not really worried https://t.co/2jE8P2HRmJ ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The median is not necessarily the average and for Auckland housing market most definitely not equal #postcab *seething on the inside*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamespeshaw @JulieAnneGenter not that issue. But some candidates both for and against various issues including island bay cycle way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieAnneGenter both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Break for tea. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last question. How many houses do you own. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul eagle. Ran a petition against it. But isn't saying no now. Will support community lead solution. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry red haired cyclists are good. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee = yes #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Island bay cycle way. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon bonner hits out at his generation buying up houses in there 50s  #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unmetetered water. Brendon bonner. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry. On water. I have a shower once a week. Less. Maybe. Gold. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pierson doesn't support metering. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee supports water metering. Talks about stopping lakes. We have deferred second damn by fixing leaks. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next question first mic fail. Water metering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40% turnout. 90% complaints afterwards. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon endorse Paul.  How will you ensure that or this. I can't insure anything. All I can do is give it my best shot. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry. Some people have a second house.   
#meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul eagle references district plan. #meetthecandidates more character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee talks road enclosure on tory st. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Pierson hits back a fan of minimum parking requirements. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @JulieAnneGenter minimum parking requirements being raised at #meetthecandidates Newtown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul eagle hits sea level rise on south coast right away. Thanks David Lee.  #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How wide is four lanes to the planes? #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roads are going to be 90 meters wide. You cannot cross. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More poetry. I hear the planet groaning. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee climate change is my portfolio. Lists what wcc Green econ reduce emissions. councils own ghg. Waste. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't keep robbing the environment you have to pay it back. #meetthecandidates Pierson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Pierson.  Live within limits. Keep trolley buses. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attacks middle class liberals who care about penguins. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon bonner talks about balance. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change in one minute. Go #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audience question first up climate. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is best to eat in Newtown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith it's Brent! Oops #meetthecandidates https://t.co/eBbPDv0wta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith maybe. I'm confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A road can't exist without people! #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul eagle transport. Let's reflect on the last few years the basin and island bay. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More poetry. Less cars,  bus be twice as quick. Don't slack back to your cars. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution to basin is a school in karori. David Lee  #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee @NZGreens transport problems are poor urban planning. What happens in school holidays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland will fall into a big hole. #meetthecandidates people from auck can fall off planet. Steve Pierson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First heckle of candidate. In answer to a question. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basin reserve cut and cover. Steve peirson .  #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had light rail in 1908. We can afford it then why not now. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the trolley buses till electric buses here #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transport a favourite subject of Steve pierson. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conditional support or opposal of runway. Brendon bonner. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the routes for light rail. Where is bus conjestion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon starts talking about eastern suburbs. No more tunnels. Out of cars into public transport. #meetthecandidates not a light rail fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same order. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning bell at three minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next up transport. #meetthecandidates talk about light rail vs four lanes to the planes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support for affordable housing attacks govt running down state housing.#meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul eagle focus on Auckland but  I don't want to see Newtown be the next ponsonby.  #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don Mcdonald sums up problem. Not enough houses! #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don. Mcdonald. A gold coin cubed 70 meters of housing debt. And greedy banks and cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four pronged approach. Including push four capital gains and address supply with support for apprenticeships #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Lee housing is a basic right. @NZGreens ##meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rent should be based on ability to pay. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Pierson.  We can't do anything about house prices. But calls for building social  housing stock. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Joseph savage reference before call for wcc to build houses. Brendon bonner. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the age cared workers gonna live? #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falling back on local govt cause central govt won't address. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon bonner. Have we got a crisis muted yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A minute or two each on housing affordiblity. Should house prices rise or fall. 
#meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the hot issues. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clap for social housing. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need more buses. ~ #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Don Mcdonald with a poem. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now David Lee @NZGreens. Talks about his experience. And opposes airport extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now talking about investing in airport. :( #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Pierson next. Supports supports living wage. :) #meetthecandidates but qualifies with as far as I could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon bonner thinks he has a long time. But looses track of time. #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confusion over timing but the egg timer will rule supreme.   #meetthecandidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently we using #meetthecandidates #wccmeetcandidates]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>