<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We should probably invade Mexico before we build the wall, you know to save gas money having to go around it.… https://t.co/yGlzaRx1zE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bobcat is *ok*!  https://t.co/EhS8qiQwZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists: I expect you to be writing articles showing most terrorists in the US are white Christian males. Get i… https://t.co/kV4RGcNdeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny_Odegard @johnthelawyer I guess law-practice and legal-tech are just fundamentally different.  *shrugs*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny_Odegard @johnthelawyer I get that, but I'm saying that after years of hiring, arbitrary screens dont help me find *better* candidates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnthelawyer @Jenny_Odegard As the employer, why make hiring harder for candidates? I've been a hiring manager for years, don't get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnthelawyer @Jenny_Odegard And I certainly don't expect them to answer trivia. A job is just a job, not a talent show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnthelawyer @Jenny_Odegard it's pretty hard to jump through *everyone's* different hoops. I'm not offended if an applicant flubs a letter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnthelawyer @Jenny_Odegard I'm guessing y'all haven't applied for a job in a while; when you're sending out *hundreds* of cover letters..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chezrebellion @MMazanec22 @aidanfeldman again, it doesn't work that way. Not to be pedantic but it's not "investing" its paying for things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protip: You probably don't need a mobile app. https://t.co/jOPDapcGsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*waves from DC* not for everyone, @SenFranken  Please remember this when our Statehood bill comes back. https://t.co/Mu3C9JOdJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMazanec22 @chezrebellion @aidanfeldman Totally agree. I'm just pointing out that you can't compare apples and oranges. NY != OH != KS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chezrebellion @aidanfeldman I spent years working this data for FTA, it's not so straightforward as "states pay for it".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chezrebellion @aidanfeldman state money is only part of transit income; federal, local, and revenue also count; agencies are locally run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waldojaquith @pcrickard Yup, that's the one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waldojaquith @pcrickard Ohhhhh I remember *that* book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidanfeldman New York has one of the largest heavy rail systems in the country, Ohio... not so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost like our entire government is acting as some sort of huge distraction... 🤔 https://t.co/FVDEHCCZ8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abhinemani I thought it was Dark Knight Rises ?  https://t.co/wgEUGVXEs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not how charts work, but some useful numbers in here anyway. https://t.co/QuEQxVOMmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thread: https://t.co/pSTf1EpsLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webinista Sorry, I didn't see that! My apologies, I saw Paul's first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open office plans: still a terrible idea. Privacy creates productivity.  https://t.co/OThn8RZ6SP https://t.co/2jYXS1gmF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krues8dr (Disclaimer: I also made their website. As most of you geeks will realize as soon as you view source.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The work @LegalAidJustice is doing is critically important. I have supported them for years, you should too!  https://t.co/vShZBLtQEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knowtheory @manuelaristaran It's a remix, but forever one of my favorites: https://t.co/NsLS4vC7fP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single representative should be held accountable in this way. Get to work! #accountability https://t.co/dNX9kWDHUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A private company is in no way required to provide equal access to hate speech in search listings.  Period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #GooglersUnite really wanted to do something meaningful, they could start by removing hate sites from Google's listings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juphoff As a resident of DC, this is too close to home on way too many fronts, but mostly literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the best 80s movies I've ever seen. https://t.co/j9H4lJFWCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski Right now you have it set on "duplicate t-shirts" but that only works on cotton unless you load a polyester cartridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sharon_Paley the ACLU isn't a nonprofit. They have a foundation that's separate, but the main body isn't that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely day for a march!  We can keep doing this, every week! Every day if we must! #Resist #DC https://t.co/AEIkpuB33C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realize what the ban + https://t.co/8lN6ScTVMK together mean.  Time to add #NoWar to #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jalbertbowdenii Then maybe you shouldn't go. We have to put the cause ahead of personal feelings. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jalbertbowdenii *We all should go and be respectful if we want them to listen to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielschuman There's a light... over at the Frankenstein place? https://t.co/a46l1PPl5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to GW Law and @vdavez for having me to talk about Government Data. My slides are shared here: https://t.co/IuelqQ53vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidhubaba I think they'd bum me out too much.  https://t.co/bnosxAe8kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomadicism @elle_mccann Historically, this hasn't had any impact, @IBM and others are still doing fine. https://t.co/wVbxzrkyXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sashacuerda @jeremybowers Have you heard the gospel of PostgreSQL who added JSON support for our NoSQL sins?  https://t.co/Xt8jAQMKTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremybowers I think we're going to have to have an intervention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like that we are scheduling the resistance to coincide with taco days.  This is good thinking. #🌮 https://t.co/i6ULrUVcNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW POLL: Trump voters think he should be allowed to have a private email server https://t.co/7bKhpgqgb8 https://t.co/eqCpHGlADL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am still furious that @npr "Well, actually"ed the American people at this moment. Now is the time for boldness. https://t.co/z9dazLUGZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@npr if you are too cowardly to call a lie a lie, you will not get another dollar from me. https://t.co/ByNAKJDjoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ghost In The Shell ad on the screen in the DC subway is the most #cyberpunk thing I've ever seen. And dystopian because whitewashing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@internetrebecca All day today! Weird, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spent a long time wishing there was a twitter for just news, and then remember that's what "journalism" is supposed to be. 😡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My current ability to deal with the news: a gif. https://t.co/VtWbdKRoIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjl Is this because we must first protect the Marcel Duchamp pieces?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really more of an ad for the need for better sexual health education in schools. https://t.co/cSXHWV8TmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you finally start seeing news agencies using plain, non-doublespeak language to cover politics. https://t.co/Rhfagr09jQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DataLensDC @laurenancona Or maybe we should start a pets choir group?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewSaysGoVeg Check for single-bolt clearance, and don't forget that dyeing is always an option!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewSaysGoVeg Depends on what you need. Wholesale you need a business license usually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewSaysGoVeg Wholesale/by-the-bolt is usually going to be cheapest.  Remnants won't get you but so far if you need *a lot*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@internetrebecca Which falls faster: a pound of patience or a pound of brains?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah but where do I get one of those Open Law buttons? https://t.co/99ZMIUQIeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elle_mccann I will gladly give my dollars to a news org that tells the truth boldly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If Roe Fell? A state-by-state breakdown of abortion rights in the US. https://t.co/CWCihs0bMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepGoodlatte Remember when we gave the TSA "gold keys" and now anyone w/ a 3D printer can open any luggage?… https://t.co/iIoI1O3wuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greydnls GovTrack is a great way to follow bills like this! https://t.co/2MKS9tBJLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bitb They redid it in 2009 you know!  With Morena Baccarin of Firefly fame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski Glad that I could help spice things up there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJordanDetamore That's closer to what I'd expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJordanDetamore UPT (trips) / HR (heavy rail) / DO (Directly Operated) is the relevant metric here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJordanDetamore I just checked; that doesn't match up with the NTD data.  https://t.co/b5mqGXxvDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJordanDetamore That doesn't look right either. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJordanDetamore That doesn't look right. From my days in transit data, ~700K would be closer, and ridership is down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other terrible ideas include: leaving the United Nations. https://t.co/Z2RqHK5sPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a privacy reminder: it's not a smart idea to text a random number telling them you attended a political rally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The McDonald's that everyone was so worried about yesterday was doing plenty of business during the rally today.… https://t.co/Lgjot7vfEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never seen so many people in one place at one time! So happy to be surrounded by passionate, loving people!… https://t.co/gpZu3LhfJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theophani those are generally oil-based and not ideal for drinks since they don't blend, they float on top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@internetrebecca Our cats tore a hole in the bottom of our box springs so they could climb inside.  We had to put plywood under the bed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if you think that the going gets tough
Just remember
What Time is Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidhubaba only downtown. Quiet everywhere else since most of DC is shutdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jalbertbowdenii We still have drug testing in the fed :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jalbertbowdenii most of the gov is closed today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrisj Good stuff.  Was just listening to PTF and Empires yesterday.  Airships also seems kinda relevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most talented gypsy jazz musicians I've gotten to hear – definitely give this a listen! https://t.co/sn90ibSI46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenvholmes @razvancaliman I'm not sure - but I get visible *flickering* of gradients in Chrome for some reason. Must be weird internals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wikisteff We're already seeing this; e.g. WMATA in DC is struggling horribly due to underfunding and declining fares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vees iFixit for parts and do it yourself?  Takes about 15 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @libbycwatson! And moreover to @gizmodo who've gained a great teammate! https://t.co/59aZ8RhwoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paultag uhhhhh not sure I'd want to be wearing a cross pattée in today's political climate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Droppin' pull requests on the weekend like https://t.co/B4FkQgUFMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistersql There's also a large amount of Jpop in there.  I haven't looked for the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistersql Spotify has a pretty extensive Kpop collection. It's even a default "genre." https://t.co/K2ciEE4N8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski I have always had a similar issue with the DQ Blizzard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waldojaquith Just need the right tool for the job. https://t.co/WWiStm9wZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlissner My partner's father's zip code is 65536 =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[98 people a day. 4 people every hour. https://t.co/P9X0jtr1TH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zines and posters are awesome, too! https://t.co/CJY7j2YKeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaseGilliam @chris_whong as I said offline - if you have to resort to scraping custom log formats, you've chosen the wrong tool. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wahoowilky certbot's got a command you can add to cron to auto-rotate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris_whong You'll be unable to tell the atomic changes without more digging. So it doesn't solve for that use case easily?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>