<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine Thank you. Please vote NO on Sessions. Please Withhold Consent &amp;  Filibuster all legislation until immigrant ban revoked, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edyong209 @emilynussbaum @NewYorker More efficient just to add the 6th "W"... WTF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And the question becomes: Are we going in out of our national interest or because there’s a Trump casino around?" https://t.co/lkFr84isBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MassGovernor @MassAGO Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["botched roll-out of the immigration executive order was coordinated for the most part by...Stephen Miller... and .… https://t.co/ta7b1aqpub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, still selling Trump products.  What say you @JeffBezos, time to clean house? #GrabYourWallet  @shannoncoulter https://t.co/S9P8BpNfWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Republicans will have to decide whether they will be complicit in the President’s reckless, wrathful and unconstit… https://t.co/OEsU5SqoiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PernellMeier @shelly2161 @IndivisibleTeam Go to their twitter. Live stream pinned tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Sorry, no. You're not taking into account the "eggs" with 0 followers. Dig a little deeper, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yet you had Americans meeting Hitler and saying, "This guy is a clown. He's like a caricature of himself."  Sound… https://t.co/07TAUNVgFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what the #UnholyTrinity is counting on. https://t.co/JI36XFi7fE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon-"pathological liar who has a temperament that governs by bullying &amp; intimidation &amp; functions very much like… https://t.co/Z321lkPRvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, it's the #UnholyTrinity that must be stopped. Trump is just a stooge. https://t.co/53NkyeBczU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy Does anyone else feel that Trump is a delusional patsy and Pence is the real monster we should be watching?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Latinatude It's the Zombie Apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["20 Diversion Tactics Highly Manipulative Narcissists, Sociopaths And Psychopaths Use To Silence You"  https://t.co/uKgs8Zjx2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Because giving clean air and clean water to everyone has got to stop." https://t.co/2olbG4O8gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So, those dead ones who registered to vote, they're zombies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Trump is doing 1 ridiculous thing after another HOPING to get "fired" because he doesn't really want this job - just wanted to win it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Do you suppose he'll have TRUMP in gold letters displayed all along his wall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slpng_giants They're an alternative facts site. ~smirk~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattOrtega This is a distraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum It's a distraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump 11-18-2016, "“The Statue of Liberty is an ugly statue... Certainly not a ten. She’s got no chest." https://t.co/lBK8SquxR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump Hotels to Triple Locations in U.S."  https://t.co/xoV5KCiCsB via @MattOrtega https://t.co/HfhLR7oehU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["a membership at Mar-a-Lago now includes a chance to mingle with the 45th president." https://t.co/xoV5KCiCsB via @MattOrtega]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["only 21 percent of Trump’s Twitter followers are real" Trump’s Biggest Lie? The Size of His Twitter Following. https://t.co/fXwzCeMgtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["only 21 percent of Trump’s Twitter followers are real, active users" https://t.co/fN6UAdUyxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Campaign slogan, "Hindsight is 2020." Hope that made you smile - or at least groan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fangeeker @tedlieu I may have to steal that sign. It'd make a great twitter cover photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["United States will import the same amount of crude from Canada through 2030 whether or not Keystone XL is built." https://t.co/MS19tavygP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaajenBhaskar @thinkprogress @POTUS Gotcha. Thanks for the info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam @thinkprogress Is this normal? Is this legal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaajenBhaskar @thinkprogress Is this normal? Is this legal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer Can you win back your credibility? https://t.co/Yr8TQyw9oO Sean Spicer 1/4/2017 interview with David Axelrod re lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got Call the Halls: Contacting Your Representative the Smart Way from @editoremilye on @Gumroad: https://t.co/dOlDaDEJH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein @ProfCAnderson @AoDespair I guess I shouldn't be surprised politics works this way. Just heartbreaking on all levels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter BTW, I haven't said this, yet, but THANKS for all you're doing. I'm learning lots and making calls thanks to your efforts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Same mindset as repeal ACA - a "disposable" mindset to throw stuff out instead of fix it. Lazy and potentially disastrous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Or cutting your nose of to spite your face... you know, all those cliches that are cliches for a reason? ;-).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Looks to me like throwing the baby out with the bath water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explains Trump's press strategy - be warned. https://t.co/cWs6DYpOlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marchers, what's next? @womensmarch: CALLing https://t.co/15OenxaxyH, ORGANIZing https://t.co/cfqesCqssJ, LEARNing https://t.co/OuNzjABEEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...the Trump cake was intended to be more of a prop: All but a three-inch slice at the bottom was inedible." Becau… https://t.co/51btQZLrAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS, unfollowed, FLOTUS, unfollowed, trump, unfollowed. TV, off. Signing off Twitter, now, cya tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnnDwyer5 @lsarsour Divided, we fall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Support I know it'd be a temporary fix, but couldn't you delete all accounts with 0 followers and 0 tweets, say, after 5 days? = trolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump article, but also "Erik Prince’s sister, Betsy DeVos, was named Education Secretary by Trump, despite having… https://t.co/UQH8gUCoHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei James, I'll admit, an interesting POV - a true separation of church and state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Yes, please? Ditto re phone anxiety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei James, I believe everyone has the right to marry whomever - regardless of gender identity or sex organs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei James, human right - a right that is believed to belong justifiably to every person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei  James, marriage - the legally or formally recognized union of two people as partners in a personal relationship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei James, we won't change each other's minds, but I'll go a round or two...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingjames8289 @GeorgeTakei It always amazes me when people against Human Rights for everyone claim to be Christians. smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realWhitWatson hirotadad1 is a Trump supporter and a troll. Please do your own research? His comment is not supported by facts. Best Wishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Unfortunately, no. "Can TV Viewers Protest Donald Trump's Inauguration by Changing the Channel?" https://t.co/HDFKhkLbF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Unfortunately, no. "Can TV Viewers Protest Donald Trump's Inauguration by Changing the Channel?" https://t.co/HDFKhkLbF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics He has no clue. He says what his supporters want to hear, then points to his team and says, "Make it happen." Clueless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indivisiblenj4 Questions and supporting info so clear and concise. Brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMarkTakano Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJudyChu Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTedLieu Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepRubenGallego Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Possibly your tweets are annoying Trump's team so he/they/Putin turned their trolls loose on you? I'm not even kidding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Because he prefers little girls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoAnnDwyer5 @PPact Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts  Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @womensmarch Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkRuffalo @womensmarch Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATT You're sending mixed signals by advertising on Breitbart - please block them. @slpng_giants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_hami_chi @shannoncoulter @ShopLloydCenter @Spencers @MaryNumair Hope they come thru. Imagine explaining that shirt to young daughter?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Republican Party currently unofficially endorses sexual assault." https://t.co/vEMB5I1sMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[370 Cities Across The World Just Announced Trump Inauguration Protests - https://t.co/1A2fvLUHCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepDonBeyer Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig Trump's favorite weapon - fear - in the form of intimidation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesilberman Check out this young actor's work. https://t.co/V9Pd3blT2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint @womensmarch Thank you Michael Moore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for a chuckle, heh heh heh. https://t.co/IY64I4HDxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMarkTakano @repjohnlewis Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepYvetteClarke @realDonaldTrump @repjohnlewis Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJudyChu Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllisGBS @shannoncoulter @LLBean Amazon is my achilles heel. Too easy to online order EVERYthing there. Trying to retrain myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan  Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marching in DC with @womensmarch on Jan 21? Please watch this short video on being prepared.   https://t.co/WrMhlImNu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell The ONLY reason I read DJT's tweets is hoping there will be Bess replies - the only smiles I get these days. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @IndivisibleTeam for How To steps on contacting Congress and more - Trump Resistance. GREAT info. https://t.co/PV6k9V5L1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @IndivisibleTeam for How To steps on contacting Congress and more - Trump Resistance. GREAT info. https://t.co/1QYSgJgNSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An investigation led by Jeff Sessions and Jim Comey will never be accepted ... as having fairly and adequately add… https://t.co/a1muEszmQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis Thank you, Mr. Lewis, for standing up for us. ALL of us. I am eternally grateful for your courage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The news media can’t afford a backslide. It’s going to have to do its part to avoid one." https://t.co/d5Fx6qM11a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He showed us that the office, and the pressures therein, will further derange him." https://t.co/WLkWqSdN78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone should run up and grab one of those folders. I bet most if not all of them hold blank sheets of paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Just... thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wyden also apparently fears that once Trump takes over the executive branch, this information...would be suppresse… https://t.co/VF1Re5W94b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow Regardless of what happens moving forward. One silver lining is more Americans are getting involved with their government.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>