<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[OOF, from the NZ Herald's political editor @audreyNZH https://t.co/RGx278oh1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headphones on and ready to go, Sabra Lane is about to host her first AM, @Birmo will be joining her #auspol https://t.co/r7CvjIKftM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bali 9 member Myuran sukumaran's exhibit is definitely worth the trip to Campbelltown https://t.co/kRdonoA28k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still in shock Tay-Tay didn't make it to number one this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull reiterates Australia Day's date should stay #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says Australia does not practice torture (on whether he supports Trump's comments) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says the attack in Bourke st is an example of a vulnerability the govt has to address (uses example of bollards) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says innovation will continue to be his catchphrase this year #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will this just create a black market for Mexican goods? If you can smuggle people, you can smuggle coronas https://t.co/eFPHLu5DDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he wants to have one on one trade deals but not "mash pots" like the tpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captain Cook landed at Botany Bay on the 29th of April #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ScoMo says recognising Cook's arrival is recognising a process of reconciliation, the meeting of two cultures #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ScoMo says he doesn't think Australia Day should change and all Australians can embrace all of our stories #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ also pushing to continue with the TPP #auspol https://t.co/iH8ltSfpNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FJKeany @stephendziedzic you guys aren't even dads though, there's no excuse for you being keen on rain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's not much Jacob's Creek in this recipe.... it seems the perfect way to serve it is to dilute it https://t.co/LvInx2XPnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh is the only pollie who isn't pulling a weird face in this photo (which he chose and uploaded) #auspol https://t.co/ZB4CoQh2lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10% of Victroria's electricity will go to Alcoa under a deal with AGL https://t.co/ggg0uXwHZY #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelialouisenz this is too fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClareAliceMurph Singing 90s classics like "bye bye bye"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benraue yep, state premier, my bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Gladys Berejiklian becomes Premier, she'll be the first woman from the Libs to be a state leader (sorry Kate Carnell, ACT don't count)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JBish was gifted some running shoes by a spa resort in Japan https://t.co/RYmTM6CwaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baird says he'll be leaving Parliament once a new Premier is installed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baird says he tried to go as hard as he could, as long as he could and he only decided in the past couple of weeks to resign #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Baird doesn't say who his preference is for the next NSW premier #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Baird says he strongly believes his team has made a difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Baird says he's proud he was one of the first states to sign up to Gonski #auspol  and uses his resignation speech to say its important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Baird's resignation has the exact same "surprise" feel of John Key's.I wonder if they're starting a cross-tasman think tank or boy-band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you not know if you've smoked a joint? I feel like he's avoiding being branded a crim or uncool https://t.co/dYLH7VJPT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I suspect we'll have a whole bunch of mixed up presidents at some time" - Obama on race and the Presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama says Manning's sentence was very disproportionate to what other leakers had received and it made sense to commute the sentence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama says he told the media "don't do stupid stuff", sounds similar to Gillard's "don't write crap"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to be the minister for participation".... said no gold medalist ever #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[parts of that cake look quite difficult to eat https://t.co/VyK2obNiFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've sung it... many times. In public places https://t.co/pJbXBJ7Muh https://t.co/h28Q5oycQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp he instead just read the lyrics and said "I'll work on it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shorten is refusing to sing Zayn Malik &amp; Taylor Swift's "I don't wanna live forever" right now #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull on expenses says "I'm going to shake this up, I can tell you there is a big cultural change on the way" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serving 3 years of a 35 year sentence https://t.co/hWBOZfoaRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration says it was "sufficiently agile" in a "unique and highly complex environment".. #auspol https://t.co/n2k9LVVh7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joekellyoz True, maybe its only pool table in the world with 3 sockets on the bottom side or maybe there's a helpful leporcorn on the table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joekellyoz or maybe he just sucks at geometry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That 11 ball isn't going in the socket, sorry https://t.co/fNTdai5pwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says Donald Trump has asked him to come over and see him soon and he'll be making arrangements in due course #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull really selling "two factor authentication" here #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says he will be making an announcement "very shortly" on new health minister #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says Australia has a very easy going society and we don't tell people what to wear (on the burqa) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says shorten is a populist on the TPP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull has asked his cyber security adviser to give him a report on how the Yahoo hack affects Fed MP's security #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull is urging Australians to use two factor identification to avoid hacking  #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull isn't sure if Hockey will be at Trump's inauguration... but Hockey has tweeted he'll be there #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Turnbull says Ita is "innovative" and straight after someone whispers "there's that word again" #auspol https://t.co/4IGYmSOY1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton says he basically doesn't use the government's mobile phone, he uses his own #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton says he's going down in history for pointing out an admin error with the High Court #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton now listing what he says are his achievements while being a senator #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton still insisting he's not bankrupt #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says he hasn't received an invite to Trump's inauguration #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says it is in Australia's interest to have greater access to Asia markets #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, will Rod Culleton be super-gluing his hands to the Senate seats? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten says "that door has closed" says shorten on the TPP and says the government needs to be looking at other options #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten is calling for a frank and open discussion about a Federal ICAC.. through a senate committee #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten says the political donation system also has to be sorted out, like expenses #AUSPOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten says Ley's situation hasn't just hurt the govt but all politicians #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten on the TPP "It takes two to dance, the Americans aren't even up for the dance" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadiasdaly I wish, it's just a really hot day and the 7/11 seems to be the local hangout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The slurpie line at parramatta's 7/11 is ten people deep right now. No joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp *it'd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's suck if this place sucked. https://t.co/Q50kvbrSGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summernats: when the petrol station becomes da club #cbr https://t.co/Vk06G9pJhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dep PM Joyce on whether Ley's purchase was "reasonable judgement" replies, "that's a question you'll have to ask her" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyce says Ley had legit business at the Gold Coast #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp *purchase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyce says Ley made a "substantial purpose" but that's not why she went to the Gold Coast #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Albo on Ley says he won't respond to "circumstances I don't know" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I be worried that Russia is coming out of Albo's head? https://t.co/MDlB3mW3V1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCNews24 I know! I deleted it as soon as I realised my misdemeanor. Sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanieando Lindt chocolate when I'm feeling fancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I impulse buy mars bars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you tell its not Borat, Ali-G or Bruno? https://t.co/fX3FG64EVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbenjaminlaw Amazing! [locks arms and strolls to grab a roti]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbenjaminlaw do you count sub-continental peeps? I want to be part of the club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shalailah the alco-pop tax debate gave them such a bad stigma but they're really just an expensive glass of drinkable fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't skol beers but I once skolled a breezer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @SueLucyCole that looks amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payne says Australia is working very hard to overcome the issues with Indonesia #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payne says that it will be an administrative inquiry into Indonesia incident #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter yesterday, "we've recovered $300m so far", Jorgen with @kumitaguchi today, "we've IDENTIFIED $300m in tax payer's money" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Well that's like The Secret, isn't it. You'll just have to wait and see how it all plays out" - Rod Culleton on his bankruptcy case #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton insists he can pay his debts #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[over the Israel vote https://t.co/ohdLoTS9RC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That was not shaping up" - Culleton (without the rest of the Greece lyrics)  #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["it felt like one of the bulls back on the farm.... although I've never really had an encounter with a bull" - Culleton #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[quite the contradiction with their election policy https://t.co/L8gHbnQKnR #nzpol  #auspol https://t.co/S4z39DWAUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter is basically separating those who officially complain (just over 1%) &amp; those who've had to correct the record (1/5 ppl) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter is admitting 20% of centrelink debt recovery letter recipients haven't had to pay back the money #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMcIlroy surprising Tas has the highest rate, given Port Arthur was the catalyst for the crack down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's photographer reveals he hid between secret service agents so he could take this photo of Key, Turnbull and… https://t.co/bA1AwCt8ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pedestrians usually take precedence over cars in Sydney - but nye takes it to a whole nuther level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed Min Ryan on why the new lease was signed for the shooting range says the nsw rifle assoc has had "long standing use" of the land #auspol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>