<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Some people will wax lyrical over a smooth epidermis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
After a brush with the law, the graffiti artist took to the human epidermis as a tattooist. He saw the writing on the wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhamill4 - Indeed an alarming visual...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Miss Piggy knew that her friend would just keep playing spanghew until he croaked. She didn't want him to Kermit suicide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
My pet frog loves playing spanghew. Every day is Ground Frog Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
In his first week the president got up and took the oath of office and up everyone's nose

It happened zeugma rather than later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
"Not guilty Your Honour. I wasn't stalking that policeman. I was just following the loiter of the law"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Many a case of rhotacism can be traced to the loud whirring of helicopter blades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Senescence isn't all bad. Just ask a sexagenerian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Organic food, vitamin pills, yoga, jogging - all these efforts to keep senescence at bay certainly keep me on mitosis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
That expensive potion I bought to ward off senescence? One look in the mirror and I knew the quack was telomere a lie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
When Aberrant played their hit song "Waterloo" at the presidential inauguration, there was a Pussy Riot in Red Square.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Hippies throughout the land would get in their vans &amp; coalesce at the music festivals of the 60's. It was a great Kombi Nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Trump had enough voters coalesce for an election win but is his angry finger-pointing now seeing them disperse?
His short fuse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Rocky Puccoon settled into his hotel room for the day with Gideon's Bible. He hadn't red it before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The bulwark on Wall Street generated excitement but it was nothing compared to the bare walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
She was self conscious about her huge breasts so she used a large badinage round her chest. She couldn't take a little ribbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn - And yes, I put the IP address into Safari, tried login &amp; P/W but the screen froze. What to do now? New router from iiNet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn - Are iiNet customers expected to update the firmware in their router (whatever that means) as a matter of course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
A giant anaphora escaped from the zoo and there was panic everywhere. In the streets. In the homes. It was a major epistrophe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn Hi Darryn. I have been trying to get thru to support this am (AEST) My router reverts to factory settings on hot days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Wear a raincoat
Take an umbrella
When you follow
That Trump fella.

Aphorism for the cautious Russian spy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The zookeeper was proud of the progeny of his Big Cat breeding program. They were the fruit of his lions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
"How about some more bacciferous?"

Oh no, Grandpa must have run out of Borkum Riff again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Bowdlerize? That's when the rooster gets into the henhouse and it's a major flustercluck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I don't know what came over me on NYE to dance naked indomitable but when the table broke, the bottle of DOM overcame me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The introduction of a sin tax in Anacoluthia was a success. The average sentence was cut in half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhamill4  What the devil?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I can't think what to do about the billboard opposite my house that likes to promulgate lies. Maybe I just advert eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Donald Trump
Fancies himself as quite a hump
To promulgate his moves he's never wussy
He just grabs 'em by the pussy
#clerihew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
He boasted that his ability to crenellate his bed post was top notch. He must have been right. He didn't have a leg to stand on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Meiosis? Now that I have your undivided attention...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
My boss berates us with his hairy chested browbeating. He's such a harangue utan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
To be asthenic is a pirate's dream. They love a sunken chest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BelkinCares - Could have been a brief power outage or a surge or both...not sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
For the asthenic, life is no pyknic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet Hey Guys, My Belkin router keeps resetting autonomously, losing its name &amp; PW each time so that it is open. What can you do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Expertise with the glossa is in a man's DNA. It's in the way helix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Defalcate?
That's when you start with a lot
But end up with diddly squat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
We called our octopus Caesura because he always wants to High Eight us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Down Under it's Summertime (and the livin' is easy) so a gin and chthonic is just the thing on a hot day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Try and say chthonic quickly three times and you're in grave danger of inducing a coffin fit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
My dog looks so innocent but in truth he is a destructive devil. Every single pair of my shoes is verisimilitude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The South Africans say they have a good jaunce of a gold medal in the triple jump with their star athlete from Capertown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Too many people took a big gambol when they elected that liverish man with a bad dose of jaunce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
His sobriquet? We called him Sob, the old son of a bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Anyone who tries to circumscribe Trump's Twitter rants could find themselves kicked to the curb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Tolkien needed to circumscribe his writing after the Lord of the Rings trilogy. It had become too much of a hobbit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
There's nothing complicated
About terriculament
Of being aloft in a metal capsule
In the firmament
It's just plane fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fields of green
Skies azure
Pity about
The cow manure

#artwiculate #agrestic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I'm in favour of getting back to one's agrestic roots with a roll in the hay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
If you struggle with profligacy then try a diet of wan ton soup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Why does Trump's face turn puce when he watches Saturday Night Live? After all, he's just landed a plum job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Every specialist proctor needs a rear view mirror in the arsenal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
You've given us "proctor" just in time. We were about to give you the finger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
There is something fishy about solipsism.

Just ask me...
(or the 7.5 billion red herrings)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I lodged a protest when I failed my solipsism course but it was rejected. They said I had no one to blame but myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Some people get the heebie-jeebies after Lassie has one leg amputated. Most just get the collywobbles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Theresa May is quite a well known conservative but Margaret Thatcher is an even more promontory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Does a supererogation go beyond the call of booty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I'm having second thoughts about my habit of supererogation. I'm so overachievement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
When Miss Steatopygia gave a stirring rendition of "Danny Boy" there was resounding applause for her Derry Air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
No, it wasn't the first Tawny Owl to be spotted in the wild in Australia. It was just another Tawdry Frogmouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Some would say that lurid is just tawdry but I think "Walk on the Wild Side" is a class act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Why do vegans think that fake meat is crass?
There is something tawdry about mushroom dressed as lamb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
A tawdry affair
She should have known better
The truth was revealed
By a tacky French letter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The prolix shoplifter was always able to escape conviction. He had the gift of the grab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
My dog might be prolix but he doesn't understand "Yuck"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I wonder what happens
At night when in bed
To that schlock of hair
On Donald Trump's head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The Summer of Love was a time of antithesis and chemosynthesis, much to the chagrin of the parenthesis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
It's against the law to keep a basilisk as a pet as it's classified as a pesto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Life at Fawlty Towers was never the same for Sybil after she set eyes on Basilisk with his drag on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Wooed with genteel love songs her heart skipped a beat
But later that night she made a hasty retreat

"Ohh...That's a moray"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The duck-billed cat is a native inhabitant of butte country in Australia. It's a plateau puss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Impecunious? With the new US Vice President watching moral standards there won't be two Pence to rub together anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Trump lacks the panache of FDR and his "New Dealing". His noodling shows he's just a fishy pussy grabber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Many boys are told that noodling leads to blindness and they fall for it hook, line and sinker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Do you believe that Noah saved all the specious by loading them onto a big boat?
Surely you don't smell Ararat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Concinnity? Imagine.
Once upon a time, long, long ago, there was a summer of love..
You can say I'm a dreamer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Confabulate? That's just some hocus-POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Unsure whether to sanction?
It could be time to wave the big (s)tick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
When he offered to denude her, she was most offended. She believed she rated at least a 'B' nude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate #hearken
Hillary may play the hearken-saw but is she a match for Donald's strumpet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
A lily-white Trump emerged from the waters of the limpid lagoon. He left behind a fantasea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The limpid waters of the beach were perfect for a private skinny dip. The coast was clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
After too many glasses of clarety would always end up limpid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
A harpy never goes to the airline check-in counter as she just has carrion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
You can never get your own way with a harpy.

She who castigates is boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roofley From Facebook "The Soulful Woman" photos https://t.co/RhvfqExCLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fount8 @theage Shear bloody ignorance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I took a major in Psychoneuroimmunology but only a minor in Endocrinology. I'm not the glandiose type.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Trump's toothbrush moustache on his philtrum was no cover for the face cyst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
Edmund Hilding claimed to be the first man to climb Mt Everest but he was actually just a base person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
When he was drunk the hilding was nauseating. When he was sober he was a dry wretch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
The wooden jetty on the ait was destroyed by cockatoos so it was rebuilt in a synthetic material. Polly carbon ate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
It must have been a night to remember in the karaoke bar.
Everyone was saying "Opus myself laughing"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
All my dog can do is aporia. My friend has an octopus which hiatus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
He suddenly changed his mind about becoming a proselyte but he made his excuses in a roundabout way. A snip circum decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
I'm really excited about being a proselyte. They told me there would be lots of sin. Agog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#artwiculate
You know it's another cosseted Aussie softie when you hear them say "Sybarite, mate"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>