<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent #brexit meeting with @MichelBarnier just now in @EUparliament @FineGael https://t.co/ZnyDe8hrLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eurozone has defied its critics - eurozone annual growth up 1.8% sentiment best in 70 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good meeting this morning with @Antonio_Tajani @EUparliament @MaireadMcGMEP @SeanKellyMEP @EPPGroup https://t.co/KgkEFj2IAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the divine comedy at there best - full of 40 something's all enjoying themselves with music genius https://t.co/HLnZmX6P7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divinecomedyhq coming up here in @cirqueroyale - @neilhannon is a leg https://t.co/E4pmJX7tQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earlier today I signed @Europarl_EN motion opposing @realDonaldTrump #MuslimBan. This ban is not the solution to de… https://t.co/5Ntk3ECgcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My article in today's @sundaybusiness - we need to make sure that 'Irish issues' become 'European issues' in… https://t.co/KUstr54Jxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CondenserMick My only interest is the public interest -55,000 + ordinary people gave me a mandate. It's called democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haroldbarrett @IrishTimes @IrishTimesWorld Trump +hard left don't get it. without more free trade economies shrink… https://t.co/7MNHd1FruL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haroldbarrett @IrishTimes @IrishTimesWorld Macron would be great no? Free market, liberal, pro European, climate change believer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French election to be showdown between Macron and Le Pen
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/EaMU3PwpAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No place for Ireland in Theresa May’s and Donald Trump’s new world
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/TJCKsqgo8M excellent article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @FGDublinBaySth pub quiz here in @rathminesd6 @MurphyEoghan @campaignforkate https://t.co/So4iYBQSVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hayes says Ireland should issue green bonds
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/PnvqwtlIe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinnfeinireland MPs should take their seats in @commons following #supremecourtruling @irishdailystar https://t.co/ZCQWt0zOkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I met just now @EUparliament Dr. Ahmed Said, Chair of Egypt Foreign Affairs Comm &amp; raised the Ibrahim Halawa case @FineGael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy defeat for U.K gov in UK Supreme Court - parliament must trigger art 50. Legislation must be prosped. @EPPGroup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['America first' could hit us hardest - we must rule out nothing on future investment @FineGael  my article indo https://t.co/55WU7Pqa41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eu's ultra left+right must be delighted @realDonaldTrump+his anti Int trade nationalism-Strange bedfellows indeed #ttip @PopulistwatchIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the pupils from Saor Ollscoil, Dublin who visited @Europarl_EN  today https://t.co/3r8dOSf9uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was Trumps day - today the people were on the streets in big numbers.My money is on the people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The status of UK residents married to NonEU citizens in Ireland must be guaranteed #brexit https://t.co/N4EAjYk3ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God help America and God us all after that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trickstersworld Ireland doesn't have a right wing government - there I said it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Michael Ignacio talking a lot of sense on @BBCNewsnight. We all want globalization when it work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving Strasbourg and chatting to MEPS this week- it's clear that #brexit will be a marathon, not a sprint. Can someone tell the British!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MaireadMcGMEP on your re-election as vice president of the @Europarl_EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hard' Brexit simply means Ireland will have to be hyper-competitive to attract new business here - Great article https://t.co/cd5Jf4pm1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good meeting with @MichelBarnier today on #brexit He clearly understands the importance of this issue to Ireland… https://t.co/9nlOqtDPXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's no single market, no customs union uk want eu free trade agreement. Amazing after 6 mts of dithering. Brexit is 10 yrs plus away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First round of voting for @EUparliament president https://t.co/Y85iaOUWQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EU_Commission insists that we must comply with Water Directive under new system https://t.co/QC3dQio3xX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New generation of politicians seeks to erase the North’s divide
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/c5kNBlp9XL interesting article @harrymcgee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland must  not play the UK off against the EU
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/YiqOCO5V4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed visiting the @BTYSTE in @TheRDS. Great work &amp; dedication by students. Well done to all involved.… https://t.co/LHrDCGrr3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Paul Ryan @PayPal Dublin for filling me in on Dublin operations. 1600 employees is something to be proud of… https://t.co/EKiKS9iBPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be talking about the stories of the week shortly on @TodaySOR, @RTERadio1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to people of ballaghderreen - great response to Syrian refugees coming to Ireland @RTE_PrimeTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet @rioferdy5 today at @BTYSTE today - great advocate for science in schools https://t.co/QMTtxmvl8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A record 27.9 million passengers travelled through @DublinAirport in 2016; up 2.8 million on 2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Oldbawn Community School represented @BTYSTE https://t.co/WqoNeMoKIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great talent in Ashbourne today among the Irish Inclusive Karate team https://t.co/caXc8CvaCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EU_Commission should make itself available to Oireachtas Water Committee
https://t.co/hkOjOHkozq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HSBC says it will move activities ‘to France or Ireland’ post-Brexit
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/oHZj6CG8Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T. K. #Whitaker was a true patriot. His influence on how Ireland developed since the 1950s was enormous https://t.co/1m12ryW68p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Whitaker Irelands man of the century is dead.His brilliance helped to create a new ireland +successful Ireland. Long live experts! Rip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland should develop an informal #brexit coalition with like-minded EU countries  
https://t.co/0XCGNauFOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland one of seven countries to object to CCCTB-Hayes @FineGael @rtenews  https://t.co/Nx8NwKKbHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 national parliaments object to #CCCTB proposal
https://t.co/bMvdHm0H4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Hogan urges Ireland to keep distance from UK on Brexit
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/5M76ZUpCY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd Agree. thing I've learnt about Irish politics,we don't learn from history.having fixed the mess crucial… https://t.co/w2QAP1EI96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd Yes Connor we have big probs to sort. Totally agree. But those wud have been much bigger had we not foll… https://t.co/04HlLsf1pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd Iceland now want to join EU!They had plenty of austerity.They imposed cap controls+devalued.Had we done… https://t.co/kZcLaFuExE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World View: It makes sense to stick closer to Brussels than London on Brexit
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/hkYAtnBiGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd Conor we changed the conditions of deal/loans-rates, maturity,prom note etc-all done by FG/lab. No bailout=appalling suffering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd Without eu/imf bailout Ire wud have come into immediate balance ie cuts of €20b. In 2010 there was no eu… https://t.co/XsggBvUoGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's what I call leaving your mark! Pres Mitterrand passed away in 1996 is remembered today https://t.co/6H16h2d3Gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd @EPP bailout didn't stop tax collapse €20b in tax revenues went in 9 months! Eu didn't save the banks we… https://t.co/o2wExTJ8Fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMadd @EPP That's mad stuff - the austerity was because our tax base collapsed. Eu funding kept us going. Nobo… https://t.co/NbHM5Crdta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 6 years Corporation Tax revenue has more than doubled. @OECD &amp; Min Noonan tax plan is working @EPPGroup… https://t.co/eLQi0A0rtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Farage you are wrong about an #irexit - the uks decision to leave the eu has made Irish people more committed to EU @EPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No room for envoy with skill"- read my article in today's Indo- @epp @FineGael #brexit @rtenews  https://t.co/Q514O6Ug1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unemployment rate falls to lowest level since 2008 via @RTENewsNow https://t.co/KaraI3BXpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivan Roberts resignation months before his due date as U.K. ambassador in brusells is both telling and significant - @epp #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shortly on @MarianRTE reviewing papers in this New Year's Day @FineGael @EPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Year’s Eve begins in Dublin with spectacular show
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/U6o01Dh4x7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to Malta #EU2017MT - happy new year everyone &amp; don't forget - let's keep the recovery going! https://t.co/E0zM22xsqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tougher security measures proposed for online purchases https://t.co/7mAT4mSQne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Ireland would be the biggest loser from a breakup of the EU': Irish MEPs on Europe's future (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/BHXO32Xsts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New EU Rules could force extra security procedures on every online payment over €10 https://t.co/LpWbKuEh70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supermarkets have role to play in reducing food waste  https://t.co/W13sLYQYIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#leopardstown Christmas festival the only place to see and hear all the experts https://t.co/jXZq2Mg3Is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A final message for the big man in his big voyage https://t.co/ZFh8I7bQVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cliff Taylor: Greater uncertainty is the only thing we can predict about 2017
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/SKwugqIWT0 always interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BlackSanta at st Ann's COI @DawsonStreet1 - cold but great sound https://t.co/VHYTybdOey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Johns: It’s all about houses and jobs, stupid
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/oNlAEmEtWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish development NGOs will especially be affected by Brexit https://t.co/y9sHYwemnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #wintersolstice at the amazing @opwireland monument #newgrange @EPP_IE https://t.co/SjWktkUGvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our thoughts are with the people of Berlin today @epp@CDU_CSU_EP https://t.co/tEmHl5tUW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot allow the @EIB to fund the European arms industry
https://t.co/k2CakxRJji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Commission ‘exceeded its powers’ in Apple tax case
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/AsDLiVhWWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going on @BreakfastNT now to discuss benefit tourism across Europe @FineGael @epp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week I joined President @MartinSchulz  for the signing into law of the new EU Occ Pension Funds Directive  https://t.co/LHS6GM2I3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have been appointed vice coordinator of @EPP Econ - look forward to working with @EP_Economics colleagues @RTEbusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too little too late on EU ‘benefit tourism’ crackdown 
https://t.co/otd3JUnPKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to join President @MartinSchulz today for the signing into law of the EU Occupational Pension Fund Direct… https://t.co/K6u1X0dEya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big turnout for @epp group meeting Strasbourg to select @epp candidate for @EUparliament President https://t.co/zVOkC9hjNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 fact on #brexit. Dub to London air link is busiest route in Europe - every week 850 flights to and from DUB to UK. @epp @FineGael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yasidi women win #SakharovPrize - outstanding courage against isis terrorists  - they are an inspiration to all EU https://t.co/x26iftSzfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Railroad conductor became choral conductor and serenaded his train with the help of Yale Glee Club https://t.co/cdfWfoLLx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money-for-nothing era is coming to an end – better get ready
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/a9lexytUsw Saturday's essential reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK lawyer to mount Article 50 challenge in Ireland via @RTENewsNow https://t.co/0M8TfgI4Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for Ireland at @EIB Dublin launch https://t.co/0dpvUtpW7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to be at @Kings_Hospital this morning addressing TY &amp; Politics &amp; European Studies students https://t.co/y9Zx45gyAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EIB president @morningireland - EIB one stop shop open in DUBLIN from today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland’s Money Market Funds industry will remain intact following new EU reforms 
https://t.co/E6TtAhXUT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dub Local Auth should be first in line for new #WIFI4EU initiative https://t.co/pNvl3eXFY0 @sdublincoco @Fingalcoco @DubCityCouncil @dlrcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Whelan: Good news for  Irish borrowers via @RTENewsNow excellent analysis junkers plan https://t.co/PJafGEAmX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My article in today's @irishdailymail 
"The Irish Left is Addicted to Failure"
 https://t.co/J9ze0wWCa8 https://t.co/iL5kD4FYby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shop outlets start taking payment by smartphone via @RTENewsNow https://t.co/ElzkCKHuY4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>