<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@saowall i think it's unlicensed in Ireland but can be bought online but I think you can buy some melatonin products here eg melatonin milk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bad on that sleep deprivation so I am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think, therefore I am" has really gone to lengths and depths that even Descartes himself probably didn't think was possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwoovo I just can't see what good it can add but it seems to be a done thing by many? food is odd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also, using ketchup in lieu of actual tomatoes or a simple tomato sauce is.... weird and unnecessary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do American recipes think high processed foods are viable ingredients for seemingly wholesome dishes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelmed and under-enthusiastic @ the prospect of turning my lit review from a concept into a physical body of work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglington still have one more day of January, that extra day will do all our nerves some good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo some day I will have to find someone that loves me as much as I love me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Valentine] @hunrealness's Valentine should be @hunrealness! Who should be yours?
via https://t.co/fQuVXKNyzR https://t.co/ycsgIYirzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: hasn't seen a straight person in days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeDonegan her teeth are LOVELY to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I love: Teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglington IAN IS OUR HERO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leechgrl I have no idea! What would you think if you heard "rough gay", out of curiosity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJamieSugrue yes,this is all your doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I offered to go and visit and they were like "no, sorry, we are going to visit your brother that weekend"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brother, who lives in Spain, will see my parents more often than I this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to be a good daughter and call my mother and she was like "I'm hosting a party bye".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo ily your new pic but ghee discharge makes for nasty imagery!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some scrote left their chewing gum in my candle holder. Dirty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a personal pizza and some wedges earlier and it was NOT ENOUGH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I say "wrestle" but I mean hug and hold so he didn't hurtle to his death)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 5:30am and I just had to wrestle a blind pug puppy that kept trying to fling himself off heights. How's your Saturday am going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["but iona, you have to come to vet ball, when else do you get the party til the next morning"
Me: https://t.co/f15nJ45cjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My back is so sore that it hurts to breath. There is no way I can carry on this profession and not come to an untimely end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep getting stressed about my future then I remember we are all hurtling towards the end of the world &amp; my problems seem miniscule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a little Maltese from a rescue with two broken legs in and she is the most gorgeous lil fluff of an excuse of a dog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if I become the girl that always has a little trickle of blood from one nostril and it turns out I am real like Eleven? That'd be cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earlier in the week the bridge of my nose was sore so i poked &amp; it has consistently bled in miniscule amounts ever since. What a way to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, in physical and mental pain from these 2 weeks, having to spend my time dishing out pain meds to patients, talk about unfair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo angel ðŸ˜­â¤! I have other food here too though so I will survive x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My soup leaked all over my bag and I forgot to bring my crisps. Tonight is going to be a long night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shookbitnch the night shifts and HORRIFIC period cramps actually have done me in this week in particular though ðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglington they look like a better version of the boots I wore at Halloween, can't even pretend otherwise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must have been a 1000 piece jigsaw puzzle in a former life for the amount of bits I am always in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo omg I was thinking the exact same, here's me with my near zero iron intake, constantly bleeding everywhere, like why am I a wreck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexRKiernan haha! No, veterinary nursing student in a vet hospital!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight is so quiet that it takes about 45mins to do each round of checks meaning I've to spend 12 hrs here for 3hrs of actual work. Yikes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To shame someone for rejecting sex or claiming they have a moral obligation to sleep with anyone is very twisted, fyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you never HAVE to go out with/sleep with someone and you are entitled to reject people you aren't attracted to, attraction can't be forced!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 of the girlies when we think we have to call quits on the weekend and then someone invites us over to theirs https://t.co/LXjECEBaUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harry_Birdboy don't get me wrong, I always have a great time but there's certainly very little variety &amp; to outsiders must seem so dull!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: I would rather fall of the face of the earth than be boring
Also me: has done the same thing every single weekend for the last 6 months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeDonegan have a wonderful time xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very bet on that sleep deprivation. With 8 and a half hours of my shift to go this is all set to be a wild time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other versions of hell include leaving your friends to go home to get ready of a 12 hour night shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My inability to keep my own possessions strikes again, another weekend gone, another bra lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shook to bits and pieces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daithi_O_Shade go for it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler 08/09 I was busy trying to be too cool, listening to nothing but Goldfrapp and yeah yeah yeahs, tragic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler I am severely late to the party, justice are a new find for me but their latest album is absolutely magnificent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler you actually aren't wrong! Though I am slightly concerned my broken headphones are leaking sound &amp; scaring the bus passengers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Justice through broken headphones is a wild ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My face is looking particularly betdown tonight, might be that 60 hour week, definitely not worth it. What a shit deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking home at 6am: a 2 picture study of red, light and architecture https://t.co/emYvTgdrX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglington I know. I am dirt. You're probably right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglington omg these are deadly!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blindly following the SJWs/progressive Lefts/"woke"/vocal individuals is not the same as being socially responsible &amp; aware yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grumpy_Kat1 I can't believe i missed the boat on what sounds like an absolute wild time ðŸ’” ignorance is not bliss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I only need answers for the first question)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does everyone (a) hate scoprios and (b) buy into astrology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo my cafe? Can you translate into normal English pls also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo I was trying to type with one hand and walk the dog at the same time and I totally flopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zintendo omg I need to be euthanized!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a dog here called Einstein.... I nearly cried when I heard his name, what is we ng wth keep, why are my emotions so outta whack?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campaigning for Apollo house and home sweet home, rather than slating the amount of men who have stepped forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idgi because as a public figure, if she wants more female representation, nothing is stopping her from actively campaigning?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghMcKenna her point is totally irrelevant to the situation and totally misplaced IMO. Helping the homeless isn't about gender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badseaband I think trying to make a wonderful charitable movement about gender representation trivializes HSH &amp; puts her in a bad light!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Una Mullally really try to make a dig at Home Sweet Home for being too male based? gender is inconsequential to some issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight I witnessed a dog pee on his own head and into his own face, by mistake. "Man's best friend" is an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was just sitting there and heard a noise and looked down to find my watch had cracked. How does that happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler you can get them in Dublin bus on O'Connell Street x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being cool is a myth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwoovo @darthellen pickles?! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ Been there! Also pickled onions and olives (on sperate nights but still, less appealing for sure!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen surely a love of pizza is grounds to date someone? Get yourself in with the right crowd gal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am telling you, that bang in the head on Saturday has done me NO favours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I have no concept of: reality.
Example: I genuinely spent most of last night thinking it was February.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bitnch amazing!! It's such a look! Good finds!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bitnch where did you get your Christine outfit ðŸ˜?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think it's ethical for me to go 2 whole weeks without getting to see daylight due all these placement shifts but what would I know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems unnecessary / how many people had to walk into this bollard for there to need to be so many cones? https://t.co/GSWsYoLeLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just witnessed the most obvious drug deal, honestly that dealer should match himself to the gardai and turn himself in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to leave for more 12 hours of exploitation in an hour. 60 hour weeks of night shifts are not what humans were designed for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise this was petitioned for before so v curious, do you this the trans community should unaffiliate from the LGBT community?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am afraid to brush my hair because my head is in so much pain. I hate how I have devolved into an actual parody of a human.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, in the last few days, have I adopted "making shapes" as a phrase?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will a learn that a streak of brown on my cheek and a stripe of shimmer doesn't equal contour &amp; highlight?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an act of evilness, window fitters were in the house this morning and left all the windows open so now my house is even colder than usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uughhhhhh can't remember the cost but it works with a tesco mobile sim, using data. you can sign up to a data plan or pay as you go afaik!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uughhhhhh i got one in tesco when I was stuck in a house with no internet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, just make the eulogy a dramatic reading of the ScheiÃŸe post chorus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biggest weakness is old dogs melting my heart. It's hard being this sappy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonguepop me when you come save me if I haven't escaped before then! https://t.co/CmwpJ3h8eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonguepop obviously but they can fail me if I leave before they tell me I am done so it is a bit....sketch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emconcannon this story gives me hope, never change x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 3 part story:1) i've been here since 7:30 2)for the first time ever, I forgot my lunch 3) someone asked if I would stay til 9pm for checks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I lost my headphones in fundrum, I am so upset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why even bother sleeping when I just wake up looking puffy faced, bleary eyed and uglie? How do ppl love sleep, this is a rubbish result...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>