<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ it's back on now thanks. Lost broadband and tv but all good now. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ outage in Wellington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parkers got his bounce back #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh is it? Bloody hell the boys will want to come too! @NawtyBuhNice @Razco @BenFeliuai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah I wanna go. When is it? @NawtyBuhNice @Razco @BenFeliuai @SIX60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've completed the Pottery Wizard quest in Cradle Of Empires. https://t.co/Doyqjpi2dK https://t.co/U1vlWo4kxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting for my blister sister to arrive #familytime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are so lucky to live in this beautiful country #thatisall https://t.co/r9U2P0JAPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave Bahaha. Just give me your paperwork to sign. I'll be your cta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave haha you're welcome. Gotta keep you baby nurses going! ðŸ’ŠðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave good luck for your first day! I know you will be awesome!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice haha I've gained 2 tops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit the chances of me making it home for the all blacks are slim to none]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know whose worse the drunk teenagers or the parents joining in #daughterturns18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewisrdcreamery happy to pass on the details. Phone got put down pretty quick when she saw us taking a photo ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewisrdcreamery love your products. Don't want to see your reputation tarnished by one silly person!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always disappointing to see people driving while on their phone especially when in company cars @lewisrdcreamery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox those counties girls deserve to win it this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox yeah it's rubbish that they aren't broadcasting this game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox keep us updated with the score then! You are my only link I was sitting here anxiously wondering what was going on lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox I thought someone was going to Facebook live it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox yay I'm glad you posted the score!! Not so pleased with what the score is thou ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnRugby @Mitre10Cup @skysportnz any idea of the score??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to our Pride ladies ðŸ¦ taking on Counties today #semifinals ðŸŒ‘ðŸŒ• @NawtyBuhNice @slevave @WgtnRugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice your turn to take over making the jelly and custard ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow what is with this weather #cantfeelmytoes #buslife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama has to show them who's boss ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ @NawtyBuhNice @Razco @BenFeliuai https://t.co/OMLk7KYGAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game day!!  Good luck ladies #WgtnPride. ðŸŒ‘ðŸŒ•ðŸŒ‘ðŸŒ• #growingthegame @slevave @alicesoapbox @NawtyBuhNice @WgtnRugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So so proud of my awesome boys ðŸ”µâšªï¸ #Wolfpack #BleedBlue #Norths https://t.co/180bIKH6M2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tallest u6 player I've ever seen ðŸ˜‚ @slevave https://t.co/rdo8JI0bu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hurricanesrugby where are the games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to celebrating our future black ferns and all blacks at tonight Norths Prizegiving #BleedBlue ðŸ”µâšªï¸ @NawtyBuhNice @axe__ah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To whomever gave me gastro I literally hate you. So dying right now ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice @alicesoapbox @axe__ah haha yeah just saw them on the pride page too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really an earthquake. Just the pride ladies taking the field ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¦ @NawtyBuhNice @slevave @axe__ah  https://t.co/D9x91muVz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome dinner out with the family tonight. #familyfirst #ourturntovisityounext https://t.co/6Q97GuCrLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half time at Pride vs Waikato 15-10 to Pride @WgtnRugby https://t.co/9UbeaqOV38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big ups to the pride sisters taking the field today. Good luck ladies @NawtyBuhNice @axe__ah @slevave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing our Pride ladies back in action tomorrow @WgtnRugby @NawtyBuhNice @axe__ah @slevave ðŸ¦ https://t.co/yjhvitc99f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great post game interview @nz7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of our NZ girls. Heartbreaking watching you lose. Hold your heads high ladies #Rugby7s #olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to hear the crowd getting behind the girls #Rugby7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USOuljah haha that's awesome!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're keen. Come on ladies #Rugby7s #Olympics2016 @nzolympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done #toughguygirlchallenge #sportykids #gotthis https://t.co/KV0SZzPzl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready to go #toughguygirlchallenge #gotthis #sportykids https://t.co/Xki3IOuwTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the year I can take 'frustrated hurricanes supporter' off my profile?! I hope so!#ourhouse #canetrain #CanesProud @Hurricanesrugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Razco! Bus it is! https://t.co/pSwOqqk5pV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hurricanesrugby we will be at the caketin! #itsouryear #seasonpasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice haha you been shopping up a storm!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice lol. Told you! Dennis has said that for ages ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shot @lilytaurau awesome fight! #teamtumeke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoTech when will the NZ servers be back up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ outage in Wellington? Can't get through to the technical team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok who has found life's pause button because after all the shit that's been thrown at me this week I need a break!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My awesome boys #playeroftheday #norths #wolfpack #setblue ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸ https://t.co/xLw8mi1IjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some beautiful runs from @slevave #setblue #northswomens ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow and now it's 2! @NawtyBuhNice #trytime #setblue ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnRugby 27-3 to Norths. Halftime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shot cuzzy @NawtyBuhNice #trytime #setblue ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodluck cuz @NawtyBuhNice @Razco lol #these2bitching #stateoforigin https://t.co/zOJLPUN4Jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave good luck #smashembro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Mother Nature sounds angry tonight âš¡ï¸ðŸ’¨ðŸ’¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave bahaha. Save your nerves for saturday! We will be there to cheer you and of course @NawtyBuhNice!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave what's up? Why the nerves??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANZ_NZ thanks. I'll check again before I call but still down at 12:05 https://t.co/nJ1T0v2VTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANZ_NZ still down. Any updates??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANZ_NZ when will Internet banking be back up??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of our little Wolfpack today! ðŸ”µâšªï¸ #kidsrugby #weshouldhavewon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning for rugby #gameday #upagainstthebestteam #tryyourhardestkids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnRugby great timing. Was just about to ask if anyone knew the score in the Norths game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantbrookesnz and to you! Mines full of post grad study. We are having a ward awards ceremony tomorrow if you are around pop in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikes_Brother good idea but they manage to bowl us over as it is ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents vs kids rugby. Great way to end a Monday ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I definitely have more cupcake days than salad ones  ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/TsyQOjlvWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NawtyBuhNice saw this. Thought of your post the other day ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/9FLTB3brBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirNZFairy coffee and cake! My favourite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superleeni a book? A classic one that they will keep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ thanks. I will try those tips once I get home. Very frustrating!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long to have to be on hold to actually talk to someone @vodafoneNZ No TV since yesterday!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have this stupid habit of alway coughing when I'm the last one on the bus. Just so the driver doesn't forget I'm there ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banana splits for lunch #schoolholidays #theystillnotdressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone remind me why I'm doing this?! #mastersprofprac #latenightstudying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My boys hanging out with their fav rugby players today @Hurricanesrugby https://t.co/iERj4pDCTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jarrr_deen @NawtyBuhNice nothing else to do while at church ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jarrr_deen @NawtyBuhNice she might have stolen my phone ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just want everyone to know @NawtyBuhNice rocks she's the best in the whole world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice start to the season @PulseNetball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So nice having our big boy randomly turn up for dinner tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready to go #golfinglife #samoanjuniorgolfacademy https://t.co/l8sTxY5GHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope all is going well @gayle_tristram thinking of you guys. Almost there hopefully! #otwnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gayle_tristram yay! Keep going guys. Will provide you with motivational tweets and texts during the night xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come there's no score being shown on the netball @skysportnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hurricanesrugby @CoryJane1080 looking forward to the first game of the season tonight. #hurricanes #hardoutfan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire above the Mt Vic tunnel https://t.co/ZrSMqZPmQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boys found the wii today and dragged it after many years. Pleased to say I am still the bowling champion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geez @SevenSharp what terrible footage of @BindiIrwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! RIP Jonah, your battle is over. Much love and thoughts to his family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our boys are having golf lessons.  They are actually pretty good. Hope they keep at it #retirementfund ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 and 1/2hrs of sleep in 3 days is not cool.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>