<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@1rorycowan @DeirdreOKane1 yippee- can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam yes sounds great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @denisemcactress best dance p the night for me on @DWTSIRL fabulous!   #DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @Desbishop dancing to Club Tropicana on @DWTSIRL #DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1rorycowan great photo - can't wait for the next seriesðŸ–’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam cant wait x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam ah but your kids are little angelsðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy love the way he won't make eye contact with you - guilty faceðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam was Liam on the team? https://t.co/ELfLEU8A6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam twitter account for LCC https://t.co/CBQNdlmeme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liammckenna1 @DWTSIRL I know I can't believe it!! Mahogany!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubcoCU the Alzheimers Society of Ireland is a worthy cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@budgetireland @MaldronWexford me please #maldronwexford #newyearbreak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@budgetireland @MaldronWexford me please #maldronwexford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy go for it yiu deserve it especially after the train incident ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenniemcalpine congrats to you both xâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBBLive @ColeenNolanTV fake account - @NolanColeen is the verified account for Coleen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamthomas21 every yearðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlympiaPanto brilliant show with @TheAlPorter and cast - loved Polly winding up Buttons - great family entertainment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlympiaPanto waiting patiently for Panto to start - excited https://t.co/Gm8mSxGPgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioTimes em George Michael concert on instead of @davidwalliams show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes my favourite too Marian - can't believe it- ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully can't believe it - he was the soundtrack of my teenage years - can't think wait to see the back of 2016ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauleti23 @JackieLynam @Glen_Hansard @PMVTrust delighted you got a ticket x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ecclestonshire love a bit of Madness #XFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannymaconline delighted you and Oti made the final - you and  Claudia should never have been in the dance off - wrong 2- hope you win now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JamesJordan no please keep watching it won't be the same without your tweets ðŸ˜¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JamesJordan you can see by Claudia's face she knows she's going home - wrong 2 in the dance off ðŸ˜¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TobyToymaster six geese a laying #win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@U_Magazine @Ticketmaster ooh fab prize would love Imelda May tickets please #tmgetsmein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam @OTooleDeirdre @civictheatre @PantiBliss @Draiocht_Blanch ooh yes when?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wrong its August! guess July! QUIZ: Can We Guess What Month You Were Born In? via @dailyedge https://t.co/S9lMDBhssq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christmasfm this makes me cry everyone- so sad x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annanolan70 @thewhitmore agree - really missed Laura this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon never too early zzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's tommy k?#LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmythsToysIRE girls world styling head!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbroseAClarke can't view it- have to sign in - why are you tweeting during General awardsðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveTodayFM I remember you tweeted recently about buying one can you help Brenda? https://t.co/NjM2Tr2GIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam don't forget the babysitter - tired too ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaAmakeup love Claudia's eye make up tonight - all dancers look fabulous as usual!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JamesJordan @The_OlaJordan @imacelebrity wow go Ola - that was so impressive #teamola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive thanks - crazy Dublin trafficðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive traffic still backed up to Cabra cross - any reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorjr @lennyabrahamson rte 2 or rte player on line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelbuble hope you and your family  are ok - wishing  your son well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMillican75 @StandardIssueUK go on then - I got 7 our of 10 too!ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewhitmore Didn't believe a word Laura - ignore the gutter press. You know the truth. @danwootton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitrionaPerry @DrGavinJennings @rtenews @morningireland @realDonaldTrump he thinks hes in an episode of The Apprentice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @larrylamb47 on @imacelebrity - what a gent! #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JamesJordan wow well done to Ola - I couldnt do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealNatalieLowe @BrendanCole beautiful dance Natalie - can't wait to see you &amp; @ianwaite in Dublin next May- Christmas pressie for my mam!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something on my eye- just lovely @bbcstrictly #Strictly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 has to be ed balls - don't get Honey G at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuseHill  beats John Lewis ad by miles!#lovemrsclaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 ed balls on now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews thanksðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews hi could you tell me when the next 39a is due at stop 1443 Essex Quay- many thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best christmas adðŸŽ„ https://t.co/2WaVKHLvNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealNatalieLowe @ianwaite just bought tickets for your show in Dublin next May - can't waiteðŸ˜‰ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenORahilly did Ryan not say earlier that he travelled to London for the interview?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daly_anna Congratulations Anna - beautiful photos - hope you are recovering well and letting all the boys spoil you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deekoppang @GiftyLouise can't believe that decision by the judges- wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauldunphy I've loved every episode since series 1 - didn't want it to end - what a finale!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaAmakeup happy birthday- hope you had a great day and Anthony spoiled you loads!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@98FM @takethat @AllSaintsOffic me please love both bandsâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive thanks -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive Old Cabra road at a standstill any idea what the hold up is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GardaTraffic hope everyone is ok!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam for your visitors tomorrow ðŸ˜‰ https://t.co/C8li2zYmKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraffieB thanks might make it to work this morning so! ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraffieB am 10 mins behind on old Cabra road - just as bad ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam yeah I need a new wardrobe too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coldplay what about a second Dublin date please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strictly2016 @Tameka_Empson @gorkamarquez1 @pernicegiovann1 @thewhitmore wrong 2 in the bottom.- so wrong that either had to leave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuseHill @radioleary love Dermot - x factor wasn't the same without him last tear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes sorry married to Katya who is dancing with Ed Balls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam we always call it nanahide even frances and Ambrose call it that now - we go so oftenðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam nanahide didn't make the listðŸ˜¢ https://t.co/SH5fNWIZQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it called Pat Kenny tonight when it's jointly hosted by Colette Fitzpatrick? #PKTonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully happy anniversary to you both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paschald please see attached tweet about why parents and children of St Mochtas are marching tomorrow! https://t.co/unqBhyKRub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_okelly please see tweet re protest at government buildings tomorrow! https://t.co/unqBhyKRub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duncanfo hi Duncan I think you've been hacked you may need to change your password!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up the dubs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthCoppingerTD that's disappointing but not surprising - thanks for asking the question anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthCoppingerTD let us know the result- we need our school built-!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam 2 days to go and then relax x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDempsey having good the same dilemma - Don't forget Coldfeet at 9 on @UTVIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam at least you have next weekend to look forward to #monart #relaxing times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@98FM would love to go to see Grease- one of my favourite films and the ultimate drive in movieâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoeTheBall sorry to hear that- wish you both well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieLynam please follow @StMochtasNS_BAG to help get our school build back on track!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollywills look at his gorgeous blonde hair - happy birthday Chester!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner great photo - hopefully change will come from such a terrific turnout! #repealthe8th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lccguidance that's great all ahead of me for my son this coming year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkrunIRE is it OK to walk or do you need to be a runner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifesomers yeah and brendan and anastasia another good pairing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifesomers the papers had predicted that!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>