<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce He needs to be removed from office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou yup, that's why I post stuff on FB so trumpies can see real news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @POTUS I've come to believe they meant to say "get rid of liberals."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain Trump will destroy US if not stopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump and the #GOP is complicet in this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Glenn Beck, might not be a ban, but is awful for hundreds of people with visas and green cards.  Funtions as a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imillhiser I'm weeping for our country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @washingtonpost Trump ignores this!  He's Putin's puppet. Trump needs to be impeached.  Our country is in danger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @WSJ Please impeach him!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @CBSEveningNews Please impeach TRUMP! Supreme Court judges won't matter if we lose our democracy!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @washingtonpost HELP OUR COUNTRY!  Trump needs to go!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @USATODAY HELP HELP HELP SOS _  Trump is AWFUL! He hates our allies!!!!! HELP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/wgxjQWGaeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaWalsh8 @webster @MikeFitzburg Earning all that money from Soros, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brensweets @Heather43141410 @nytimes @YouTube It seems as if he's been radicalized between then and now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible.  Thanks to the British! https://t.co/qpVrCc8bqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewfangledDad How do these people sleep at night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young white men are being radicalized. https://t.co/PID3Z51Var]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @CruzWhobris Please vote NO on Sessions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betrayed the U.S. Consitution, no.   Betrayed Trump, I guess in his mind. https://t.co/PAOrCjmVPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CleverTitleTK and #TrumpTheCruel mocks his tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @sethmoulton @LeaderMcConnell The Republicans left me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpTheCruel mocks @SenSchumer tears over refugee ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC @POTUS Thank you.  Trump is making the world a dangerous place and the refugee ban is evil and cruel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp He's cruel.  No wonder Melania wouldn't move to the WH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do, too.  Not so sure after this weekend. https://t.co/LeKpwG2MH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lariti2 She warned us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @JonathanCohn @ACLU They're going to need all of it for the fight ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, didn't know love of country was a requirement for citizenship. https://t.co/CfpIyrzy9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the truth. https://t.co/Xl48VqRCBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saletan I'm speechless.  And yet, the trump cultists still follow him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip Where did you see/hear this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain Where are you when our country needs you?  This isn't going to get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports This a coup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepBrendanBoyle  needs to be today, not tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovernorVA @POTUS  Thank you Governor!  You're on the right side of history!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Where's your outrage today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes me think Trump has something on him. https://t.co/flGVxgvY8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you yell this from the rooftops? https://t.co/zuhkdrA2dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Limbaugh2016 @edatpost @mateagold @washingtonpost @GOP Please shout this from the rooftops!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifying https://t.co/S8UjgIZxIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said this then, why do you support it now? https://t.co/tVy9SBxUoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anneapplebaum @Susan_Hennessey He doesn't need to build one, he already has one:  Fox News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweidner95 His voters don't seem to care, sadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin If we lose this battle, all other battles won't matter.  Conservatives and liberals must join this fight. #GOP #DNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin Thank you Senator Durbin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GOP thanks https://t.co/Oi0utez7iE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is she part of the mob? https://t.co/cVWwrYHQdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain hope you keep your word on this! https://t.co/YgE0aGxXUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#theresistence #GOP Dump Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GOP traitors https://t.co/BJMQQ1ePY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@froomkin I needed this today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee what is the significance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GOP DO SOMETHING!!  Nothing is worth sticking with him. https://t.co/jnQ9e0cyIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN @jaketapper  THANK YOU!  #RemoveBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RemoveBannon.  He wants to deny us our First Amendment Rights and he's on OUR payroll. #GOP #StandUpRepublic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jippydedun @puppymnkey And on day 7.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Trump will listen to her. https://t.co/ueJPsAYiqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin Bannon's goal is to destroy us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @washingtonpost Scary that #Bannon can control him and Bannon is out to destroy everything - his own words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Get your dad to resign and save your family name.  Americans will have compassion for person with dementia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOP Remove #Trump  before he  destroys  USA. He  ticked off major trading partner &amp; top level state dept quit because of lack of trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmayemsinger @imgur IF this person gets fired, they'll reveal who they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hang in there! https://t.co/hmiWbLE7vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump needs to go NOW https://t.co/1CMpG2xgqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeauWillimon my head hurts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveKopack @POTUS @realDonaldTrump They're probably paying someone in another country (with cheap wages) to tweet for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evil folks in the WH. https://t.co/iajRAxgmIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @mindyfinn @StandUpRepublic Will you join with democrats in  #resistance?  We need each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the talk about helping our vets and then freezing hiring of doctors, nurses, aides. Disgusting. https://t.co/AdvE6k6Qzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@standingup4ever @AlexLeich @SenFeinstein @MoveOn @IndivisibleTeam Why did you support someone that okays torture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan They need FEMA to act now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan No, You're going to have a lot of folks without health insurance. Evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greta @SpeakerRyan @MSNBC Please ask him about Trump's mental health.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imillhiser Dementia possible for both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin We need to raise taxes and have single payer health care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseLehrich @leahmcelrath @GOP Medicaid pays for 1000s of elderly in nursing homes when their savings run out. Elderly &amp; poor to die.Sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath Who do we believe?  We can't believe the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain The Republicans are the only ones that can save our country from fascist Trump, Bannon, and Conway. Dems don't have the votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @sarahkendzior He's succeeded to some extent based on FB posts I'm seeing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza @GStephanopoulos @SenJohnMcCain Sen McCain, I'm in horror at who is in WH:Conway,Bannon,Trump. Your answer speaks volumes. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewfangledDad All of them were made in America by Americans!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos Please talk about the fascist now in the WH and what you personally are going to do about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I see signs of it already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp @Lawrence there's a lot of organizing at a grassroots level via secret groups on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davebernstein He's snifffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshtpm  axios has an interesting group of Launch Partners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow.  and interesting https://t.co/VsCapGwlU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotACohen President Elect, not POTUS.  Yes, it is incredibly disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delicious cheese:  Rush Creek Reserve - the backstory here: https://t.co/a8jAv3f7XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad was diagnosed with AML 8 years ago and lived two months. https://t.co/iNOtuUY5nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens to pardoned turkeys after Thanksgiving? https://t.co/PFtaeG9E40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Chicken People" film - interview with Director https://t.co/TLDQYYboha @thepoultrysite  @Ellenat5m @ChickenPeople… https://t.co/lyuTiyXYBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backyard Egg Producers Need Salmonella Caution, Research Reveals https://t.co/LZmjapxuQE via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dark Side of Agritainment https://t.co/nGeX4JFKYM via @CivilEats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do Monsanto’s Plans to Open Up its Digital Platform Mean for the Agriculture Industry?  https://t.co/mPefZIfPkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool infographic! https://t.co/TV8LqHBcvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improved Natural Light for #Perdue Chickens in Major Push for Better Welfare https://t.co/3gX9nSpUIv via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw Dough's a Raw Deal and Could Make You Sick- and it's not the eggs https://t.co/PkDHfMcvOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Photos Could Change the Way You Look at #Fruits and #Vegetables https://t.co/qhBztH4Tj5 via @CivilEats]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>