<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this sweeeet Friday Late Night poster.... Keanu Reeves kicks the asses and takes the names in JOHN... https://t.co/Doc2Xw2Ghp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breaking into Hollywood with films like CHILDREN OF MEN and GRAVITY, Alfonso Cuarón made a name with... https://t.co/DVMS3eBhox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suuuuper looking forward to Colin Quinn gracing our stage (for two nights) in February as part of the JFL... https://t.co/FN9Dn0YkPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! Gael Garcia Bernal stars in surrealist thriller NERUDA at 6:30 pm + Amy Adams in Denis Villeneuve's ARRIVA… https://t.co/cJjakfdnlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday! Join us tonight for surrealist suspense thriller NERUDA (starring Gael Garcia Bernal as an... https://t.co/4KpIuL7CsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given all the accolades and attention being given to LA LA LAND (currently up for 14 Oscars!), it seemed like the... https://t.co/llxwaxtUKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Join us at 7:00 pm for a series of short films ft. #LeonardCohen from @TheNFB + Gael Garcia Bernal in… https://t.co/QdAMIuC3wZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ticket update! We're almost 20% SOLD OUT for tickets to RAMMSTEIN: PARIS, the one-night-only concert film... https://t.co/f1UX3b7Gm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news! Advance tickets to the Harry Potter Burlesque event on Thursday, February 23 are on sale now at... https://t.co/b78BbGhoT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! Final chance to see the Geekenders' incredible (not to mention original!) production of Portal 2: The... https://t.co/kcsUP6J3Tz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Gosling and Emma Stone star in what is now one of the most Osar-nominated films (including Best Picture,... https://t.co/55prFN7oCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you believe that Paul Anthony's Talent Time is celebrating its 9th Anniversary on Thursday? That's nine whole... https://t.co/udPdo6cP5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ll have what she’s having.” Billy Crystal, Meg Ryan, Carrie Fisher and Bruno Kirby star in Rob Reiner's WHEN... https://t.co/03wsPOolgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheGeekenders #PORTAL2 is upon us! Advance tix ($ave ca$h!) at https://t.co/tQGEY9VN5g or at the door. Minors wel… https://t.co/o51z7OkPSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats all RT @Crazy8sFilm @DGCBC Top 6 #Crazy8sFilms17 filmmakers @Crazy8sFilm @DGCBC Anniv Screening @RioTheatre https://t.co/V0hQ1HkvRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAY! @Crazy8sFilm @WoodmanFilm @ActorPeterNew 
   #Crazy8sFilms17 writer/actor of  tonight  #livetweet https://t.co/IXQIhUhmIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait!!! RT @cartoonmoo @TheGeekenders Performing #Portal2 with @TheGeekenders tonight at @RioTheatre  #SPACE!! https://t.co/vb0glHMzzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Geekenders' Portal 2: The (Unauthorized) Musical at the Rio Theatre is happening this weekend, #Vancouver!... https://t.co/8TvzG5QmAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When mammoth dandelions puff out spores, the sight is as seductive as it is lethal." (The New Yorker) Based on... https://t.co/F2wJdcDJi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because our screen is bigger.
Waaaaaaaay bigger. That’s why. 

Enjoy the ultimate game day experience at our... https://t.co/2C2pX4UZIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Tom Ford hits it out of the park with a stunning film noir that resonates with ghostly, poetic terror. Don’t... https://t.co/SywkDKuGl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet 'n mingle 'n watch some past favourites with Crazy8s Film Event alum and this year's batch of filmmakers at... https://t.co/wDnVrFaX3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost that time of the month! Get your #DNDLive Humpday with us tomorrow for the very first edition of The... https://t.co/fI0yWMuhH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news: All showing of the Geekenders' production of Portal 2: The (Unauthorized) Musical at the Rio Theatre... https://t.co/QuqsFQzCZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary Oldman is spellbinding in his breakthrough performance as Sex Pistol Sid Vicious in Alex Cox's look at one... https://t.co/jGll7uBoeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The HARRY POTTERTHON Weekend is on now! Tix and passes available at the door. Minors OK. Costumes contests! Trivia!… https://t.co/sFwA63ndRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you believe that Paul Anthony's Talent Time is celebrating its 9th Anniversary at The Rio Theatre on... https://t.co/FhpEU4nHrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more sleep (!) until The Harry Potterthon Weekend at the Rio Theatre takes hold, muggles! Do you have your... https://t.co/aMY8EWF333]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 points to our friends at the WestenderVan for including The Harry Potterthon Weekend at the Rio Theatre among... https://t.co/dTx1r7nsph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance tickets to #RAMMSTEIN: PARIS on March 23 (one night only!) on sale now. @RSprachrohr #Vancouver… https://t.co/1QMjtTVMe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's Friday Late Night Movie is Russ Meyer's FASTER, PUSSYCAT! KILL! KILL! at 11:55 pm. Get off the couch... https://t.co/YKGzn5ZJ2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 points to our amazing staff for making the lobby look as Hogwartian as possible for this weekend's The Harry... https://t.co/G89m202qdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to our purrrrfect pals at The Georgia Straight for including our screening of FASTER, PUSSYCAT! KILL!... https://t.co/u1sWVEDPkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The HARRY POTTERthon weekend is upon us! SAT: Movies 1-4 SUN: Movies 5-8. Minors OK in balcony. Do you have tix yet… https://t.co/FknrzaF9ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna win TWO free passes to this week's Friday Late Movie at the Rio Theatre, FASTER, PUSSYCAT! KILL! KILL!?... https://t.co/EK0gEhRK1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like tonight's Miyazaki Double Bill will be a very, very busy event! Though the posted door time for MY... https://t.co/Q3pfMWPtHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This whole world's wild at heart and weird on top." Get into the Valentine's Day groove on February 10 with a... https://t.co/lKQJgSOZpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesday's Miyazaki Double Bill is looking like it will be busy! Advance tickets to MY NEIGHBOR TOTORO at 6:30... https://t.co/TCbtu1xjuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“But you know, happiness can be found even in the darkest of times, if one only remembers to turn on the light.”... https://t.co/MBOArGUyAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russ Meyer‘s “turbo-charged” exploitative skin-flick and “ode to the violence in women” FASTER, PUSSYCAT! KILL!... https://t.co/zYidSljVLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Wednesday, January 25, the gang from The Critical Hit Show: A Live Improvised Epic Fantasy return to The Rio... https://t.co/Lz3SMV8GCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, due to unforeseen circumstances the A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie concert scheduled for Wednesday January... https://t.co/vaVwFjUFtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fact: Tuesdays are one of the best days of the week to catch crazy-good sci-fi on the big screen. Seriously,... https://t.co/NyyPRcleRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you as excited about the Geekenders' revamped remount of their original production of Portal 2: The... https://t.co/YloLk8W148]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday, movie-lovers! We're warm. Our popcorn is buttery. Join us for ARRIVAL at 6:45pm &amp; BLADE RUNNER: THE… https://t.co/mzk3PnVTsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Geekenders are back. For science. You monster! Tickets going f-a-s-t to the Geekenders revamped Portal 2: The... https://t.co/nYJ7JRQx7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a double-dose of sci-fi movie goodness on Tuesday with Denis Villeneuve's ARRIVAL at 6:45 pm, followed by... https://t.co/kCHyexmvab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to screen David Bowie's 1973 concert film ZIGGY STARDUST AND THE SPIDERS FROM MARS on Monday,... https://t.co/bKraBEiAho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This whole world's wild at heart and weird on top." Get into the Valentine's Day groove with a Friday Late Night... https://t.co/Pd7KUR2T9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Monday, muggles! Tickets for Mischief Managed: Harry Potter Burlesque at the Rio Theatre this Thursday... https://t.co/JQmsYXXfJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know about our Studio Ghibli Double bill this Wednesday, right? We've got two favourites from Hayao Miyazaki... https://t.co/CbEg3WNXsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything's gonna get heartshaped n' horrible when The Fictionals Comedy Co. presents Improv Against Humanity:... https://t.co/CDgEE8NlEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All aboard, muggles! The Hogwart's Express is making a special stop at The Rio Theatre (Commercial Drive via... https://t.co/zwcVYq6UxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a double-dose of sci-fi movie goodness on Tuesday with Denis Villeneuve's ARRIVAL at 6:45 pm, followed by... https://t.co/4XB8Y0AyEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Geekenders are back. For science. You monster! Check out these costumes (and that amazing Core earpiece on... https://t.co/S4mEvor6c0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doors for tonight's EYE OF THE STORM XI are at 8:00 pm / Show 8:30 pm. Tix in advance or at the door.… https://t.co/nIDfqaZUHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're cranking it up to 11 tonight, people! Vancouver's top underground artists are turning The Rio Theatre into... https://t.co/Ivv7luLoXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live.” We are days away from Mischief Managed: Harry Potter... https://t.co/lzfsSEfl5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's David Bowie: Live Band Burlesque Tribute at The Rio Theatre is SOLD OUT, but we have more Bowie... https://t.co/ptdWFZ6dkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animation powerhouse Titmouse's (Black Dynamite, Moonbeam City) first feature NERDLAND is coming to The Rio... https://t.co/aKAk7uifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us at The Rio Theatre on Monday, January 30 at 7:00 pm for a celebration of Leonard Cohen – as seen through... https://t.co/H1Xa3jfu7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAMMSTEIN: PARIS is a one-night-only theatrical event happening around the world on Thursday, March 23. (Did you... https://t.co/0je1GFYUKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday Late Night Movies return to our screen on January 20 with Russ Meyer's FASTER, PUSSYCAT! KILL! KILL! at... https://t.co/RJV0FnAgFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super stoked to welcome back the EYE OF THE STORM A/V CLUB's immersive audio visual environmental experience on... https://t.co/zfAQ3j76PO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Geekenders are back. For science. You monster! Catch the all-new, revamped Portal 2: The (Unauthorized... https://t.co/KLZRogmfLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic German outfit Rammstein rock In this state-of-the-art concert film which debuted at the Cannes Film... https://t.co/YlmrVYMZbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us at The Rio Theatre for a celebration of Leonard Cohen – as seen through a curated collection of four... https://t.co/Y3nPrXEBg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“But you know, happiness can be found even in the darkest of times, if one only remembers to turn on the light.”... https://t.co/H3IxR6uybb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! Join us for @TheGeekenders 'Batlesque' Tribute to Gotham UNCAPED CRUSADERS at 8pm + FREDDY vs. JASON Late… https://t.co/m43neXfMbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the words of the Purple One and his Oscar-winning entry into the world of Batman,"Get the funk up!" It's... https://t.co/YRZpzKDDFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything's gonna get heartshaped n' horrible when The Fictionals Comedy Co. presents Improv Against Humanity:... https://t.co/CMA8bQPlJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It does not do to dwell on dreams and forget to live.” So true. So very true... Aaaaaand we are now one week... https://t.co/3TZYNS0agh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've had a change of plans! Due to an unforeseen cancellation we have added a previously unscheduled screening... https://t.co/pwhR3Jklke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to those purrrrfectly tasty tastemakers at The Georgia Straight for selecting the Geekenders in Uncaped... https://t.co/f9yXp5PhLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes two to tango this Valentine's Day at The Rio Theatre! #EastVan's favourite heart-shaped tradition is the... https://t.co/Y8RQj3rvX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! 50th Anniversary #ULTRAMAN Double Feature at 6:15 pm followed by #evangelion 1.1 at 9:30 pm. See… https://t.co/ZDavuEU5oZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got your plans for tonight? We do! It's so on... At 6:15 pm, the spandex-clad Japanese superhero Ultraman gets a... https://t.co/aMiqSJ3uU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna win TWO free tickets to see this week's Friday (the 13th!)  Late Night Movie, FREDDY vs. JASON? Read on...... https://t.co/Rtktb857c9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't had a chance to check out EYE OF THE STORM A/V CLUB's immersive audio visual environmental... https://t.co/G4Enhq0rKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riddle me this, riddle me that... Tickets to Geekenders glittery Gothamesque tribute to everyone's fave Dark... https://t.co/RbDkjP6J5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Thursday, we are so going there. WE ARE GOING THERE! At 6:15 pm, the spandex-clad Japanese superhero... https://t.co/3K2vkUNoeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced..... via The Georgia Straight. https://t.co/FpGJVCfHAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! Hayao Miyazaki's NAUSICAA OF THE VALLEY OF THE WIND (minors OK!) at 6:30 pm + @GentHecklers riff on master… https://t.co/LQtWVpl5wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERUDA stars Gael Garcia Bernal as an inspector tasked with hunting down Nobel Prize-winning poet Pablo Neruda,... https://t.co/GrdW8RLcfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commencing countdown and engines are most definitely on for Kitty Nights West's David Bowie: Live Band Burlesque... https://t.co/zINJQDq1WC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Geekenders are back, you monsters... And this time, they're bringing the completely re-vamped, professiona... https://t.co/OL8Zo7qr3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Friday night is a Friday night unlike any other, when time, space and movies collide into a world of...... https://t.co/bR9ZyiK9YV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is so much more to Wednesday than being the poster child for "mid-week." So. Much. More. Anyway, join us at... https://t.co/Wvu40Je0W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though frequently enjoyed alone in the dark with headphones, David Bowie‘s concept album 'The Rise and Fall of... https://t.co/JUmdszpkGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced! Remastered concert film ZIGGY STARDUST AND THE SPIDERS FROM MARS touches down on our screen Jan. 23… https://t.co/lNGtEhzW25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced! @TitmouseInc #NERDLAND hitting our screen for one night only on January 23. https://t.co/YFUt7VM9O6 https://t.co/JvYkg90o6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animation powerhouse Titmouse, Inc.'s (Black Dynamite, Moonbeam City) first feature NERDLAND is coming to The Rio... https://t.co/mJo73PD0Xm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am Catwoman. Here me roar." Gather round, all ye Jokers, Penguins, and Dark Knights galore. This Friday, The... https://t.co/4qbDgEgQFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday, we are going there. WE ARE GOING THERE! At 6:15 pm, the spandex-clad Japanese superhero Ultraman... https://t.co/kMFlaB5hp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheas_slap_shot No current plans but we loooooved that movie to so you never know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesdays are made for movies, right? Of course! Join us for the final screenings of two realllly good ones. Brian... https://t.co/bNjzhswCEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to The Georgia Straight https://t.co/zS4lyIu8gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you miss out on ARRIVAL last week? It's cool. The extraterrestrial spaceships are landing again (or are... https://t.co/a5I3731qWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed out on BLADE RUNNER last week? Chillax. We have replicated the situation for Tuesday, January 17 at 9:30... https://t.co/wSZ9767gP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced: #ValentinesDay #BurlesqueDuos returns to the Rio Feb 14! It's an #EastVan tradition, kids.… https://t.co/1BfKhQR1mC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>