<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Miraculous Magnolia blossom in the Garden Shop at Petersham Nurseries - bare branches then an overnight sensation .… https://t.co/srnt2dqNdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under a desert sky .... / in the tropics - beating the weather at Petersham Nurseries .... https://t.co/lHKGgYdhKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonardaB Radicchio though I forget the name. Like lettuce but with more (welcome) bitterness ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 2 -taking down Glasshouse 2- a brilliant team from the Nurseries making it all happen ... https://t.co/jgCBwx3Nsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a rose but beautiful... https://t.co/xWaZdsHEve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thug, the Petersham Cat, looking daggers at Noriko Choy - no laughing matter clearly ... https://t.co/mfZmTA2xUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rainbow- heading straight into the kitchens ! https://t.co/EzUeQd8sWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Garden Shop #petershamnurseries https://t.co/2KTPQzrTj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Garden Shop #petershamnurseries https://t.co/FIIZIXz2S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chance to warm up on the Glasshouse - Paphiopedilum Maudiae, Paphiopedilum Maudiae Magnificum and Paphiopedilum w… https://t.co/STNd6UZY6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swags and trusses of bright translucent berries on a large spreading stand of Viburnum betulifolium https://t.co/AJGM6Ur5bE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamamelis Harry and by way of contrast, Pallida - both at RHS Wisley today... https://t.co/VS7lylPpQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamamelis Harry - my new favourite - happily RHS Wisley have planted a few by the Glasshouse https://t.co/MRGJZbgBCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebores to fall on love with - the double Spring Promise Lily, clear pink Walberton's Rosemary and tightly budde… https://t.co/5gNWVe1Whv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bone white Birch, Salix Yelverton and a weeping Cedrus atlantica Glauca - a perfect trio at RHS Wisley https://t.co/EdR6yFa1vO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful combinations of Dogwood, Willow and blackberry at RHS Wisley- bright despite the chill grey ... https://t.co/38ZAvw9flc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek 'twas a superstar hanging basket plant for last season - just 2 plants and 3' globe of colour. Will repeat this season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Horticultural for the month ahead … and a little tour of Petersham Nurseries https://t.co/IjHY40bKvh https://t.co/ohFcuvCACy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine by Ham House ... https://t.co/D4Mf10IQD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning commute ... https://t.co/LGNao1O0bK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gallery upon gallery at https://t.co/8hv3JGLePZ in the Princess of Wales Conservatory at Kew Gardens and more besid… https://t.co/QqebKGIq2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kew Gardens – Desert, Tropics, Mountains and Forest…. https://t.co/iqYcwZRuiH https://t.co/8X3kXeCpaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went last January and loved the tour https://t.co/V7de2ULpOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This blackbird fought itself on these mirrors for a very long time - could not be discouraged ... https://t.co/u6i761n9AD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A view through a shard of ice - of which there was plenty... at Petersham Nurseries today https://t.co/EkQ5rdeji2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A day at Petersham... https://t.co/gQC8beSI4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helleborus thibetanus in the Davies Alpine House at Kew. Quiet which is just as well as I was laid out flat on the… https://t.co/yExvdtVHAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galanthus John Gray and G. plicatus Florence Baker - the first of many coming through in the Rock Garden at Kew ... https://t.co/4uZpP9kRCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corydalis popovii, Northoscordium  dialystemon, Helleborus thibetanus and Scilla maderense in the Davies Alpine Hou… https://t.co/NNlnDsmC3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it was all yellow - Chimonanthus praecox Grandiflora, Hamamelis Pallida and a wheelbarrow in a very cheery colo… https://t.co/5jyUnWm2Q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of bird life about too at Kew ... https://t.co/CVTZKNxc3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hechtia argentea - this plant was exhibited at Brussels in 1864 ... Princess of Wales Conservatory at Kew. Seriousl… https://t.co/9F59cuHGCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deserts too - huge collection of cacti in the Princess of Wales Conservatory (needed time for the camera to warm up… https://t.co/8kuipnIYEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Princess of Wales Conservatory at Kew, preparing for a tropical month long display come February 4th ... https://t.co/z89DlQozs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escaped the chill for an hour or so at Kew Gardens ... https://t.co/XyQq2jl3vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparations in the Princess of Wales Conservatory well underway for their annual orchid extravaganza #kewgardens https://t.co/DdT1onxySV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This day in 2013, a very late blooming rose Lady Emma Hamilton and snow ... chill today, more chill then. Such an u… https://t.co/5L3JNzWaUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A frosty start at the Nurseries too ... https://t.co/1knLWlAulT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little hangover from Floral Monday ... https://t.co/I7EQjh5UQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine and Citrus ... https://t.co/KEisQXoc7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bright and beautiful start to the day by Teddington Lock https://t.co/G9L3ickQaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Floral Monday to banish the blues #floralmonday https://t.co/dSdyqCwqJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orchidology https://t.co/YJg8gjDHV1 https://t.co/nzXdGXHLfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technicolor Rainbows in the Alpine House at RHS Wisley https://t.co/IGgKCHjA2g https://t.co/otmmHlCObB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamamelis for a New Year https://t.co/BFpTGnFKfT https://t.co/g1CI3KgHIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebores for a New Year https://t.co/lNQtwn1E7L https://t.co/Rw1oXa6kAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crocus laevigatus #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/EaEVEgRT0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tightly budded - Daubenya aurea var. cochinea (predictive text hates these Latin names - latifolia, earlier came ou… https://t.co/Bo2pjjGNMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very early Auricula 'Blue Yodeler' #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/0xLGdWNibi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go! Bulbinella latifolia subsp. latifolia half way up... #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/zgNpjsH9b2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulbinella latifolia subsp. latifolia - just thinking about opening out #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/rEH64CQaMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in a cage of fine leaves, the flowers of Narcissus bulbocodium subsp. praecox var. paucinervis. Delicate in every p… https://t.co/dPMWMWUrhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daubenya. marginata - on the Hyacinthaceae family - sitting pretty #alpinehouse ##rhswisley https://t.co/d2FyEwHUaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tecophiliaea cyanocrocus Violacea adding to the Alpine colourwheel #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/Pb6FEHYEIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lachenalia bulbifera bringing a shock of forced-rhubarb pink to the proceedings #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/VbpQWJOCIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daubenya aurea yellow-flowered warming up a wet grey Sunday #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/5Y9Fu2KrKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange Peel is, year on year, a thoroughbred... #rhswisley #hellebores https://t.co/ixqYXgrz88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Hellebore Gold Collection, Camelot... https://t.co/RDUVH2VgRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reverse of Hellebore Painted Bunting #rhswisley #hellebores https://t.co/dz58tMsF21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss Muffet, a miniature narcissus of rather great charm https://t.co/9GWbs35szx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreadful, ubiquitous concrete blocks from the '70s given a beautiful new life #alpinehouse #rhswisley https://t.co/zO3otdsHR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna's Red, a Hellebore from Rodney Davey; I remember him coming to sell the first few plants at an RHS Spring show… https://t.co/SGn9mbFUvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty wall sculpture at RHS Wisley ... https://t.co/7p4KnLOlUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another rich red, the new Ice N Roses Red Hellebore ... https://t.co/qXpE98iOK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daphne bholua Limpsfield - a rich lilac pink and even on such a chill morning, fragrant as all out ... #rhswisley https://t.co/2Ns07sIx2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite a collection of Witch Hazels in Wisley - beautiful, curious and richly coloured ... https://t.co/O1iV0lAQda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebore Anna's Red. Quite the superstar ... https://t.co/ccSUi7p5lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Ho! Its off too @RHSWisley I go... #alpinehouse #battlestonhill #hellebores #daphnebholua https://t.co/dP8sBCeWu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only kind of snow I want to see in the morning - my kind of blizzard https://t.co/8ZZxIPSS07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Amaryllis are flowering again (third year now). They enjoyed a summer holiday in the garden and an autumn repott… https://t.co/hD56TA5VhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebore Angel Glow - a beaut. https://t.co/X2FpCcMETW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebore Molly's White - beautifully cool flowers and remarkable leaves too - https://t.co/V7n1EPyT0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarcococca confusa already reeking if sweet scent ... https://t.co/F1nbWxyXDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favoured Paperwhites https://t.co/5nRr6A9XcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebore time - hybrids of Hellebore niger from the Hellebore Gold Collection starting us off ... https://t.co/pug14UEesf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise of Spring ... https://t.co/6CMRohm81o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And more ... Brass monkeys https://t.co/QdazV9CSiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More frost ... https://t.co/R6NqQczDAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brass monkeys, yesterday ... https://t.co/TC0n2O2RHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only blue evening ... https://t.co/LSOYEmFALb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a bright blue day ... https://t.co/mBWcX0rkTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellebore Mini-Blanc to wish you a massively good New Year's Eve everyone ... https://t.co/1144H5X01s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts turn to winter colour and scent #petershamnurseries #hellebore #daphne #sarcococca #springbulbs… https://t.co/ncZiY0hSKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hydrangea paniculata and a midwinter sun https://t.co/9OulwAe06l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The warming glow of Cornus sanguinea Anny's Winter Orange https://t.co/i3h35RYwMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some seasonal berried treasure - Ilex aquifolium Bacciflava, Viburnum betulifolium, Skimmia Pabella &amp; rose hips fro… https://t.co/eUgtfXX7Om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on my bird table this morning ... https://t.co/gCTkfdpZU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely a tweet, this ... https://t.co/QMfvldrzgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful plant hunting trip - more needed though - and definitely more glittery twigs (got the red, went out and… https://t.co/F7GxP0eb8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blows own trumpet having decanted 4 tons of compost into new raised beds yesterday - happily I didn't seize up comp… https://t.co/mzd7z5DAzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graham_Rice Happy to say I have the original!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An end to a very Floral Monday ... https://t.co/5TScpcLpLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Tree (Larch) ... after Calder https://t.co/M6ZQmwPYZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser-cut Christmas ... https://t.co/39ohRTzpDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Bang! Here comes Christmas again ... https://t.co/O8mtUL3gwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fragrant Paperwhites ... https://t.co/1xwT2Ghe6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toasty at Petersham Nurseries this evening #petershamnurseries #roaringbrazier #coffeelogs https://t.co/gnR8vccYr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big bright blue / bright gold https://t.co/s6AuISI9Dl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright chill calm - crossing at Teddington Lock this morning ... https://t.co/WKuwggXDTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeperrone Not new (must they be?) but a 5* read - 'The Well-tended Perennial Garden: Planting and Pruning Techniques' Tracy DiSabato-Aust]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>