<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to find us?  Here are the directions to our Office! https://t.co/brg3VtYYZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our Australian of the Year! Biomedical scientist Professor Alan Mackay-Sim. How amazing to be... https://t.co/B06cD40UT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know what is in Court today? Check out the Federal Circuit Court list in Canberra... https://t.co/gK7Egx4fBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know where the Family Court in Canberra is? https://t.co/AOOZGs9aQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personal Protection Orders - another type of restraint orders... https://t.co/vs8rRr9XcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a section 60I certificate?  Do you need one?  #familylaw #mediation... https://t.co/jcpBgLSyYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce that Lawyer Ms Natalie Mead has commenced working with us this year!

Natalie has... https://t.co/fIOC6r4sJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/ezy8MIichI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNA Testing - determining parentage (parenthood)... https://t.co/6Zg5qjRwfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forced marriage. Claire Naidu &amp; Co talk about forced marriages (not to be confused with arranged marriages).... https://t.co/gb66mi2QBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some tips in the event of a family breakdown to protect yourself... https://t.co/xnc2zScZ00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about engaging a divorce lawyer?  Here are some tips to consider... https://t.co/PkCDzlCLBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New way to get to and from Court? https://t.co/poFHeYcf3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all a Merry Christmas. 

Thank you to your support and engagement with us this year. It has been an... https://t.co/89FD2O8qh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/r8hDEJ5hIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private school fees and child support - common questions... https://t.co/PNcZpFBzAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We welcome the appointment of new Judge to the Canberra Registry of the Federal Circuit Court - Amanda Tonkin.... https://t.co/nVVgu1U6dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a special visitor today!!! https://t.co/auLd6yOOJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget free photos with Santa tomorrow! https://t.co/Al6hLwPgTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been nearly 12 months since I met Sir Bob Geldof in person and we spoke about families and separation.... https://t.co/RObdOdxYcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra man cannot reverse his adoption... https://t.co/wjxNdrbAJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overnight time in family law matters https://t.co/cLVAlPUjRN https://t.co/ZDLvSaZvLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can help you finalise your family law affairs. https://t.co/MyqdS02t1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriages Families and Separation Brochure - information for those considering, or affected by separation or... https://t.co/ymA51zteCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge of the Division of the High Court in London intends to speak to the child personally via FaceTime or Skype... https://t.co/PxOyh65IyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physical abuse v physical punishment of children... https://t.co/EAIK3h4esk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you interested in knowing more about alternatives to court - Claire Naidu &amp; Co Lawyers and Mediators discuss... https://t.co/mqwmDELSpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relocation - are you wanting to move away with the children or is your partner wanting to move away with the... https://t.co/esu7z8XCgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mullet defamation... https://t.co/1991uw1YAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about representing yourself in family court?... https://t.co/udgdqwK7nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How cute is this little pirate?
We are pleased to announce the Winner of our best dressed costume for Halloween!... https://t.co/hxU17P49RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is more than one way to divorce.... 
https://t.co/CxSCYSFi4z https://t.co/xDp2VCDotc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superannuation in family law matters - what should you know?... https://t.co/FSOOPiokut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/HvA3h3Y0Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the office today - in Sydney for specialised training in the social sciences and parenting matters. https://t.co/chLFvHihZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you separated or thinking about separating?  Have you updated your Will?... https://t.co/2E8S1ubgYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for everyone coming today to our Trick Or Treating Halloween event. It was great to see you all and your... https://t.co/2pGaiGlbOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/DJB39bXe1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard the terms FDR or FDRC and not sure what they mean?  We discuss Family Dispute Resolution and FDR... https://t.co/nDaEHDytOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget Halloween Monday - 31 October 2016 3.30-5.30pm.  Come to Claire Naidu &amp; Co, Lawyers and Mediators at... https://t.co/Gy0iRDWxJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love celebrating with amazing business women in the Telstra Business Womens Award. Good luck to all the finalists!! https://t.co/RZMNvXRiHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queensland woman's defeated High Court bid to become the first deaf juror.  The ACT Justice Directorate is... https://t.co/ZyibAmAjaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your children make you re-think what you have just said... https://t.co/DqInaFy1dP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great tip from The organising Bee. https://t.co/V9rAESguSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/YW9Uz79v8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental Health is a serious issue and one that is often raised in family law matters.  We have a prepared an... https://t.co/UUElkZoZit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stayed tuned to the Domestic Violence Crisis Service ACT for more details about drop off points for Secret Santa.... https://t.co/G0KEZSbMwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to get a divorce but your husband or wife does not agree?  Do you need their consent?  Check to our... https://t.co/NjUlgD4ogH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you and your partner been talking about separating or divorcing but you don't really want?  Relationship... https://t.co/InWW0NGSWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneNeedhamSC still jealous though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gungahlin has recorded the wettest September since records began in 1998.  133.8mm fell - beating the previous... https://t.co/AYxeCFeZBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal News: The David Eastman retrial over the alleged murder of a police chief has been tentatively set for May... https://t.co/tb8ewri2tP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a grandparent or know a grandparent who wants to know about their rights in seeing their grandchildren?... https://t.co/nOMmNLHZJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you looking for advice from an Accredited Family Law Specialist?  Contact Claire Naidu &amp; Co, Lawyers &amp;... https://t.co/GuYrbTW8M4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verbose lawyers?  Is there such a thing? https://t.co/Kr7JThAYfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you need to protect your assets?  We can assist you and discuss all your family law questions about your home... https://t.co/sI1bCqUkK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The old adage of he said/ she said.  There are ways that this can be overcome - if you want to know how to best... https://t.co/orqBPaY957]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your children make you re-think what you have just said... https://t.co/Pu1tTDMRv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keough_william hadn't heard that saying, but I like it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come and see us at the baby expo, exhibition park in Canberra (EPIC)! https://t.co/JpPECpjina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has been a lot in the media about Channel Nine and the children in Lebanon and their mother who tried to... https://t.co/5kI8xj4ZOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great post!!! https://t.co/uNw57RQvEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency court orders after hours for family violence victims - ACT Magistrates Court has raised concerns about... https://t.co/qI0qQO6thb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nasty posts on facebook - Woman sues her ex-husband for his facebook posts https://t.co/RkEGPumfUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you spending this rainy day? https://t.co/3de6Ro1tMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how many RHONY fans follow us but FYI the Wansteins are set to divorce https://t.co/SN08EAVxOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eastman appeal hearing set for October - if successful, the appeal could prevent David Eastman's retrial over the... https://t.co/iPpdrKgbdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are so excited and pleased to announce that we have moved premises!  

Claire Naidu &amp; Co have been operating... https://t.co/XqyJipWnsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When going through Separation and divorce, it can be a time of getting caught up in unhelpful thoughts... This is... https://t.co/C6RcfDPjop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighWatson4 if she is the one at the front, she is an awesome dancer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So vivid! Thanks to "This Canberran Life" for sharing such great photos. https://t.co/P8DuspWf3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason why I love Canberra. 

How cool are our police officers!! 

Right back at you New York and New... https://t.co/x7bkbnB7BX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Family Court Judge in Canberra 
https://t.co/I22xxOJPIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Commonwealth Attorney-General’s had announced that Mr Shane Gill has been appointed to the Family Court of... https://t.co/EyEikPrrE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity for lawyer... https://t.co/NiWRWMeGgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to ACT Mum of the Year - Dannielle Kelly! #Canberra... https://t.co/DwPl5lOtCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of cross examining the witness fun! https://t.co/qvmTAv3uHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of the good ex... https://t.co/wbuiTQku6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drew Barrymore and her husband, Will Kopelman, are separating and obtaining divorce.  They have two little... https://t.co/zTkBGoM7lN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Easter!!! Hope your have a great day! https://t.co/3teL1thcBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jay Davis on friendship and marriages... https://t.co/SGVp7YKJTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that our principal Lawyer and Mediator, Claire Naidu, is also an Accredited Family Law... https://t.co/sG3pq4efl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of our fabulous Lawyers, Kavina Mistry, has written this interesting piece about Kesha and a great way to... https://t.co/DFWkPoy9Yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad was not prepared to divorce, but he says they were on the verge... https://t.co/cAbxkai4TM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listening to @666canberra  on my car radio on the way to a family event https://t.co/cX1Q9JdJdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such a lovely story!  I love Canberra and Canberrans!... https://t.co/K2Ekux1peq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidence in chief can be like pulling teeth.... https://t.co/KohqE49kMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneNeedhamSC oh what a cutie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra's Dickson window washer 'Scrubbie' dies: reports https://t.co/6Ac9lXADOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot day in Canberra! When our lovely  staff member Kavina had finished at court this morning and was on her way... https://t.co/CdtVaKup44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We advise our clients of a healthy clean lifestyle https://t.co/fHCGNDIKq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you enjoying your Sunday? https://t.co/IFot5bJXED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope everyone is having a lovely Sunday!  We start back tomorrow and our office is open from 8.45am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your ex asks you... https://t.co/WoOpbtUsy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone guess the most popular day to marry in Australia in 2014?  https://t.co/GAWC9fopjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who saw the ball of lightening? https://t.co/qWgl28NCEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gungahlin baby - the first in 2016! https://t.co/clHU7gFHvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child abduction alert https://t.co/U8TmXF3GAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird ways couples annoy each other https://t.co/FdjSVEiZeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relax, turn up the sound, open it onto a large screen and just be present and amazed.  Happy New Year - this is... https://t.co/ZA0qRE6Q9t]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>