<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace your whole self! "The more I like me, the less I want to pretend to be other people." Jamie Lee Curtis #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to truly master something? "...the way of the Master consists in doing one's best...that is all." Confucius #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no growth without change. "[Be] strong enough and smart enough to let go and grow." Marc and Angel Chernoff #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no substitute for wisdom. "There's a beauty to wisdom and experience that cannot be faked." Amy Grant #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you express yourself? "Now it is your turn." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep an open mind. "The soul should always stand ajar; ready to welcome the ecstatic experience." Emily Dickinson #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indulge in learning and thought! "The noblest pleasure is the joy of understanding." Leonardo da Vinci #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress never stops, life carries on. "Nature does not hurry, yet everything is accomplished." Lao Tzu #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn more to give more and forever. "Education is the best provision for old age." Aristotle #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all need warmth, time and communication. "The combination of these gifts is pure intoxicating delight." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep trying until you do it! "Failure is a word I don't accept." John H. Johnson #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's your self-talk? "Your thoughts, the way you think is the most powerful influence in your life." John Patrick Hickey #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace what makes you smile. “If you smile when no one else is around, you really mean it.” Andy Rooney #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay young at heart! "You're never too old to be young." Snow White from Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your expectations become reality. "Expect more than others think is possible." Claude Bissell #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear not the storm but learn to sail in it. "All great changes are preceded by chaos." Deepak Chopra #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life has miracles for those who look. "Don't believe in miracles; depend on them." Laurence J. Peter #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aim high. "Aim for the moon. If you miss, you may hit a star." W. Clement Stone #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's fight for what we believe in. "Ready for battle." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you live simply? "I believe that a simple and unassuming manner of life is best for everyone..." Albert Einstein #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live your life with the passion that matters to you. "The big secret in life is that there is no big secret." Oprah Winfrey #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top is in our reach.  "It is within everyone's grasp to be a CEO." Martha Stewart #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace change in your work and life, "Open your arms to change, but don't let go of your values." Dalai Lama #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake each day with this attitude: "My eyes with new gifts to discover and see." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be open to new ideas. "It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it." Aristotle #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who teaches you now? "Every child grows, everything depends on the teacher." Shinichi Suzuki #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give loved ones the honor of your attention. "The first duty of love is to listen." Paul Tillich #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile and watch the world be happy! "I believe that when you put a smile out there, you get a smile back." Heidi Klum #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have faith? "Accept what is, let go of what was and have faith in what could be." Marc and Angel Chernoff #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We learn to look past faults. "Love is blind; friendship closes its eyes." Friedrich Nietzsche #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best decisions need facts and reasons. "Judge behavior, not motives." Miles Anthony Smith #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is a new day. "My next morning might provide." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ever give up hope. "Even miracles take a little time." The Fairy Godmother from Cinderella #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are lessons to learn "Don't bury your failures, let them inspire you." Robert Kiyosaki #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find your something! "We all have something that we are meant to do." Robin Sharma #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have only yourself to overcome. "Real learning comes about when the competitive spirit has ceased." Jiddu Krishnamurti #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn, plan and do.  "I have to trust what I do, and then do it." Ednita Nazario #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose to be the best.  "No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." Eleanor Roosevelt #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know the joy of giving a hand. "What do we live for, if it is not to make life less difficult for each other?" George Eliot #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joy of laughter improves love. "To laugh yourself is to love yourself." Mickey Mouse #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the work of a leader. "Leadership is an action, not a position." Donald McGannon #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will reversing let you move forward? "Sometimes you have to take a step back to move forward” Erika Taylor #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must challenge and be challenged to grow. "I have never learned from a man who agreed with me." Robert A. Heinlein #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace of mind creates happiness. "Learn to be calm and you will always be happy." Paramahansa Yogananda #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your calling, find it, love it, do it.  "Do what you love and the money will follow." Marsha Sinetar #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always choose to look ahead. "Some people cannot stand that you're moving on with your life..." Marc and Angel Chernoff #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to connect. "They may forget what you said, but they will not forget how you made them feel." Carl W. Buechner #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reach out fearlessly. "But, what if?...Jump, even while you are asking." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What move will you make? "It's the move you make, mind to heart to body parts." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it! One step at a time! "What saves a man is to take a step. Then another step." Antoine de Saint-Exupery #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create a great you! "You are essentially who you create yourself to be..." Stephen Richards #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need both. "Travel, in the younger sort, is a part of education; in the elder, a part of experience." Francis Bacon #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Books can push your start button. "A book is a device to ignite the imagination." Alan Bennett #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passion gives power to your dream! "Ambition is a dream with a V8 engine." Elvis Presley #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revel in the magic of life. "Fully enjoy the wonder and beauty of each moment." Paramahansa Yogananda #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your opportunities.  "If you don't like the road you're walking, start paving another one." Dolly Parton #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you truly happy? “Learn to value yourself, which means: fight for your happiness.” Ayn Rand #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't complicate: "Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not simpler." Albert Einstein #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See as much of it as you can! "The world is a book and those who do not travel read only one page." Augustine of Hippo #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need stillness to think clearly. "I rest easy into my still self and breathe." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make changes that matter! "We're here to put a dent in the universe. Otherwise why else even be here?" Steve Jobs #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a search. "We search something permanent, something that will last." Jiddu Krishnamurti #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love and grow.  "The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain." Jennifer Aniston #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspire those near you! "I am not a teacher, but an awakener." Robert Frost #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good choices produce better futures. "I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions." Stephen Covey #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be confident! "You know, you do need mentors, but in the end, you really just need to believe in yourself." Diana Ross #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep climbing. "The man on top of the mountain didn't fall there." Vince Lombardi #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be kind.  "As much as we need a prosperous economy, we also need a prosperity of kindness and decency." Caroline Kennedy #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligent choices matter. "...all that occurs in your life is the result of your own making." Stephen Richards #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust; make choices - it is all possible. "I am where I am because I believe in all possibilities." Whoopi Goldberg #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make inspiration come to you. "You can't wait for inspiration. Sometimes you have to go after it with a club." Jack London #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take pride! "Change not only was inevitable, but usually brought its own rewards." Nicholas Sparks #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The echoes of bounced ideas can grow.  "Ideas are like pizza dough, made to be tossed around." Anna Quindlen #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decide. "Failure will never overtake me if my determination to succeed is strong enough." Og Mandino #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boldness and courage are vital for achieving dreams. "Anything's possible if you've got enough nerve." J.K. Rowling #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always strive for your best. "Doing the best at this moment puts you in the best place for the next moment." Oprah Winfrey #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work through adversity. "The best way out is always through." Helen Keller #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shine! "The beauty of a woman is seen in her eyes...the doorway to her heart, the place where love resides." Audrey Hepburn #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does chaos hide the answers we seek to discover? "From discord find harmony..." Albert Einstein #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love yourself! "Life is too short to spend at war with yourself." Marc and Angel Chernoff #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is happiness. "Nothing is more precious than independence and liberty." Ho Chi Minh #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be swallowed by your craft. "I don't do fashion, I am fashion." Coco Chanel #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which are you? "...some are born great, some achieve greatness, and some have greatness thrust upon them." William Shakespeare #Array]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always take chances! "Wishing I had taken a bigger chance." Laura Probert #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be rooted in belief. "Give me a place to stand, and I will move the Earth." Archimedes #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think and write but always have perspective, "Don't let a little dispute injure a great friendship." Dalai Lama #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did you begin? "Home is where one starts from." T.S. Eliot #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think yourself great. "What we think, we become." Buddha #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise yourself: "Never, never, never give up." Winston Churchill #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improve their lives to prosper. "A business is simply an idea to make other people's lives better." Richard Branson #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love your life! "It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy, that makes happiness." Charles Spurgeon #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make each moment count. "Life can only be understood backwards; but it must be lived forwards." Søren Kierkegaard #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An invaluable and unforgettable education. "Experience, travel - these are an education in themselves." Euripides #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose to be happy. "No man is happy unless he believes he is." Publilius Syrus #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust yourself and do it! "Do what you were born to do. You just have to trust yourself." Beyonce #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show pride in your confidence! "Never bend your head. Hold it high. Look the world straight in the eye." Helen Keller #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take it day by day. "The best thing about the future is that it comes one day at a time." Abraham Lincoln #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be generous, act. "Words are plentiful; deeds are precious." Lech Walesa #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to be successful, show up and contribute. "Today it's important to be present, be relevant and add value." Nick Besbeas #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you attempt the impossible? "I am always doing things I can't do. That's how I get to do them" Pablo Picasso #NimbleQuotes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>