<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga channeling every world leader "stop calling me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancitychic Happy unofficial anniversary, nonetheless. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancitychic Because it's your anniversary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stroppy_Girl My British colleague made himself a canoe...he's more Canadian than me I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellieLeitch I'd rather pay equity than pepper spray, FYI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpicyTunaRo There should be a bra reduction service for people who've figured out their correct size and/or had reduction surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_braincandy And when their bad ideas are ignored they get testy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink No problem, thanks for the reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the day off of work to shovel snow actually really appeals to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Ahem, this time with more information: what's the best route for getting to YVR from Waterfront?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Best strategy for getting to the airport today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpicyTunaRo If it's still snowing at 10am does it then become 10am the next day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrillCheezKilla Alternative facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the day when @POTUS is overshadowed by a bunch of rodents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loxyisme More like fuck off, fuck off, fuck off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpicyTunaRo I assume it's basically saline nasal spray..or was it a cream?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, the world is still falling apart? Same as yesterday? Alrighty, back to the smaller scale catastrophes that I can control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanAMartin When it's food they call it "fusion."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's dinner: pierogies with leftover Swedish meatball gravy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellieLeitch Do you ever think before you speak?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moebius_strip Also the ones who've advocated not to face-punch nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway has really perfected that drowned rat look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moebius_strip Right. I should've known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moebius_strip Oh god, who is doing that? They need a punch in the face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awg_allan BoC is simply another organization that has problems helping women move up ladder into senior leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_braincandy Cesspool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only a matter of time before Trump administration starts legislating forced sterilization of groups they don't like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stroppy_Girl Well, that would finally prove the chemtrails conspiracy theory partially true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynMarlow @CBC180 It stood out when I heard it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh...morning monitor glare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YVRDaniel @AnthonyFloyd @ironring1 Tomorrow, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YVRDaniel My brief review of the Wikipedia article led me to believe they can be challenged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish the phrase "Trump's travel ban" was describing a ban on Trump traveling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexishinde Yeah. I have a mat with a bunch of blankets for cushioning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My back/neck pain is exacerbated by my mattress so tonight I'm going to try sleeping on the floor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dansinker @DavidColeAIA The escalator makes so much more sense now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loxyisme Thanks! And yeah, I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, it's the last year of my 30s but I'm not insecure about the size of my hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noturrevolution @SpicyTunaRo Thanks! It's the last of my 30s...it's going pretty well. Events down south are distr… https://t.co/6dXwwondHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking mimosas and watching Jurassic Park while folding laundry. It's not everybody's idea of a day off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ac_awesome Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpicyTunaRo Thanks! I will proudly wear the wannabe cat lady label.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistergoats Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@604Heather One day he'll realize that if his family snores there's a very high probability that he snores too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to buy a Time magazine to help the hat issue outperform the Trump issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faintingincoils Also, apartment building are filled with criminals, ahem, renters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy your guacamole made entirely from peas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passerelle to nowhere. https://t.co/FOdeNPu67v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RochePotter Be honest, did you archive it with a celebratory bonfire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDigiPol Well, he set up a company in November called "Trump Walls Limited."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@604Heather Did you complain about something? Apparently that's Scottish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Trump always comparing himself to a Peyton Manning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New experiences: IMS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanAMartin @otctu I don't who those people are, can I still come?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsonlyzach Today is a big day in Canada for talking about mental health. This was my addition: https://t.co/MImGAl7zpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelownagurl Go do something else. It'll be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January 25th, 2017 12:09PST is when I descended into a profound despair about the state of the world. #bellletstalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the US back on the gold standard yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's not 7th on its own. It's lumped in with other resource extraction industries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calgary man confronts Trudeau with "oil is the largest employer in Alberta..."

By major industry group, it's 7th. https://t.co/nfzDgN9Uc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gusgreeper That's really good to hear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cazzy I think it's been barely 24 hours since I started following you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertdall I'm actually going to Prague...but the suspended monorail is calling to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw Ivanka's expression is also kind of weird and Stepford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scowlyguy Good lord, who thought that was a good idea?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scowlyguy I don't blame you, it's a bit like "schweddy balls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scowlyguy Some websites call it a suspended monorail. Even better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accidentally chose my next vacation spot from a Google image search. (Wuppertal, Germany - suspended railway!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moebius_strip I'd say something but I've learned that we white women are not to be seen or heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moebius_strip I'm open to punching sanctimonious men in addition to nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Nazi-punching debate is almost as good as the safety pin debate. The left can't do anything without analyzing it from 15+ angles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're 3 days in. How many more days until he fires all his staff so he can watch tv? https://t.co/w6L8gON7kF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnamatrix @noturrevolution @SpicyTunaRo just butting in to mention that I was also planning to head out your way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time, you should rehearse your li(n)es a bit more. @seanspicer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatJBrown Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black is definitely my colour. #womensmarch @ West End, Vancouver https://t.co/wwBEKBnFee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I think I'll stick with calling him president elect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@somecanuckchick Oh, he knows. And in a year he'll take credit for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyFloyd Reminds me of ye olde 1990s when you downloaded video as a series of smaller RAR files and then combined them later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney Ask a hipster?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Torticollis sounds more delicious than it actually is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretInVancouver I understand that it's an algorithm thing. It sees that many of my friends follow him and I don't so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jackstar009 @stillwellgray Sociopaths have high IQs...maybe that's the point he's making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter suggests I follow my ex. Except I've been so much happier in my life since I stopped following my ex.
Anyhow....dismiss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSC_63 Cool, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSC_63 How much did it cost you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cfhorgan "I can also read tea leaves."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brycepugh He really should consider what the people want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed opportunity when O'Leary declared he was "jumping into the race right now" didn't jump into a pool w/ 'The Race' written on bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexishinde That's not good.

Unsolicited advice: make sure to stretch throughout the day. Especially if you're normally sitting a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rush...to shut off the radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robonto @TODesignOffsite What's that massive pink thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ybrend The mayor looks like he's planning his escape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl on the bus shook her wet umbrella all over my book. Actually, not my book...it's borrowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Theresa May talk about Brexit and realizing she's delusional about why people voted for Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistergoats What's my word?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hurrrdurrr Do you have greater insight into Stranger Things now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lazin_Ryder It depends if they're referring to something specific or just the system in general. Also ppl use inco… https://t.co/6Z7b1hMiyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lazin_Ryder It's called a grate. Or were you asking for people's preferred colloquialism?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>