<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJemaineClement He wasn't good enough at comedy :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer's here and there are #stingrays in the lagoon #whywellington https://t.co/HLpAJRaYMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSaplingNZ I just had a meeting with my CEO with Maggie on my lap, "helping". :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brannavan @BooksellersNZ Sometimes there's a cat at the train station, too. Zoo, schmoo.Until we find out what the family perks are...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ I'm never going to win :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ Comms and Marketing :-) I was all pleased about the cat then he told me he's off to meet the cheetahs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boyfriend's 1st day of job at the Zoo. Not jealous coz this cat is hanging outside  my office. Not jealous at all. https://t.co/u9VFgyONE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's not "run to the chopper" I'm not watching. https://t.co/Jy1Eu1OQ7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just kept dipping and sort of drew it on. Luckily it's meant to look rough! https://t.co/yMhZsNwgDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #Moana cake for my soon-to-be-six sprocket, who's memorised all the lyrics. #yourewelcome #shiny https://t.co/e01jKBgLCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelindywest @vulture Run to the chopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting 2017 at the leopard tortoise Creche @aucklandzoo https://t.co/YVEPEBH5XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas for cats. https://t.co/KVVe7h98UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum's cat, coping with the grandchildren. https://t.co/bDuVwz8AXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mixtape for the road trip tomorrow! https://t.co/jHrKh6OLxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wibble #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found my childhood My Little Pony on TradeMe and can't wait to give it to the 5yo for Xmas. #mistycolouredmemories https://t.co/Bu6VPBHiQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay my #nzsecretsanta finally got her gift and is stoked. Feel like I really got the hang of it this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 the huggiest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My awesome #nzsecretsanta dropped the hint they have a sister who was a @VSAvolunteer in Bhutan. Cats, chocolate an… https://t.co/jaJSkBGlsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winner winner chocolate dinner! Thanks @Wellington_NZ and @wellychocfactor ! https://t.co/pbaWN1BfNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they know it's WINTERVAL at all? @AllusionistShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa has spokey-dokeys! #whywellington https://t.co/Rp338N0xgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moar_moar @MxDEJ This book also has Hill and Pickles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxDEJ That's a the main problem with history. Its well-known feminist agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library copy of The New Oxford History of New Zealand with earlier reader's thoughts. History is written by the bia… https://t.co/NzZJqIdKcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wellington_NZ Two for one at @WellingtonZoo !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 that was you! Racing for a bus and in a Now Show fog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a peek inside the Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar https://t.co/AWVYnHBuEZ via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nzsecretsanta is it too late to ask for a Paradise Shelduckling? #bigbluebackyard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day we'll all look back on 2016 and say, as one: ¿Que? BBC News - Fawlty Towers star Andrew Sachs dies aged 86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can make just one little corner of the world right again... https://t.co/U3V8HFxY6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How would you lose an 81m tree to begin with? https://t.co/7wGu03nBoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you thank you thank you @NZSSProdder my santee has tweeted hints that showed I was WAY off base. Whew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi to my #nzsecretsanta , sorry a don't tweet more. I like cats, dogs and goats and I cry easily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#stationcats of the world! https://t.co/xSz0mz5qiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I see this I wonder why people are complaining to Hillary Clinton. https://t.co/WLe1ZJig8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 I, for one, fully endorse this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #WorldPrematurityDay - and thanks as always to amazing neonatal staff everywhere @NeonatalNZ https://t.co/Gypnz2UcCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 can't believe we don't have any damage - hope you guys are okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was long and scary. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nzsecretsanta has begun, so I need to start dropping breadcrumbs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kitchen gadgets review: Tomorrow’s Kitchen pineapple slicer – an emasculating experience https://t.co/gAlLwIICKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ The possibilities! How about an Iron Maiden Voyage? Motley Cruse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am doing so well at Duolingo that if I run into the #Dutch royals this week I can tell them the woman drinks the milk AND the juice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me reading @SteveBraunias on Valentines Lincoln Road. "Her happiness was like a lesson I wanted to learn." https://t.co/WA9ygxmVY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onethreenine cranes! Up they go! https://t.co/lahkEX24N1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From our new office I can see planes, cranes, trains, ships, buses, trucks, cars, mountains, sea and sky. Living the Richard Scarry dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 @GuiltFemPod I'm a feminist but can't accept thank without deflecting :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuiltFemPod @MaryFrances110 No, thank YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 @GuiltFemPod I subscribed and listened on the bus this morning - another top recommendation! If men had periods = gold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Bill Murray and/or Tom Hanks look like now is JAW-DROPPING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another family road trip, another day spent playing Horse all by myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Garden Party and No Other Stories #ScalebackanNZbook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 5.30pm Question #ScaleBackaNZBook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 But WHEN ARE THE SANDI TOKSVIG EPISODES COMING????? I am impatient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local Avon saleswomen lists one of her interests as "keeping up with End Times news on YouTube."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys guys the UK has Marmageddon now! https://t.co/BFhSyQwSKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moar_moar This has made my morning so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our CEO repping in Bonn @VSAvolunteer @gillgreer https://t.co/vY3wo6kr3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to boyfriend, 39, and daughter, 5, argue about whether unicorns exist. Going to ask them to say one nice thing about the other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure this is a perfectly reasonable picture for this story. https://t.co/3b2mERBxPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 My dream of home ownership is entirely driven by wanting a dog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dritchie Justice comes around eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: huge closing down sale at civic video Johnsonville. Come pick over the carcass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dritchie I'd buy it. It there a Bridgeman extension?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Day Planner includes this a a Principle of Time Management: Ensure that you make the best use of your time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommendations for a good pub quiz in Wellington CBD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five-year-old: "Wait. New Zealand has an army? Why? They must be nice guys who just learn karate."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso That or the Vaticanoe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost thanks, have DM'd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @nzpost failed to courier to my work address, made me organise redelivery, confirmed redelivery and returned parcel to sender anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 Don't draw attention to it, they'll just close all but one of their service windows!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 Put it on your naked flesh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 I especially like the ads for lighter fluid and turpentine. Brighten up your kitchen! *buuuurn it alllll doooown*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 All of this is AMAZING. I want kitchen stools just to give them a saucy frill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: baby sloths on Prime right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop The salted caramel ones are even better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ @stephaniesoper I thought matching my bike shorts to my skirt made me Claudia. It did not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalena I'll pass that on - good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalena URGENT request from IPU: pls bring some coconut gold back 🌴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalena @VSAvolunteer Have fun you two!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behold Your Newest Silver-Screen Sex Goddess, Jane Neighbor https://t.co/6V38MR0dM5 via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lyndonhood Haven't had a gouda enough excuse to link to this in aaaaaaages. Best comment thread, ever. https://t.co/vU2e0yx3Nw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 Thanks Mary. I miss her velvety face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My beautiful fur-niece made it to 13 before she ran out of puff. Go well, pup. https://t.co/BlEJAkuiRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, this is so lovely. "The children of Niue are in good hands." https://t.co/ad7zIwzsDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryFrances110 "As you can see, the diet is going well."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@di_f_w I met someone from Corrections' volunteer team recently and they're struggling for vols as it is :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello, fellow regular humans https://t.co/AliJkBVJY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways can't wait :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @AnaSamways for the Terry Teo tip! That was Sunday evening with a pile of cheese and spaghetti toasties when I was a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ cool, thanks. That's one School holiday activity sorted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ how did your sensitive five year old cope? Mine is desperate to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's mix all the Lego sets together, we said. It'll be fine, we said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brown paper packages... https://t.co/CVCe8IspRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordered M's scooter from @toycostlukes - not only great price but no "girl/boy toy" rubbish anywhere on site. Woo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something for the AV club... https://t.co/SBYKepeDyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My niece has started texting. https://t.co/ZizXrFCkQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard at school: "we're going early coz grandma locked our baby in the house!"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>