<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Provide Minorities with a Richer College Experience https://t.co/7cHa0DQrhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student Success in Any Path, College or Career, Involves Letting Students Take Responsibility https://t.co/hgOAq4DUJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping Students to Develop Presentation Skills https://t.co/MPvdaKR4xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Makerspaces Are the Key to Innovation https://t.co/VZPOtCBa7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Create Virtual Learning Experiences in Your Classroom https://t.co/KJyZbw8vml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Gamification in Education Leadership Development https://t.co/YfFmVwNG7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Lessons We Can Learn From Communicating Through Design https://t.co/3qqXL3Tjmc via @jeffbullas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Jargon for Good, Not Evil, in Your Content and Marketing https://t.co/argbjmy6l8 via @marketingprofs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Comedy Central Is Replacing Commercials With Branded Content via @contently https://t.co/UtpkCHATxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online Content: Is Longer Really Better? https://t.co/tV6ZfkO3wI via @Kissmetrics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Write Attention-Grabbing Headlines in 2017 - NewsWhip https://t.co/B2ePa9g2x5 via @NewsWhip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day Three: How to Polish and Prepare to Publish Your Content https://t.co/rVkjeQhiEp via @ProBlogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Brands That Hit A Home Run With User-Generated Content https://t.co/6tm6putPcp via @smxplorer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to go above and beyond with your content https://t.co/UXRj0EenBO via @marketingland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 undeniable signs your competition is beating you online https://t.co/Z6YjhxiYFn via @marketingland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Killing Your Content Team: 3 Ways to Scale Work With Existing Resources https://t.co/x0FJoXiyFR via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Native Advertising, 2017 Looks Like a Year of Clarity - eMarketer https://t.co/l0l0ApC3KG via @eMarketer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build a "Backbone" for Your Content Marketing https://t.co/ZH7uwNlEAz via @ProBlogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Inventories Don't Have to Bog You Down: Use Random Sampling https://t.co/AzeWk2ZHVK via @jdavidhobbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes an effective brand slogan? https://t.co/I3BNOj301u via @Econsultancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Ways to Repurpose Your Content for Email Marketing | Movable Ink Blog https://t.co/fIdfE0HmJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Know Exactly What Content to Deliver to Convert More Prospects https://t.co/1UyLGjBMWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Killing Your Content Team: 3 Ways to Scale Work With Existing Resources https://t.co/2DViaGVrSR via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Native Advertising, 2017 Looks Like a Year of Clarity - eMarketer https://t.co/pTbCypb7C9 via @eMarketer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day One: How to Build a "Backbone" for Your Content Marketing https://t.co/ZH7uwNlEAz via @ProBlogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A System for Easily Publishing Consistently Great Content - A Pamela Wilson Series https://t.co/is9yopejDz via @ProBlogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Ways to Make Controversial Content Work for Your Brand https://t.co/KoViDkq2AZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of retention marketing as a strategic priority in 2017 https://t.co/LR5tCXr92b via @marketingland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ecological Society of America writes Trump on Immigration https://t.co/IBJSn7KjX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Marketing In The Engagement Economy https://t.co/Fdch0BnCBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Internet Users Give Cold Shoulder to Sponsored Content - eMarketer https://t.co/cMlHXWZdul via @eMarketer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to ACE Content Marketing in 2017 https://t.co/I2sR52Nzsg via @iantruscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Marketing Success: Why Answering Questions Sells https://t.co/R01Qivpa5U via @smexaminer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Tips to Engage Consumers with Sponsored Content in 2017 Amidst FTC Crack Down https://t.co/BFFbAxYEUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In protest of Trump entry ban, some scholars are boycotting U.S.-based conferences https://t.co/3mMgtx3ghH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[101 Marketing Tools and Technology Tips for 2017 https://t.co/EvUIzwq8Qs via @razorsocial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measuring Your Content Marketing’s Real Performance https://t.co/HC0JYw9POS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Virtual Reality Could Change Content Marketing https://t.co/10po0wbNAQ via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Know if Your Content Is Actually Useful (and What to Do if It’s Not) https://t.co/G3PK2hbhuy via @simonslade?lang=en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Get Your Content Published on Forbes and Huffington Post https://t.co/6y0P7onkEz via @jeffbullas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Evaluate the ROI of Branded Content https://t.co/4BjGpCjHfp via @Kissmetrics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Reasons Influencer Marketing Starts with Creating the Right Content by @BrianHughes116 via @smallbiztrends https://t.co/0JuwRZzIhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put *Them* First to Win Big https://t.co/6SiHZSJfAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original Research Moves the Needle for B2B Content Marketers - eMarketer https://t.co/piF1fvhEfr via @eMarketer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top tips for efficient marking https://t.co/GLZ8aZTuib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to use digital media to build relationships with families https://t.co/kbbGaBrycM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The free teaching resource with incredible potential https://t.co/EpZNJEsGzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Cross-Cultural Dialogue Builds Critical Thinking and Empathy https://t.co/PhS7sV65dk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Tools for Teaching Critical Thinking and Problem Solving Skills https://t.co/lmpGvOp1a1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Grab and Hold Readers' Attention In Academic Writing https://t.co/rIjXGowELe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Digital Games Help Teachers Make Connections to Lessons and Students https://t.co/FmGoEqfiU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Local Inbound Marketing Tips To Target Desirable Postcodes https://t.co/dvpEJYg0Re via @WebpresenceUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Type of Content Marketing Gets the Most Social Shares? https://t.co/X5zpup92Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Content Marketing? by @nashriggins via @smallbiztrends https://t.co/oil4jDRw2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create Best-Answer Content: 6 Inspiring Examples https://t.co/XL7xte9Q8L via @toprank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mars Takes a Bite Out of Content Marketing https://t.co/dnzKGf2gAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Big Content Marketing Strategy Trends to Know This Year https://t.co/671TpWxPW3 via @DannyNMIGoodwin, @sejournal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Go-To Types of Educational Content for B2B Brands https://t.co/AfWB0KIuZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should academics boycott Donald Trump's America? https://t.co/8lfYbialtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Proven Strategies for Effective Community Marketing https://t.co/kre1Yb3ruT via @ExpertsExchange @sejournal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create Authentic Hyperlocal Content At Scale https://t.co/lfoM7PoQK0 via @moz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content strategists take heed! 10 lessons from The New York Times' 2020 report https://t.co/lYhqpcLjpU via @Econsultancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Digital Marketing Strategies You Need To Know https://t.co/m322WBA1wM via @ppchero @AlainaPThompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art of Seductive Content Marketing https://t.co/eI21OITM9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 Traits of Successful Content Marketers https://t.co/T12ROw9C0T via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Produce 300 High-Quality Articles a Year: An 8-Step Process https://t.co/9qeOKwKZg0 via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News Impacts All of Us: Here's How Content Creators Can Adapt https://t.co/BkhTYxCtOB via @dshiao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News Impacts All of Us: Here's How Content Creators Can Adapt https://t.co/DIxpMLJqnA via @dshiao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Content Marketing Trends That Will Change SEO In 2017 https://t.co/z1IQ7NRRzD via @senginepeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you writing too much content? https://t.co/aviaGXpzwc via @marketingland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need Engaging, Authentic Content? Unleash the Power of Conversations https://t.co/SO7jMg7Bv3 via @cmicontent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Key Takeaways About the Future of Content From the Brand Storytelling Conference https://t.co/rW6RKrw2is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How digital media won the White House for an ‘analog’ audience https://t.co/LIrFCMoWD5 via @marketingland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disengaged Students, Part 4: The Evolution of Anti-Intellectualism https://t.co/txBfssx7HJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Virtual Reality is Changing Education https://t.co/Pgk27Pslg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gamifying Your Social Studies Classroom https://t.co/MdBWgHBvIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Teach Digital Citizenship to Your Students https://t.co/Em5gSC5UUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Coding Should Be a Compulsory Subject for Students https://t.co/NY8KiDqJwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Elements of a Strategic Marketing Program https://t.co/ZfmDTVFtvS via @abrearton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viral Content Marketing Campaign Checklist https://t.co/0bF52wiVHA via @senginepeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Subterranean Foundations of Any Good Content Marketing Strategy https://t.co/Osp9hGMsgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Marketers’ Perspective on the Content Marketing Ecosystem https://t.co/ZXcqRCNTgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Time Marketers Rethink Their Commitment to Content https://t.co/zn0eaRLr57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Define Content Marketing Objectives in 3 Simple Steps https://t.co/67rbFkF5Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: How Boomers and Millennials Use UGC Differently via @contently https://t.co/qhIZvlyHYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extend the Invitation: What Kids Eating Kale Teaches Us About Content Marketing https://t.co/9saWTGHfi0 via @simplymeasured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Tactics to Make Sure You Never Run Out of Content Ideas https://t.co/NrLUbmxRCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Things You Don't Know About Influencer Marketing - eMarketer https://t.co/c72MHuhEnl via @eMarketer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Google’s Knowledge Graph Secretly Damaging Your Content Marketing Efforts? https://t.co/4OgYQj8azi via @Kissmetrics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Female-Focused Branded Content Studio Connects With Its Audience https://t.co/Zvur6K9E3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 evergreen resources for content managers https://t.co/dU7AS1NMJH via @Econsultancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching Is Establishing The Need To Know https://t.co/jv6kJ4R6a7 via @TeachThoughtPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Definition For Equity In Education https://t.co/gNjALM3VC1 via @TeachThoughtPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are You Teaching Content Or Teaching Thought? https://t.co/zOKAiAY62W via @TeachThoughtPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Project-Based Learning To Flip Bloom’s Taxonomy For Deeper Learning https://t.co/AiCw1nJFEU via @TeachThoughtPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to rise to the top in influencer marketing strategy https://t.co/gH7pNXAV2c via @tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Content History Should Live Forever https://t.co/0YTXaGaYSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Content Marketer's Approach to Successful Social Selling and Sales Enablement https://t.co/j09lLF1drL via @marketingprofs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmatic Delivery: The Future of Content Marketing and Promotion? https://t.co/CjXHP7ObsK via @moz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsourcing Content Marketing: How to Make it Work https://t.co/glQiKIUEjm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>