<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite placards from the Wellington #WomensMarch https://t.co/ZIrkJJlbEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Around 3,000 people across NZ joined the #WomensMarch I went in my #pussyhat https://t.co/t0KxyGLoBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'M SO PROUD OF YOU ALL
WE MARCHED IN NZ
Women's March events mark Trump's first full day in office – as it happened https://t.co/hC8N81UdSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump didn't drain the swamp. He just threw in some alligators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously though... them's some tiny hands https://t.co/4LCHkJj8dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God I love the Obamas
#Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Hillary Clinton has just embraced this as the comedy show that it is
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bradt89 not that he had a choice. he didn't exactly have a lot of people lining up to perform for him lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear
#nationalanthem
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude if you have to say "this is good", it's probably not that good
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washing my medicine down with booze. How apt
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will never be ignored again"
Not true. I'm ignoring you all right now
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an awfully long winded way to say "fuck everyone who isn't American"
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Trump just rickrolled an entire country
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god. Well congrats USA you now have a VP who supports gay conversion therapy. You dickheads
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit the crowd just made angry noises because a speaker mentioned lgbt+ WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG W YOU USA
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dubstep1988 they did cheer very loudly for Hillary Clinton though, so they're definitely still brave
#Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wat the actual fuk how r they allowed to co-opt presidential hand-over to preach??Wat happened2 separation of church&amp; state
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait what they have an actual Christian prayer during the inauguration??? That's bloody ridiculous 
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus even the music sounded sinister before he came out
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, Trump really does fit all the physical descriptions of Dolores Umbridge... minus the pink
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naheedR HA good point! Though there's always a fair bit of crossover so at least she'll get plenty of warning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet Melania's wondering what the fuck she got herself into right now
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my first experience rage-knitting, and I must say, it does make for fast progress 
#pussyhatproject
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah there's hardly ANYONE there!!
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump family in the crypt... As if they didn't already look enough like bad Bond villains
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still half expecting to see someone get shot
#InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5am here in NZ as I get drunk on pink cider and watch police throw tear gas into crowds of masked anti-facism protesters 
#inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knitting my pussy hat and watching the #inauguration 
Thank god for alcohol https://t.co/bs1HXMZA8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mother and I just got a fright because her phone rang.
Me: You still have a home phone??
Mum: It still works???? https://t.co/hd2LHwX1Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made my first bone wand, which I sculpted from clay. https://t.co/IzsShF2dJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a decal for my mobility scooter https://t.co/3JNSsdE4QJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShortlandTweet ads have got super intense. Shortland St ad guy u ok? Did u leave ur wife for a prostitute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: goes to the zoo
Also me: photographs sparrows https://t.co/uCbGA9WULY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder has its upsides https://t.co/blrrbLhBYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew this fuckin luscious wheatgrass for my cat to nibble on and she just... https://t.co/dPW3a5E98C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Pepper gets really into playtime she does forward rolls https://t.co/qP2PZrCJoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabinaKid the catnip shark I made was a hit https://t.co/Y7o7d3LY3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was Pepper's first Christmas and she had the TIME OF HER LIFE https://t.co/2SrQuHbGGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I not like cucumbers but fucking love pickles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY DID NOONE TELL ME YOU CAN ACCESSORISE WITH PRETZELS https://t.co/ug48kzV9NB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cat has the best resting bitch face I've ever seen https://t.co/b7BWuD4kXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSERVATIVES: black people are criminals. Prosecute women for having sex. Ban gays
LIBS: That's not okay dude wtf
C: YOU'RE SO INTOLERANT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of UK football players on their bravery coming forward about their abuse. You've given others the courage to speak out too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JARED HARRIS OBVIOUSLY https://t.co/qWMTX8EhPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah I'm that kind of cat lady https://t.co/A9HOPUpsFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In NZ even our earthquake specialists are adorable https://t.co/IDOAlV4G8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a tail what a tail what a tail what a mighty good tail https://t.co/D5vqWEsv8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were a millionaire I would definitely regularly buy those big-ass wheels of cheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lost my favourite pen for a month and just found it INSIDE A UKULELE what is my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquakes, tsunamis, flooding, gale-force winds, and now a tornado... The Trumpocalypse continues in NZ https://t.co/yfv2DxD3ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geonet had to turn off my "notify of every tweet" setting cause there are so many quakes! Crazy how they just keep coming! Stay safe evry1!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all US protesters:I support you. Make your voices heard. Exercise your right to peaceful protest.Fight for love &amp; equality #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BertHendo on #USElection2016 https://t.co/6fSGvtSDkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some hope. Please share - @HillaryClinton got majority vote in #Election2016 they should honour that.
https://t.co/LHQiljWbZs via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well now even @johnkeypm looks like a saint, so there's that...
#ElectionResults #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cspan @HillaryClinton Fuck she's great. You gave up this strong, gracious woman for that? Don't stop smashing that ceiling @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamEveryDayPpl @junejuly12 Given the state of things I'm not ruling it out. Nothing would surprise me any more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffreywbruce 49% is nowhere near enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to dedicate this election to all the white people who told us racism was over cause you had a black president.
#ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he does #BuildTheWall it'll keep you in as much as keep them out.. You really wanna trap yourself in there? #ElectionNight #Elections2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #USA how does it feel to be a citizen desperate to flee a dangerous government? What if noone wants you here? #CanadianWall? Such irony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaBloom too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, there's been an enormous surge in "move to NZ" googling. The world will hear way more bad accents very soon #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News teams here in NZ were speechless. Signed off with reminder of his sexual abuse, racism, fraud case, attacks on Muslims, POWs #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassie_complex it matters to us. One day they will learn we are people too, and the shame for their actions will crush them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not angry, I just feel sick. My heart goes out to Mexican Americans, and victims of his abuse. They must feel so betrayed #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, America. You're even dumber than we thought. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have hope for you, America, however faint.

https://t.co/npeXz13vVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how Houdini would feel if he knew his biggest contribution was giving tens of thousands of people a name for their naughty cats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to blend foundation into your neck 101 https://t.co/dymyFZqwVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hobo_Splendido @sophienuuttall Which base is what I wanna know. First base? Or are we going straight to third]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IOnceWasJay not yet, but flick me an email at sabinawandmaker@gmail.com and I can make one for you ☺ NZD$20 kids NZD$25 adults + postage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started making wands for fun and people keep buying them and I think I accidentally a business https://t.co/F71m01h4AV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samprimarolo97 @_gapc guess I'm not the only one getting weird shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabinaKid thank god for Vice https://t.co/76ol7L54uB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazmatnz nah they've specifically said money... Apparently he gets off on giving women things under threat of blackmail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I may have accidentally acquired a financial submissive. This is the weirdest wrong-number situation I've ever s… https://t.co/nwmMMmJc9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump campaign is like a grotesque performance art piece by an art/pol major that got in too deep and doesn't know how to end it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL trying to pretend he said "big league" not "bigly"... Like that would've made any more sense https://t.co/hsbYIRIvRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a strange man.
Imagine if the President called himself "the Obama". You're running for office, not Frathouse D… https://t.co/L7N7THHv2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me to my mum when she sees my bad report card https://t.co/Kiezd4TgQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohchicken @SarahKSilverman No wonder he's so full of shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Watching my kitten)
Me: haha she looks like one of those... snake cats
~5 mins later~
Me: FERRETS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some dude wrong-numbered me texting some chick about a spa voucher and now I might get a spa voucher today is a goo… https://t.co/Rwq3Pk5p5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hobbit... Give me a break! Now there's some small hands, believe me. Hairy-footed women... Sick. C- #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Matilda, great example what happens when you give nasty girls books. Trunchbull should'a shut that down fast. WITCH #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The prince gives up wealth for a pauper? Pathetic. Can't hack it. It's a joke, believe me. Sad #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Expectations? I'll tell ya who's got great expectations, folks. I do. Ill be so great, trust me, I'll be the greatest #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Chatterley's Lover? Dull. Don't bother with the book. Check out sex tape #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voldemort, give me a break... 30 years experience and he couldn't kill a child, folks. Couldn't kill a baby. WEAK #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Snow, now there's a leader. Not like that Katniss girl. Thinks she can fight with the big men. WEAK #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She'll take our guns and those mockingbirds will be everywhere. But I could kill it better, folks. I could kill it better. #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frodo, there's a pussy, can't even get a ring to a hill without a bunch of weirdos helping him. I know it, you know it. SAD #TrumpBookReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just told @nbcwashington who I think is winning. Cast your vote now! #Debates #NBC4DC
https://t.co/TxAU0kitFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody has more respect for women than me" -Trump
Even the live audience laughed #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fastest way to get all flatmates in one room is to say "pizza" out loud.
The "Bloody Mary" of reclusive 20-somethings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't really need to contact you when you've already been recorded confirming everything... https://t.co/vszoWVkTZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pepper threatening the pigeons. Very scary stuff https://t.co/hwNaWoWuZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I finally get sleep and risk missing more amazing Trump meldown or stay up refreshing his feed every 7 seconds? Serious question]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>