<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Change of heart, &amp; admission of guilt for the current state of Trump, by Conservative Commentator. The first of man… https://t.co/BauqSGeFlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jazzikiki @joelbernstein @ianbremmer Not to mention the Bali Bombings of 2002/2005. Indonesian terrorists, hundreds killed. Not on the list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Butthole_Fucker You've provided no proof.. did you forget to include the link to the EO by accident?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see a time in th near future when Democrats who Didn't bother to vote are strung up in mass lynchings. And GOPers will help #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthColangelo This is a 1st. Oz PM chooses not to comment on how other leaders run their countries? Iraq, Afghanistan, Indonesia, Malaysia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@907lissa Perhaps this may help you, because you're wrong - neither Korea nor Japan have Muslim bans. https://t.co/6akpMjbLNd  @Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@907lissa Really? I'd be very interested to see your reference for that. And no, Trump himself has said Christians will be admitted @Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo @janecat60 @guardian Erm - isn't StopTheBoats 'purely to stop the tragic deaths at sea'?? #Scumbag #Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@907lissa No, USA is the ONLY country to ban based on Religion. https://t.co/8Dq217heWT and https://t.co/24WXPyTmNJ #PeskyFacts #muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brn2Wander1 You obviously don't realise that when you say "I COULD care Less" means you definitely Care.? It's: I couldn't @washingtonpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No #MuslimBan in Israel, arguably the most vulnerable to attack. https://t.co/sh5hUCdXXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @CBSNews @CNN et al: Pay attention to this. This is how you do your jobs, and why. https://t.co/CWosLyaclf #mediablackout #msm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The epitome of Narcissism - re-tweeting yourself from your alternative account, @POTUS. #MuslimBan #ResistTrump https://t.co/sSxnWP0jhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianOpen Tennis needs @RafaelNadal to keep playing. He (&amp; Federer) brings a higher moral code to the game. A leader by example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkell1970 Because none of those 16 countries purport to be Non-Secular. Nor do they claim theyre "Home of the Free". USA does. @UKIPNFKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Rafa.. I hope you take heart,&amp; continue your rise back to the top. I was torn tonight - my 2 favourite players. Win-Win for me #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow.. NY is a Blue state, but I guess the taxi ban would trap a lot of Trump voters. ?Karma, for them to be unlawfu… https://t.co/DHMkpHAXOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind you - I was going to be happy if Rafa won, too. #jadore But this puts Roger even further above Sampras. Rafa has more time. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimbos2002 The attacker is from Morocco - which is not one of the countries under the #MuslimBan. Cheap shot. @JeremyLRedmon @repjohnlewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This needs to be retweeted a gazillion times. #MuslimBan #Please #MakeAmericaGenerousAgain https://t.co/o6S00Q3pFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Americans have no idea that FOXNews is owned, &amp; thus the USA is manipulated, by Rupert Murdoch. Am glad he's n… https://t.co/HC7YRLEJP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MontyDeWitt Not me, but I'd certainly support @neiltyson . If I could vote in USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeMySylvanEye I doubt History is his strong point.. or indeed with any GOPer.. #MuslimBan @cathywilcox1 @aronkader @smh @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElwoodHolgrun aaah, but it's not an unborn person until 20 weeks..or whatever your jurisdiction states is the term. @tabinfl @ericmetaxas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassic_snark_ Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassic_snark_ I have no idea.. They're hardly providing more education than any other state or territory. #cringe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service to the country counts for Zero under Trump.  https://t.co/SCB4DOD6d4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basicwhiteM0m oh, Honey.. It's like talking to fence posts, isn't it? *hugs @Biglued1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump toilet paper? Fantastic.. God bless American ingenuity..  https://t.co/BibE2Lvau7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimbos2002 Well dufus, I guess that #MuslimBan needs to be extended to MOROCCO. Or are Trump businesses there? @JeremyLRedmon @repjohnlewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is the #MuslimBan being applied? This from Saturday's Washington Post. Far more broadly than first thought.. https://t.co/DBYyaaSyey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix This from Saturday's Washington Post (of Watergate &amp; Nixon fame). As I said, we all need to pay attention https://t.co/Yz9MmB1FLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix And that's in no way meant as criticism - it's just everything is happening so quickly, you need to be attentive. Xxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix No, it came into effect over 36 hours ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix seriously, he signed Order on Thursday. Can I give some quiet advice: the world is changing rapidly. Might need to pay attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix Really? For the last 4 days? Wow.. Can I have some of what you've been taking, please?  Hahaha! @_Domerella @hannahdinhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenobilein None of those countries purport to be non-sectarian, nor do they boast how they're Land of  the Free. @hannahdinhd @mshafiquk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phoenalix ?Seriously? It's been all over the news, social media. I guess you've been busy with Australia Day, etc @_Domerella @hannahdinhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Samhedonia My thoughts exactly.. Seems oddly inappropriate, &amp; jarring. @hannahdinhd @atbobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am waiting to see the UN's response to #MuslimBan. It contravenes UN Refugee Protocol - which USA signed. https://t.co/O4UOdyXOoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I truly hope none of these voted Trump. Like the Iranian taxi driver I had in USA recently.  https://t.co/8L5YKXEQdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RouteI0 that's better.. Thank you. Bedtime for me. Xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RouteI0 oh..okay.. It comes across that the 4 of us mentioned above are all guilty.. I'm tired.. After 1am.. Zzzzzzz xxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RouteI0 erm - do you think I've been cyber-bullying, James? Of Melania? Sorry, it's very late, &amp; this confused me. XXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff Not to forget Indonesia &amp; Philippines.. @linc0lnpark @BBGVisualData]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump bans entry into USA from 7 Muslim countries due to terrorism concerns: Iraq, Syria, Iran, Sudan, Libya, Somalia, Yemen - no Indonesia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, let's get that Voter Fraud investigation going.. https://t.co/ZwE9GB82Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena almost looks pregnant, the way her stomach heaves.. I wonder if that explains her apparent weakness today. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer That would incl investigative branches, as well as all officials. No need to poke the dragon daily. Just saying..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer If I was you, I'd just Block any account associated w the Administration, for safety. Set up other anon. accounts to monitor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmuthuk Gotta love that exactness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJohnsonson erm, I think it's 8 years, not 4.. Double wipeout.. I wonder if he was hanging 5, or 10, during sentencing?  @kochie_online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yinyangman69 @SpaceKidette Bedtime here, got early start.. Xxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette Only problem is - then there's no PHs after Anzac Day to October. That's tough on the school kids. Winter, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette Mine for Oz Day, yours to replace Queen's Birthday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette in October.. Consecutive Monday's. They'd have to move one of those.. Never work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette HaHahahaha! Oh, well, if that's the case, how about 13th December? Us Xmas bubs get diddled. But, nah, ACT already has 2 PHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette Huh.. where did that come from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His wife is an immigrant. As is his first ex-wife.. https://t.co/5PiSrjYYID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette "On 3/3/1986, the Australia Acts came into force..Westminster parliament can no longer legislate for Australia" #changethedate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet it's just for show, though.. https://t.co/LNjwTslbks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lynquest I think this is a good argument for 3rd March. Which would still be a summer holiday - be more popular. https://t.co/9jlhMkHIUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cscviews And it's not like I'm obsessed with it, don't go looking for it. It's been everywhere @SpaceKidette @noplaceforsheep @RecogniseAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cscviews It's been discussed at length on TV, in print, twitter etc for the last few years. Resounding NO. @SpaceKidette @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cscviews Here's a good argument for March 3rd. Still summer, so #win. https://t.co/ea57cAYSyD @noplaceforsheep #changethedate #AustraliaDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cscviews Nah, no-one wants to share New Years with Oz day. That's been discussed ad infinitum @SpaceKidette @noplaceforsheep @RecogniseAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurrowDweller73 hahahaha!! Well, it's going to be a very hard sell to get it put in the middle of winter. Aussies love summer celebrations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AustraliaDay #changethedate May 9 seems significant.. https://t.co/oZZhhx7hro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep Yeah, nanosecond after I posted, I headslapped.. Doh! @5oh19 @SpaceKidette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5oh19 @noplaceforsheep @SpaceKidette But you know, there's a poetic Ozzie-ness to May8. I quite like it. Tough sell, tho.. #AustraliaDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5oh19 oh? Why? sorry..  @noplaceforsheep @SpaceKidette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep @Info_Aus No, it's always been on 26th, but the public holiday was declared either the Mon or Fri to make it LongWeekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New date for our National Day of Celebration - ie Australia Day..? May 9? https://t.co/oZZhhx7hro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep Openly here, on twitter.. Get some publicity for it. May 9th. @SpaceKidette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep My daughter would love it - it's her birthday! hahahaha! But seriously, it makes sense. We should push for it @SpaceKidette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep I suggested that last year, &amp; was shouted down by many. "It's not summer.." But yes, that's ideal, to me..  @SpaceKidette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette but then, in great Oz tradition, that'll clash w the Easter public holidays sometimes, &amp; we can't have that! @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette landing on Plymouth Rock, they celebrate Independence Day. Same as France. So, maybe March 28? 1st Elections? @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette I dunno.. that could be a long way off. That's a Referendum, &amp; they usually Fail. But, USA doesn't celebrate @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette I actually DON'T think we should celebrate Settlement. It should be a date significant to our independence. @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette I agree we need to find a new date for National celebration, but 26th is historical  https://t.co/OxEOknUb7y @noplaceforsheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NesrineMalik Surely Trump's ban on refugees from Syria etc makes a mockery of the Statue of Liberty quote. It's now a greater terror target]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtheistRepublic FOX News. And Breitbart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette Seems so, according to The Guardian. I'm gobsmacked. And frightened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once used rhotacism to disguise my opinion of his sexual prowess. I said he Ranked well. #artwiculate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanGosling which is the first time she's played her piano since her Dad's funeral 2 years ago. So, Thank You for inspiring her. #tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanGosling I'd like to thank you: my 13yo went to see LaLaLand again yesterday, &amp; has spent last 24hrs trying to learn to play CityofStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idiot. Stage ONE totally survivable. She needs to talk to some widowers. #breastcancer https://t.co/97D0dir1ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 Oh, FFS! This is something Pete Evans, of #MKR &amp; #Paleo fame would be all over. This woman has Stage ONE!! Good grief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicCraig I always say "Cry" - it's very healing. Lots of hormones are released with crying, hormones that help your body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gardener_John From a baking hot 37C (98F), this looks anything But Dull..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry @PressSec - this isn't a Camera Angle issue. https://t.co/32KRomcb0h Perhaps it's a Wishful Thinking issue by you &amp; @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such a sad picture. I feel so sorry for Melania. https://t.co/GYgkEV5wt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww, isn't @realDonaldTrump such a romantic gentleman? All that affection &amp; respect he's showering on Melania. As f… https://t.co/I8fihDw7Yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OscartheOrange Hello, mate! Did you see this? https://t.co/TjdXJfdINd Hilarious!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette oh.. That was just a wild guess. Sorry.. I'll put it on my list to do some research.. I'll get back to you.. 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceKidette Mmmm...maybe cos he's a dick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, I believe.. https://t.co/H9st0XNBmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh, that's a bigly crowd out to rejoice in @realDonaldTrump's inauguration. #sad https://t.co/g47erZegsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleepingdingo Okay.. I just wasn't sure if I'd missed something in the last 12 hours. All good, and I agree with you. XXX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>