<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to go to dinner tonight around 5:30. I'll tweet when I can. I'm also in pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to go out on a limb here &amp; say that 1/2 of my tweets are Video Game related]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GameGrumpsisoverparty They never finished The Last Guardian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/DmeWbNKfsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do any of y'all remember the show "Good Luck Charlie"? That was one of the shows I grew up watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There stuff is more YouTubers, while then stuff I talk about can be YouTubers  mostly it's more video gamey stuff. https://t.co/jwjyk1FTvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the communities that I'm in are great. The people are so sweet, understanding &amp; kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love drawing characters w/ facial scars. Do you care? Probably not. Do I care? Probably not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand French as much as I do Italian 

Which is not much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I legit just know some words in Italian on my own. 

Bene (OK/good), Merda (shit) Cazzo (fuck), Fottiti (Fuck you), ect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech, History, &amp; Orch are my safe spaces @ school. I feel so comfortable being in those classes, you know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend RESEALED my can @ lunch today. I-I honestly don't have anything to say. https://t.co/Vr6vt7N2OH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Leave the sneaking &amp; spying to my sister. Toss me my brass knuckles &amp; point me to a good brawl" -Jacob Frye https://t.co/MxK2hXgSeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have talked about AFiL very much. 
The roasts are real. And it's sorta funny. 
Jacob is a main character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've wanted to quit the Grump notebook multiple times
But I won't. 
B/c I want to have something accomplished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, encouragement only works if a) you're not a family member b) I like you c) value your opinion d) you actually mean what you say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone came up to me today &amp; said I looked intimidating... OK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this happened today. And it somehow made me realize how much better my life had become since the first 1/2 of Ja… https://t.co/pgQjOGUfaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So overall I'm 80% done w/ everything in the main game of Syndicate, but I really want to play it again. Should I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My profile picture brings me great joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did it... Also deleted "Artist" part of my bio. https://t.co/UFIpKcIMsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm going to delete all my art off my Instagram b/c I'm tired of being insulted by my brother every time I post something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ART. https://t.co/z6kQDK1pYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I have no problem being a small account, it's just sorta annoying is all I'm saying. https://t.co/ivYdXUsNHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like how people complain they're losing like 10 followers &amp; they have like 10+k &amp; I'm here w/ my mutuals like "Wtf gtfo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My IRL friends keep saying a mutual &amp; I are dating, even know I've told them we aren't, they're still 100% not kidding &amp; it's annoying af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing might be the death of my wrist/middle finger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Technop1p @Steampunk_King @ponycrazy_123 Definitely pupper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls, Never lash out at an artists art/artwork. Especially if you can't draw yourself. It's rude &amp; destroys their confidence. Encourage them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls break the tie someone. I STG IF IT BECOMES A 3 WAY TIE https://t.co/yPdVPOLrVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I have this spare account Idk what to do w/ what should I do w/ it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daz_black It's ok, family stuff is more important than videos sometimes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/DmeWbNKfsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea your puns are so *chuckles* basic. https://t.co/o5SowrthPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) That's amazing
2) Your handwriting is also amazing. https://t.co/HSgpSs0eA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hair is like half straight half curly. WTF IS GOING ON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those of you who think it's weird that I get attached to characters it's not. SO STFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B/c why not. https://t.co/mVwgazxJ0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf is this angle. Why did I start drawing @ this angle?? It's so awkward. https://t.co/zPrknyzJ9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksfilms I challenge you to fix my awkward bio #fixbio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if I'll play that game more tonight or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matthiasiam At least you look better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That DLC actually made me cry. Cried for @ least a solid minute. Still teary eyed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksfilms I actually told my friend on of them &amp; she actually believed me. She told her family and the next day she was ready for my blood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; why isn't Evie even worried about Jacob. I mean SHE'S HIS FUCKING TWIN!! I'm so done w/ Evie's shit. https://t.co/IeqlVvgxdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I'm going to have PTSD or some shit after playing Jack the Ripper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some places I would like to go in the future: England, Italy, &amp; Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to do the plot of the DLC then worry about the other shit later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sorta want to watch Stranger Things again just for the hell of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to play the actual mission but I get distracted really easily w/ the associate activities. UhhHhhHHHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AC memes/comics/fanart are the things I love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What a prick" https://t.co/qOmYIZVrxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any emotion I have rn it's toward Jacob b/c I wanna know where is is. B/c HE'S NOT DEAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can't be. It wouldn't make since. Why would they kill the superior twin?? https://t.co/nwKsfkNbfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still undergoing emotional stress over not knowing if Jacob is dead. He's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOOK AT THE CORGI! IT WILL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER! IT IS THE FEEL BETTER CORGI! https://t.co/cmbl3UUAuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never in my life have I ever been so attached to a character. https://t.co/hmJkS0mbhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to take a little break b/c my eyes are actually filled w/ tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evie looks really ugly and then there's just Jacob. https://t.co/HeE2CMss9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I refuse to believe he's dead. https://t.co/k5QByWofK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do it! I believe in you!! https://t.co/alplXZz3Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've started the Jack the Ripper DLC &amp; I actually almost started crying b/c you have to hunt down &amp; beat up Jacob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS HAS ME SO EMOTIONAL &amp; IDK WHY! GOOD LUCK YOU TWO! https://t.co/OCZPEXgII3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wiishucomments Are you more of a cat person or a dog person?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also my hair can be curly or straight. https://t.co/IbyseAV1Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I flipped the part on my hair and it's sorta weird tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as you know https://t.co/Zn9Chhv2Zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could be less awkward it would much easier to talk to people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullshit is being pulled my mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to play DLCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so pissed. 
And anxious 
I shouldn't be on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Later I'm going to try to talk to him again b/c I feel a little more comfortable w/ it now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have strict rules about phones &amp; stuff, then again he probably has it silenced. https://t.co/Nvz53pziNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sorta want to bother the guy I like again but he has Solo &amp; Ensemble today &amp; I don't know when he preforms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't fair. I just woke up like 10min ago, and not to mention I haven't eaten. https://t.co/GTfORXO2Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my mom is acting like I'm overreacting for having to clean my room AND the dishes for the SECOND time in the row.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/DmeWbNKfsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to talk to 'im more, but it's 1AM &amp; no matter what I'll feel like I'm bothering him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*@ lunch*
Me: *gets interrupted every time I speak*
Me: *goes silent*
Friend: Corvo, you've been really quite.
Me: Hmmm wonder why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My calm has now turned into a small panic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like our convo was awkward but @ the same time I want to keep trying to talk to him to build confidence &amp; for it to be less awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'M SO PROUD OF MYSELF. https://t.co/X0eu9hFY0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GUYS I'M DOING A THING
I'M SORTA ACTUALLY HAVING A CONVO W/ MY CRUSH &amp; IT'S AMAZING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot believe I am 80% done w/ this game https://t.co/psb9mTOzQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple days ago I was checking some of my notifs on the bus and I said OUT LOUD b/c Chad uploaded a roast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process. https://t.co/dwchL33DHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same is happening to me. https://t.co/QWqRK1Ef7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I have filled up, vs what I haven't filled up. https://t.co/e2nz4zHgK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of focusing on everything you have yet to do, focus on the things you have done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all remember this. B/c I do. https://t.co/O8yprWhc3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea, everything is so much faster https://t.co/JDwarpMGuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that I'm complaining but when &amp; why did Chad follow me. I'm so confused, but ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sorta want to create a moments full w/ some of my drawings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's cool. Also, it takes like 5 seconds for my feed to load opposed to the 30min it used to take. https://t.co/J7rqOgwDnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWWWW. RIP John Hurt. Great actor. :'( https://t.co/dpo8ldivDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I had to uninstall Twitter b/c it was acting weird, and I think it just needed an update b/c it looks a little. different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to go make a really dumb decision 

YEA CAFFEINE! 

BRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you look at my other social media accounts they're clean &amp; then you get to my twitter account &amp; I'm like: SHIT DAMN FUCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a story for y'all, but I'm going to make sure I have time to type it, so in other words I'll tell you later 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got my haircut and I'm so self-conscious.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>