<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AislinnOT @realDonaldTrump but the "good" would have not travelled &amp; not been persecuted! Better 100 guilty men free than 1 innocent jailed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terribly sad John Hurt has died. Lovely lovely man and sublime actor. #RipJohnHurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randyfenoli @nikkihayes @RTERayDarcyShow yes it was!! With your gorgeous dog 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the privilege of seeing #DenialFilm utterly gripping, outstanding cast &amp; touching without being saccharine- abs… https://t.co/KVkfladhvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celticpussycat @Benefit_IRE uhhh well you certainly looked fab with your tutu!! Pretty as a picture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebyrneoffic @Barbarian_FC @AllBlacks class! Yes a few dodgy high taxkles!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theSeanPower saw you in #DenialFilm just an incredible movie!!! Gripping &amp; touching &amp; fabulous performances by a stellar cast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihayes @randyfenoli @syttd mum &amp; I would have competitions to see if we could pick the right dress!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihayes @randyfenoli even signed a photo for my mum Iris who watches him every day! https://t.co/yoOj6bifnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihayes @randyfenoli seriously he's a doll!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihayes @randyfenoli I met him! He couldn't be nicer! https://t.co/pMexQPoXlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc @DublinLaduree @dineindublin oh that is too chic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek we used to have chives in pots in the kitchen - loves the little purple flowers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PapaSonsFilm funny that my therapist makes me say - does this benefit you? When I do the same thing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy yes! Yes indeed it has!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc it's only January!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG #SplitMovie is BRILLIANT!!! M.Night at his absolute best! @Universal_Irl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulEOC @behindthesenes class actress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaSmurfit @robertcarlyle_ @mcgregor_ewan it's BLOODY brilliant! #chooselife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaSmurfit serious how fcuking awesome for Ruth Nega!!! #Oscars2017 #lovingfilm ('scuse my French!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lennyabrahamson just download an IP address changer and you can watch anything from anywhere as it thinks you're in the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy raffle it for charity!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzanne_Brett @barbarascully thanks Suzy x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzanne_Brett @barbarascully they're good &amp; like mum but you can't get 1on1 attention so it's always going to be what's easiest for staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully @Suzanne_Brett we pleaded sayings she's 89 with alz &amp; nurse said oh well I have a 91yo woman here since midnight! And? So??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully @Suzanne_Brett oh we're busy &amp; we don't have the drugs. It's a hospital!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully @Suzanne_Brett &amp; our treatment in Vincent's was terrible. They wouldn't give her Alzheimers &amp; anxiety meds. Just kept saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzanne_Brett @barbarascully things happen I know but when it's out of your control it seems cruel &amp; unusual. Getting old sucks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzanne_Brett @barbarascully it doesn't feel like that especially when she had a fall on sat &amp; broke her nose https://t.co/JEgBzIfi0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully I had to put mum in a home 4mnths ago. I'd give my left arm to have her home today. Fair Deal is not fit for purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyricmoviemusic @RTElyricfm am I the only person who thought this movie was very disappointing? Her performance was hollow &amp; brittle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alzheimersocirl @HMcEntee @ClaireByrneLive the state don't care about the elderly!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alzheimersocirl @HMcEntee @ClaireByrneLive &amp; cant go on strike! €204 a week for 24/7 care. But force people into Homes &amp; take their]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alzheimersocirl @HMcEntee @ClaireByrneLive oh please! "Consultation" total BS! They've know for years that carers are vulnerable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aileen_otoole @alzheimersocirl @BrendanCourtney took me 6mnths to do forms! Mums in a home 4mnths now &amp; I still don't know what will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByrneLive impossible situation. Couldn't afford home help - did it on my own for 6yrs. Heartbreaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByrneLive &amp; im still not sure about the implications. Mums gone to a home now. We only had 9hts from Alzheimers Soc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByrneLive took me 6 months to do #FairDeal forms &amp; dealt with 3 offices in different parts of the country. It was a mine field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDermaClinic fabulous can't wait to try!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc @Universal_Irl slightly gutted I'm not there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanCourtney well done on #LateLateShow just sent you a very long text! Great to see you at @andreahayesie book launch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeraldKean always loved it - lovely food. Although the company obviously doesn't hurt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonegalNoel @BTYSTE @RTELateLateShow serious! Every year I am more proud &amp; just in awe of the genius of our young people!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickFreyne1 @IrishTimesCultr it really was very entertaining!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herdotie if only cases like that happened here! It's almost impossible to prove &amp; the woman ends up vilified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc @andreahayesie @farrierdraper @Briantredmond @Fran_Kav cocktails are imminent!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc @andreahayesie @farrierdraper @Briantredmond @Fran_Kav fabulous night - can't wait to read the book!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy please! Bertie?? He makes Haughey look like mother Theresa!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElaineCrowley @Republic2fm @JenniferMaguire @boshea5 @KeithWalsh2fm @RTE2fm because boobs are fabulous!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitrionaPerry @goldenglobes the woman is just beyond incredible! I was in awe and tears!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amylross85 I know seriously the woman just doesn't get any better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEOne @AmandaByram @NickyByrne massive congrats! Great show - so so much better than I thought!! #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RushFitness2 bloody hell that's terrible John!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_merrells @realDonaldTrump Jason if he had any honour he wouldn't have stood in the first place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailyedge to be fair most people do! I don't know why they bother trying to do a brogue at all! But I love you used "hames" #irishwords]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deric_hartigan The Blacklist. Elementary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_LambOfficial welcome to every day of most women's lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GEORGEZAKK hey George Happy New Year!! Can I dm you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colonel_meow @crazyavey we love Uncle Mark!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually holding my breath!!! #eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy I think you should be applauded for cooking! Don't criticize yourself because your eggs aren't perfect! Most of us go to McD's!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek awww you got a rabbit for Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy did you add vinegar to the water first??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year!!!🎆🎊🎈 https://t.co/gX5OvS8Rb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbceastenders AMAZING storyline with Lee! Incredibly filmed. Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealBrentPope super film - you know the outcome but still finding yourself holding your breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjgallagher mine too!! Breaks my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef does it work with antibiotics and cough medicine???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef now THAT was amazing! Maybe it will pick up?? Or throw in a topless Aidan Turner 😇😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef it's very slow #witnessfortheprosecution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek so many comments so few characters...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angelascanlon @McMahonPhilly wow that was just so eloquent - my dad died a couple of days before my birthday (and his) so I partly get it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soup, turkey &amp; stuffing sandwich and James Bond #Perfec (ala David Jason in darling buds of may)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef it's a great cast and it takes effort to feck up Agatha Christie!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek Phils having surgery &amp; dum dum dummmmmm Max turned up!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebyrneoffic royally shit alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AislinnOT oh holy god miley that's fabless!!! Can I get the recipe??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneLawlor right back at you 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaSmurfit it's ok I have the matching toilet roll holder AND toilet paper!!! https://t.co/Rn4xgwCXTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AislinnOT oh it's one of my pet hates!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krystleniteclub @WayneLawlor @CiamhieMc another brilliant night last night - thanks so much guys xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek go to O'Brien's Irish Pub, corner of Wilshire Blvd &amp; 23rd St Santa Monica - best craic &amp; food ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_plantgeek my favorite part of the world - I used to live on Sherman Canal!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krystleniteclub @WayneLawlor @CiamhieMc and how did I end up on the ferry to Liverpool with no shoes??? #KrystleTales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef @randallandaubin oh go on then - seeing as you asked nicely lol - next time I'm in the U.K.!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbaineschef @randallandaubin what are the chances of bringing it to my house for dinner?? #cantcookwontcook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doyler9 @CGraceCassidy @breakingnewsie absolutely- no one with an ounce of compassion could convict her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CGraceCassidy @breakingnewsie just awful. I hope the poor woman finds peace in time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDermaClinic wowwwww can't wait to try it!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilliesdublin at least she still has her shoes on!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilliesdublin uhhhhhhhh Christmas love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilliesdublin haha love it! Where's Ken??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennyeclair but put the card in the flap instead of the tray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennyeclair throw it out the window]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamLegzdins ah look there you are!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrileconteoff YOU CANNOT BE SERIOUS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEOne kids were fantastic &amp; Ryan is brilliant with them. Trad set was so good!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEOne best #latlatetoyshow in years!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww bless his little face! Rory McIlroy!!! #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then I shed a tear - gorgeous little kids! #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>