<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmiSmiles holy shit i got on in all caps i got scared for a second. congrats kimmi!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmiSmiles that really does sucks, not finding your pet for an hour kills me. I really hope you find him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeAleck but i love it at the same time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeAleck this is stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going to the beach like 

"this place is tit lit"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people ask me about relationship advice and like life advice when i'm single and have no life lol what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision you shouldn't feel bad if you want yourself to be happy and someone with any depression should see professional help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision I know, doesnt get people can go under and around the wall? people sneaking in are gonna find a way. the wall is a waste of time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laineybot lol why do people care what you do with your money? it doesn't have to be a public thing when you donate money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision I love u like I loved my pet rat. Not enough hang out time to actually have a friend relationship but u still pretty cool ya know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ealuker @RealAlexPreston I think it's a luker thing, I don't even drink beer and that's how my convos go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Co_Mill @smosh I think you gotta fight him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyCostanza I wanna go to airport full glam one day, one day. Idk how to do make up tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex is a lot like money. I don't have any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery @CarrieHFletcher @petesjams and hey I can tell you've been working out Emma, your biceps are looking good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery @CarrieHFletcher @petesjams ur hair looks great here Emma. Hope u guys are happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smosh @SmoshStore @Co_Mill @anthonypadilla @AtomicMari dat ass and hair and stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmiSmiles sorry to hear :( hope you find him, maybe he went into someone else's window. Idk good luck kimmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery tf are you fucking serious? Holy balls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[in shitty bar]

*guy walks up to girl* 

"What's a guy like me wanting to be inside of a girl like you?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm almost 23 and i still do this, this is why i'm single https://t.co/gzz0fSyeMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just need a good romantic comedy, ice cream and coke amirite ladies?

cocaine

actually no

i don't like ice cream tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you shake someones hand remember that that hand is the hand they use to masturbate with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have a sex addiction, i'm addicted to not having any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there are a lot of things that suck in life, there are a lot of things that sting in life like gonorrhea, i have gonorrhea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeAleck i've faked every orgasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% of women who fake orgasms die. Be aware, be safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaseholfelder are you able to put it on iTunes or anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@authorajhartley those look sexy. I want one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaseholfelder awww :( I loved that cover, for a cover tho? Tf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexPreston that's sick. I want the name now, I will start playing funk to have it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery I know right? I love the effort put into this lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this https://t.co/nwzpOBBy7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild we both know i'm not good at anything else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild i know, you tweeted like 30 seconds ago and i got scared and panicked lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild who's bravo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyCostanza fuck. I wish I thought of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes dick pic

*uses micro lens* 

If you know stuff about camera lenses this is kinda funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision keep up what you do. I admire that work ethic you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild that's right bc I already proposed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexPreston @TheChainsmokers @halsey @YouTube love the thumbnail too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexPreston @TheChainsmokers @halsey @YouTube sounds good dude, well produced and mixed. Can't wait for the next album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MTV how hard is it have my own show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery it's still January in on this side of the pond or whatever that saying is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild do you really trust people u don't knows opinion what to do wit yo life? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im here to eat ass and chew bubblegum

Wait no

Im here to eat ass THEN chew bubblegum

No one likes shitty breath

#thankyouuuuuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild lol its 50/50 right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to wet my alarm an hour before I'm suppose to wake up so I can struggle to get up and cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaseholfelder where's the without you cover?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bandtrash66_6 @Onision oh fuck it was him? That's fucked up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmiSmiles nahhhhh not all. I'm in then out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmiSmiles tf, what do they do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its Tuesday now and i got no mcm :( tf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeAleck @MagnetoTheWhite @Onision and just because they were different that doesn't mean they were "semi-nomadic" the Europeans took over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision Europeans were not the first nation in america so they are immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision I know, she made the right choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision I didn't say that, check again. And there was nations here already before Columbus arrived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision So if you go to a foreign land with no law when there are already people there are you legal? no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision EXACTLY, so they were illegal then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision i'm pretty sure in 1492 there were no legal European immigrants. Common sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision and the fact is america was made by Europeans a.k.a. immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagnetoTheWhite @OMGitsRuthless @Onision great argument but yeah it was all 100% native americans who lived there first than Europeans came]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laineybot lol what bout Greg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ealuker I give you my condolences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump u think a walls gonna stop people from coming? Thats more ridiculous than a rich white reality show dude becoming president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everything happens for a reason is a stupid saying, sometimes shitty stuff happens for no deserved reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you go to prison you can get a free highschool diploma and a free college degree. what the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roomieofficial but she a gynecologist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild tweet something, i'm bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision god how can people be this stupid in the first place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmablackery I can just see a bunch of kids making like dozens of accounts to just like this lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild me too girl me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision shits gonna keep escalating unfortunately, it doesn't look like he's gonna stop anytime soon. Good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild it was accident i was playing with it then the ball came out and i'm not talented enough to put it back in lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watch this 

https://t.co/LbVRhLept5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeAleck 1st world problem, people are being denied into US and i'm complaining about my stupid piercing lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild nothin, im just chillin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild truth, i want you to sit on my face until i die. i win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isabelbeltrann no joke i was like "fuck yeahh" took my pants off, ate pizza and now watching yt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild lets be honest, you're not shocked i disappoint people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild more like
me: i'll disappoint you in every way possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isabelbeltrann me too, my friends bailed and i was lowkey happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davedays @ToriRoper I only get the important notifications https://t.co/y2yVnekW7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision stay alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild so only fine asses allowed eh? (I mean you, if you didn't understand this vague reference)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGitsRuthless @Onision except America was made from illegal immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGitsRuthless @Onision some of the Muslim people might've been born in the us. Idk who the people he wants to kick out are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision when I'm sure his family descended from Europe and he's telling people to go back to their country? His logic is? Lol what a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision new Zealand's amazing. They got hobbiton and lambs everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonD idk its pretty complicated #thankyouu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helli0nChild only for you Aleksandr ;) only bc i don't leave home and i'm kind of an asshole sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markhoppus sounds lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when you were really into uptown funk by Bruno and that other dude? What was up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision from Canada and i'm applying to a internship for a government job and they had this at the end https://t.co/LUamN9DQ3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision "everything happens for a reason" 
*sibling gets in a car crash*
that saying is stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Onision trump. Wall is in everyone's head. Break that wall down, more space to do shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laineybot what you looking for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roomieofficial I'd love to come but I'm kinda in Canada and getting over there isn't cheap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isabelbeltrann some documentary about sex robots. Watch it, cringiest and funniest thing I've ever seen]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>