<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[YUS @ICENINEKILLS at last! Worth debating catching their set two days in a row! https://t.co/dsO2rY3tkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlamDunkMusic @oceansatealaska so fucking stoked for @ICENINEKILLS #FaithRestored @FearlessRecords merch guys are sound too :D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me @Busted are NOT playing a 16 song setlist on this tour. They promised a much longer set post-Night Driver back in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE that they've brought the high articulation basic 6inch figures over to the Homecoming range. Even if Spidey is… https://t.co/NjdrThYhO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminbruce can it just be as good as The Black but somehow with Dsnop? XD. Also Irish shows, please, always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Beez_says is it wrong that I enjoy the records but disliked them live? Thought they were boring. haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlamDunkMusic heavy bands this time yeah??? @TDWPband and @issues (again) please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyCostanza truthfully I am not sure if I liked it or not. Fine to binge watch though, and it suits the January blues well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is why I can not comprehend doing any more college courses after this one. Just not able for it mentally. College work makes me sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have serious issues mentally when it comes to getting back into the 'groove of things' like this. I always do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the same module that was the first assignment of the college year, I drove myself nuts doing it at the last minute...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First college assignment of the new year is due in less than 24 hours, I haven't started it and don't really have a clue...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATTILAga Queen and Moshpit! Guilty Pleasure songs too please :P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matttraynor @blessthefall The bottomfeeder one! Loved the videos pre-Awakening! Need to do a jam like that song again btw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoked to hear @eric_stuart in Yugioh The Darkside of Dimensions next Wednesday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met @eric_stuart this weekend! Got him to sign a SDK Blue-Eyes (obviously) and a Peten (as I adore him in Yugioh Th… https://t.co/ohNGdNbu6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet to see the new screens, been pretty worried about the renovations to screen 2 though. @imccinemas @SavoyDublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily my favourite place in the country to see a movie, Savoy's other screens are sadly lacking. @imccinemas @SavoyDublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @imccinemas decreases the size of the room for @SavoyDublin's screen one I will probably NEVER attend a movie in the cinema again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorM_Photo I still thought they were meh live back in 2015 haha. Everybody to their own and all but another band I don't get the hype.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your favourite song off the new @ONEOKROCK_japan album is the one featuring @5SOS. haha https://t.co/gGHiP5bR4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beyblade_burst can't cause its region locked!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beyblade_burst not available in country tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@issues does this mean ye are playing @SlamDunkMusic again since its days beforehand? Would be so stoked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So gutted about this. @JoshBalz is lovely. https://t.co/XOQl0qwxyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Mandarake_En! Looking forward to using these! https://t.co/Qyrs2RgLsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY got my order from @Mandarake_En! SOOOO stoked for these! @beyblade_burst https://t.co/3HYFWgOW64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cane_Hill @ATTILAga fam should add ye to their European dates in April too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorM_Photo it's going to be a few bands who had or were on tours just before Christmas. haha. But HOPEFULLY some actual surprises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stfucuunt I bought the last TDWP album and EP on vinyl, I don't even have a player for them. haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am half debating making my New Years Resolution sober 2017 but I'd like to be able to drink a bit when I move back to Shannon for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly this was the right amount of innocent nostalgia I needed right now. Christmas/New Years comedowns suck. 1… https://t.co/bJ7NJ9E7vX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniMusicIreland @TheOfficialA7X @3arenadublin @GIZMOthePIKACHU saw you looking for comps lad :P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reviewing @TheOfficialA7X &amp; @Disturbed tomorrow. So that is a thing, that, just happened in my life! What a way to kick off 2017!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@issues Bring this tour to the UK/Europe guys! Or just do some headliners again! Don't even care that ye will never play Ireland, will fly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beyblade_burst yo when is the UK/EU release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtTiLaSean sad to see ya go man! Was gonna try and catch ye in Glasgow in April! But good luck in the future and with your marriage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATTILAga Moshpit &amp; Queen for sure. Maybe All Hail Rock And Roll too. #NotJustTheSinglesPleaseAndThankYou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlamDunkMusic so when is the next announcement? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stfucuunt like good albums released but very forgettable ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stfucuunt I found this years releases to be so meeeh that I can't even attempt to do mine haha. 2015 was almost as bad. haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sad to see @ODEONCinemas taken off meteor extras @Meteor_Mobile... Disappointing to not have a cinema to use the deal on in Limerick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new baby! &lt;3. @lenovo The thing is so fecking light too! Perfect for travelling! This live music reviewer is ha… https://t.co/xz0SrMod3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel Legends finally released a classic rogue (instead of the green mess she is nowadays) so I had to pick it up… https://t.co/NuE3F1Zco5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still think it was hilariously stereotypical 2010 era scenecore for the 2nd last song @TheYashin played live to be a Britney Spears cover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf that came out of nowhere. https://t.co/lVUTGI1lFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SumerianRecords @AAofficial and it's almost four years since it was recorded... #23MonthsWaitForADVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tlums you won't have that issue next time cause you'll be playing the fucking main room. Show was dope, crowd was dope. Come back soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danisilviaphoto Placebo was on so most of the Dublin based gig photographers were at that! I'm reviewing the show for @IrishRocknMetal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Achievement unlocked: use a @neilstrauss article on Green Day from 1995 in an assignment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when @issues was meant to be playing Ireland? Was so stoked, especially after I had to cancel my trip to Birmingham to see them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[them low quality phone pic problems. But savage stuff from the @Fangclubband guys! @twinatlantic were perfect live… https://t.co/nfhOPvCqyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah sure here is my review from the last time I saw @Fangclubband when they supported @NBThieves last year! https://t.co/9xaDuJPPh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY getting to catch @Fangclubband again tonight! Check them out if you haven't yet, you won't be disappointed! https://t.co/efzOQAKBzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLifeOfRyanC Reviewed their Dublin show, probably the best live set Ive seen this year, massive set &amp; production! https://t.co/WMxdRSUVZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCKING YUS! @TheWordAlive added! VERY tempted! https://t.co/tqq6CoESgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicoletters somebody beat me to the Hilary Duff reference. XD. I still have a copy of metamorphosis lying around somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HacktivistUK @timfyjames @BadSignBand @unfdcentral @JHURLEYhizrec @benhacktivist @zoaxofficial ah shure lads can ye bring that to Ireland!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BiffyClyro @brandnewrock @lissabreen ah shure here is my review now. You can ignore the Biffy Clyro parts if you wish :P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the horror of my laptop breaking I finally got my @BiffyClyro &amp; @brandnewrock review up! Check it out here: https://t.co/WMxdRSUVZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sadness being told that @EntertainerToys had no SS Beyblades left on Saturday :(. Staff knew about them so clearly sold out recently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilesExpress999 I've seen it about 15 times and it remains my least favourite too! Does very little for me! Pretty etc. but still!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously @riserecords keep bringing shit like The Rise Up Tour to Europe. @issues and @Cane_Hill next time ya?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BourgeoisXander 6 months sober here! Told myself I could drink this weekend if I wanted to but decided that I didn't need it! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Glasgow for @TheYashin's last show, holy fuck. Gonna be in a serious rush to make it on time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like how does one even review @BiffyClyro without writing 1000 words on them? haha. 27 song sets are NOT easy to cut down the word count on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about the last 1/3rd of Biffys set has taken me 460 words... So this is looking at 1250-1300 words when I have rewritten the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My laptop broke while I was in the middle of typing my Biffy Clyro review and I hadn't backed it up... :'(.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLifeOfRyanC @TDWPband how long did they play for man? Want to know if it'll be a longer set on Saturday in Glasgow or not. haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way too stoked for these shows now! @ENTERSHIKARI @CrossfaithJapan https://t.co/pcbE4YXy0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sweet @FIROfficial, @issues, @MIWband &amp; @dangerkids tour package NEEDS to come to Europe. It could fucking sell out smaller arenas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riserecords 100% WANT! Got @CalebShomo to sign my copy of This Means War when I saw Beartooth live back in 2015!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Glasgow for @TheYashin's last show on Friday! 1st time seeing them in over 3 years! Happy this is in the set! https://t.co/F8PotVkWS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lissabreen ah 40 minutes was better than 30 anyways! That set was intense as fuck towards the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lissabreen Hoping it's a mistake and their set is longer than 30 minutes. &gt;_&lt;.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lissabreen I don't even get why the band wouldn't argue for a longer set, Jesse is normally a diva like! Very weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lissabreen I just don't get why Brand New are not starting closer to doors? I know support is normally a tad rushed in 3arena but still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing @BiffyClyro &amp; @brandnewrock  in the @3arenadublin tonight! My review of the show will be up asap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloConnor new band formation going well so? Gonna be heavish or?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @SlamDunkMusic this year is looking good so far! https://t.co/3BHYLjCFX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorM_Photo I don't mind her and big ups to her for where she has gotten and how she has done so. But it just makes no sense. haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorM_Photo like I feel bad for the people going, Tennent's was the same price with class bands also playing it... and it didn't sell out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorM_Photo legit makes no sense. People in Belfast were confused as it was by Labrinth being on that bill... Lady Leshurr makes no sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BushiroadGlobal Otherwise, I see nothing but solid improvements, most of which took far too long to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BushiroadGlobal to avoid shit like x-1s not top-8ing, a problem Cardfight has constantly had. Making it an auto 10 rounds swiss is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BushiroadGlobal I still think that you guys are having issues understanding swiss... you play rounds based on attendance numbers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloConnor After the November 2012 gig we tried to get ye out and ye were having none of it! One of the messiest gigs of my life. haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloConnor is that November or May? You seemed fairly sober at the November gig so probably May :P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloConnor I had no ID &amp; couldn't get into the after party so you passed me a beer over the smoking area barrier after we went McDonalds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloConnor I would like to point out that I owe you a drink from Slam Dunk Ireland back in 2013. haha. Gonna be a good night dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy that @LiffeyHead now exists, an actual reason to go @atLiffeyValley! The GF picked up @bmthofficial - Count Your Blessings for 15e!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new @Fangclubband EP is delish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two weeks until @TheYashin, @WOLB &amp; @dividesofficial in Glasgow! Then @TDWPband, @MemphisMayFire, @silverstein &amp; @LMTF the next day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 months sober.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MemphisMayFire flying to Glasgow from Dublin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as does booking flights and accommodation for two dates of said festival the day dates are announced :P.… https://t.co/vAXu6jpwX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tellesmith Like just saying I'd be mad jealous hearing that people who paid for VIP got those unlike the regular fans of the band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tellesmith seems like those would be better inclusions for a set in front of a full crowd. #Pits Would make more sense to play new jams?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlamDunkMusic @ENTERSHIKARI No Sssweat! My absolute favorite ES song! Had it as my ringtone for years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lissabreen Birmingham was also tempting but Leeds is a Saturday! haha. Enjoy!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>