<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarpblanket maybe I could be one segment of the podcast where we talk about how difficult it is to get mass buy-in on new networks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarpblanket I just don't want to be a bad guest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarpblanket I mean I would have to get it first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much (or little) the environmental movement coalesces around the NDP compared to '09 and '13 will be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bun fight in aisle 7! https://t.co/QPWQcDop5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AN OUTRAGE WHICH MUST NOT COME TO BE. https://t.co/CTrgYI3PUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile they have to @richardzussman - will not be directly be doing stuff for the Liberals this election. https://t.co/bxjqas2rOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonplittle didn't make it into my copy, for some strange reason!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smasuch by which I mean "I must write about beers I drank months ago using a completely arbitrary ranking system."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smasuch this appears to be a Japanese puppet show inexplicably popular in Peru, but I don't have the time to go down that rabbit hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErikTWiik hey Erik - how long has the exposed wiring been there for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm six hours into my Twitter feed being 80% stories of U.S. foreign policy rapidly changing. https://t.co/cfx04ixg9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well i suppose all the journalists who didn't make that decision deserve to be fired then https://t.co/YFPVgdxqX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Monday was Bell, Black Tuesday was the Vancouver Sun/Province, Black Wednesday looks to be Rogers. NO JOKES A… https://t.co/op5UT4cTHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnywakefield look let's settle for Nelson and not get too pie in the sky here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellekane no, they need a story of the struggles of Los Angeles creative types, interspersed with ruminations about jazz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanBurritt @A_MacLeod_Tyee Jeremy's great, but I think it's a stretch to say that most of stories focus on B.C. https://t.co/injR6o0yOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhawthorn agreed. Until new models for Canadian journalism are proven, important to pay for the prototypes we want to succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAthleticTO @DogBoyBlue also I should probably put my money where my mouth is. Keep up the good work - really ho… https://t.co/I2mGLk54Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAthleticTO @DogBoyBlue agreed - meant niche not in popularity of subject, but demand in people paying for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogBoyBlue I think there can be. @TheAthleticTO is one example of trying it. But it requires reteaching audiences to pay for niche content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But Justin, you've developed certain beats," you say. Yeah, but I pursued those at 3am daily AND MOST PEOPLE HAVE LIVES/AREN'T CRAZY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I worry and wonder...and the meantime, love the ones in Vancouver still plugging away. But we need more than generalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Canada, there's still a business model for journos that do local breaking news, for federal politics, for trade pubs. For beat reporters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will those beats be replaced? Do papers have the resources to allow younger reporters the time to become experts in a subject anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many of the people who are leaving the Sun/Province are veterans with beats: soccer, university sports, immigrants, fed. politics, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of depressing things about the continued lobotomization of Postmedia papers, but one is the loss of specialized, impartial knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaaaand there goes the last reporter on Parliament Hill focused explicitly on B.C. issues. https://t.co/piF1Hugfcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnywakefield gotta divide up Fort St. John/Dawson Creek from the rest with tabs, and then change the x-axis range. Geez.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A group of folkies just showed up at my late night dosa place and are playing songs for the 5 of us in here and it is just the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a fairly big deal. Effectively creates tougher sentencing guidelines for fentanyl in B.C., it appears. https://t.co/S9MtYusQLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stitched sorry to hear that Peter. This business is not the kindest place these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voice of the Whitecaps, top Whitecaps reporter in the city, and sports editor that gave the Whitecaps the most coverage. All gone in 1 day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vancouver media scene has had many depressing days over the past five years, but this one is up there. https://t.co/PdnBPmcD7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladurantaye so was it a good stout or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jstrocel @tomhawthorn look I've always said that if you make the cloning machine I'll happily step into it, and our problem is solved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanBurritt @jonnywakefield will enforce this law tonight dan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hseidema Whitecaps maybe signing a guy that boosts their goals per game from 1.3 to 1.4 better than @jonnywakefield getting PR, for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@risingaction also helps explain the glut of players from the 90s on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jonnywakefield such an easy process, amiright?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEST NEWS https://t.co/LPdzXI1oty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Though I will note that Housser has long opposed the dumping permit: https://t.co/kf31CIPszj)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which the Liberal candidate for Cowichan Valley tries to neutralize a potential weakness ahead of May's provinci… https://t.co/EZmolYNT2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katiemercer glad to hear you'll still be in the game! Glacier has some great papers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickwellsy nope, you're only allowed to tweet your pieces at 4 in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite polling station in British Columbia just may be #82 in West Vancouver-Sea to Sky. Which person switche… https://t.co/KPgC04kSJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarajcarman @chadskelton I've always started the very next day after switching companies. You are much smarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This helps illustrates why many newspapers were slow to adapt digitally: The "Internet" had been "coming" for a dec… https://t.co/39zMDZQW1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UbysseyNews not paying too much atteniont, but this seems to be a "Greatest Hits" version of council.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder that some places in B.C. are more conservative than others, and the more remote a town, the more journo norms can cause a ruckus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jonnywakefield reported on Fort Nelson's mayor buying a $5M unit in Vancouver's Trump tower, and people are furio… https://t.co/0GOsMoSAcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnywakefield @akurjata wait where can i find this delightful comment thread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewBucholtz sad to hear that's how it ended - glad that it hasn't stopped your great writing from continuing apace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kainagata unsure where to get them until the Census data comes out later this year, sadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanBuckley @KamilKaramali totally unfair claim! A simple tallboy normally suffices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Patmeister just Stats BC numbers. Projections for 2016 appeared to have come out recently: https://t.co/PFPNKiqzCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The largest population increase in B.C. from 2011-2016? 

Not in Metro Van: It's Langford, up 31.2%, followed by Fort St. John at 16.7%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Vancouver's population decreased by 4.7% in the last 5 years, the largest decrease for any B.C. city with at least 20,000 people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamilKaramali this is an excellent way of ensuring I never help you again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C. municipalities with at least 10,000 people that haven't grown in any of the last five years:

Prince Rupert
Po… https://t.co/j0mjWS0ffr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustinrgodfrey @electionatlasCA it's possible one would make that leap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know this will shock people, but the BC Liberals get a lot of votes from Shaughnessy in elections (image from the… https://t.co/n8F0ElRIqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardzussman @christyclarkbc @ubcprez (insert gif involving the rolling of eyes here)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardzussman @christyclarkbc @ubcprez was this your joke or Clark's? I need to know who to groan at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Tzeporah was part of Christy Clark's Climate Leadership Team, but was sharply critical of the end result: https://t.co/wVGdfZjsEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadbent Institute just announced  an event with @jjhorgan "in conversation" with @Tzeporah today at 1:30, which should be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story by @ChrisWalkerCBC on how one couple might have grifted the B.C. town of Greenwood is insane: https://t.co/HuCxkC7zFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ono's predecessors wouldn't commit UBC funding towards the line. Spent years attacking Metro Vancouver oversight. A… https://t.co/iLGw0ABTDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Elliott is the NDP's candidate in Cariboo North against @coraleeoakes. Finished with the 2nd most votes for Q… https://t.co/gaqwNvygCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clark announcing end of the $50K stipend on a Friday night at an event renaming a mountain peak sure to raise eyebrows in the usual places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I demand more local news promos where reporters are berated by the children of co-workers. https://t.co/1i6OygevXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus this is stupendous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta @nickwellsy I've already said too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickwellsy @Planta nick shhhh don't tell him trade secrets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UbysseyNews has a thread on UBC President Santa Ono addressing UBC's Senate about the Furlong flipflop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a look at overdose deaths in B.C. by month if we go back to the beginning of 2013. Staggering.… https://t.co/gn7M0hbKiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final monthly report for 2016 overdose deaths has come in from the BC Coroners Service. 

Final suspected overdose deaths for the year: 914.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officially (by my made up metric), Vancouver was in a cold snap for 44 days - the longest in 45 years, but only the… https://t.co/uvXPIOCqKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday the average temperature at YVR was 6.9 degrees - the first time it was over 5 degrees since December 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronwynMaye I say every time you spend an hour doing that @nyonson is allowed to search through council committee minutes. Problem solved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akurjata I finished it a month ago (it's an update from 2007), so now the only thing to do is write it/publicly embarrass myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobKronbauer @Planta @DanBurritt Halifax Explosion is properly appreciated by people. Too many people think burnt toast is #1 all-time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobKronbauer @Planta @DanBurritt I continue to maintain that is an overrated heritage minute and will grumble loudly at those who disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Planta @DanBurritt I would have screamed incoherently about Amor de Cosmos for five minutes and it would have been uncomfortable for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillDrews1130 yeah, I tried to listen in different moods to balance things, but it's more an excuse to do some fun non-work writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarpblanket I stand by the take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you enjoy my writing at its most curmudgeonly &amp; least essential, here's a personal project I've started on:… https://t.co/rFo8TXEycy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickeagland definitely do at least the first two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnywakefield *joke about what would happen if he does a bc rail piece that i'm too afraid to actually make*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@risingaction fairly confident that's the first time that phrase has ever been uttered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CindyDalglish I get your passion on the issue/disappointment in my article, but I don't change stories for editorial reasons after the fact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CindyDalglish @ynaffit79 but I know I'll be talking about overcrowded schools in future Surrey riding profiles (6 more to go)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CindyDalglish @ynaffit79 ah, missed that! Article notes the opinions are those of KPU professor Shinder Purewal...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CindyDalglish to what? Don't see a question linked to this tweet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardzussman richard i could make you a graph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robshaw_vansun given the Liberals ran a no-name candidate in '13 and came within 10%, good test for how much high-profile candidate matters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kobymichaels @jackhauen @Ubyssey @ralph_sultan baby steps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixbced @rmfaris could have said "winnable if the election were held today, based on very strong historical trends", but 140 characters etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaneyInkslinger hmm, looks like D'Eith was acclaimed, but the party hasn't announced it through social media yet. 4th time lucky for Yiu?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>