<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[CBC Radio interview with David Frum on Trump = provocative https://t.co/FoYnJrlXvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The First of many national webinars from DOC in 2017 #DOCorg  https://t.co/dDE0yTyZny https://t.co/UZN3G2A5ZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The First of many national webinars from DOC in 2017 #DOCorg  https://t.co/dDE0yTyZny https://t.co/3HGYW9UF6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wants to renegot NAFTA - https://t.co/UTz4zmPWgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dan Rather is back! https://t.co/VBUym8nHcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching from Canada - Sickening to see what's happening to America under Trump.#MarchforLife https://t.co/YEbduX3e3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Demand the palm oil front runners become true leaders https://t.co/VdI6gPzwwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first act gag-act of Trump's totalitarian presidency silences National Park Service. The end of free speech https://t.co/Mt3sLPyfDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline for Hot Doc's Documentary Accelerator on Jan 23rd for recent grads...https://t.co/9m3ob09mlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC BC event examines the RADIO DOCUMENTARY.  Free for members.
https://t.co/AE3gI9REdh https://t.co/LDnTZXES65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art and Opportunity of the Radio Documentary.  From DOC BC - Free to Members Jan 25th https://t.co/ueRyqxUKQJ https://t.co/HvzVlNzok1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in the podcast revolution?  https://t.co/noRSIXJrov https://t.co/ef6LQG15u6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New DOC BC event on THE AUDIO DOCUMENTARY coming soon!  https://t.co/AE3gIa9f4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Marcuse - Urban Planner and Columbia professor emeritus on undemocratic elections in USA.… https://t.co/kfMRo8Ppx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politically, BC not so far off from Trumps USA https://t.co/rgT0OLnSub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good comments on the state of Van Newspapers https://t.co/mry2l0gQmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need space for lanterns, costumes, fabrics.  Artists face constant stress in Van to find space! https://t.co/Gd4ROlQPgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! https://t.co/amn7AfA4Wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Teachers taught a lesson to the BC Liberals.  It's time that the BC voters teach the BC Liberals another one. https://t.co/iG5DGet687]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I could do it this year... https://t.co/oeUVmkAYI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This victory belongs to the teachers! https://t.co/A6uPSENv5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best news in 2017.  BC Liberals lose the right to destroy our education system.
https://t.co/cERhM8v6p0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCCoupar My favourite spot for the holidays. The Bloedel Conservatory at the top of Vancouver! https://t.co/DDQXSxqAtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your Impact Producing Tool Kit hot off the presses https://t.co/YJHC6yDaox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great festival - great looking award https://t.co/R2dCAVvxbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentary filmmakers curl up near the fireplace with this. https://t.co/A1P5fCMzst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[READ this document to KNOW the CHALLENGES facing CANADIAN documentary FILMMAKERS https://t.co/RcSlz7k1hQ https://t.co/vMMku0mnVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I will protect the water,' Trudeau tells tearful 12-year-old girl https://t.co/2BiDKtOgnY via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For DOC BC members, a gentle reminder... https://t.co/yuMezDVmnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC  BC supports this cineworks initiative https://t.co/dsGNCJWgWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dec 5 and Dec 6 HERITAGE HOME CONSULTATION see below:
https://t.co/7ONZCw7DF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Heritage Home Consultation needs your input this week.
https://t.co/iIkcRVr6qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were there. https://t.co/G2Xnb3rVbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of political will on civic and provincial levels... https://t.co/AVI2UjbXil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming next week. https://t.co/hEK0qN6aOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were there! https://t.co/lNw20e63eI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly Kristy - she does what she can to separate the rich from the poor. https://t.co/9jzrI9LIxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's my choir - me in the back - overexposed! https://t.co/TT4afMnxxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pipeline Protest Today spking with community leader:  David @DavidChudnovsky https://t.co/58KhMH2WN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-pipeline Rally at City Hall Tomorrow! https://t.co/EDv9Z6EFSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filmmakers to follow... https://t.co/3NfikAVpeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you there https://t.co/Zaab0MGLIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is our national documentary association https://t.co/A1P5fCMzst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Bolton's crazy genius https://t.co/LIBLV92c64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$226,000 to Liberals from Holborn...Douglas Todd: Foreign money poses threat to democracy https://t.co/He0eAnqYBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking out for public education https://t.co/ga5PUPkNv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to TELUS our Masterclass sponsor https://t.co/rA1eNiH05F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will see my neighbours there... https://t.co/AnSOmWE1EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met many of you @DOC_BC Masterclass yesterday.  Amazing team https://t.co/gLjfWY7JeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out KM's favourite NW film@canadawildwatch https://t.co/7wE8PzHYSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @SarahRace! https://t.co/rA1eNiH05F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thank you to TELUS for financial support! https://t.co/HsF3i1MaXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone at top of their game https://t.co/oQLKoaIrVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nettie's sound team = deep analysis of art of sound @DOC_BC masterclass https://t.co/EZ1NaNAzuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High-5 to DOC BC board and volunteers https://t.co/EGvtPw3ibm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch Konaline at Vancity Thtr this week https://t.co/ADByC0HPQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREAT shot Mitchell https://t.co/MLKthLplXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art of the Documentary @DOC_BC today https://t.co/Mc9RL8s0L2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action is lacking. https://t.co/kSV04BPNpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC livestreams with Nettie Wild today https://t.co/TVarjv82LA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming soon to CBC Docs https://t.co/Lx3VykJRd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diesel containment failing after spill on B.C. coast  https://t.co/vor2pXtBqi via @NatObserver
Small demo. of disasters to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting!  I wanna take a short trip to NYC! https://t.co/yxOknYokE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! Gotta catch a breeze and head up there on Sunday! https://t.co/jtixKoS9AV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this stream and sign petition https://t.co/zSmCBDXwFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalling charges. https://t.co/9z2mTx7qDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC BC's two-day workshop with Nettie Wild - almost sold out https://t.co/bzRHsV9svc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VIAwesome Book your date with Wild at DOC BC event https://t.co/bzRHsURR6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets going fast for The Art of Documentary with Nettie Wild https://t.co/bzRHsV9svc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic tweet thread! https://t.co/0On9BnypUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Vancouver ready for Light Rapid Transit? https://t.co/BPvldEFpXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this in my garage - time when we had enthusiasm about the Van's future and our place in the world. https://t.co/o6vvM5wIQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC's major event of the year! https://t.co/NnAt6VHpQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO THEY HAVE ENOUGH VOTES NOW?  Last day  to support DOC  BC colleagueshttp://www.storyhive.com/project/show/id/1669]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day left! https://t.co/l4PPZE8sAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day to vote! https://t.co/E51wzKFISp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC BC members - vote for colleagues in short doc film production - one day left https://t.co/ZgqNFI5oBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I voted today.  Support DO I HAVE BOOBS NOW at https://t.co/ZgqNFImZtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I Have Boobs Now?  A film by Joella Cabalu and Milena Salazar - Voting ends in 2 days:  https://t.co/ZgqNFImZtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I Have Boobs Now?  Voting ends in 3 Days.  Joella Cabalu is a colleague at DOC BC  https://t.co/ZgqNFImZtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I Have Boobs Now?  Voting ends in 3 Days.  Milena Salazar is a colleague at DOC BC https://t.co/ZgqNFImZtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this ROB REINER MASTERCLASS from TIFF 2016 https://t.co/9bwNrVKqE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important article on Little Mountain https://t.co/hBLeqZoeBc https://t.co/x64qAqLr7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice on Fall Cycling:  https://t.co/6qNYqI2kP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC brought the issues to the Globe as part of national advocacy strat: https://t.co/7gX8mEdbpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pressure by DOC, CMPA  leads to changes by CRTC.  Good News for Indi Filmmakers in Canada.
https://t.co/2Zhu2rnqXF https://t.co/4TlB58Nt72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VIAwesome Awesome cycling day trips in Vancouver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On bikes to Iona Park with the kids.  17KM from home but they made it.  Awesome views! https://t.co/oWJKPEKLtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke and Annie are my Peeps - ART SEEN: Artists Talk is a well written guide for emerging artists https://t.co/0xoqPx90Px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls share:  Let's hope article is read by Vision Vancouver Councillors https://t.co/VMMamnMZwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next Tues. Vision Vancouver makes final vote on Redevelopment of Little Mtn.  Kerry Gold writes...

https://t.co/VMMamnMZwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesday next wk, Vision Vancouver makes it's final decision on redevelopment https://t.co/VMMamnMZwe https://t.co/2TPK03mhfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director's Lab is fortunate to have Nimisha https://t.co/EoWNAtZ0tR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOC BC board member... https://t.co/47SB7AzllY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...To be continued next week. I was last speaker of the night. The director of LMNH on camera above. https://t.co/hitzoADOAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at City Hall the Me and the Press record the story on Little Mountain.  Proceedings cease at 10pm... https://t.co/3DYswobvKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global News at 5 &amp; 6pm w Ted Chernecki,  Check out https://t.co/8PMJsseYU5 for details on Friday. https://t.co/EhtInBdaKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can still catch HUNT FOR THE WILDERPEOPLE at Tinseltown!  Great for everyone including kids 9+
https://t.co/X7tpIe3Pnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision and the BC Liberals are beginning to act on a few of COPE's ideas https://t.co/HNqEsBMCjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally...something https://t.co/LZWUxOUxj1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>