<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit my Insta follower goal so #giveaway time! To try win you just gotta like/retweet this &amp; follow me. Good luck! 💖

https://t.co/lS2rRKHNaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog got 68 views today. 68. That's crazy to me. People look at it!.Thank you people! I will try do better 😂

https://t.co/DyfejIc7gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoviDreams really appreciate it 😊💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAAAS hit a new views in a day record on my blog, many thank you to everyone who clicked, lil surprises like this a… https://t.co/d1J08Kwwfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoviDreams oh thank you sweetie! 🙈💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will serious up my blogging game once this thesis stuff calms down 😅🙈

https://t.co/n0TXLgmkHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm 4 views from breaking previous record, any topic suggestions or constructive criticism &amp; I'd be happy to know!

https://t.co/n0TXLgmkHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a new book to read for February?? Check out my recommendations for feel good books here! #bookreviews

https://t.co/MFrl7o2bhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty close to breaking a previous views record &amp; also making the most of the last day of #ThyroidAwarenessMonth 🙈

https://t.co/2CUaiUz5S1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're concerned about your thyroid or just want to know more, check out all you need here 😊

https://t.co/2CUaiUhv0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrapping up #ThyroidAwarenessMonth &amp; here's a summary of my personal experience being diagnosed &amp; living with it ✌

https://t.co/DyfejIc7gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being around people in my course literally sucks the life out of me like a straw 😑 https://t.co/CREXW11pAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For facts on the thyroid check out here -&gt;
#ThyroidAwarenessMonth 

https://t.co/2CUaiUhv0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day of #ThyroidAwarenessMonth so I wrote a more personal account of my thyroid experience 💖✌

https://t.co/DyfejIc7gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah Oh you beat me by a year, my first event was 4th year for MH soc hahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah Yah I wish I could see it like that but its literally the biggest source of stress in my life rn haha I can't get better here 😅😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait it's only TUESDAY???? I thought it had to be Thursday at least 😅😅😅 https://t.co/lrHwcDrkNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so wrecked.... Why must college be so early 😴😴😴 https://t.co/Bu3tQHbNxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaasBall cheers, appreciate it. I'll go into hibernation here 😂😴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that rain I hear??? Cos if it is there's a 200% chance of me going back to sleep https://t.co/0v06SFRWjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett he know https://t.co/KiQcddtHA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary stop omg I'm actually crying, does my phone know something I dont hahhaa fucking Janet and her 1am retweets 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary omg who is Janet hahahaha wtf this keyboard 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary wtf is up with their Twitter, 1am and they do be retweeting stuff. Like go to sleep Janet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary half perm, half dread. Throw a braid in for good measure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLouCleary @SarahhBrett biology teacher, hair constantly moussed, glasses, friendly but won't take shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary you're already gross so....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary wandering the corridors and telling anyone who asked it was debating &amp;naming ms madigan even tho we never spoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary @HayleyWalshx3 yeah cos Clara shouted it at Hayley &amp; her mates and they were like wtf 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLouCleary @SarahhBrett smelling specifically of arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett @SarahLouCleary she just said what we were all thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLouCleary @SarahhBrett saz is nasty anyway so won't notice the difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett yeah it looks fucking weird alright hahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My antidepressants have been very poorly managed by GP &amp; long waiting for psychiatrist #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett Hun... I fucking have dreadlocks anyway #noshowersforme #nastywoman #wherethathygieneat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah haha hopefully! Lmk if ur around DIT or town &amp; free, unfortunately I kinda live there at the mo &amp; I'm billy-no-mates in college 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah I really just don't deal well in college &amp; knew hardly anyone else in room so anxiety was through the roof unfortunately 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah yeah &amp; I was soooo stressed from my project work, was not having good day 😅 I can't believe we were so close omg gutted 🙈😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah oh my goddddd. So close to meeting you 😂🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah I thought I heard someone introduce themselves as Jessica! Then go to the bathroom...? That was around when I left, bad anxiety 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah omg.... We were literally in same row...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett nawh you could pull that off no bother. Seriously, go for it !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett honestly you could pull off either. Go for it. Seriously, would be deadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah not to be annoying, but imma just leave this here https://t.co/mieqteecdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett all or nothing bish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett go for it! Seriously you could pull them off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahhBrett just to avoid the effort of washing??? Same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah oh sweetie, I understand too much. Sending love 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoiraGeary @MentalHealth_Hr you came very highly recommend, lots of people said to follow you! 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah on the left or right?? Cos I was on the left by the window in 2nd last row 😅 eh ish, eventful journey home 😅🙈 bed time I think 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah same unfortunately! I was way down back &amp; left when pizza arrived cos of anxiety attack 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knuf1985 at least we try!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 these jobs should be for AMERICANS ONLY cos they only deserve rights in USA, not black or native Americans tho jst white ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 hating trump cos he's a man, he's preventing actual terrorists from getting in! Even tho stats don't back this but ISIS OMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 no sorry get back in your lane, why you want equal rights for everyone? 🙄 You don't care about refugees you just hate trump 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatlyddid it really is! But I'll keep trying to turn up to things anyway 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 how dare we want equal treatment and pay 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 don't you know that feminists probably caused the Muslim ban? Pesky feminists cause everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatlyddid that's really nice, thank you 💖 I'll try think like that when I calm down a bit 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatlyddid thanks! Wish I could feel like that tho 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bailed early, honestly why do I even try 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EndTheStigma tempted to just leave 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EndTheStigma honestly the most annoying thing, why can't I just socialise like normal people 😅😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*goes to event to meet new people*

*Sits at back of event away from everyone else*

I'm great at life 😅✌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi my name is Jodie and I'm dying of anxiety at a minor social event, I need to make friends in college 😅😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inaseaofemotion followed sweetie! 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onelastkick71 followed! 💖🎉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_nulty @AprilRhynold love these 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#followspree https://t.co/9WYmpwcH9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also need to follow more people on Insta, so lmk your username or follow me at thedscully101 for follow back 😊✌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im looking for more blogs to follow, especially MH ones! If you have a link in ur bio &amp; youre not sure I follow you, like this &amp; I'll sub! 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been sitting in front of screens all day, why is my brain so slow lately 😭 I blame thyroid brain fog... 😳😅 Pro… https://t.co/PZu4QMkVjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 not even being dramatic, he's causing worldwide commotion, he's gonna start world war 3. Fucking impeach him already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 same, every day I wake up it's like he's done something else to fuck up the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 you've got me on a rant hahaha, I actually just cannot stand the man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 I feel sorry for them. If you stand for nothing you'll fall for everything. And how can you not stand up for your own rights?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 yh! Or imagine Obama said "grab em by the pussy" "blood coming out of her whatever" "I bet you're a pretty sight on ur knees"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 oh yeah, and the women who support &amp; defend him- get some self respect love. Stand up for yourself &amp; all other women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 imagine Hillary said she was going to build a wall? Do you think people would have supported that or called it as it is-bull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 I mean he gets away with it because he's a white man. Imagine Obama had rape allegations against him? Or 5 kids by 3 women?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 that is literally it, they can cry emails all they want but that's bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 no tax records, blatant sexism &amp; racism, no care for working class, controlled by corporation, greedy &amp; a liar. Now POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 she had 30 fucking years of a political career and a fucking bankrupt reality TV star wash out waltzes in &amp; gets elected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 "I have no problem with a female president, but crooked Hillary read some private emails, best vote in an orange tyrant"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 let's be honest, Hillary got a lot of hate because she's lacking a dick, they just hid behind the emails to avoid sexism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 also how many times has trump been bankrupt? Where's his tax records?? Previous political experience???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 OMG stop, crooked Hillary with some fucking emails, get a grip, 2 other candidates had the same issues and no one said shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairjones640 its like they didn't even listen to what he was saying, they just wanted anyone but Hillary?? No wonder they're regretting it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fem_rulez it's actually sickening to look at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness themed giveaway coming soon cos I'm feeling super generous 😂 keep your eyes peeled ☀ https://t.co/54kRE55Kf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fem_rulez anyway it's hard to support such a racist, misogynistic asshole, he makes me sick 🙄😷]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fem_rulez no problem, he's lots of opposition here too! We marched with you all after inauguration, we got your back 💪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunnyScattered @davecalproject @EndTheStigma_ie haha that's good, need to prioritise your health sometimes! 💖☀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happinessplannr omg cutest thing ever 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying not to be dramatic, but I think I'm dying 🤔😂 https://t.co/UwWNXLrKhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't meet @realDonaldTrump &amp; think you're representing Irish people @EndaKennyTD #NotInMyName  https://t.co/QGFmRrNXN8 via @UpliftIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo important, will continue to retweet https://t.co/YFHD9doEKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_nulty @MentalHealth_Hr oops ignore the college, damn autotype, still getting used to new phone 😂😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_nulty there's often guest tweeters &amp; different themes. It's growing by the week &amp; a fantastic community co… https://t.co/6C8MdvVxSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_nulty @MentalHealth_Hr it's every Sunday 9-10pm 😊🎉]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>