<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Man it's weird rewatching Band of Brothers and seeing actors I recognize. Who knew Jimmy Fallon was in it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from that, it seems neat. Everyone seems a bit broken in an interesting way. Reminds me that Twin Peaks isn't far away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like haven't we gotten past hearing about the whole student teacher thing and just saying : https://t.co/zugck4Npu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels not great the way statutory rape is treated like some racy plot point in it, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riverdale seems hokey as all get-out, but I think I can get with it. Scratches the same itch as the Scream show did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sound proofing is bad enough that either everything is booked up that day, or they just really don't care about any of that stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 1986 and both groups just rent some random practice space. They're tired of the stale studios to which they have access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to live in a world where the RUN DMC-Aerosmith "Walk This Way" collaboration actually happened the way it does in the music video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" a good noun is really good. Like, bear? That's a good one. That sounds good." -@alexanderbkim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's gross. https://t.co/ozUyG7mpZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The switch looks really cool and all... But not calling it Spla2n is a missed opportunity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, ick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["we couldn't get anyone good." https://t.co/BrnM6XWpKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mammoth oral history of Final Fantasy VII. Really tremendous stuff here. https://t.co/bYIphauyzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The readers and spoken and they want more hoods on their super heroes." https://t.co/wckNOKI622]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That new Scarlet Spider looks like someone took entirely the wrong lessons from Spider Gwen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get not having a huge budget for this kind of thing, but does Vancouver just not use salt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The parts of the sidewalks that were covered in ice when I left town a month ago are still covered in ice. Hope that melted and this is new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old lady scary doll why are you in The window? #nye https://t.co/h6jD2SUStr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been awhile since I've been in the north end late at night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to a pizza place that hat rats and no slices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I paid to be here. I will catch pokemon if I damn well please, thank you ver much. #nye2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid $40 to get into this NYE party and therw are a remarkable amount of old folks here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexanderbkim What's a hockey sweater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But did he eat well when he was alive?" https://t.co/BATf6Z5SSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@br_tten @laurentdcar oof. Fair. That was better than the long johns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight's delayed, but I'm wearing long johns for a second day this week, so really how bad can it be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's snowing, which means I get my one chance to wear long-johns in Vancouver. Today is a good day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evacsenge No, these were strangers. You were burning up the dancefloor with moves all your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at a bar with a dancefloor and someone was just reeled in. Unironically. Like, for sure seriously. As a dance move and not a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the @CAH Holiday Hole  stream be the new Yule Log? I'd be down to leave that on the TV this christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurentdcar I can only imagine what he thought the C stood for when he said it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertVS92 @MichaelWolffNYC Don't you need to look for information for it to be research? It was right in front of him all along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelWolffNYC @AlbertVS92 His birth year's in the twitter handle, dummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aside from his obvious wrongness, his choice of letter to change is disgusting. https://t.co/jz0on07a7d https://t.co/RIy697efuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FABlichert It was for sure trench coat length and shape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a long denim overcoat. Gonna assume I'm just out of touch with the hip jeanware and not that someone waited till 2016 to make one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck my whole day's been spent watching loading bars. Get me the fuck out of here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing a lot of buzz for the game(s) from people who say they hadn't played one since Red/Blue, which seems like the same Demo. as Go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be fascinated to hear what influence Pokemon Go is having on the sales of Sun/Moon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fuck brings a birthday party to Elwoods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ungggggh. The urge to buy a 3ds for the new pokemon is so real right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBS is strange and finicky. Fucky, if you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[e-learning is my favourite kind of learning. https://t.co/EKMSCFpXzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisrock Plz run on a platform of "That Ain't Right."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my picture taken with @MichaelKeaton https://t.co/oOEkfQMstc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Vaughan, too?! This week sucks shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olafragnar hey now, Wasabi House isn't great, but I think that's a little extreme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'd appreciate a sunny day tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like hating things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I hate this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really really don't love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really don't love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard a man answer his phone "Hey dad, how's it going bro." The fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presented without comment https://t.co/VQl0HEXU9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Video games are boring" https://t.co/NlOac9NfRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Overwatch League sounds super neat. Great to see an org jump in having paid attention to pitfalls faced by other scenes and leagues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never really thought about how VR can open up new avenues for being a scummy person on the internet. https://t.co/fVtajbeRFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man this Midnight Diner netflix show is charming as all get-out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere in the back of my head, a tiny imaginary buddhist is saying "Ohh 108 years... how auspicious."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one boring inning is a small price to pay to witnessing history. "Extra innings, folks." Naw fuck it, baseball's too boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brittanynduggan yeah, he's a real treat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brittanynduggan Sounds like the man who bragged to me about getting off a murder charge with an insanity plea. He sound british?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertVS92 #moneyways is a good shade throwing hasthag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brittanynduggan was he in all black and sunglasses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes. Mother Jones coming out swinging https://t.co/592O8hUODT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker @HillaryClinton Thanks, Scott, I'll do just that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a man dabbing in the audience behind Faker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever tonight's result, seems safe to say that the sentiment that tournament winner was decided in the SKT- ROX semifinal match is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE KENCH, UNBENCHED #Worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SILVER SCRAPES #Worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last thing I ever wanted to do after a 70+ game of League was play more. Can only imagine how that's wearing on these guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure if that was the best professional league of legends game of all time or the worst. But it was definitely one of them. #Worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was exhausting, on to game 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously what the fuck is this game #worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That MF hover made this theatre lose its mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also was that game not close or what. #sktwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appropriate response, twitter bot #worlds https://t.co/0ylDgsivzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool seeing new Faker on Ryze. The map presence is unreal #worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a first game. Hope the rest of the series is this good.#Worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bengi. This guy... what a beast. #Worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wolf the god #worlds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That touch bar seems suuuuuper cool. #WWDC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I guess devs will have to develop two separate UIs for their games? Or maybe ignore the touch screen won't be us… https://t.co/Jw3WlFydPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other out of the blue  news, Vine died today. https://t.co/jHz27h8BTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evacsenge Is this the one where they talk about that interview?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mouse has disappeared. WHERE IS IT? IT'S IN MY BED, NOW, ISN'T IT? GREAT NOW I'M SLEEPING OUTSIDE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a mouse in my room. Guess I'm not sleeping tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's quarter after 6 and tonight has already become very weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FABlichert I curious to read the study and see if it actually tries link the two, or if that's a detail people misinterpreted and repeated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FABlichert What... What could that study have been? "You'll catch autism if you watch it. Trust us, it's science."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's profoundly strange reading a news article that ends with imploring people to take a drug. Sounds like a Dr. Oz… https://t.co/X3hJ78Hood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreakinClever Well, you need to actually be in power to literally be a dictator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch seems super neat. But since everything is modular and works on its own, will it all need to be charged separately?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoeducklow fucking oof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fictionlies #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FABlichert Fred, the car is already called the E-Tron. I feel like, at that point, just go all the way in showing you don't understand tech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not just call it "The Cyber." https://t.co/4OfMTPnEkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Lie in April is bad and dumb and- what?... No, YOU'RE crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FABlichert I regretted writing burr-eats as soon as I wrote it]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>