<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess that's why they're called snowdrops #SnowdropSaturday #vancouver #vancity #snowcou… https://t.co/ojrt6IA69x https://t.co/waNeHuNvjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The snow goes ever on and on... #vancouver #snowpocalypse #snowpocalypseII #snowpocalypse2… https://t.co/Rcc16P8UxM https://t.co/JwLpL7GNxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please! :-) And clear snow from *all* your windows and lights, and have a little patience, eh? (Think before you be… https://t.co/AVxvKP5zsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-tone fog over Stanley Park #throwbackthursday #TBT #OnceAroundTheSun #OATS #stanleypar… https://t.co/DBfxYCBpk1 https://t.co/Io1FlWFlCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hiker_Steve I like how they make a right-angled triangle :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouvertrails @outdoorvan Thanks! I won't advertise it in the newsletter just yet then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outdoorvan @vancouvertrails Is there a #bchikechat this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The End. Good movie, a well paced build-up before a heart-pounding climax with some beauti… https://t.co/aXAz3LMpbp https://t.co/ZxlBNbvztN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sense of scale - a hiker gets up close and personal with the ever-receding Illecillewaet… https://t.co/iemKDBCEyg https://t.co/0Ue0KG55Ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching the early morning (f)light - a floatplane banks in front of the western peak of C… https://t.co/tlN476YmHy https://t.co/oLMrWYlsIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seymour sastrugi for today's #winterwonderlandwednesday #mountseymour #mountseymourprovinc… https://t.co/ZFMNBC2jrY https://t.co/TsFtekfh5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The high-rises of the West End reflect the glow of the western sky. The seawall at Kits Po… https://t.co/Agt7AaVcD3 https://t.co/IwEQCSg03e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splintered. One of a number of red alders brought down by this winter's snowfall. #alder #… https://t.co/YbVZPeS8xD https://t.co/WHl48mIwsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver in view - admiring our fair city from the North Shore mountains #vancouver #vanc… https://t.co/xtXl0LTQyY https://t.co/9rn9icNJJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last light on Mt Seymour - another #throwbackthursday shot from my picture-a-day project 5… https://t.co/A7MhBPAKIT https://t.co/a0nucsuMMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouvertrails Yeah it was pretty busy up there today - we ended up parked in the overnight lot (P1), added about 2.5 km to hike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selfie of sorts - my shadow at the top of Pump Peak (First Peak) on Mt Seymour, looking … https://t.co/3EZVJiiBSg https://t.co/SykcVCtx3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted! A spotted towhee makes a rare venture out from the safety of the undergrowth. Thi… https://t.co/2wVODHP396 https://t.co/IPQnOaJaGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A glorious nearly-full moon rise over Robie Reid with the last rays of the sun lighting up… https://t.co/VsG293FXWF https://t.co/ax0wrkk1oS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visit all 23 regional parks? That's two a month - should be possible! https://t.co/K9t536FDg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nhotte what a beautiful morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL that there is a #Capybara Appreciation Society https://t.co/6dKG6f5WXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Voice4Silent It's not so bad when the sun comes out is it? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrkcompw Thanks! It was a gorgeous evening down on the seawall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AColoradoGal I had a similar nail slightly further from the sidewall and still had to get a new tyre...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stasher_SK I laughed out loud when I first saw that sign but I definitely approve of the message. I like that concept of stewardship too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yak Peak, intimidating and majestic in its winter coat, but a surprisingly fun hike in sum… https://t.co/mzg3Dqbfg2 https://t.co/Xv12HPWdMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't get to see the Pioneer Cabin tree before it fell, but did see the CA Tunnel Tree in Mariposa Grove https://t.co/vvBWnLPQWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lions, framed at the north summit of Black Mountain #cypressprovincialpark #thelions #… https://t.co/T752Ed4mnJ https://t.co/EleRJUtwgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowy tree family - another photo from our Christmas day snowshoe up Hollyburn #Hollyburn … https://t.co/52EywuAi45 https://t.co/p1vI14S93l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watcha lookin' at? Getting the evil eye from a squirrel... #throwbackthursday #TBT #OnceAr… https://t.co/vhrnrppMSV https://t.co/a1o96JPkVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out with the old... The penultimate sunset of 2016. May 2017 be a better one! Happy New Ye… https://t.co/tTxRacn4Ju https://t.co/a9sHzmlrBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all a very Merry Christmas and a fun festive season! #merrychristmas #hollybur… https://t.co/HNWKLCid8W https://t.co/BqpnidCeBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alpenglow. #FlashbackFriday to a Thanksgiving 2012 backpacking trip to Garibaldi Lake. #ga… https://t.co/hOPhsZgEan https://t.co/YN7UBwf4xI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thursday again already? This is probably my favourite photo from my picture-a-day project … https://t.co/53C4Y8n3i9 https://t.co/mGadlHZycv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer for the longest night, although technically I'm either 3 months late, or 3 months ear… https://t.co/09u8fUTp8l https://t.co/LL0Ivy4wJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An otter in the snow. Just another day in Vancouver :-) I watched this otter for several m… https://t.co/Wl2VQaQDG0 https://t.co/l1xqXrK2UT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minimalist monochrome Monday. It made a nice change for Sunday's enveloping grey to be ass… https://t.co/fJcAS3UTif https://t.co/EouWx59kzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowy beach rocks #kitsbeach #kitsilano #vancouver #vancity #snowday #snowonthebeach #ifttt https://t.co/jcYrwMoZWn https://t.co/DBp1vvt1GM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Seymour looking nice and warm at sunset #mountseymour #lionsgatebridge #stanleypark #se… https://t.co/psp6lquN8s https://t.co/0QB4Q1fHZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Twas a chilly sunrise this morning, but worth seeing the light on those North Shore mount… https://t.co/KOCtxwqE9q https://t.co/TFeBGnyrFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waves of clouds lapping at the forest. A #throwbackthursday sunset from 5 years ago, when … https://t.co/qsZHVVAKPJ https://t.co/OB8jOrAY57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A different kind of waterfall for #waterfallwednesday - this trickle follows the curve of … https://t.co/LmkvNnn7gY https://t.co/hN1DTrCX3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stature. I've taken so many photos of Crown Mountain over the past few years, yet very few… https://t.co/Cs25tESXM1 https://t.co/AU2o2HqQPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White out. Is it really a #FlashbackFriday if it was only last week? After a few days of v… https://t.co/uNt7Pxwz2m https://t.co/Un3eUDVFwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a full moon rising - throwback to a chilly December evening in 2011, much like these… https://t.co/vCgr5q4nrh https://t.co/sSpmN3Hov9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our turnaround point on the way to Mt Seymour. No marker poles, no obvious trail - we were… https://t.co/7DNLFU3jH9 https://t.co/vkUwJ60hpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback to 5 years ago when the snowy owls came to visit #throwbackthursday #TBT #OnceAr… https://t.co/GybynmFwrM https://t.co/2M82oCPZ4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few wisps of cloud drift around Mt Assiniboine, and some welcome blue sky after a soggy hike… https://t.co/ZBTKiGdbtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute little mouse munching on foamflower seeds #furryfriday #mouse #capescotttrail #capesc… https://t.co/D2uPO2KH5t https://t.co/EIjwsQ7JWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Added to the list of things I did not know - it's been a while since I worried about computing sines and cosines https://t.co/5KHVwSMrEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A trio of otters swimming around Stanley Park #throwbackthursday #TBT #OnceAroundTheSun #O… https://t.co/dU2LljNYng https://t.co/ifdK4PnXEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got to see Multnomah Falls in person! #waterfallwednesday The standard photo of th… https://t.co/HkqctdxOXN https://t.co/kIcr9ZagNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could be a nice Christmas gift for hikers... https://t.co/9ON15SUnK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's back.... Finally looks like winter has arrived in the North Shore mountains #vancouve… https://t.co/iT57Qjz4Th https://t.co/lRhPryPKK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aira Force in all its Lakeland glory https://t.co/w2a1vpZwVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouvertrails I love this section of Lynn Canyon &amp; some of the new signs they have up, e.g. https://t.co/nxdGzO3YMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see snow in them thar hills #northshore #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I, for one, welcome our new feathered overlords. One is cute, but 6 starts to feel like yo… https://t.co/nGD667KQxA https://t.co/JsQJLf8C3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm - well, I'm not in the habit of relying on ibuprofen after a tough hike anyway https://t.co/QIMvnWXhmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stasher_SK Pirates of the Alpine - best name yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obligatory #greyjay photo #whiskyjack #camprobber #canadabird https://t.co/nUJ6mU5Bws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute? Yes. Friendly? Sure, if your idea of friendly is being a sneaky little trail-mix-and-chocolate thief :-) https://t.co/A8e0UEKVZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A photogenic pair of fly agaric mushrooms in early morning light #throwbackthursday #TBT #… https://t.co/RQwjGNPXbA https://t.co/LWjJ2tHVyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@womenwhoexplore @TravelAlberta @AlbertaHiking @TourismCalgary Can't argue with the photos but - ahem - Mt Assiniboine is in BC ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the MkII; it's a very good camera but wouldn't mind MkIII+ for viewfinder, wider angle &amp; faster lens #rx100 https://t.co/jQ6OSjcddd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks cool; I just need a phone with a camera worth using... https://t.co/U6uXwRLQqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A different kind of mountain shot for #mountainmonday which I guess is less about the moun… https://t.co/OOc5zuPtnW https://t.co/azxJxvwH8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phooey. Or words to that effect. #nut #brokennut #bass #yamaha #rbx170 #music #bassguitar … https://t.co/1bVM5cUD5T https://t.co/nDZzbmUJTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is about as close as I want to get to a humpback while sitting in a kayak! I was amaz… https://t.co/6KSiQ6ALif https://t.co/swGJsfH6Et]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aspire to be a librarian, scientist, artist, and carpenter https://t.co/pTuq8vgd3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of gas at the place across the road is 111.9. If it were up to me, I'd have dropped it to 111.1 for today. #remembranceday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CP-140 Aurora flyover for #remembranceday in Vancouver. This one was actually taken in 201… https://t.co/K0t8H7JtUK https://t.co/klOGWSPofR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical street scene in Vancouver at this time of year #throwbackthursday #TBT #OnceAround… https://t.co/TF8qVlB2qk https://t.co/xByUyzC9sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nairn Falls for #waterfallwednesday from a mini road trip back in April. I imagine there h… https://t.co/fa9qz0LK9D https://t.co/9OGabRebcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outdoorvan I think there may be a few new waterfalls south of the border tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A double rainbow from this morning to take your mind off politics for a while #rainbow #do… https://t.co/UQjMqf9Nyk https://t.co/IcmgTkaay1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were you on Mt Seymour, Sun 6 Nov? Let NSR know if you have any info https://t.co/2v10lzYv2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FATFEastVan Ooh they are fine falls indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@synkdancer Don't know if I'd be of much help, that photo contains pretty much all I know about fungi :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor @vancouvertrails  @outdoorvan something to plan for a rainy(ish) day :-) #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outdoorvan @vancouvertrails thanks again guys! #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor @outdoorvan I haven't been out there since they put in the suspension bridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of good multi-day hikes loaded with waterfalls are Berg Lake and Iceline/Whaleback (both in BC too!) #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6: pick a cloudy day and use a tripod. Polarizer also good for cutting reflections and acts as neutral density filter too #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor  @FATFEastVan sure why not - and have a live in-person chat as we go :-) #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor @vancouvertrails I want to go back and do that hike on a dry day...! #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A5: so tough to answer... Niagara is impressive, Helmcken, Emperor, Takakkaw, Yosemite (inc Vernal &amp; Nevada Falls), all of Kauai #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FATFEastVan maybe this winter sometime - I plan to do the East &amp; West Canyon circuit now the new bridge is in place #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4: I was going to say Della Falls, but then I remembered Calvin Falls on Nootka https://t.co/CjtkAhJ6VK #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor do it :-) It's spectacular but save it for good weather. The camp spot on Panorama Ridge is one of my faves #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FATFEastVan haven't explored the upper falls yet - my impression is that it's a bit dicey if wet #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outdoorvan Ooh, now that's still on my list... maybe sometime this winter? #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor there's a side trail off the West Canyon trail heading up towards Golden Ears https://t.co/HmsZI7ftMu #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3: I'm partial to the falls and cascades on Brothers Creek, but Twin Falls in Lynn Canyon is a close second #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TourismBCNorth definitely on my list! #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2: Gold Creek - I think the best view is from the opposite bank. The falls on Eaton Creek are impressive too #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happiestoutdoor it is definitely a little trickier to get a good view but you can hear them for most of the hike #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1: probably High Falls Creek but Crooked Falls is a close second #bchikechat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evening all, Andy here in Vancouver #bchikechat]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>