<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@spin1038 Thanks for having me on your station with excellent Lauren+Gordon.A few mins on #medicationnation 
Recording will follow😊love spin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot wait! https://t.co/xLSEsJiWoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karen, Irish tv aired #medicationnation You'd have been open mouthed at times!
https://t.co/noW5aU2h8b https://t.co/Ojhguopx9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember guys, if you are in distress today, pls call 116123 
@samaritans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't say what you could or could not comment on, but let me tell you people with clinical depression don't  see… https://t.co/3iyGqUndEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for all your wise words https://t.co/YMCais4FRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can relate and I hope you keep up yoga and everything that's therapeutic. I have been glued to your shared experi… https://t.co/wzSElvHh8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MentalFitnessXX Your words on FB led me to write this lady fri pm,If you have 5, you might be interested ' Aidan https://t.co/8Ty9hnK2MB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMarkRowe as a GP you'll have watched #medicationnation , if you get 5 mins, see the other side prescription meds https://t.co/deMOEbLngb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyONeillNews The truth must win Holly - against biased RTÉ documentaries  https://t.co/FbAIbQjfUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Loved your honesty last night. https://t.co/7Uf8DSs5ER My thoughts as a fellow Mental Health Advocate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stritchj Still no idea what a thanatologist is ,but I'm guessing you saw #medicationnation RTÉ controversy. I argue https://t.co/OJjaK3l0HW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headspace_irl @GROW_Ireland @SpunOut #medicationnation aired on RTE and there are 2 sides to a story! https://t.co/wTdtNehj2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishhealthhour I wonder did you see #medicationnation onRTÉ last night.Various points on health.Not too impressed https://t.co/c2IthqLu68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG that was bad!!! What about that arrogant guy episode 1 / the gay guy who let yer man pay and go first on feelin… https://t.co/LAN12RH4qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Did you read my blog on addiction ? https://t.co/UaZJJeO6do
You're not up to date!! I know you have a job plus… https://t.co/LRKvzaxzZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MentalHealthIrl @MHReform #medicationnation stirred the pot Monday night . Here's a genuine view https://t.co/rR3j2z4Zzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrOliviaHurley Olivia,you might be the wrong lady to send, but if you have 5 ltr #medicationnation aired on RTÉ https://t.co/KpMedBf9QR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see such positive support from @GarveyGroup Well done #Supporters #ShopThere #5KMChallenge #LiveLife… https://t.co/mZBl0TfT93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihayes I am not sure if you saw #medicationnation last night on RTÉ. No reply needdd, but I wasn't happy https://t.co/Criuk1AZGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carmcguigan @ProfJimLucey @paulgilliganceo #medicationnation aired Monday+the country is up in arms , https://t.co/SMeVPP5RtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jensology Jen your social life is super full, but did you see #medicationnation https://t.co/4TuCwR7cJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's very positive to hear. I'm so glad you made the leap. It's worth seeing on player Dee, as quite 1sided. I'm… https://t.co/NrxX7yDqxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rte @rtenews @ClaireByrneLive An educated personal response to #medicationnation https://t.co/UvZNeXZYeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was being semi sarcastic! I have read your blog and it was very difficult to read. Very tough times, but      you… https://t.co/Gv1Qq4SBTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well yes! It is! I find walking is still preferred over running,but open to getting back in sport! I'll keep taking… https://t.co/4qiDdcC5g0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All because you started this ! Good man! Have a great night tonight! https://t.co/29XcnPcIwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Alec! https://t.co/wwOz8BZXHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible blog entry. It must be hard to write about dissociation and so clearly and put the reader in your shoes.… https://t.co/RCEk2LGEEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I totally agree! https://t.co/N4mvgn45tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you very much. I fell asleep last night! You're very kind https://t.co/eBb5rYE9tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely right. Well articulated. "Exactly what she says"! https://t.co/f9AaXt6yPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LoL I'm engaging in exercise now,but I needed to be at a certain level.I know or have come to know so many with sto… https://t.co/oxfSUseDux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and they do go together. Being honest, therapy is powerful, but you can't engage in therapy in my opinion till… https://t.co/o0VCqGq7l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its lunacy to suggest a walk.
Diet, I'd complete loss of appetite.
Reading,I lost all interest, Housebound near pos… https://t.co/0jPUrALQkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good. Glad to hear. There's been an Irish documentary tonight finger pointing at meds. There's been talk oh exercis… https://t.co/EIPwEubdgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long overdue.I'm so sorry.I've been off the radar busy.It's midnight twenty+I've hundreds of notifications!but zoom… https://t.co/KqClV6gn6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean Clinical Depressiom, Major Depressive Disorder, Post Traumatic Disorder.These are serious illnesses, suggest… https://t.co/nTXSYXXEDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That'll work for mild conditions.If we are talking moderate or severe,you are so off the radar, you're views are in… https://t.co/3oBKozmkVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely, I endorse the end of stigma on meds. Fought long and hard to encourage Irish society to take meds. https://t.co/ZpWEAO0EbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I again entirely agree https://t.co/D8GlzoEMbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I endorse that and fully agree https://t.co/a1CwF3eXgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm delighted to hear that https://t.co/TBUptN1LVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to hear that! https://t.co/06h5jL27GK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. I never knew that about you June. I am in the same position. Meds saved my life. Suicide survivor. CSA survivo… https://t.co/yBjOdX6rT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I totally agree.Where's the reference to severe conditions or for those where therapy is good theory, but getting o… https://t.co/NrV5URDdSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking will really help mild and moderate conditions, but we must remain cognisant that severe conditions do need… https://t.co/0QUCl3tyUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental Health on the school curriculum may be coming soon, touch wood https://t.co/IQ3Zrk8iIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad that worked for you https://t.co/3nHTMFqF6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry you were unable to find a solution https://t.co/KNl0ZUznD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all stinger together. Keep up the fitness going forward in February https://t.co/Pg58HvyrAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Alan, I'll definitely take a look. Thank you https://t.co/eU88KM8pVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you understand from study or experience major depression or chronic anxiety or Bipolar? If not, best not comment https://t.co/D8P6RvwHqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EverthingIsHalfTint https://t.co/fTfm5xTSo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am going to take that and ride my energy and if people don't like it, so be it! https://t.co/1636edZ6dW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fully subscribe to this Krystal✔ https://t.co/3eSvcIDu55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved and no two better women. Great to see recognition for @CCRTLim https://t.co/J1SJf5HbmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel in distress this evening, don't hesitate to contact @samaritans 116123]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Expect some shocking statistics"
A rather crass controversial line..
Let's remember script meds save lives. PR com… https://t.co/9cppcqkkfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about someone with Bipolar I or II or EUPD or Schizophrenia or severe anxiety or major depression or clinical… https://t.co/TJlzgukDcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Dr Eva or Claire Byrne read this

https://t.co/zBzBOlfy41

It's popular to group and bash meds tonight,
I'll b… https://t.co/YbTgXGktRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regretfully not. I have had some sight of it. A significant part is on anti depressants, anti anxiety meds, miscell… https://t.co/vXl3elcbG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrEvaOrsmond Eva, hope you're aware that there are tens of thousands in Ireland safely taking script meds that have transformed their lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just hope those anxiety and depression and bipolar under the care of a psychiatrist don't stop taking their meds… https://t.co/0bQ5xeJ9Sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you suffer with depression or anxiety or EUPD or Bipolar? This programme is dangerous. Each case is unique. Eva… https://t.co/X2S3wcItJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very kind gesture for a great hospital and services https://t.co/5yquefwyUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doloreskeating Dolores. Pls have a look at Medication Nation @rte I believe the discussion on psych meds will be dangerous+worry patients]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a positive reply. The Minister with responsibility for Mental Health ready for @MHFAIreland when her diary all… https://t.co/lSX2r4u4Ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MoreThanASelfie. Well done @bodywhys Let's encourage youngsters to use Social Media to reflect how they look now.… https://t.co/Tb5hNUA87P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to see Mary entirely in orange 17 Feb! https://t.co/xjZ8AFDnvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Mary! Note the date in your diary! https://t.co/zRIpEsNODu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm catching up with Jess Hill as I've been super busy. I think we are looking at a future screen /reality star, co… https://t.co/sua8ky2uMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe Anita will get good news in a few weeks. Passion for @Bully_Dont and high emotional intelligence and a go… https://t.co/h63a3CeluA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great initiative in the UK and how absolutely honest of Rebecca to mention her teenage Mental Health. I wish Irelan… https://t.co/TqKmVdjl6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The present is called that for a reason! https://t.co/nzcNS59H6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you can definitely get your book out in 2017. I'm right behind you Davina. I'll support you till it's out t… https://t.co/flRSPDAnW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am leaving the negatives, where they belong... the past https://t.co/sT4BvVErCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FollowYourHeart https://t.co/0ktp1fO94z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leanne, I want you as a positive motivational coach! https://t.co/t72OvluuyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an excellent point! https://t.co/NhOfYDapSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FallenBlueHalo You need to follow this lady on Twitter and blog! Discover why Victoria is the lady in the hat! #Psychoanalysis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this https://t.co/8Fhcr1hrJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you. I'll make it to Canada one day soon. Far better than USA! Ssh! https://t.co/H1eJ5qEiJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL. Like this tweet if you think I'm crazy! https://t.co/FLwzwvM8bm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leanne, may I use some of these?
This is another piece of wisdom?
Connects with me. https://t.co/nKhvNzenGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davinalytle Davina, any update when your book will be out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are one of the most remarkable women, I look forward to the day our paths collide. Thank you for allowing us re… https://t.co/yauTtSdHuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addiction, Jody is so profoundly intense and consuming. I hope it's not inappropriate to say your mom was strugglin… https://t.co/pjBFieVGty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely superbly written. I wish I could give you a huge hug right now. I believe writing can be therape… https://t.co/AHhTFFm5Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my tweet of the day.
It's all about belief 
#Believe https://t.co/ikoif3IdZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can tell you however, like a glass of good champagne. Only the best for you my dear! https://t.co/TDCCPHJbRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls don't call me an elephant. I'm wise enough to do 5KM a day to become a wise baby elephant ! https://t.co/dHkTPeovzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strongly recommend a minimum of 8 hours sleep, but can be challenging.. https://t.co/4p2w5CoYn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be who you are. You're genuinely positively unique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We may not always agree +sometimes I I'm almost envious of her,but Fiona makes a damn lot of good points+ is a top… https://t.co/0DXutjOb9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have the pleasure of seeing you tonight in Medication Nation! RTE1. 930 https://t.co/VWZtOu0CYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even as a committed non drinker, I see this as very wrong .. https://t.co/PgHXFYAFSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good man. 2 let's afternoons for me to go! It's something I'll always keep up! https://t.co/O42pIPrdXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! https://t.co/lMbgvNmG0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls Remember https://t.co/0Y7hM6jyx3 +opportunity to avail of their great  services including the below free to att… https://t.co/oICew53sXU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>