<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenXpatriate haha! I'm pretty sure my top five includes a &lt;local sports bar&gt;, as well. Cities may change, habits don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Receipts for @Uber rides were the top business travel expense in 2016, followed by @Starbucks and @Delta. https://t.co/02abb6qEX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HendWex I had a Yellow line car to myself this morning on the way to @Reagan_Airport!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprises here, @TSA at #ATL and #DFW confiscated the most firearms in 2016. https://t.co/UcNtXaTwzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life: DC is not the country of Colombia, it’s not a city in Maryland and our licenses are real. https://t.co/CXcVEAtWon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curiosity, exploration, discovery. Ideas that propelled the US forward, and ideas that can bridge our divide: https://t.co/Oqrswzcc8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentNelsen: "Trump's brilliance is that he understands the pain of the working class. His problem: he has no plan to address that pain."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newsgirlron perception is more important than truth, and fear a stronger motivator than logic. Still, he is one man, and we are a country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, fear trumped reason—but tomorrow is up to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwrichards congrats and thank you for your service to our alma mater, @FurmanU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @realDonaldTrump thinks people are #skittles, why can't he taste the rainbow and realize the country isn't just white men?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When all you want to do is get home and you're watching your @Uber drive laps around #DCA... Third time is the charm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership, opportunity, brotherhood: how @PiKappaPhi shaped my college experience and career. https://t.co/cKqrU7arL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coreydu great company, indeed! Pleasure to have met you and to have worked with @BofA_News Comms Exec Jim Mahoney and @B_M WW CEO Don Baer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coreydu, congratulations on ranking #26 on the @prweek Power List 2016. https://t.co/brGkxtvZvo #PRpros]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Brexit, a still-life. https://t.co/BfavobGGXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyMKreis, they obviously missed the commandment, "thou shalt not write in passive voice." CC: @DCHomos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From app to Outlook, @Starbucks now offers email plug-in to send gift cards, schedule meetings at nearby stores. https://t.co/5NazWy8qBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional recording from @elilieb written in memory of the #OrlandoShooting victims. https://t.co/UHldLsjZtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing @andersoncooper hold back tears reading the names of those killed in #Orlando on @CNN is bringing me to tears. #LoveIsLove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful message on the ongoing challenges and resolve of the #LGBT community: "What It Costs to Be Gay in Public." https://t.co/zxqTqfjAsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There’ll come a time when the love of country will trump hatred of #HillaryClinton,” @GrahamBlog. https://t.co/A1HmUUaViu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The airline industry expects global profits of $40bn even as airfares are expected to fall by 7%. https://t.co/4OyLtN4AhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraged to see @google taking a stand banning #ads from predatory #payday #lenders: https://t.co/W3XjnhxcpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to support my Alma Mater on #DinsDay. FU all the time. https://t.co/EWnKt4DAMJ https://t.co/DxEZBYQnbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible story of #faith and the challenges of being #LGBT, through the lens of a @FurmanNews chaplain. https://t.co/XidvCpxoKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday #NC voted to make me unwelcome in the state I was once proud to call home. https://t.co/GnWTOeL1o6 #WeAreNotThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My feelings when I see friends post from happy hour and in sunlight. #confession #truth https://t.co/bhdgD5QU4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leap year = an extra day to do my time sheets. #LeapYear https://t.co/Adj28DioeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find solace in this headline: "The Smarter And More Independent You Are, The Harder It Is To Find Love." https://t.co/fIb4eGWaqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir, I'm a day late, have been to three airports today and am further away from home than I started. #help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cratetwelve, sadly @LindseyGrahamSC already endorsed @JebBush. Early blow for Frank Underwood's campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a candidate I can support. Frank Underwood opens a campaign office in Greenville, #SC. https://t.co/2Tm9almGMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @nytdavidbrooks, "Sanders [is] so blinded by his values that the reality of the situation does not seem to penetrate his mind."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To hear Sanders or Trump, Cruz and Carson #campaign is to wallow in the pornography of pessimism." https://t.co/dTQOt4qf5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Longtime U.S. sales leader, @BMWUSAnews, slides as @MBUSA overtakes #1 spot for monthly sales. https://t.co/TyeLjhbmBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean her family has enough experience with both... https://t.co/iONeMw0d5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDPW thank you. @DCDGS @NatlParkService it's not safe for pedestrians trying to get to work! #DCDigOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDPW why don't you clear sidewalks in Thomas Circle so pedestrians don't have to walk in the road (and don't fall when crossing it)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A perspective on Why D.C. Hates Ted Cruz: “he is incapable of delivering anything but theater.” https://t.co/QeKP8xTe7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daltonjgoodier larger question, how do you define "journalist" and "news outlet"? Today anyone with Internet access is a journalist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to be kidding me. #SC State Rep. proposes bill to create #journalist registry. https://t.co/6aHjchw251]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @Delta for surpassing @united to become the second largest U.S. #airline. https://t.co/jNxBnheWzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Five on @FoodNetwork planning to film at Grits and Groceries on 12/9, featuring Joe's famous fried pies. #yeahTHATgreenville #SC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever do something and think, "now I'm one of those statistics?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wall #Trump hopes to build would do more harm to his cause than good: More Mexicans leaving than coming to US. https://t.co/pa3VSTlUO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ask me how my day is going when I'm holding both a hot coffee and an iced coffee. #TisTheSeason #INeedBoth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin, my momma don't like you, and she likes everyone—but your new album is real good. Confessions of a reluctant #Belieber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When its a ghost town on your commute and you think you're really late to work, then realize its #VeteransDay. #DClife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipster thought of the day: ride a tandem #bike to the bar so it's easier to take someone home. "Want to ride my bicycle?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pickle-brined, golden-fried hate chicken coming to a District corner near you. Chic-fil-A to expand in #DC. https://t.co/S3Lz3cVNYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget I live in #DC, then #BernieSanders gets out of a Ford Focus and on an elevator with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time ... #BMW leverages #Uber to showroom new 7 Series flagship sedan. https://t.co/yisDUg3uVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation for good: The US Holocaust Memorial Museum has a new online tool to forecast and prevent #genocide. http://t.co/Lj29dtR0iY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir I did, they weren't helpful—but it sounds like you had larger tech issues today! Ultimately got the tickets booked. #thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir you're killing me with website login errors and unreal hold times via phone. All I want to do is book a flight! Help @Delta?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bikeshare many thanks for the response. Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bikeshare happy 5th! To celebrate there are 5 non-functional bike docks in the Vermont and 11th St. station. #DC #commute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time, can we actually talk about mental health reform and access to firearms--not flags, religion or terrorism? #EnoughIsEnough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope to see my fellow @Furman_Alumni in #DC tomorrow at @LostNFoundDC for #FurmanYAD. Info and registration: https://t.co/YUT9NJbqyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found while reading, "People seem not to see that their opinion of the world is also a confession of character."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoPville 7th Street NW blocked off between U and S. Dozens of police and EMS vehicles. Police won't comment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoPville what is going on at the Shaw Metro? http://t.co/jdowvfS9bT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support thank you for your timely response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber_DC infuriated in my #Uber this morning, driver intentionally going out of the way with a surge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Swamp Rabbit Trail in @Greenville_SC was named the #1 urban #bike path in the US, #yeahTHATgreenville. http://t.co/p0kJJdOobc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["America is killing itself through its embrace and exaltation of ignorance." https://t.co/7o5KWNOT9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats, @apenalver! Well deserved--proud to call you both a brother and a friend. https://t.co/mKpkkCvrDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leasing accounted for 28.9% of #millennial #auto purchases in 2015, attracted by luxurious, tech-forward cars otherwise unaffordable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lower fuel prices could make the #GreekCrisis a blessing in disguise for domestic US #airlines. http://t.co/tWEO33yoOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a non-issue. From my personal experience, gays don't eat cake--in public settings at least. http://t.co/ifr7AG5RpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeMcCWYFF you can spot that truck driving along the National Mall in #DC periodically. Must be making rounds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to the Russians to publish a guide on safe selfies. Narcissistic friends, take note: http://t.co/YgUPiIeS5w http://t.co/0ajDk04L0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they haven't already... https://t.co/T1J3gE07qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshBinsz interesting to see someone (finally) defending the @nytimes guacamole recipe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbitSupport my Flex shows a full charge when plugged in, but is unresponsive otherwise. Tried restarting--no luck. HELP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @SteveGrandMusic at the #DC Capital #Pride Hero's Gala tonight. http://t.co/9oy0yxn8zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NorrabRetsbew Ted Winters got free pizza from @Delta in Destin #FL after his flight was canceled!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting read on @AdWeek: How #MadMen reshaped the #ad industry and inspired a new generation of creatives. http://t.co/0UWfE0kceQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud supporter of my alma mater, @FurmanU. Thanks to Dr. Karwan for encouraging me to donate to a new #business lab. http://t.co/rImQ5jpkE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bikeshare 2 days in a row that the 11th and Vermont station hasn't had bikes! Also a broken bike has been there all week. #TheMoreYouKnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to my fellow @B_M family colleagues. Well deserved! https://t.co/snnwqxfQ8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simplysweetbos thanks for the LinkedIn message! I'd love to connect sometime soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for cherry blossoms in #DC? The @nationaljournal's #cherrypicker app helps you find the nearest tree. http://t.co/AO7iSoNupV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schock and Aww, Illinois Rep. and high-style socialite to resign amid spending controversies. http://t.co/Sw7ctPquAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most #auto companies are obsessed with growth. At @Porsche AG, the challenge is to stay small, maintain exclusivity. http://t.co/l8zhQ0tLm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my pet peeves (I have many). Stop saying 'should.' https://t.co/9oiiBh59Vf #communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alumni from @FurmanU have been all over the @nytimes this week, from @YikYakApp to the lead defense attorney in the Boston bombing case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defense led by @FurmanU #alumnae, Judy Clarke. Why the strategy for defending Tsarnaev includes admitting his guilt http://t.co/m0VtguWGQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daimler (@MercedesBenz) is spending about €6,000 per #car on #advertising compared to €1,500 at @Ford and @GM, http://t.co/I6Hqdx82L4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiking the Appalachian Trail? @FortuneMagazine Where in the world is Vladimir #Putin? No one seems to know http://t.co/sQ6zUklBwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born that way? Pew study shows Americans remain divided over origin of #sexual orientation. http://t.co/NQCyDYwndE http://t.co/ESPr0M0Dvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AHRicci So true, some day somebody’s gonna make you wanna gobble up a waffle fry. #guiltypleasures https://t.co/uOlS7W1u70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chic-fil-A poised to take a bite at the Big Apple this summer. Hate never tasted so good. http://t.co/UYoFxxSKm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps a #news show that allows for truthiness is better for #BrianWilliams? @TheDailyShow has an opening, I hear. http://t.co/PX6CkVvojO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014 @Euromonitor data shows US top decile outspent the bottom by a factor of 7.3, allocating 43.2 times as much on miscellaneous purchases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We respect the past, but we don’t pine for the past.  We don’t fear the future; we grab for it." http://t.co/UJ9SStxqjI #Selma50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New study reports 71% of #Millennials said they would rather visit the dentist than hear what #banks have to say. http://t.co/cW82EOGoj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun #automotive fact: one out of every three @bmw M vehicles sold currently finds a home stateside. #german http://t.co/jD6iIJNVjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just referenced "opportunity cost" when giving a friend relationship advice. I think I'm heartless. #ValentinesDay]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>