<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#MAGA #Trump A very reasonable explanation I think! https://t.co/pGcd8hIO0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CClaudiabarry Wrong, he actually was against the UN resolution criticizing Israeli Settlements on the West Bank. He tore into John Kerry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Labour happier now over immigration? https://t.co/aSZf9UWaOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday Night Live - President Trump - Cold Open https://t.co/1OcSSdBLfy via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Really_JimB He's a white nationalist and neo-Nazi sympathiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Axelrod: I woke up this morning as an alternative fact @CNN https://t.co/BoV7G9AlJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Leda412 Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turfguy08 What about the undocumented Irish? They deserve legal status of some sort!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turfguy08 Do you not acknowledge the suffering of his relatives at the hands of the Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is what #MAGA looks like! https://t.co/RmmtYjMnR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YvetteCooperMP @jessphillips Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliseviebeck @MsMainstay Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepBarbaraLee @HouseDemocrats Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRMoffitt @OMAHAGEMGIRL Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vgliatti Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @workclassjane Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_CreativeEdge Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mightybattlecat Many people want him to run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons @chronicle Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mightybattlecat Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katiedawson23 Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Mattingly Some people say Steve Bannon is being lined up as a future POTUS to succeed Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azleatherneck What about all this white nationalist stuff? That must be a dangerous thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnoughAlreadyFR It has caused anger in the UK and there was widespread criticism of Trump in parliment from both sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnoughAlreadyFR I think the EO could have been handled better. State Department wasn't given any notice nor was congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azleatherneck Ah ok. Heard of the guy. Bit of a nutcase from what I heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freon500 Sadly they are filling a vacuum where religious leaders of islam should be giving clear moral guidance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azleatherneck Who's Milo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azleatherneck What do you think of Steve Bannon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnoughAlreadyFR In the UK there's a lot of anger at the way the EO was issued and written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Azleatherneck What ever happened to the centre ground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Really_JimB What do you think of Steve Bannon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ricktekk Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freon500 There are many descent muslims around. Sadly there's no central leadership like the catholic church to give them guidance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimEvan58277834 Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalphHause Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagentaMelee Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turfguy08 Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnoughAlreadyFR Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artmaniac Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CClaudiabarry Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JT0sca Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@albo9124 Senator Schumer had relatives who were persecuted by the Nazis in Ukraine during WW2. So give the guy a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freon500 Any thoughts on Indonesia, UAE, Egypt, Turkey and Saudi Arabia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freon500 What do you think of Islam as a religion then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Steve Bannon is a real danger to American democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristiChat I don't think Steve Bannon should be on the NSC as h's not suitable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Where's your Nazi lackey Bannon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lottyleeming hi hun. how are things? xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's travel ban wouldn't have stopped these deadly terrorists @CNN https://t.co/bBCAwvmNiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anna_Soubry Brilliant speech Anna. It was to the point and very meaningful. You are elegant as always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MandiXXXMcGraw Ur clit looks very tasty love xxxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stellacreasy Don't count on Boris. He can't eeven tie his shoelaces!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liverpool_FC_ Any sign of Joe Hart or Bernd Leno coming to Anfield?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCMOTD Bernd Leno linked with Liverpool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airman, citizen worries travel ban will hurt his dad @CNNPolitics https://t.co/xXoBngZNFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KWH88 @GaleThoughts Well said my friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RodneyEvans Are you saying all muslims are evil? Sure the Nazis saw all Jews as evil and look what happened!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xmaselmo1 Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspades Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stump4TrumpSF Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FieniRfieni Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stimulus4U Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenexox Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithdboygenius Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jase0910 Senator Schumer had relatives that were persecuted by both the Nazis and the Soviets during WW2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They are honorable men!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republicans were obstructing job creation in congress. What do you think! https://t.co/4qa0G2mlvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsayler Exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Jones: We need to try to understand Trump @CNNPolitics https://t.co/iihVjsBHcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaleThoughts @KWH88 Who me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What about Saudi Arabia and Egypt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaleThoughts @KWH88 Only reporting what he said!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH: No mention of Jews on Holocaust Remembrance Day because others were killed too @CNNPolitics https://t.co/kUh4oooDkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annemccoy I hope Dermot Bannon is no relation to Steve Bannon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaleThoughts Trump didn't say much paying tribute to the victims of the Holocaust on #HolocaustMemorialDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the #MuslimBan the GOP are going to get wiped out at the mid-terms next year if they don't ditch Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkfranklin @annabella232 Ted Cruz has said nothing about the ban!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House discussing asking foreign visitors for social media info and cell phone contacts @CNNPolitics https://t.co/WwvoNgUmaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - US refugee ban: Canada's Justin Trudeau takes a stand https://t.co/gEibyKZVYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Labour's Harriet Harman claims lecturer 'offered grade for sex' https://t.co/4hszZgeUdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins Culture is different and thee weather is way too hot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling Well said General. I think it's outrageous that Steve Bannon is on the NSC replacing Jo Dunford!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MuslimBan wouldn't have stopped 9/11 as 15 of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia, 1 from Egypt,1 from Lebanon,and 2 from UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KayBurley #MuslimBan wouldn't have stopped 9/11 as 15 of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia, 1 from Egypt,1 from Lebanon,and 2 from UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgeller #MuslimBan wouldn't have stopped 9/11 as 15 of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia, 1 from Egypt,1 from Lebanon,and 2 from UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MuslimBan wouldn't have stopped 9/11 as 15 of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia, 1 from Egypt,1 from Lebanon, &amp; 2 from UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MuslimBan wouldn't have stopped 9/11 as 15 of the hijackers came from Saudi Arabia, one from Egypt,1 from Lebanon,and 2 from the UAE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@authorsyoung Hey gorgeous xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I suppose your next Executive action will be to deport all illegal immigrants!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotinMyName The Nazi's carried out a similar crackdown against Jews in Kristallnacht in 1938. This eventually led to the Holocaust!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smokey_pawsback Kyrgystan comes under Russian protection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astonishing that Saudi Arabia left off the #MuslimBan list. Apparently Trump has business interests there! 👎😡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder Astonishing that Saudi Arabia left off the list. Did I read somewhere that Trump has business interests there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamingWithNuke Tell that to Mr Zahawi and Sir Mo Farah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realRichHunting That's how Mr Zahawi feels and a lot of his colleagues in parliament feel the same way and are very angry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch @EmmaKennedy Steve Bannon now has virtually full control of the NSC. This guy is extremely dangerous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realRichHunting This is a conservative MP! https://t.co/7OocMNg7fx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>