<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @hbwx! You're on in Sterling, VA at Millers Ale House. https://t.co/1nPNGUA8md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh, tough question. I love both! 
But nothing beats being out in the elements getting to describe extreme weather… https://t.co/JBOXxSSPPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sunny but brisk Saturday - but a big warm-up is in our near future. A look at which day we'll hit 60 on @wusa9 https://t.co/drdYr0wACl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty but COLD to start this Saturday. @wusa9 https://t.co/3aYikpFQOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook just told me this...
#eyeroll
Trust your local meteorologist, not facebook. See you on @wusa9 https://t.co/OzwJrleq1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WakeUpWash starts now- join us! @wusa9 @IleanaMDiaz @stephitv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markwaddell11 Me too! But Phil is only 39% accurate, so just take his prognostication with a grain of salt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smgarth But if the 6 more weeks of winter are anything like the last 6, we can handle it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barry_Tyree It's not fake news! This is an old tradition, one that only holds a 39% accuracy. Prognostication, not a real forecast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil saw his shadow. It was cloudy out but they lit the stage, hence the shadow. If the 6 wks are anything like the last 6 we can handle it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six more weeks of winter.... #Punxsutawneyphil #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! It's #GroundhogDay - why do we still look to rodents for weather prognostication? We'll compare their accuracy… https://t.co/mbbXA5JRZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You normally don't see such a neat-looking skyline at lunch time. See you on @wusa9 News at noon - is snow in the p… https://t.co/X41OZRis6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryJMar Seriously! Just decided to freehand without the tank lid on. I'm too lazy and cheap to call a plumber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomAckermanWx Thank you! This is proving to be the biggest pain in the butt ever...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 4 of painting the new house. I officially hate painting bathrooms 😠. Advice needed: How do you paint around a... https://t.co/9rzDe7qaaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thin blanket of snow in DC this Monday morning. @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx @TenaciousTopper @hbwx @WUSA9weather https://t.co/J5uMihfvaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just passed Melwood Elementary- it's so beautiful here with the snow-covered grass and scenery! @wusa9 @pgcps… https://t.co/loM4L5YLOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning from Prince George's county! Starting the week with a winter wonderland but not a nightmare on the roa… https://t.co/tTQ4EuxndD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Snow is my favorite variety of snow... I'd never complain about seeing more of him. Agree, @HCaseInPoint? We a… https://t.co/vleEGVMlfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only ok with light snow with abv freezing road temps like today. Any more snow... no thanks. Agree, @AllysonRaeWx ? https://t.co/rXPDsblH4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MD 301 / Rt 5 in Brandywine. Wet roads, wet snow blankets the grass, shrubs, and trees. @wusa9 @WUSA9weather… https://t.co/kjttCxTiQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These gentlemen have been treating the roads all morning in Calvert co. They say even neighborhood and back roads a… https://t.co/I7EtuTgL3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLBFan1991 Morning! You too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School closings/delays continue to stream in - a full list at https://t.co/iqI1x37ceJ @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx @pgcps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful winter wonderland! https://t.co/HoAVqF6s3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car dealerships are always such a pretty sight after a light snowfall! @wusa9 @WUSA9weather @AllysonRaeWx https://t.co/qX6lAqD3Vb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're in Charles county with @wusa9weather looking at road conditions https://t.co/4OW4q6IY8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From La Plata to Waldorf - generally between 1" and 1.5" @AllysonRaeWx WET roads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow reports in Virginia #VAwx @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx https://t.co/1YDt4ehOmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading south on Rt 5 in Prince George's county. Roads are wet, but grass/trees have turned into a beautiful winter… https://t.co/hK4cOfCDIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading south through DC in @WUSA9weather - #WakeUpWash starts early today starting at 4am! @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx… https://t.co/CXIBrambUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#snOMG - large wet snowflakes quickly coating the weather terrace!@wusa9 @WUSA9weather @AllysonRaeWx @hbwx… https://t.co/xvwKsZyKSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us on Facebook live talking about the snow heading this way https://t.co/2bG9nMIDfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for joining us on #WakeUpWash today! @MikeaTurnerTV @wusa9 https://t.co/0CWbGDK3uF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right after #WakeUpWash - we'll be hopping on Facebook Live on @wusa9 discussing snow shower timing &amp; impacts. https://t.co/0kCrRKnlp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another half hour of #WakeUpWash starting now! @MikeaTurnerTV @JaniceparkNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up next -- a recap of an incredible group of @pgcps students we visited this week with @wusa9weather! @wusa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hour of #WakeUpWash underway. Join us! @wusa9 @MikeaTurnerTV @JaniceparkNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads up -- light accumulating snow starting early tonight! We're on #WakeUpWash til 9am. I'll break down how... https://t.co/LJG6DThBLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky glows at the start to this Sunday. By the end of it, we'll be tracking snow showers. On #WakeUpWash - a loo… https://t.co/hy9o3Ax53m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up next- an incredible story of a woman's survival when a strong tornado hit her home. @wusa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow showers with light accumulations are likely tonight. What does this mean for your AM commute? Join us on… https://t.co/nuoUgut8Xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow showers arriving before midnight tonight. Pinpointing how much you could see on wake up wash. @wusa9 https://t.co/2iFqhKk3wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliemartin Nice to see you forecasting on CNN early this morning. Hope you're well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are new home owners! 
First project: painting https://t.co/tgROMOOPWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So you're sayin' there's a chance"
It's not much, but snow showers will be in the cards for some before Monday AM.… https://t.co/NxTctg1RBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeaTurnerTV joins me on the anchor desk this weekend on #WakeUpWash- see you again tomorrow morning 7-9! @wusa9 https://t.co/Zyjcu7aFJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Z1m16xG68Y- one of my favorite parts of Saturday mornings @HCaseInPoint @marcelwarfield @MikeaTurnerTV @nleimbach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilly temps but increasing sun expected today. @wusa9 @hbwx @TenaciousTopper @AllysonRaeWx https://t.co/7mXMFsKl7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will be a chilly Saturday, but sunshine is in the cards. Cold-weather fans will not be mad at my forecast this w… https://t.co/8ILWQ0Jd9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cold weekend ahead - and perhaps some snow showers before Monday AM. Join us on #WakeUpWash - we're on til 8! @wusa9 @MikeaTurnerTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now THIS is a twitter battle everyone should approve of! Baby animal alert! https://t.co/RKsXiZy716]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning, DC and Happy #FriYay! @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx @hbwx @TenaciousTopper @ChrisClimate https://t.co/slStv2XbZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's SO #Windy right now! Outcome: colder temps. @hbwx will show you the #weekend forecast on @wusa9 https://t.co/9toQHehti0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Humane_Rescue #DesignsForFelines underway! These are homes for community cats in DC. @wusa9 @NikkiBurdine https://t.co/rGKH3CNq8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Headquarters for @TEGNA WIN! Empowering Women. @wusa9 @abuddy https://t.co/ixgHIkzmxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mild and sunny right now, but it turns MUCH colder later this week. Breaking down what this means for the weekend o… https://t.co/KKtWfbL8kP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buenos Dias from Overlook ES! Learn more about their Spanish Immersion program on #WakeUpWash @wusa9… https://t.co/3IrPpObBDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaviest rain &amp; highest wind gusts will be late AM through early afternoon. Some trees could fall in higher wind gu… https://t.co/ZbwRSSULQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tree down on power lines on Seven Locks Rd in Bethesda, flames have ignited for a second time. High winds + wet soi… https://t.co/zWVDBPB45q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combination of gusty winds and damp soil caused this 65ft pine tree to come down on power line on Seven Locks Rd in… https://t.co/zHVbXHifkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain intensity and wind gust speeds really crank up after the AM commute. @AllysonRaeWx and I break down impacts on… https://t.co/9RyDrvVdfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll be guiding you thru the heavy rain and blustery winds tomorrow morning on #WakeUpWash. Join @AllysonRaeWx and… https://t.co/MmjjdBeCOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll always be an Atlanta native. Rise up!!! #NFLPlayoffs #Falcons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year ago #Blizzard2016 was beginning. Do you remember? @wusa9 @hbwx @TenaciousTopper @AllysonRaeWx https://t.co/8bcvbcOWGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year ago today... Blizzard 2016 was just beginning https://t.co/VeAagwibUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dense fog in Linden, VA this morning, sent in by @wusa9 viewer Steven Ross. Fog advisory continues N &amp; W of DC unti… https://t.co/lPQrozopzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Widespread 1-2" of rain between now and the end of Monday, w/ locally higher amounts. Looking at when the heaviest… https://t.co/G73m2xHlJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NWSSPC upgrades severe outlook to rare 'high' risk in southern GA, northern FL, and SE AL. Tornado outbreak likely… https://t.co/y2N5ivCpo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hour of #WakeUpWash getting started. Join us! @wusa9 @AndreaMcCarren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where'd the city skyline go?! 
Dense fog this AM - send me your weather photos! https://t.co/9FOxBvRHkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VERY dense fog this Sunday morning, along with drizzle. I'm tracking locally heavy rain returning soon - breaking d… https://t.co/FsJ2Q6H5pG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fog &amp; drizzle early with light rain returning mid to late afternoon. Your AM commute- heavy rain &amp; wind. I'll break… https://t.co/9lrImYLn1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dense fog this AM, similar to yesterday! @wusa9 https://t.co/Ws2A0tZ2bA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dense fog advisory extended until 1PM - Visibilities will still be below 1/2 mile in spots for the duration of the… https://t.co/JcsHr3FpSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We will be continuing our coverage on the @wusa9 facebook page live starting at 10AM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloudy, foggy, damp on the weather terrace this morning. Walking you through the #WomensMarch forecast on @wusa9. A… https://t.co/HQhCBnYsYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MolaReports We LOVE your package on Bao Bao!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hour of #WakeUpWash getting started. Tracking fog - plus big crowds traveling into DC for #WomensMarch. @wusa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VERY dense fog this morning! We're on #WakeUpWash until 10AM. 

Is it very foggy where you are? Help me out -... https://t.co/F3c98HLyfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locally dense fog dropping visibility down below 1/2 mile. This is a look at VA-28 right off Dulles Toll Road.… https://t.co/CzdivTFCFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 fatalities confirmed in Hattiesburg. Severe wx continues across the deep south today, heading into AL &amp; GA https://t.co/nuTRcCbPfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visibility at @Reagan_Airport may not be too bad, but west of town - @Dulles_Airport visibility is down to a quarte… https://t.co/9XLbO9M5Ua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Widespread fog, locally dense blankets the area, along with mist and drizzle. Timing out when the fog will lift on… https://t.co/4gEumBz5DX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fog and drizzle as #WomensMarch attendees arrive. Mainly cloudy into the afternoon with temps in the 50s. @wusa9 https://t.co/Rvba9NwwxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Severe weather, tornadoes ongoing in MS/AL. Reports of people trapped &amp; injured after likely #tornado tore thru… https://t.co/GupCTJ2q5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Widespread dense fog early this Saturday morning, some visibilities &lt; 1/2 mile. Dense fog advisory west of town unt… https://t.co/5RhML0Q0ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few isolated showers will linger in the metro for early afternoon, with patchy drizzle/fog for the… https://t.co/MoYQQwkgDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light rain arrived at the Capitol. Ponchos and umbrellas out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The peaceful transfer of power is complete. @wusa9 https://t.co/7NGQ5V2AC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light rain closing in on DC &amp; the #Inauguration #InaugurationDay @wusa9 @AllysonRaeWx https://t.co/K4Fz5N5qja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes the light rain. Should arrive at the National Mall between 11:30 and Noon. @wusa9… https://t.co/PZofC9egvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's getting pretty rowdy in some of the protest areas. Be safe, fellow @wusa9 team members! #Inauguration #Inauguration2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello! Welcome from Kentucky to DC! Unfortunately, rain looks likely for the swearing in... ponchos are good ideas. https://t.co/DZoMYeBdbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know where it's raining and where it's dry? RADAR: https://t.co/RePcIF8fbi
@wusa9 #Inauguration2017 #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes- a very light rain shower as @realDonaldTrump walks into church. Our forecast was spotty showers early, steady… https://t.co/jvDO7nBZNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to the National Mall for the #Inauguration?  Dress warm &amp; take a poncho/small umbrella. Critical Rain Timin… https://t.co/JRBBYd4ZO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great photo! https://t.co/2YmfitPavh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wusa9 #WakeUpWash team on #InaugurationDay2017- plus many more behind the scenes! https://t.co/U4QJAzPBrs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>