<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for dumplings! #yearoftherooster #Melbourne https://t.co/0Uab9OtLPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Joyce Chant deserves better than this. She was battered for YEARS, she wasn't a cold blooded killer #deadlywomen #netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganLeaderNews "he raped her on one of their first dates, I think that says more about HER"...no Candice. No it doesn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Deadly Women on #Netflix. Wish Candice DeLong would stop finding ways to blame the women when men abuse them though 😒😒😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are more people here than Trump's inauguration https://t.co/3MPdo4melV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite a few people getting on the tram to the women's match #afl #collingwoodvscarlton https://t.co/gNdn1yH1hQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the US in the middle of a coup? https://t.co/G8K8229zDc via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week in #Dandenong crime https://t.co/lw0u0fVWcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloquent_89 Well, we certainly wouldn't be as much of a terror target had we stayed out of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye Dimity! We will miss you here at Frankston...until you come back in October https://t.co/bFrrQ2vOBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible https://t.co/XSkr9dQgkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, the disrespect the US is showing to Australia is soooo funny. So many edgelords on here #PrimeMinisterTrumble https://t.co/Y3apBvA17B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, does this mean we don't need to join the next war America starts on a whim? #breakingupishardtodo https://t.co/WvBE6OJSbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so amazing and beautiful and I love it but it's also very 'awkward family photos' https://t.co/fjrPzHcFte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't regret immediately unmatching people on tinder because they said they loved this book 😹😹😹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never read 50 shades of grey so I'm watching it on 7 to save time/understand pop culture and oh no it's as tedious as reading the book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I learned that "broga" (yoga for men aka bros) is a thing. SMDH. What's wrong with regular yoga?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone makes you send their quotes to them before including them in a story because they aren't sure what the… https://t.co/VmUiJjnjpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calls for Annastacia Palaszczuk to change QLD bail laws for family violence offenders  https://t.co/KSqKuSOefi via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week in #Casey crime https://t.co/GQm4IovyNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body of #Frankston woman who died in Japan finally coming home, thanks to strangers https://t.co/KPBsobWEmO via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We do not and should not deal with parties who are on an extreme fringe...we should defeat them" I hope you do.  https://t.co/YYGZOkBzpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What https://t.co/rsLjfiYg7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters battle #Lyndhurst blaze https://t.co/5SzaFRzFKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the angry people who yelled 'being gay isn't normal' and 'being gay is a mental illness' @ me over last 12hrs  https://t.co/gTmEkdnmlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom areas in #Cranbourne and #Clyde have celebrated the opening of three new schools this year https://t.co/fvKVb89LOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subjects I took at school: Japanese and (basic) IT. Subjects students take now: coding and Mandarin. Oh no :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police called to out-of-control party in #Berwick https://t.co/cGpYBiSc76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: I have a story for you about an out of control party if you want?
Ed: Why weren't WE  invited to this party?
Me: We're not cool enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington state suing President Trump over his immigration ban https://t.co/HmLfClfOVV via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blocking finger is getting tired of these people defending their right to be a parent who hates their children... #brideandprejudice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qld_Jack what is unusual about being gay? You choose to be hateful, you don't choose to be gay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so glad I never had to go through what Chris has to go through 😢 #BrideandPrejudice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't support and love your child because they have a same-sex partner you don't deserve to be a parent #BrideandPrejudice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victorian schoolboy believed to be first Australian hit with US visa ban | SBS News https://t.co/Ie1lvlBtot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously? Starting to wonder if it's worth a visit to the US these days https://t.co/TGvt4xMNUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a #Cranbourne or Casey resident who has a small Valentines Day-related business? Is it fun and interesting? Get in touch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie Widower Posts Gumtree Ad Looking For A Fishing Mate &amp; We Can't Cope https://t.co/FfaauEPNGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Casey council shuts down attempt to force councillors pre-selected or endorsed by political parties to step down https://t.co/wKPkVbIH27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car smashed after #Cranbourne man's STD scare https://t.co/MEtWIAZllu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New life in #Dandenong for injured stray https://t.co/U2LvalIqod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best story of the weekend: Lifelong friends from day one https://t.co/HAYNmtdwoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fun. https://t.co/Xahyr8cBNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan 26 is also the anniversary of Charles Manson being convicted of murder and the opening of the Phantom of the Opera.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan 26 is also the anniversary of President Clinton saying "I did not have sexual relations with that woman, Miss Lewinsky"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Spike' in used syringes around #Cranbourne shopping precinct https://t.co/PFCyQIXQ1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How would my Scottish cousins feel if they had to celebrate United Kingdom day" #AustraliaDay #changethedate https://t.co/iFn9NoeQz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every 90s kid remembers the old anti-piracy ads on the rental movies. This is very clever https://t.co/3FuGZyR8rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseDGraham I like it better than 'fake news' though. I yearn for the days when 'clickbait' was the insult de jour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone complained my burger story was clickbait. If you know what the story is from the photo, it's not clickbait. You did this to yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well then... https://t.co/3RjZ2iycvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will probably be my most-read story this week https://t.co/rC9VENzmtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tee hee: Female Legislators Unveil 'Male Ejaculation Bill' #alternativefacts https://t.co/JOdKj2oScD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man jailed for nine months after breaking into Pakenham girl’s bedroom to steal her mobile phone https://t.co/O3yZ6Po8CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Casey Street Watch: #EndeavourHills man robbed at gunpoint, #Cranbourne drug raid nets 91 cannabis plants https://t.co/gNLe6C6Xhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedCrossAU finally lifted my blood donation ban and allowed me to donate tomorrow! No alcohol, lots of sugar and hopefully no fainting :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NarreWarren mum Lani Brereton speaks out over horrific drink-driving incident: he stuffed up, but he's human’ https://t.co/BrCEccyhVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists arrested covering anti-Trump protests https://t.co/VdkZUgANWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article about men staying home and looking after kids during #womensmarch compared to suffragettes posters https://t.co/7skU8oaAo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FourCorners giving me those tinfoil hat feels...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2013 #neighbours prediction: Dee comes back as ghost. 2017 prediction: polyamorous situation for Toady, Dee and Sonja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casey welcomes new Australians https://t.co/XFhjF3o1is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sigh https://t.co/J9iY4g5t97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vic Liberals call for ‘one strike and you’re out’ bail laws and presumption of remand for those charged with violen… https://t.co/fI8b4MwaRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sure hope everyone at the US-based #WomensMarchOnWashington went out and voted last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The least basic person I've ever seen on family feud. Go, Dominic! https://t.co/lzorJTCaVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police say driver had drug, mental health issues #bourkestreet  #MelbourneCBD https://t.co/PQu7ptHeo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THREE people have been confirmed killed, 20 are hurt including four young children https://t.co/PQu7ptHeo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Street performer said Bourke St driver "deliberately directed the car at the people"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Details: shots fired in Melbourne CBD https://t.co/rB062oJIXL via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police say one person has been confirmed deceased #BourkeSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone in Frankston felt a tremor at about 10.25am it was just the journos at the Leader office running to the tea room for muffins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyer: allegations of sexual abuse are 'almost automatically treated with scepticism' in family court https://t.co/xNoL0m6zKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do the candles smell like? Vanilla? Pizza eaten with a knife and fork? https://t.co/5nHJ6ulCUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't even imagine 😢: Self-abortion in #America on the rise as #PlannedParenthood clinics close https://t.co/jX7sRcH1d8 via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Casey Street Watch: Hallam man bottled during fracas at Doveton Serbian Club, police hunt NYE attackers https://t.co/n3RHvhR9lB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man under investigation by the Echo taskforce has been allowed to keep going to a gym with Comanchero links. https://t.co/hJmFSdWAUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope and pray to whatever there is to hope and pray to that I am never in a situation where I have to rely on wel… https://t.co/Jus4nr6mMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helen Kapalos: Who really qualifies as Australian? https://t.co/oXOWNTOON2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four men linked to the Apex gang will be kicked out of Australia after their visas were cancelled. https://t.co/VGgczIReKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone supports the #PutThemBackUp campaign either https://t.co/t141DPPSJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I am officially the religious affairs reporter now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rise Up Australia Party leader's #Hallam church not a charity, watchdog says https://t.co/8R1Fuvsu2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decision to remove #hijab #AustraliaDay advert sparks fresh outcry https://t.co/orti62QsdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is now a petition to reinstate the Australia Day billboard feat two girls in hijabs  https://t.co/Iicja7RWk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jayson and Leesa Lowe open Time is Key ‘escape room’ in #Dandenong ...which I tried and escaped :D https://t.co/FvKAoq7ekG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jltownson That's probably the closest one. I need a word that describes something that is always making waves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need another word for 'controversial'...there really aren't too many good alternatives. Maybe the French or Germans have one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casey looking at having chaplains in shopping centres and sports clubs to help ‘at risk’ youth https://t.co/KPOJ2ugOz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria’s Chief Health Officer's #measles warning follows two cases detected in Rowville. Teens affected visited #FountainGate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accelerated particles can't melt steel beams.... https://t.co/htdt39jAQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you THREATEN someone because they created a billboard featuring people you don't like, are you still a defender of 'free speech'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing Dave Chapelle's ‘Black Bush’ to Trump: The Fear of a White ‘Black Bush’ https://t.co/HMxQnIu66C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens aim to outlaw political donations from property developers https://t.co/w2LHUcSmMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defenders of green wedge say plan for huge Lyndhurst Coptic Church 'an eyesore' https://t.co/Y8QQDxIeyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tsunami" of crime sees spike in car thefts #Casey #Dandenong https://t.co/vMjgt1uURh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoblePark imam Ibrahim Omerdic charged with conducting marriage ceremony involving child bride https://t.co/8KO3xKH4O9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well...I HAVE had people threaten to stop being my friend because I'm not into HP... https://t.co/ykaj1YuxE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Indigenous community describes lamb ad as "highly offensive" and "disgusting"." https://t.co/u2hGX8UNyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the use of the word 'mole' here https://t.co/z5h1kaIJoX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>