<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please!!! #ImACelebrityAU https://t.co/0D7nJknFSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stan Grant for #abc730 all 2017 https://t.co/HAqC3ZNi8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what? 
Nick Krygios doesn't bother me at all. He's a young man with more talent than he knows what to do with just now #cracksmeup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well duh...and it's the easiest gig James Ashby has had yet (That's saying something) #auspol https://t.co/tdq2ZnF8MM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never know what I want to do.That's probably the most defining thing about my life. I never had ambitions to do specific things"#JohnHurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OZloop one of all time favorite actors John Hurt https://t.co/tNziY0gxYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tlvtoga2015 my grandfather looked like that - young man on the Burma Railway a Japanese prisoner of war. Still inspired by that strength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indecision is a decision https://t.co/bu0pcZx7mv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MarkLatham is another sensational media puppet for the sake of being sensational. Devoid of substance &amp; vision #auspol #tasteless #murdoch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was wondering when someone would get on to these payday lenders #auspol https://t.co/A08FGzyack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle as a sledgehammer Trump is https://t.co/Lstq1DaIgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They sacked a lot of frontline #Centrelink staff at same time spouting new increased vigilence with less staff.… https://t.co/dvz8ogYTPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @smh Conditions are a big part of it. Staff warned about overcrowding plus facilty never really built for current purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not FIT for purpose #Malmsbury https://t.co/jI8CTsngpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see our youth justice system properly preparing the next generation for adult detention system. Just a feed… https://t.co/jB8XopuoIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#malmsbury not fot for purpose. Not secure. Warnings by detention staff ignored https://t.co/HnIrUgceou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo Netherlands! https://t.co/7Xo2vmkLE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel strangely privileged to live in such times. We see the #climatechange What a change.
I just don't understand… https://t.co/Y9gIcBJgoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous misleading headline... compounded by Turnbuĺl's whining about Bill's comment when it's his mate Trump th… https://t.co/xOayxrHOvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#globalgagrule promotes unsafe sex and more abortions, HIV infection and unplanned pregnancy. Interesting "urgent"… https://t.co/yMLIjC8Kil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump forgot you don't actually say that shit out loud again https://t.co/lzTVrNN8Dl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #NSWPremier has subsequently made some great points about not being judgemental.
Hard not to despair on lack of… https://t.co/c9SRW816G4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of very intelligent but understimulated and academically frustrated children also diagnosed with #ADHD then… https://t.co/3t7d8Jq2st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CartwheelPrint you MUST see Elysium. Looks like Murdoch's global vision for our future in a nutshell. From director of District 9 #SciFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you expect nothing less... wow https://t.co/MjiGo04maL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😅 I hear you https://t.co/9gpeHbd950]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CartwheelPrint think it is a belief they can conquer nature.  Why I keep having visions of movie #Elysium all the rich bastards up there 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know Murdoch is playing with our lives. For decades now. But I've never fully grasped why this need in him is so… https://t.co/OwTfvllub8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithKaren1 @Channel7 agree, just an irresponsible grab for ratings, sensational #politics nothing real. Willful support of misinformation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps plan for dealing with #ClimateChange https://t.co/oQijEUOBPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roldschoolcool #PaulRudd has had a much longer entertainment career than I first realised. Not bad either :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about not wasting any time! Well, buckle up I guess #TrumpInauguration https://t.co/3LEAvLKFgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryFallon2 classy aren't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SaveRNMusic 😣 jusr axed #LNP cuts are coming hard and fast to ABC Radio National @MichelleGuthrie https://t.co/IDrzSGkXBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly a child has been lost. Horrific #bourkestreet https://t.co/rc14FTbRVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😉 Treasury Nominee. Funny. Just sly hundred million, clearly a game of worst possible choice to fit the role. Now I… https://t.co/yZpYQAiogR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once stood there, many years ago in quiet contemplation of what might be - never imagined this future… https://t.co/gWTxtUx3Gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no the # LNP kiss of death for #Medicare https://t.co/kw401ENlud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["any law which attempts to say you can criticise any idea as long as it not a religious idea, is a very peculiar la… https://t.co/IIAKWMejey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rationalbitch How indeed. Just happens, no expectations of questions let alone accountability #notmydebt he says! Wow. Make the poor pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about saving money either #ourABC https://t.co/xxe6YJkn9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I hope so! #Fabulous https://t.co/VtqMTRnd1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG!!! Come on. Onus on us to provide "clarification" on #notmydebt which is then completely ignored / rejected? Se… https://t.co/8PhnLXMpBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slsandpet haha. Yes, still got some in my freezer I hate throwing food out but wow. I use word "food" in it's loosest sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slsandpet I like Bega and Bulla products. I don't like "Cara-Mite" icecream (Woolies) Caramel icecream with #vegemite swirls. Just #Wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra @davrosz lol golden parachute. Dont worry #Baird could parachute safely from a snakes asshole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpudBenBean keep forgetting about the anti-protest laws in all that horror - clever, cynical but clever. Thorough too. Assessment? #evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@khtagh @PurePapua 😅 dear god, you're right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core of a dead planet, just throw a rope round it and drag it back. Hmmmm. https://t.co/1TNSsUnxdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canberra still very gusty, bit cooler now...Firefighters gain upper hand on Sutton, Tarago fires  https://t.co/atGjq6wGFD via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateHack1 from today's @canberratimes plus other #Centrelink comments and articles. Nothing at all in the @dailytelegraph . Again. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Preuss if so then the Australian government should fight to have #Assange returned to Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No human contact as callers soon face #centrelink 'virtual' welfare officers" approach allows more #welfarefraud t… https://t.co/D71LG6gphu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you f&amp;@# kidding me? What despotic fear ridden country are we living in? No accountability no questions no #ICAC https://t.co/UbO0f2Oi5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good news today. Pleased to hear it #ChelseaManning https://t.co/Q4wYl0rI47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal #ICAC if you keep wishing it might really happen boys &amp; girls.Cmon wish with me now? "I wish for a federal… https://t.co/iNuINNWL69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_DeWeaver @billshortenmp 1 hour work classifies you as being "employed" yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not agree more! https://t.co/LfNeLUZCbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LennaLeprena @OZloop @slsandpet @Loud_Lass @ComissionerKate @LaLegale @CivilSocietyOz mygov my ass 2.5 million aged pensioners next target]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pensioners and disabled next in line in Centrelink robo-debt campaign https://t.co/AeAGMQSP5Y via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% of course they do #auspol we accept endless sub and associated entities in our company structures. Find a… https://t.co/CAViypT4Vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is about to hit 20 million #twitter followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dodgy tactics involved in getting as many #jobnetwork contracts as possible. No negotiation or questions a simple "… https://t.co/DIG170bCJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My experience also. The incentive is to spend as little as possible on each #jobnetwork client to pocket remaining… https://t.co/UdAxtvMqu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lilllith @elliemail @davrosz @bugwannostra Any initiative /request for training funding are discouraged as they pocket what is NOT spent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canberra declared a "free for all" by outlaw bikie gangs. Damn it - they've been watching the #LNP again #leybuy… https://t.co/heaxx8Gnhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliemail @plabg @Lilllith @davrosz @bugwannostra Haha. Now that's a lot of jobs! So she knows bit about short term jobs &amp; underemployment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["grab all you can while you can" this pretty sums up all that is wrong everywhere #climatewars are coming https://t.co/M70AKmx9py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliemail @plabg @Lilllith @davrosz @bugwannostra Russo's rise started under Howard, was steady under Labor, exploded under Abbott/Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICAC Now! Seriously now federal corruption out of control.Must be reviewed independently. 
NOW!!! https://t.co/1WNpjq5RpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful and mysterious the #humanbrain https://t.co/LunK6z61zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is going on? I go to sleep, wake up and it's what the? John Lewis? .... https://t.co/zftcmKtWUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big whatever really. Probably opposite  of what # Trump asserts now. What does it all mean? We'll soon find out I g… https://t.co/jWk4tBhGML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vjwsydney @AmbientUXr (yep. the irony deserves a little snigger)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helena_Sindelar very sad :( hope she's able to detatch herself - as much as she can, emotionally, from her father's ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End the failed #WarOnDrugs and get real about #addiction https://t.co/y4NFLzhSJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early days too, a lot of #Trump supporters aren't yet aware they lost their health insurance because of a trick - m… https://t.co/nYQXwlHAXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is in USA but this sounds like your #LNP punitive approach to #RenewableEnergy policy. https://t.co/JgOB8mquM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just another extinction we really need these little guys - makes no sense #WeNeedBees https://t.co/lFdKOLLMZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing is the #LNP use the data from the #Centrelink #welfarecard to screw you even more. Bravo. https://t.co/SrKAxWAYmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha no one thought that #datamining would be used to their benefit did they? #Centrelink https://t.co/SrKAxWAYmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrownSquirrel 😅 and yet I'd much prefer/trust Roberta Williams as a neighbour to Pauline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well duh... even a small "comment" would require tiny bit of backbone &amp; leadership #auspol is as depleted as… https://t.co/282gYVpHw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought #OneNation trending cause Pauline wants #Centrelink recipients to provide photo &amp; fingerprints re… https://t.co/GI2qFJK6WA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#putyourblazersonforjulie from New York 😅 https://t.co/1QCExjBhFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth a view if you want to see a blatant example of #WorkplaceBullying #putyourblazersonforjulie Quite incredible… https://t.co/J24E3jtiGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not fit for purpose" not just security, very overcrowded, lacking basic conditions and remanded children there too… https://t.co/HivtnrwC33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he should give clemency for all petty drug offences #WarOnDrugs a farce just to supply an ineffective inefficien… https://t.co/tX7FUlFoSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linked to heat &amp; no aircon /airflow. Staff were expecting it. Very poor conditions for inmates make their jobs hard… https://t.co/P0RSa5JV6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politijo noticed we will sort out "this distraction...and that's ALL it is - a distraction"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if this cut applies to those with recent abnormal results - who should have more frequent testing to try avo… https://t.co/L78mlmqmM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamcather1 I hear your point. Perhaps no sane person could do that - he wants to die &amp; be a KKK martyr which is another problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamcather1 yeah, not sure any illness would've worked cause #DylanRoof was "I'm not crazy. I just really wanted to kill black people"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😨 This can't be good! https://t.co/LOIGBtL5Me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DylannRoof sacked his lawyers who tried an insanity defence &amp; represented himself. He's not sorry. 22 years old -… https://t.co/oE2uKIcOJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Left_of_Labor I don't think #LNP have any intention of being reelected next throw. They're waging an ideological war for permanent changes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Left_of_Labor really not sure which half is worse! Sacked #LNP or looking at what's left 😨 no wonder we've been screwed every day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed! Stan Grant please  #abc730 https://t.co/bg6aUOCaPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateHack1 Point being, if #SussanLey struggles to remember travel details, events &amp; purpose thereof I'm sure Sarina Russo can help her out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genaro_zapico @realDonaldTrump Yes haha. I was just saying that to someone...I think #Trump was drunk tweeting last night]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>