<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @lisamurkowski and @SenatorCollins!!!! https://t.co/bYkpuPXMcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila Amen to that :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kellyannepolls 'post-feminism' is a con @HuffPostBlog https://t.co/KqFkhTbFci via @HuffPostWomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping my guard up since the SCOTUS pick is tonight and the national prayer breakfast in Thursday. There is a trap… https://t.co/fqnwL7CvRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hated saying that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bs_mccoy @TomiLahren It may not be a TOTAL Muslim ban, but it is still a Muslim ban if you ban people from 7 MUSLIM countries lol. #facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bs_mccoy @TomiLahren yes, it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uniformsdeluxe @AaronLarios No, I said they voted for racism. :) Thanks for playing though ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all you #alternativefacts pushers... https://t.co/irJgkF7kTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Says the one who had a youtuber thrown and beat up at a party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Well considering your leader Trump is constantly on the defensive..... lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren But the 7 ARE Muslim dominated countries. Logic is hard for you, I know. It's okay. You're forgiven, except not really. #bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me and @NPAlive &amp; sign a statement opposing President Trump's EO on immigrants and refugees. https://t.co/AiTMR7mVvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff :-( I'm very scared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uniformsdeluxe @AaronLarios Hint: If you have to start a sentence with "I'm not racist", your argument is off to a bad start lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChazBono You tell him Chaz!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila but it is a ban on Muslims from those 7 countries, which are predominantly muslim countries. Call it a partial ban, it's a ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila I love hearing your thoughts on the view but I have to disagree today. It may not be a full Muslim ban (cont.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just donated $20 to @ACLU. Best money I have ever spent. #fightback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @FoxNewsSunday And I wonder how you still have a job with all the lies you tell. Or as you say "alternative facts".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @seanspicer: You realize that the muslim ban would not have prevented the San Bernadino shooting.... right? #factsmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyD The Muslim Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronDunbar4 @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite It is true though lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite You. Again, thanks for playing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite People of color cant be racist against white people. Thanks for playing though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite No but federal judges are :) Thank you  @ACLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Midterms always hurt the party in power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Actually 2 when Trump drags down the republicans down ballot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite 37%, that's all i have to say lol. Have fun with the protests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennisrperth @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite I will because they bought the BS from a billionaire elitist lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Again conspiracy theories lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite And then picked a bunch of corrupt billionaires to run the government. lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Hence why in his first week Trump has a 37% approval rating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite No one is denying that she had her flaws. She was still far better than Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFretired2009 @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Actually it is lol. He played to peoples fears and they bought it hook line and sinker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bs_mccoy @Mediaite Ok so now I know you're nothing but a conspiracy theorist lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bs_mccoy @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Again alternative facts lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bs_mccoy @PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite No, I voted for Hillary Clinton. Again spewing alternative facts lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not being like anything lol You looked past his comments, his racist comments, sexist ones, sexual assault comments, etc. lol Not me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite no lol a vote for Hillary was a vote for Hillary. Enjoy your "alternative facts" though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PixyMisa @AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite Nope, I voted for Hillary, but thanks for playing though :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronLarios @JedediahBila @Mediaite He won because of racism, sexism, and lies of making this country great when it already is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila If it annoys you, you can turn the channel to something else lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Actually islamic extremism has killed many more fellow Muslims than Christians. #realfacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Says the person pissing off every country in the world.... #hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls you should truly be embarrassed for how you were with Chris Wallace. I hope your kids were not watching. #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnn @msnbc why are you not covering the refugee protest in DC??? #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls How does it feel knowing @POTUS lost his first court battle? #WeAreTheResistance #nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @aaron_rva If only you were smart enough to not get yourself arrested when you try to embarrass people lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump and you lost!! Lol #WeAreTheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes you should also accept the fact that you lost in court lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are #theresistence. Take that @POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iverson7502 Confirmed!!! https://t.co/3iNNmvUpzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading that the Muslim ban executive order has been stayed in court. Does anyone know if this is true? Link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's just be honest here, the #MarchForLife is a farce just like being #ProLife is. #justadmitit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMAROSA Correction from @TheView, you are NOW a Republican. You were fired from the Clinton White House as a Democrat. #factsmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHITE WOMEN Elected Trump "NOT WOMEN" https://t.co/lEkKX5D6S5 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress: Require Trump to prove he has no Dakota Access Pipeline conflicts of interest: #NoDAPL https://t.co/Qs7Xtfk6QK @moveon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you claim to be #ProLife yet you support the death penalty, stripping benefits to the poor, etc. you are not pro life, you are pro birth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Disconnected WH Line, so Bernie's Team Set Up Way to Call the White House Satellite Locations! https://t.co/jzxfDVNcmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright So we're just gonna continue with the Bernie bashing instead of recognizing that Hillary had her own flaws leading to a loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright @afrthnkr916 Or you know, Democrats could keep fighting for same day registration which Republicans stifled in a lot of areas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright @afrthnkr916 This is why though the Democratic party moving forward should keep pushing for same day registration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FishFunSun @sunny That is also a choice, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if the people marching tomorrow in the #MarchForLife realize they are actually pro-choice.... #justathought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunny I would argue that you are indeed pro choice. Choosing to keep the baby and raise it is a choice, just like abortion and adoption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila you're story on being the crazy one made me bust out laughing at work and now people are giving me weird looks lol thanks. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Nah, we just like shutting you down lol. You're all talk and no action. You must have small hands like @realDonaldTrump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMarriottANC Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls And any poll would show that alternative facts is not a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @FLOTUS @IvankaTrump And common sense shows that alternative facts are not a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Good luck getting that money appropriated from somewhere else LOL #keepdreaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TherealTaraji deserved an #OscarNoms for @HiddenFigures. That's all I'm going to say. #snub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @EW and yet you could barely get anyobe to come in person lol. The white space is real with this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls the IRS said he can release any taxes not under audit. Lol. Nice try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @PressSec so basically he lied the other day about rhe inauguration lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My closest Swing District is VA-10, won by only 23,079 votes. Find yours and help swing the House left in 2018: https://t.co/cenUCbmaJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls That's awesome. Though that was a pivot to not answer his ACTUAL question. No such thing as alternate facts. Just facts. lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreeIngles I'd watch that show though lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright got the gun legally and then later went on a shooting spree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright Im not arguing that either. I'm arguing the premise of holding a manufacturer accountable instead of a person who (cont.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRichWilkins @SallyAlbright im not arguing that. Im arguing that in her previous scenario she gave no accountability to the shooter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright you didnt bring up the actual shooter once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright and then months later go on a rampage, then according to you i should have no accountability and it falls on the company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright no about gun manufacturers. You seem hell bent on holding manufacturers accountable. If i buy a gun legally (cont.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright You still haven't responded to my response to your argument about guns and Bernie lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRichWilkins Same. Whoever wins I just want them to stomp the winner in the AFC lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRichWilkins I like Atlanta to win, but personally im happy with either winning representing in the super bowl :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melzy71 @TaraSetmayer or it could just be because a) not that many people wanted to come or b) they couldn't afford it. I bet the former.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump i guess @KellyannePolls told you to put your man pants on and suck it up lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @KellyannePolls: there is no such thing as "alternate facts"... just facts lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilaGraceRose @PPact says the woman whod rather see the mother die than have a life saving abortion. Sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm one of the #7in10forRoe because a woman should be able to make a choice that is best for HER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They did. You lost the popular vote by 3 million votes ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The same ones you shamed publicly just a few weeks ago lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not true at all lol But thanks for playing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does @CNN have only one woman on a panel about the #WomensMarch ?  Something is not right here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching @seanspicer trying to spin the inauguration to make it seem better than it was made me feel embarrassed for him lol. #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillanBoyce @kayleighmcenany "Siri, what is ISIS"? LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany Yet he provided no specifics as to how lol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>