<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect wet Sunday afternoon activities: building lego while listening to @clattner_llv on @atpfm https://t.co/RI8MKuSbix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in America do you have a cup holder in your trolley for your festive Starbucks, after Christmas #plusclub https://t.co/1RdYhiZzGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last Peppermint Mocha of the holiday season :( https://t.co/8bby88azuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @cooksimo1 showing me Portrait Mode I am the proud new owner of an iPhone 7 Plus, matte black #plusclub https://t.co/IjXcUboYmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hackerssidekick I'm going to have to use that photo out of context at some point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When can I start teaching Hazel ruby @nicktmro? I'm guessing older than 6 months :( https://t.co/6oIQUCpLBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hapiben what did you think of the course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hapiben yay, that course was great!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro https://t.co/JHq8kjutuA gives me a 404. Hyping anticipation or bug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro yeah that jumped out at me as well. Well done Apple!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ewok_13 Typical spelling mistake from @DomPost https://t.co/rXnrA8z7Y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed The New Glif: A Tripod Mount for Smartphones, Redesigned on @Kickstarter https://t.co/X0LyvMtRGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1amstudios isn't he just fulfilling the 'everything must be bigger in America' stereotype?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone have a 45W MacBookAir MagSafe ("L" style) adapter lying around? Apple wants $150 for a new one ... https://t.co/sQwefXq5I1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status: behind the wheel of a ~450hp 1968 Corvette Stingray. My clutch leg is now sore! https://t.co/My4Wxwj4ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro sorry. Jokes are so much funnier when you need to explain them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro why? is there something special it does? I see tvOS app for streaming also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro I was thinking it was too early for WWDC. Did you or @cooksimo1 win a ticket to WWDC in the lottery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nullfry unfortunately not sorry. If you don't have access to your email address anymore there is nothing they can do :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nullfry I don't have the password for the account or access to the (old) email address anymore. I've contacted support, will let you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nullfry hey! Yeah I don't use that handle anymore. I'll change it and let you grab it ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caseyliss That's so cool! I love hearing these stories, people can make any change they want. I went Java -&gt; Rails and never looked back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro it it not weird that we have Siri on the phone but not on AppleTV? What's stopping it? Doesn't seem to be technical? Maybe load?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro can you ask them when Siri is coming to NZ Apple TV users? Love my AppleTV but I know it could be awesomer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Behind the Lens: 2015 Year in Photographs” by @WhiteHouse photographer Pete Souza https://t.co/0UgHZXQ79N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghammadi I'm trying to get to @webstock too. We should catch up for dinner!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater I will always fondly remember "As a developer I want Solr4 to be stable so I can sleep at night"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater so, 'development' then :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouDoCrew at least there were pastries! https://t.co/ogZ6Wz248B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro I'm about to buy one the moment that @plexapp is released. Can you have a go when it comes out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloud66 What user permission do I need to 'Add an SSH key' when deploying to my own server?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the 'Hail Mary' of the Rails world `spring stop` saves me again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwgnz yeah I noticed that too. Not worth it even if the plans are cheaper (no VDSL fee)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I look to backup my 100GB photos, a new provider comes out. First Amazon Cloud Drive, now Google Nearline https://t.co/G5RxQg1EOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's nice to be back in NZ "Spark will have *a* technician on standby at the stadium to monitor the network". Just 1? http://t.co/yzx3jxdZOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater Least. Comforting. Announcement. Ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hackerssidekick @nicktmro it's also on the menu in San Fran. I'm scared to have it ruin flat whites for me but I'll try it &amp; report back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every set of lights since I got on has been red and my Newlands bus has accelerated through them all. This should be a fun ride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 4 spare (free) tickets to the basketball tonight at 7pm if anyone is interested? http://t.co/dVJ9dVAA07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newportandy "at 3AM in the morning. You want to be able to roll out of the bed, grab your partners, and develop the idea" is not a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imyke you should check out the recently updated @memrise iOS app. Huge update, soooo much better than when you tried it last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghammadi Wow "Human error is a consequence of other things. Never a cause" is prophetic. I'm LOVING these drawings btw, keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM I also don't always listen in chronological order as there are podcasts my wife will put up with and some she won't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM I would like to see it back if possible. It was nice to easily find podcasts I had fallen asleep to the night before with timer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Ahhh. Aso, I see you removed the 'Play Status' filter from the Playlist settings. Why was that? Is it coming back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Awesome, yep it's back up. What was it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM I (and everyone I've talked to) are getting HTTP 503 errors from https://t.co/aTrWKxxz06. I presume you know about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see that #genderstereotypes are being drilled into college kids for the beep test http://t.co/Tv7GmsDEqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hackerssidekick @mojocoffeejapan yeah it was totally as good as @mojocoffeenz. Also surprise Anzac biscuit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to backstreets of Tokyo to find a decent flat white from @mojocoffeejapan. Totally worth the adventure http://t.co/rrCfO7jJnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weirdly alienating experience at Tokyo Apple Store - all the watches are behind glass. Also thin MacBook is thin http://t.co/CnQNkm8Jfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrGrazy @fogonwater @benedictaluan epic! Hopefully it has been simplified so much it needed to be redone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan in a nutshell - amazing breakfast sets, Shinkansen, wide city-scapes and unintelligible signs http://t.co/qRULHP6rCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the awesome food and street-scene in Seoul http://t.co/PzRarxIbzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am now in Tokyo, along with 4 million people taking the Tokyo underground daily. That, and eating European pastries http://t.co/MijRE6PsS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwibankNZ iOS8 and TouchID have been out for ages, when is the Kiwibank app going to support unlock via TouchID?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlishaDaya awesome post, it was fun building the app. Made any progress since?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater @Sereeena Look at this little internet thing bringing people together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sereeena The cartographer/map nerd I was talking about last night is @fogonwater who works at the National Library/DigitalNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent 15 mins trying to work out why my javascript function wasn't working. Turns out I was missing ye olde 'return'. Thanks #ruby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found the perfect coding soundtrack: Miyazaki/Studio Ghibli playlist: http://t.co/DK1MKl80rT にほんご]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@four_seven Wow I thought people were going the other way. Is unicorn not web scale?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlishaDaya I've been looking for that chocolate milk for ages. People literally run across the supermarket for the 2 mins it's in stock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@four_seven This is Randy Pausch Last Lecture I was talking about. Long but well well well worth it https://t.co/d5SNM1zMNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveharris I would really like your account name if you aren't using it anymore. Would you think about giving it up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlishaDaya You just now need to hook it up to Heroku/Ninefold and Codeship.io and you will away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlishaDaya So excited to submit a pull request to you! https://t.co/k5RZKSExED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anthony_Mace @Railscamp_NZ @four_seven @AlishaDaya I love the internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Railscamp_NZ Do you an email address for Anthony (sorry don't know his last name) from #rcnz5?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rcnz5, the only conference I've been to where speakers and attendees are treated the same and everyone goes swimming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlishaDaya @AlishaDaya the fact that you are now doing hipster coffee should be enough for Wellingtonians and Melbournians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigitalNZ do you know the work plan tables get cut off on mobile (iPhone 5S)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow this really is living in the future https://t.co/QwCxHjeLmV #2factorauthentication]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater That is amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put myself down on the speaking list at @Railscamp_NZ. Self, no backing out now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having an awesome time in Christchurch with @Ewok_13. Gondola, tram, Hagley Park &amp; #hipstercoffee at #restartmall http://t.co/MFxo0GBlAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds Air is the only airline in NZ which does impromptu whale watching on the way #summer http://t.co/VC0wseJGk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater agreed, it's been on fire recently. Wish there was a better way to surface stuff on http://t.co/oAN3YsnuWy for non-nerds to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benedictaluan you are most welcome. Chef has a special place in my heart #nerdlove. Also @getssj is taking me out to lunch on Friday so win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that a guy going 8 laps of Taupo's 160km has completed his first lap in 5h34m. That's my target time for one lap :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put my money where my mouth is, I donated to help make a second season of @serial http://t.co/iKKDipqms7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this guy loves @serial so much he is going to be murdered http://t.co/5aX3iY6t49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro Wow I had no idea that you had 30 mobile devs, that's crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlascarides I have a great little D-Link DNS323. 2 drive bays, gigabit, and it hackable so mine runs a full Debian install from USB drive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater @serial there has got to be something up with Jay's story. I wanna know so badly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater we are listening to @serial and are totally and utterly hooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish Ruby was a complied language #thingsineverthoughtidsay #refactoringwithoutspecs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater @mlascarides Sorry I had a lot of spammers replying when I hash tagged things ages ago so protected tweets....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlascarides This is amazing ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36% smaller Rails memory footprint through Benchmarking http://t.co/VKpCLQAJ6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is Why Australians Hate Starbucks http://t.co/vP1iP07z4z #coffeesnob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow Ha awesome, my brother @1amstudios works at Riverbed. Pintrest's offices looked super sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Railscamp_NZ Do we need to be there *before* 4pm for the bus? Like will a flight landing at 4pm be too late?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really inspiring hearing people leave jobs to follow their passion, the Relay.fm podcast network. Congrats @imyke http://t.co/eFXYOtdkrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm I wonder when Yosemite and iOS8 were released this month ... http://t.co/W31evQLbRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwgnz Wow view looks sweet! Have a great time ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow You really couldn't make this stuff up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dryglue http://t.co/1Is8B1eqV0 http://t.co/hfOHqIYVLV http://t.co/RpHVnKimvw http://t.co/9M89VIgllf &amp; pure comedy: http://t.co/zF7K8j9WZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater Re-watched Game of Thrones season 2-4 over the weekend, I recognise some landscape!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater @DigitalNZ Ohhh wow, would love to catch up when you're back in Wellington]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>