<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesSmith1001 is he as good as his dad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had a look at the womens AFL they're just as unco as their male https://t.co/sz0kAEaA2O, what a terrible fucking game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestSydneySport AFL invented women's sport.No other sport has ever had a female competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the egg man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Goatman62 @RubinReport all good. I agree, it's over the top &amp; somehow all this violence is his fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Goatman62 @RubinReport of a black man being a white supremacist. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Goatman62 @RubinReport i think you have misunderstood my joke.what they accuse Milo of being reminds me of the Dave Chappelle joke 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Goatman62 @RubinReport is this Milo? https://t.co/StWlqYIYGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewRules333 @ttowntrumper79 @MMFlint @nytimes ha ha ha sure they are. https://t.co/r3a1doFOp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi it would be out of control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@singgenberg @latimes STFU you whiney bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrownTweet @nswpolice @VictoriaPolice that bloke is a grub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mj_lynch the most shocking thing in that article is that there's a game plan.the game looks like seagulls fighting over a chip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@almostjingo @UCBerkeley i wonder if these pussies would take on a Bikers for Trump rally? #doubtit #cowards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Booze__Hound @shitno1says__ especially with Fitzsimons on the show. @shitno1says__]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcrf @Kieza_cmail he's a boxer? Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kieza_cmail @mattcrf how old is that kid? He looks 15.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strandleper @DebraMessing @UCBerkeley I'll go with idiot lemming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegoRomero @neworderguy @DebraMessing now that's worth protesting against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegoRomero @DebraMessing she has a show?who is this has been?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho oh shit.that podcast with KO friggin rocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heritagexiii @LadiesWhoLeague it's true. AFL actually invented women's sport.just ask them they'll tell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennajameson l bet the MSM don't even report on this, it doesn't suit their agenda of Trump bashing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with Barba going to RU he'll walk straight into the Wallabies and be their player of the year. #hewontbemissed #shitgame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheParraEels Peni should buy himself a lottery ticket. he's very lucky not to be sacked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barba: "Mate, I've got to look after my kids and my family. They're my first option."
he should've thought about that before snorting coke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7NewsSydney Goodbye and don't come back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarksTristan @GunbusterDDG41 @Todd_Greenberg  i've said before and i'll say it again, Greenberg is out of his depth. #timetogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GunbusterDDG41 i don't think Todd will be happy with that comment. what a grub. Goodbye and don't come back. #fuckwit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mj_lynch @FinancialReview what a great article. No BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[does anyone really think @Todd_Greenberg will do anything about Barba?Look at their history together. Greenberg is a very weak leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint you should watch this, you may learn something. https://t.co/z54IDhCGHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcrf the app is garbage.i got it last year and had massive issues with it and i got refund.if you can get foxtel back do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrownTweet @Tenash921 @BBL I'm sure the @BBL can name their price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint please tell me again what BO done for Flint's water besides hand out bottled water? #YouLost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint so what you're saying is that Trump has done as much for Flint's water as BO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebundyeel this guy would be good https://t.co/ohHenZZmjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebundyeel very silly.Maybe he thought he was playing for the Broncos and all he would cop was a slap on the wrists. 😄 #noevidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebundyeel unless he has a really good reason for not informing the club i have a feeling he'll be shown the door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OneNewsPolitic as if @realDonaldTrump would give a shit if they went on strike. I hope they do. #outoftouchdickheads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simo_393 @Derby71 @NRL of course they didn't cover it up and if you believe that i have a bridge to sell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simo_393 @Derby71 @NRL Stewart has treated very harsly by that idiot Gallop.I don't blame for telling him to get F ed after the GF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simo_393 @Derby71 @NRL not at all.nothing was hidden from the NRL with SKD matter.the broncs have form when it comes to cover ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simo_393 @Derby71 if there is nothing to hide the club should release the CCTV footage and why has the @NRL put him on a booze ban?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@butch4682 @Todd_Greenberg wouldn't be the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo_Blo2014 how do you know he doesn’t?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dablueroo @ReadingThePlay @Todd_Greenberg of course there's proof,why do you think the club owner wouldn't hand over the cctv footage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phillutton78 what a load of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgejkollias @Todd_Greenberg how does that work? i'm sure Sailor got 2 years for the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgejkollias @Todd_Greenberg what a great decision.good to see his doing what's best for the supporters. him and Grant need to go ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgejkollias @Todd_Greenberg 100% George. the game is going nowhere fast with this bloke in charge.what has done for the game? Nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if Roberts has done nothing wrong why is there a booze ban? @Todd_Greenberg 
decisions like this is why the game gets bashed in the media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FakeDavidSmith @RLPlayers because @Todd_Greenberg has NFI and he didn't want to upset the broncos too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Todd_Greenberg and the @NRL are as weak as piss.If Roberts was playing for any other club he would have been suspended or fired. #joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love test match RL i suggest you turn over to Fox Sports 2 now. What a game. #austvpoms1986]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee those Pommies were dirty bastards back in the day.if they played like that today they'd have 3 players on the field. #austvpoms1986]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oAnqx1kp88 @RitaPanahi I'm not sure if you've seen this or not but it's a must see. Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oAnqx1kp88 @PMOnAir you need to show this.Big Joe rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching Aust v The Poms from 1986 on Fox Sports 2 and The Moose is commentating.Some legends of RL in action. Great stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandylanceley @MrBrownTweet right, thanks. That makes sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandylanceley @MrBrownTweet what i don't understand, why was the US funding planned parenthood in other countries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennajameson it looks like she's wearing a ham sub costume. #subwaymarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods time to start a mens march for free razors. #freerazorsmarch #mensmarch #whoswithme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that's looks like a soccer game. https://t.co/rpqZvARdwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi @TheSafestSpace how long has this being going on?I could've "shaved" a fortune. I'll leave now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the real issue of today is, why are the new episodes of the Simpsons so bad?  #Simpsonsmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julia_goo_lia @alicevictoria19 seriously, what are you doing out of the kitchen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't care less who won the election but it's so much fun winding up the anti Trump people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julia_goo_lia @alicevictoria19 thanks toots, now get back in the kitchen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voodoorock @tater_chips  wear wood i bee wifout pople cerrecting me gramer and spealing. Fanks agian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @thebundyeel that wouldn't be the only thing she's blown. zing. I'll leave now. 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricGrotheJnr @mattcrf it's great plus it gives me something to do in the off season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicevictoria19 who let you out of the kitchen to tweet? Back you go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt lets hope there all marching straight to the kitchen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great. Enjoy. https://t.co/ADPOm64FX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilieautumn @WestSydneySport hopefully you're marching straight to the kitchen. 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrownTweet @MeganBrutonOZ @realDonaldTrump and so he should.The people of Sydney have spoken. FMD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrownTweet @MeganBrutonOZ ha ha ha I'm sure @realDonaldTrump will be shaking in his boots about that protest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandylanceley these people are scum, taking pot shots at 10 year old kid. #grub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmHarleyShow @EmRusciano @harleybreen @2DayFM Sydney's newest show from Melbourne. No thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parracookie @MMFlint why is that old lesbian so upset?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi what has attacking  a Starbucks got to do with @realDonaldTrump ? Fucking idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint good lord. Please STFU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLeyonhjelm you piece of trash. #scumbag #grub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mj_lynch @realDonaldTrump i don't think they do either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[are these celebrity wankers ever going to stop whinging about @realDonaldTrump ? it's getting boring. STFU please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Todd_Greenberg @mikebairdMP @NRL please follow him Todd and make sure Grant goes with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seaeaglenut @IpswichTitans @Todd_Greenberg @ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seaeagle16 @mj_lynch @ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland @brisbroncos they sure are. @Todd_Greenberg doesn't have the balls to question them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seaeagle16 @mj_lynch @ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland @brisbroncos oh i forgot, they don't have a cap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seaeagle16 @mj_lynch @ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland @brisbroncos i wonder if what they've paid will be counted as part of their salary cap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simo_393 @ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland if there's nothing to hide the CCTV footage should be released.Until that happens he looks guilty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland Roberts should be stood down until this is cleared up.This is a cover up worthy of an AFL club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Thoroughbreds must of sorted this out .I'm sure @Todd_Greenberg is happy with this as now he won't have to upse… https://t.co/2YQl3E73z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anthonyqld how much did the Broncos pay?it's a joke.if he's done nothing wrong they should release the CCTV footage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GunbusterDDG41 @Todd_Greenberg @NRL there is no way he'll talk about that because it's not going to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoundohWaz @dailytelegraph @NRL @Todd_Greenberg I'm sure those grubs will find a way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny seeing celebs lose their minds over Trump being elected.They're unhinged.After Saturday I'm sure their h… https://t.co/DIRqHWLF5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRichman dude, your Western Suburbs Magpies rugby league jersey rocks. #represent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mj_lynch @tensporttv @Channel9 way too much AFL talk.i don't think they realise half the country doesn't care about AFL.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>