<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@piguanaSue Isn't always true that just when you stop looking for something, it turns up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haiti’s “linguistic apartheid” violates children’s rights and hampers development https://t.co/S8O6NMqcWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists to Trump: Torture doesn’t work https://t.co/kJVPAlVkk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump refugee order dashes hopes of Iraqis who helped the U.S. https://t.co/XDZLXYR3p9 via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent suggestions in this thread. https://t.co/Xm0XH5extX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting now! https://t.co/bCJUcbfKDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It can be hard for scientists to hear "you're wrong"  #shrcoalition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions that meet the scientist's priorities may not meet community priorities #shrcoalition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key to effective collaborations with communities: respect the community's knowledge #shrcoalition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suren Moodliar: data must be viewed as a tool for social mobilization, especially in current political environment #shrcoalition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second winner of environmental prize killed months after Berta Cáceres death https://t.co/pKVHApYb2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Group Launches to Help Activists https://t.co/zbDPvjyVJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transitional justice works but can negatively impact mental health of participants https://t.co/xhSYal2IvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know? You can support both science and human rights with one gift to @AAAS_SRHRL https://t.co/MzWyu46JjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially social &amp; behavioral science. Compared to gathering empirical evidence about people, rocket science is ea… https://t.co/pMTkk33eWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwfrick Anytime! We're always here doing our thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This didn't happen by accident... https://t.co/eZEv20GB3l https://t.co/Tz3ol5ezm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video - @omctorg celebrates Human Rights Defenders worldwide https://t.co/9JTwxNfkDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Colombia, Turning a Peace Deal Into Reality https://t.co/RDqjtZ6MM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dec 7 Join @AAAS_SRHRL for tech, design, innovation + human rights (and breakfast too!) https://t.co/b4Yw9KH6ll #HumanRightsDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citizen science efforts should be scaled up - via @SciDevNet https://t.co/BypPmViwWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's a sound cannon? Fact sheet from @P4HR https://t.co/Pj8P3NJm66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where else would a bear dog live but Texas? https://t.co/UDdg9NVFhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10/25 Human Rights Documentation Toolkit launch @AAAS_SRHRL Register soon, filling up fast! https://t.co/lkdMtXdOnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10/13 Webinar - Chemists Contributing to Human Rights: Enhancing Research, Teaching and Global Impact with @jefftoney &amp; @AmerChemSociety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of Money Hinders Effort to ID Remains of Migrants Near the Border
https://t.co/OHR4x5Pdjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlights several threads discussed at #shrcoalition meeting on #bigdata &amp; #humanrights https://t.co/c087nzcbUH https://t.co/WpCW4hWZRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional medicine for modern times: Facts and figures https://t.co/lFLmgkFw2c via @SciDevNet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tools for talking about #science &amp; #humanrights on campus: https://t.co/UNcZPEvBe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey shakes up universities as coup fallout continues https://t.co/4byLJPIt7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Who is getting left behind in the internet revolution? https://t.co/m47PEVjCFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nominate a scientist/engineer who has made an exceptional contribution to society - deadline Sept 1 https://t.co/q7Md1VORsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 90 companies are to blame for most climate change, this 'carbon accountant' says https://t.co/R99N7gqMnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katherine Johnson, the NASA Mathematician Who Advanced Human Rights with a Slide Rule and Pencil https://t.co/zE1Ky01ofY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Result of fantastic work by members of #shrcoalition https://t.co/kLn1iCzibb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sept 1 deadline: AAAS Award for Scientific Freedom and Responsibility https://t.co/5XpeJXPd45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Venezuela, #humanrights advocates want reliable socioeconomic data https://t.co/LRO92HlLCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applying machine learning to human rights documentation https://t.co/pUIePNb7x8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cascheller I'm afraid it is possible that could actually be the same person...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science can ease human rights effects of climate change https://t.co/OakIblsMCI #shrcoalition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @openRights_oD for publishing my article on scientists &amp; engineers as #humanrights partners https://t.co/IT1bgGchcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final agenda is now online! https://t.co/Z4eqyOdLX9 #climatechange #humanrights https://t.co/EF97GUlyX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech for peace: Facts and figures (cites work by @AAAS_GTP) https://t.co/izOyRDmgxh from @SciDevNet @giorgiawired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy getting ready for #climatechange &amp; #humanrights on 7/25. See you there? https://t.co/b7sfnz7k4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN Human Rights Expert to Visit Baton Rouge, Ferguson, and Convention Host Cities https://t.co/Bl37d0K3hy via @aclu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for building #science + #humanrights partnerships https://t.co/fTQVM3awtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her record as a basketball coach would have been an amazing lifetime achievement by itself, but Pat Summit was so much more that that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does #climatechange have to do with #humanrights? Join the discussion July 25 https://t.co/b7sfnz7k4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for the 25 July #shrcoalition mtg! Videos &amp; reports on #climatechange &amp; #humanrights https://t.co/b7sfnz7k4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Medical Association Gets Tougher on Gun Control https://t.co/gvJJx29wTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change Hits Conflict Zones Harder: Syria Case Study https://t.co/0vv8rCufX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian biometric project raises critical human rights concerns https://t.co/jxRxtwLtgp via @SciDevNet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to do more about climate change? Register for July 25-26 #shrcoalition mtg on #ClimateChange and #HumanRights: https://t.co/Z4eqyOdLX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True for #humanrights too https://t.co/ImfMWQ85Th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scienceactivist The coalition is looking at some new working methods. We should chat. Not well suited for 140 characters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scienceactivist Thanks for the suggestion. Always welcome new ideas for #shrcoalition meetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standard for war crimes is objective, conduct of other nations not relevant, says @lenrubenstein. https://t.co/DSsC0K6Glp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too! Tracked EVERY hurricane on the map on the side of a Publix bag #FloridaKids #ThinkLikeAScientist @mc_longshore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speakers emphasize importance of local communities leading decision-making in these projects #scienceforsyria https://t.co/lRre8P1y2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continue the conversation on climate change &amp; conflict July 25 https://t.co/b7sfnz7k4W #scienceforsyria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussion about how scientists can contribute to these policy conversations #ScienceForSyria https://t.co/MEDaCQ7Jp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ColinKelley2 says climate change puts additional pressure on fragile states, increases vulnerability #scienceforsyria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PeterGleick: water conflicts btwn nations prevented by international law but those norms not as useful inside countries #scienceforsyria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting now: talks on water, climate change, and conflict #ScienceForSyria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow #ScienceForSyria today to catch the highlights from @AAASFellowships symposium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial crisis causes IACHR to suspend hearings, massive staff layoffs https://t.co/SYQuB2hoja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Documenting Torture: Doctors Search For New Ways To Gather Evidence https://t.co/S0VMqZBiqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students! Just a few days left to enter #STEM &amp; #humanrights essay competition https://t.co/tnurVbQcfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Guidelines for building partnerships with scientists for #humanrights projects https://t.co/fTQVM3awtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lancet study says indigenous people in both rich and poor countries miss out on vital services https://t.co/bmHEPhkpye via @SciDevNet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUD offers $2 million in grants for research to reduce housing-related health hazards https://t.co/XGZxJ0dRUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter by May 22! Science &amp; Human Rights Coalition 2016 Student Essay Competition https://t.co/tnurVbQcfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join AAAS &amp; help us achieve critical mass needed to champion changes this world needs! 20% off membership here: https://t.co/VSkLCpIVAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidence-Based Research Contributes to Human Rights Work:  https://t.co/kHlSHdSVvU via @aaas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran: Imprisoned Physicist’s Cancer Care in Jeopardy via @HRW  https://t.co/tcna7N9pn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More research into treatment of torture survivors &amp; increased "scientific vigor" needed https://t.co/2M5DS0mZRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @hrbrief on the new website! https://t.co/XlxMP6FJbl #humanrights news in an easy to access format]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow 1pmET: #humanrights to water &amp; sanitation - Flint isn't the only place this is an urgent issue @HuRiSc  https://t.co/B20lVTZx4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New study: No differences in child health outcomes between same-sex and different-sex parent households https://t.co/2OsByykvAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone asked me just last week if text analysis of comments is possible. Question answered!  https://t.co/u01eeZ0HDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AAAS Joins Call for Federal Gun Research:  https://t.co/4G7z3LK1rA via @aaas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impacted Communities Testify on US Water Crises At Human Rights Hearing https://t.co/w3RxpLT4gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students: Host a #STEM &amp; #HumanRights event with our campus toolkit https://t.co/BDHt1M4pNJ @AAAS_SRHRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish scholar who eluded arrest describes 'witch hunt' https://t.co/kH8MauchWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know if your #humanrights projects are working? Learn how to use indicators to measure impact @AAAS_SRHRL https://t.co/hKMUgBMVT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science and Harm in Human Rights Cases: Preventing the Revictimization of Families of the Disappeared https://t.co/T2iwvNHwCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free scientific support for human rights projects https://t.co/KorS4Y0LMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reboot Gitmo for U.S.-Cuba research diplomacy https://t.co/HwYNRCnuVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Violence data: what human rights practitioners need to know https://t.co/HKFCVoxdjX via @openDemocracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mar 31 at @AAAS_SRHRL - Using indicators to monitor human rights interventions https://t.co/8jLv8KxRf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academics Jailed For Signing Petition via @HRW  https://t.co/uAloTmG9Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March 30: Join @AAAS_SRHRL for "Science and Policy of Marijuana" https://t.co/77rc4hf9KZ  #NeuroSeries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions or problems voting on #PrimaryDay? Call @866OURVOTE (1-866-687-8683). You'll be connected to someone w/ info for your state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why African scientists must be champions for democracy https://t.co/k6mcN3YhYM via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where young scientists gather, there must be discussions about democracy  and human rights..." https://t.co/E9hUz7bIEs via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent case studies of human rights + data challenges.  https://t.co/KJTIrckLll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call for Entries: #SHRCoalition Science &amp; Human Rights Student Essay Competition https://t.co/tnurVbQcfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SciDip editor in chief E. William Colglazier on role of science capacity building in #SDGs https://t.co/JV89f6R3HJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organize a campus event on #science #tech &amp; #humanrights with guide &amp; videos from @AAAS_SRHRL https://t.co/BDHt1M4pNJ @HuRiSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN's own experts chastise Ban Ki-moon over handling of Haiti cholera outbreak https://t.co/VKZWyqkMAv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>