<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@FabrizioRomano Stop bullshit please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elinbenja @Vondopoulos Twill be better when we win tomorrow. But worse when we lose on saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Tony Blair organised Iraq away?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamBeefySmith ain't that the beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MieshaTate @VenezuelanVixen @Cowboycerrone reaction to defeat is the core ingredient to a winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickconlan11 ducking cheats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scouskid @Carradona23 haha. Immense respect for Carl. Epitomises class and dignity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealCFrampton oozes class. Clapped the decision. Hero. So proud. Even his speech now. So dignified. The trilogy is on. #Belfast #tigerbay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redbrowny stomach says the trilogy is on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LSC fight. Both warriors. Trilogy will be lethal. In Belfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've this 5-3 to Carl but the fuck do ino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2olid_2nake fascinating fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carradona23 @redbrowny agree Cain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One island United. Let's go Jackal. @RealCFrampton #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFC was good. Times @RealCFrampton on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DustinPoirier @GamebredFighter whist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @MMAFighting ah yeah he needs a fight or two b4 a title tilt. Winner of mewis Browne maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAFighting be over quicker than the fight tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francis_ngannou wow. A date with my boy @stipemiocicufc awaits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_Jones_82 @Independent come to county Donegal. We'll go fishing and watch the fireworks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 imagine what he's feeling now? I'd be nose deep in a bottle of Jameson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 heartbreaking for him. If it was in the euros at least hed have a break to get over it. He'll surely be in the squad for hull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kev92Kelly @Maclifeofficial ino. Mentalists. Ferguson a tougher match up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted mane back ASAP. But not like this. Poor fella will be a mess. Gutted for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kev92Kelly @Maclifeofficial he KO's the Russian in the first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmerro1 for once you speak sense!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_dodd @KTHopkins I said nearly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_dodd @KTHopkins shagging trump would nearly be preferable to that walrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Truckerpaddy *heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Truckerpaddy I haven't seen one person say Lucas is good enough to play for us in years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 payet!!!! Sell him on to China in June then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 Robert fucking snodgrass would improve us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarraGabs Woodburns a player too. You can just tell he's quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philyburkhill so true. Wij really isn't good. 25m. Fuck me. Low wages tho I'd say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philyburkhill we spent that on Moreno and Markovic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 aye. ASAP. Just set him on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jomez is rusty as fuck. To be expected tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 don't think we'll ever see Randall again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merros tugging the cock off himself now with a belt around his neck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cnertington people think he's good going forward??? Mentalists. Useful as a marzipan dildo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaintlessRed me 2. Lucas and Moreno off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class the way Wij is world class at hide and seek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Randall's reaction to the second goal is hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cnertington worst left back I've seen at the club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbie_OR @Truckerpaddy they really aren't Rob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8GoalsCombined the shanks hologram would do a better job than that disease of a player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 I don't hate Randall so for that reason I'll go with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 Randall's probably better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmerro1 @empireofthekop you were in nappies the last time yous won a trophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wee cousin Noah was born yesterday but I'm fairly confident he's already better than Lucas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stxvo Wolverhampton was voted like the 4th worst place to live in the world a few years back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is that rabbit hitting corners?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z disease is good term to describe him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That goal was so shit from us I'm almost impressed at how shit we were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually miss fletch and sav on Saturday mornings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smilensam @LOCKloaded 4 in a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kev92Kelly Beatles doc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevosideways @AYPrivateEye back to the keeper and start again. Been saying since Pepe was in goal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Heaton @Christo90228121 @TheAnfieldWrap champions league in his bio 😂😂😂😂😂😂 #LAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure milners a good footballer. Sound defensively. Has a brain. Morenos isn't applicable to any of those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure does he not have a heap of assists for us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure milners sound defensively. Morenos not. I would like a natural left footer tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure in one game. Where we had a tampon up front. Moreno either hits first man or a throw in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure except JE had more ability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure but football isn't based on stats. Milner is better than Moreno. There is no argument. AM is just Enrique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @AIUnderPressure you can throw any stat you want at me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z his ability on ball is ten times better than the other gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z his passing is awful. But he thinks he's messi. There's a reason klopp doesn't play him. He knows he's shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z he's atrocious going forward. When he's wide he just hammers the ball across. Can't beat men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 not a notion Paul. Belongs in the cuckoos nest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z he's awful. Can't cross. Poor technique. Fast and has a hard shot. Such a poor player. Wouldn't get near the Burnley side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z and what in the name of God would moreno offer on the wing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z lovren did very little wrong tonight. One occasion he went towards the ball leaving space but realised and retreated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z you think Morenos good tho so.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrometheusX1Z @SouthamptonFC @wanpark_ no. He's nowhere near as bad as you say he is. And not as good as his fans say he is. Decent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmerro1 @JamesPearceEcho sure yous are billionaires that will win everything ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalvLyfeson @colinjones surely he'll have had a heart attack/been shot/been impeached or blown up the world by then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalvLyfeson @colinjones laying the groundwork to guarantee his reelection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merro having a gegenwank into a sock tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redbrowny don't disagree. Mad how one player makes the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mane is a huge loss but there's no pace in the side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sturridge is so bad it's sad. Playing him out of hope rather than expectation. Doesn't even score chances anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaintlessRed even though he can't cross a ball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shite. Get sturridge off. Offers nothing. Firmino and origi through the middle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmerro1 @TransferCentreL even though he's a winger lad. UNLACKEE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump is building the wall. Only one man for the job. https://t.co/U9BPXScqDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR that's too funny. Shows that most fans are clowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR pfa fans player of the year?? Actually?? Hahahahahahahaha. That's shocking. The most meh player we've had in years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR because he scored 5 goals? We were abysmal that year. Bang average player. As shown by how his career went.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR totally unsuited to English football and was therefore shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR soft as baby's shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KopiteLuke1892 @CarraGabs any Liverpool they doesn't is an idiot. Rolls Royce of a player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarraGabs @KopiteLuke1892 Hyypia underrated? Get to fuck. Best defender I've seen at the club!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmyrhol @Robbie_OR he scored 5 goals. He wasn't arsed half the time. Pulled out of tackles. Been shite ever since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbie_OR @fmyrhol meireles was shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcC185 @joel_archie the only season he was fit 08/09 Fabio was quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAnfieldWrap Peggy Arphexad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @Kev92Kelly @pxdr0 @DACrookster too much muscle maybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TesticleOReilly @Wollerto @iantn84 agree with this. Just when we lose one or two the drop in quality is huge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy https://t.co/SzUi3Fg1KS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>