<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrzyzstofOngaku non removable batteries are a reality now especially since people want waterproof devices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrzyzstofOngaku this phone is only 7 months old now so it's still fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ can take some best photos but can also take some really bad ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ so many people rave about the camera on multiple Sony models. I've never found it amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Just a bit busy this evening now. I'll find links for you tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower You could download the old firmware again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ That sucks. What are you using now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower But it is as simple as it seems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower I'd never done it before so practiced on my Z3 last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Woohoo! Cancel alarm voice command works. It's been broken for ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Just download flash tool and the AU firmware release. Google will help. Can send the file if you can't find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Incredibly easy to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Australia was one of the official releases before it was pulled due to the encrypted SD card speed issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xHighTower Yes official Australian release. Very simply with flashtool app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nate @mushion22 @ajobbins dunno. @chris021 is the boarding pass barcode expert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just flashed my Xperia Z5 with Nougat. It's definitely a nice improvement over Marshmallow, especially the new screen scaling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroDamo NYC next week though so I'll get over it. @FlyAirNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapperley @paulbrislen Caltex. National price has risen to accommodate this discounting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapperley @paulbrislen Yes that should be banned also but that's funded by Countdown. A 10c Smartfuel discount is fully funded by BP or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroDamo I may have an undiagnosed illness. @FlyAirNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRockNZ @JudithCollinsMP Smartfuel has driven up national price to accommodate instant discounts. It's why such deals were banned in AU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapperley @paulbrislen fuel prices are inflated because of AA Smartfuel. AA are in denial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudithCollinsMP a max of 4cpl for the very same reasons the ACCC did. Importer margin is high to allow for discounting which is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudithCollinsMP Please do something about petrol discounting. AA smartfuel should be banned. We need to follow AU and limit discounting to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successfully completed #dryjanuary didn't have a single @FlyAirNZ flight all month. First month plane free since early 2014!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall want to.  But nobody wants them..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like DB just purchased 100% of Tuatara brewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea you will fly NZ metal from NZ and then connect via SIN or elsewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea Go and look on the NZ website now and look at the special $859 to London - you can't fly NZ metal all the way for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea Lots of people who don't like flying via LAX already so I don't see why such a change would be needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea cheaper to fly via NZ to SIN/HKG/PVG/YVR and onward on partner airlines than NZ metal all the way now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea Vast majority of NZ ticketed pax on NZ 086 ticket stock flying to LHR don't fly NZ metal all the way anyway. It's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea @FlyAirNZ and NZ wouldn't give up LAX to LHR due to demand from US pax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea @FlyAirNZ 2nd landing slot at LHR has been leased out so that can't happen either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea @FlyAirNZ Yes. That would make the situation even worse and unlikely to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @moylea @FlyAirNZ If only it were that easy. Canadian Govt is very protective of Air Canada and routes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rosspnz @WLGAirport Air NZ operated this for a year from 1999-2000 https://t.co/ngWF6iuwHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut the fuck up Winston Peters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve so as a NZer applying for an ESTA of you've visited those countries you're excluded from an ESTA and need a visa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve in fairness to him those countries were selected by Obama. They were also part of the new ESTA rules that came in during Dec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UBNT_Brandon Sure. I see multiple people having the issue - do you want to debug a problem install?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ I have my cap. I'm all good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikiszikszai Sweet. I'll drop by when I'm down that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkepes what date do you fly out to the US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikiszikszai I've been meaning to swap my 1st gen Snapper for ages also so I can do phone topups So you still do free swaps at your office?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wellingtonista @MiramarMike FYI @BillEnglishMP is a parody account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColdDaemon @hamfritta @Coleadve were withdrawn from service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColdDaemon @hamfritta @Coleadve wouldn't fix in the railyards was parked there after payment for the last units fell through after they]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColdDaemon @hamfritta @Coleadve All the original Ganz were parked up there awaiting shipment to Africa. I thought the overflow that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onslaught86 You much of an expert when it somes to Xperia flashing / unlocking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPrimoNZ @DylanReeve it's only voluntary (at present).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamfritta @Coleadve @ColdDaemon moving them from Woburn to the rail yards to finally load onto a ship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamfritta @Coleadve @ColdDaemon the sale of the last ones fell through which is why they're been sitting there for so long. Maybe they're]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamfritta @Coleadve @ColdDaemon more that the normal ones parked up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowdy_possum that ESTA restriction isn't new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_Chirgwin I submitted my new one ~3 weeks ago and it was there then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_Chirgwin Has been on the ESTA website for quite a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_Chirgwin this is not new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@not_friends It's one thing I don't understand in society. Much like people who abuse airline staff when planes are delayed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atomeara Would have been total carnage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogergray61 I spent the first 30 years of my life in supermarkets. Bit like airlines really, far easier to actually lose money than make it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@not_friends people wouldn't say what they say on FB or Twitter to a real person..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plambrechtsen I'm sure your outage can be traced back to pineapple being put on pizza! @scottjpalmer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yakmoose @jpdanner @nzben some garlic salt which was delicious. Was quite a young animal &amp; definitely did dry out during cooking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yakmoose @jpdanner @nzben I'm not sure really. Was caught yesterday &amp; been in the fridge and simply cut into medallions and pan fried with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpdanner @nzben @yakmoose damn I should have posted my 24hr old wild venison. I own you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsouthernman @nate I would never use a debit card. Too much risk and useless for things like rental cars and hotels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm They're so popular they don't need to discount them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belindanash @jordantcarter All fixed line broadband was down for a couple of hours. Mobile up and down ever since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to deliver some good news so have a PSA. Briscoes have a 30-60% off sale on this weekend* only. (* = could be next weekend also)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve Senator Ted Harvey is mentioned when you ring it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belindanash it's been down since about 9am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sararoseflips @sez_sez @SparkNZ people wouldn't ring a CSR and abuse them but will happily do the same thing online when they feel powerful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ljayes @MarkDiStef that has been the case for probably 2-3 years. Nothing new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannews Umm?? It's an Air Force base not an Army base!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's that Spark FWA service working for everybody today? Remember Spark said how much better it is than the unreliable copper network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agentK you could argue the civil war in America never really ended. That's why they're in the position they are today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibrew I'm really worried what the country is going to be like in two weeks when I'm there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time Stuff around to reporting the Spark outage it was over. They haven't mention it's restored yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vivster81 @ThatDamnRanga Mobile network is being impacted also. Loss of data and services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew so you can't even connect to their mobile network?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rafaelmagu @SparkNZ Major faults with Spark at present. All internet and call centres down.,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a Spark customer it looks like their internet and call centres are all dead. Even 0800 000000 doesn't work from inside or outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @matteastnz @paulbrislen @NZComCom fuel purchases being subsided by others. This is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @matteastnz @paulbrislen @NZComCom by the ACCC when discounting hit 40cpl. Market and margins are totally skewed now with many]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @matteastnz @paulbrislen @NZComCom No. Discounting on any schemes greater than 4cpl should be banned like it was in Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matteastnz @paulbrislen Getting back to the fuel deal I really hope the @NZComCom do something about fuel discounting this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @matteastnz We have the best campaigns. Our campaigns are yuge. We knew you'd want to know about our yuge deal at 4am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanTLS No need to remove it from your bag then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanTLS You need to get a bag with a laptop sleeve. Both my satchel and backpack have these.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjwd great work.. and great comments from @lukenicholas who will no doubt get hate mail for telling the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agentK @Qantas It's an Australian airline delivering Australian quality broadband. They probably don't know about our awesome NZ broadband.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neville_Vedder probably was earlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriel it's a shame there aren't more people here on such a perfect night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer has finally arrived in Wellington. https://t.co/1CYzCSCaqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm is there a setting for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm @LaurieFleming @lukaszfromwelly @scottjpalmer damn that's a great price]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJessjess I assume you've probably seen this already? https://t.co/jOV7HjG8Jr @ajobbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReskueDave @FlyAirNZ looks like something wrong with FR24 data. Shows lots of aircraft landing there over the last few hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ Data on Flightradar24 shows a divert to HHR - I'm guessing this is somehow some wrong data?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>