<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna party by myself tonight because nobody wants to go out with me lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What are you doing for Valentine's Day?"  

Working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even now my mum hides my presents because she knows I go looking for them. Oops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might think you're being funny. Although I'm probably just there thinking wtf are you doing you junkie, but you'll never know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: "My birthday is on Sunday" 

Friends: " we know Veronica, it's only thing you've been talking about for the past week" ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That extra spoonful of coffee really does make a difference ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you still have an hour until you have to be awake by, but you can't get back to sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're taking a snapchat at the shops and you forget you have your flash on. ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe they weren't the toxic person, maybe it was you lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there a crossfit sponsored ad on my Instagram timeline every day. I'll never go. You're marketing to the wrong girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First there's a heatwave then it pouring rain. Make up your mind Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afros are so mesmerising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're mindlessly wasting time, then you realise you have to get up early tomorrow because it's Monday. Ugh, time to sleep, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met the creepiest bouncer today. Who hires these people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm.. what can I buy for myself on Valentine's Day. It's time to spoil myself. Again.. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We found out where the dog lives and I miss him already lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first time in a while I've been asked for my ID. Thank you my love! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so bloody cute ðŸ˜ https://t.co/bmdcjlGClC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some random dog followed my dog home when I was walking him and now I don't know what to do with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if couples who put the date that they got together in Roman Numerals actually know Roman Numerals or just Googled it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody has asked me how my love life is going lately. Is this a good or a bad thing? Hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you eye off the best looking plate when you're dishing up the food you've just cooked and someone just grabs it. Heart broken ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone bill has always been due on the same date each month for the past 4 years. Now it's due 2 weeks earlier. What??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the duck song stuck in my head. Oh my.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall do you have to be before you're considered tall for your gender? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like watching Criminal Minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When sales people try to sell hair straightening brushes to people who have straight hair naturally. ðŸ™„ move along mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your neighbour has a loud party on a Monday night and you just want to sleep. Shush please!!!! An oldie needs her rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone follows you on Twitter then blocks you for no apparent reason. What just happened lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took my dog outside so he could pee. It took him 10 minutes to choose where he wanted to go...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found my Nintendo DS. Memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This couple in the oval looked like they were ready to make out, then they just start having this massive argument. What just happened? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drowning my sorrows away, but with water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is what it is, you get what you give ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When some of your favourite products go on sale. Time to bulk buy. #Food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just realised I've never seen how 'How I Met Your Mother' ended and I'm so curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're waiting for someone but you're so hungry.. omggggg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl - "I hate everyone fml" 
Me - *lurks social media page* ohhhh she broke up with her boyfriend, again. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When one of your Tweets has no interactions yet. I feel so offended lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're having a good dream and someone wakes you up.. ohh...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like reading over my draft Tweets. They amuse me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to make a big fuss over my upcoming birthday, but at the same time I want someone to throw a cheesy surprise party for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you just start hearing things when you're really tired but can't get to sleep.. ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just cringe so much when I accidentally use conditioner first instead of shampoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a night where it doesn't feel like a sauna..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes me happy to see people who were f*cked around with finally settle for someone who treats them right. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've listened to my music too many times.. but I'm too fussy with finding new music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you look bad but the person you're crushing on says you look cute. Awkayyy, happy Veronica â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was looking at the picture I was tagged in on Facebook and I swear I do not look that shit in rl. Bad photography. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you marry a complete stranger ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to try Bailey's ice cream ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw this guy with an Elmo head motorbike helmet. Where can I buy one even though I'll probably never use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear there's like a time limit on my dog for how long I can hug him before he gets sick of me lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a caterpillar lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junkies should not be on the road. ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a movie made for kids makes you cry. Omg what is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure why, but I just want to go to Melbourne lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone who was an enemy of yours from high school compliments you. "Thank you â˜ºï¸"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump may be one of the most powerful people now. Although, what's he going to do when he turns every nation against the USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so hot that my protein bars melted. Now I'm sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the Snapchat articles are actually pretty interesting to look at to pass time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weather though ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're lurking on an interesting account and they deactivate. But I haven't finished yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just watched a video on how to turn a cucumber into a moving snake. Why is this recommended to me? ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're back to yourself. ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your stomach sounds like a thunderstorm. "Shhh, it's almost 11 pm. I want to sleep."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people are drink driving and Snapchatting at the same time. Cringe level 100.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When this new dessert place is opening up but it's in another state. Fml.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're calling you darling ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/435detn3fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the food video first looks so amazing but the final product looks like shit. Hmm, I'll pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want garlic dip with Lebanese bread and I'll be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a walK down memory lane. https://t.co/qrWpOCXtcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're a savage but deep down you're a softy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm losing my voice again ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna turn off my auto correct soon. It's driving me crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realised how noisey bats were until now. Shhh! I'm trying to get some sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the only thing in your life breaking your heart is onions. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: "oh it's one of my side hoes messaging me now."

Friend: "Bs, the only person who messages you is your mum" 

ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate cheap chocolate lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When mum approves of someone first go. Congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back at photos from last night and thinking fk I wasn't even drunk when I took this photo. What happened? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's more dancing in the line waiting to get in the club than there is in the actual club. Hahahaha what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have quite a bit of money left after an amazing night out. Very proud of myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone is coughing near you, don't you fkn go anywhere closer to me ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's people having their pre drinks on the train, offt ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be savage or to be humble. That is the question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's taking like 10 years to tan my legs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sunscreen smells a bit like mango. I guess you could say I'm really happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Train yourself to let go everything you fear to lose" - Yoda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mum always used to tell me when I was a kid that dates were cockroaches and I believed her ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people just love the drama ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do certain things bother us when they shouldn't even be on our minds...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually miss my job so much. Holidays hurry up and be over lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually really excited about NYE this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the people who have my Tweet notifications on are just receiving spam from me. Okay I'll stop, for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at what I Tweet sometimes, and I question my sanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if train drivers blast their music when they're driving the train and just pause it when they're making an announcement. ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accidentally starting piling up a huge shoe collection under my bed again. Whoops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone has dropped too many times lately. I'm scared it'll crack soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mum calls Tinder, Tingle omggggg ðŸ˜‚why do I find this so funny?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>