<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day, another boycott.  Truly #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is one unhappy groundhog. Kinda how I feel when my alarm goes off in the morning. #WinterRemains https://t.co/rLtHJkYokp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The night before my son's birthday, aka the night my dinner consists of licking batter out of a mixing bowl.  Cooki… https://t.co/GMOD5STXGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy that shares an office wall with me is SUPER angry it's snowing again.  I think he seriously just threw something in his office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if I should be annoyed or flattered when my server questioned my ability to finish the big breakfast at Ted's Bulletin. #nomnomnom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to basketball, I always cheer for the blue team...tee hee. Good luck @KUAthletics @UKAthletics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A safe and happy #gasparilla to all! https://t.co/f9whP1XaLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If everybody minded their own business, the world would go around a great deal faster than it does.”  - Lewis Carroll, Alice in Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day in #energygeek land with @FERC and @NRCgov announcements. Now if we could just bring FERC to quorum...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your committment to public service Chairman Bay. #NMpride https://t.co/JjLRO24SoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @CLaFleurFERC @calafleur75!  The ship is in great hands.  #fercgeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed, a legend who will be missed.  Rest in peace. https://t.co/JqDKfBT27N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great safety video by @PSETalk re downed power lines. Please watch!   https://t.co/MRnM6Btba0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learned I share a birthday with @nikkihaley ... kinda made my day #InauguralBday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did it take me so long to find @Drizly?  Awesome #customerservice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convinced that trying to solve an issue through @Groupon live chat is equivalent to... no refund for rude merchants… https://t.co/kfGCQne9YB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or not... "postponed until further notice." https://t.co/q49JHgdzd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's go time...@EnergyGOP @EnergyDems will vote at 9:30 a.m. Tuesday on Gov. Perry and Rep. Zinke.  #Energy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be safe and listen to the warnings y'all!  My prayers are with those affected by the storms this weekend. https://t.co/CP9S0zeyQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that escalated quickly.  Sigh...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LifeandHoney first time here...wish there were more locations. Love the concept, the mood, and the food. #eatlifeandhoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a great day to celebrate a new Presidency and an era of birthdays forever more ending in 9... #Inauguration https://t.co/7rwM7pw6nI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First order of business.  #PresidentTrump #Inauguration #viewfrom501 https://t.co/7YfjuWntKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how we do...@donisec #NJSS #Inauguration https://t.co/z8vwCS9TDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw someone clipping toenails in dupont circle.  No, no, a thousand times no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One down, one to go.  Maybe two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHouseEffect saves the day! Now if my dress would behave all will be well for #NJSS #Inauguration #jerseystrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenttheRunway thanks, I sent an email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure @BadgleyMischka didn't mean for the zipper to look like camel humps.  Not feeling my @RenttheRunway dre… https://t.co/heOUNTG6TE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really should've created a confirmation hearing bingo board.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't hear what the police are yelling on bullhorn, but it doesn't look good. Blockades at 15-13th street and F s… https://t.co/Fy7DmH1bVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost #Inauguration Day... https://t.co/RZtjCGlRfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like one morning in 2017 not to start off like this... https://t.co/XsAd9G0IqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @WMcCord128! Meh, I'll just be over here in the corner repeating the #SerenityPrayer.  Apparently we no longer teach reading in school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was taught when I don't have anything nice to say, I should keep my mouth shut.  Sometimes I pass this test, some… https://t.co/kTU9pj4gAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andtheMethod @zolwaterhouse @MarcBroussard ... our band just bailed for a party this Thursday in DC.   Know any possibilities?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswhickling monsters inc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must have willpower to ignore trolls...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep telling myself only one more episode of @TheAmericansFX and then I will get back to work ... #rainyday #procrastination #bingefest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if I can get the same picture with @corybooker. Love this pic from #inaugural2013 #NJSS https://t.co/ldnMqLyLNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I register for a @lifetimefitness class and now need to take my little boy to urgent care. #momlife #priorities #nogymforme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree completely @RepLujanGrisham.  Clinging to "discretionary". https://t.co/k5XJn1Suya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your dedication to serving America and all of it's people.  You'll be missed #UncleJoe. https://t.co/guPzckBTAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @RollingStone @guardian @NewYorker you should probably have your attorneys brush up on libel and slander. #factsmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the concept of #BarBirthday ...thanks @ABAesq!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usps sorters read return address as mailing address....returned to house twice now. Sorry @lulu_kane, you aren't getting timely thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're exhausted, having a tough couple of days, but have to push through...#cookiesandmilk https://t.co/e2BIFjbRQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing food and staff @pbcatch!  Well done. https://t.co/52bcQQwEQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why should we let facts get in the way of a great headline, right @Gizmodo?   #fakenews https://t.co/9dMLutsR47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bets on actually doing a mic drop? https://t.co/IQ2ZTwdwW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Starbucks, I now have a new addiction. Love the #CascaraLatte! https://t.co/xafEbEyLp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely gift from @KRob_DC that is supposed to smell like North Carolinian blackberries and barbecue. I smell tobacc… https://t.co/f6ByyJw415]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a lively Friday night I have... #taxreform #QER https://t.co/ksEXYNNgwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza for lunch and now this... #taxreform is going to be very bad for my health. https://t.co/MkO3n4GmIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations on to the team and to Brittingham!  He will be sorely missed from the Hill.  #wrdawoes https://t.co/W63IjbOamm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I just discovering that @SIRIUSXM has a @GeorgeMichael tribute channel?  Btw Father Figure is a lot creepier… https://t.co/N3QTZf8gI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so the 115th begins... may the odds be ever in your favor. #115congress #Day1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So maybe the tree will remain up until  Epiphany. Too much on the to-do list today...and dinner &amp; Netflix just seem… https://t.co/kylxLPvpDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best wishes for a happy and healthy 2017!  #HAPPYNEWYEAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveAinDC careful or I'll send the Frozen soundtrack over to your office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TazWZZM I still cry at that scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The angle at which colored sugar no longer sticks to a frosted gingerbread house roof is 45 degrees.  In other news, my floor is festive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa fail... missing this tiny rod to assemble @LEGO_Group holiday train.  Calling all elves! https://t.co/uKJu6q2oh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AugensteinWTOP goes quite well with bourbon cider also. https://t.co/m6delq6wx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I know why the wise men didn't bring Legos.  One set down, 20 more to go.  Merry Christmas to you and yours! https://t.co/fh59I2quyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two different grocery stores today.  Both times I forgot star anise and cloves for my mulled wine. #FirstWorldProblems #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the guy that bought my @CavaGrill lunch, thank you.  I will #payitforward.  #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure this is what President-Elect Trump meant by bringing #coal back... https://t.co/dTGminI6M4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a long strange year it's been. Wishing the staff at House E&amp;C and Senate ENR some well-deserved r&amp;r this holid… https://t.co/jVdEaFriX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any last shred of societal decorum is gone: people crunching popcorn and chips while talking loudly over the Nutcracker. #respectthedancers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the category of awful Christmas songs, the winner goes to Barry Manilow's cover of Joni Mitchell's "River".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to all who have lost family and friends in tragic recent events.  Praying for a better future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expectations are the darnedest thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how the political lessons and issues from #TheAmericanPresident are still apt today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping the combination of chicken soup, @DuckDonuts, and #LoveActually makes me feel better about not getting xmas pressies done.  #SickDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a valet hit a car with his customer's car.  He rolls down his window and says "you got a problem?"  Unreal. #DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note for next year...don't wear a white coat.  #wreathsacrossAmerica https://t.co/dfz62wOhZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico reports: Obama told Putin in September to "cut it out" re cyberattacks against the U.S.  Anyone else have… https://t.co/rmifopyshb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes!  Be safe Emera team!!  #ThankYourLineworkers https://t.co/vvqnId0Yay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My IT karma is epic. Another videoconferencing fail. https://t.co/SMG4BzJgVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a good ride, while it lasted.  Guess I'll be adding @PractLawInst to my #NewYearsResolutions for 2017...… https://t.co/T7VCretjfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas in Canada. https://t.co/n84QG22lop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to the panelist who is nimble enough to work in puns when a cell phone starts quacking during the discussion. #DuckDuckGoose #onthefly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so expensive to mail parcels to the UK now?  #bahhumbug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed a wonderful performance of @IntoTheWoods today.  @kencen box office extremely helpful today - many thanks! https://t.co/6Sj2UdVydD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stay bravely green in wintertime..." #Christmas #CharlieBrownTree https://t.co/dfMdDF5Jyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of changes in #Florida regarding #lobbying.  Here's what you need to know:  https://t.co/v5YIOnnN4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The struggle is real @HPLifestyle  https://t.co/NpWtZOYkTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter is coming... #NARUCWinter17 https://t.co/8WynFLVDJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep.  Done with Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswhickling helping the forestry industry...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I may have gotten a #CharlieBrownChristmas tree, albeit a larger version.  Didn't notice the dead ends...… https://t.co/3xOuu8S6Zp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching a Christmas movie with my son...the elf just caused a blackout on xmas eve.  Ironic.  #energygeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump should hire the ceo of @Target to boost the economy. No one can go there and buy only what's on their list. N… https://t.co/XLSkgbj9kO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everything I watch six degrees of #gilmoregirls? @thelaurengraham in Sweet November, @alexisbledel in Jenny's Wedding...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TazWZZM hey, we got to hang out in October...so that month is partially salvaged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats FSU seniors...4 straight wins against UF and Miami. #FSUvsUF #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that was a beautiful play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so the holiday movie marathon commences...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of @netflix #bingewatching: watched all 4 eposodes with only one pause to refill tea and pie.… https://t.co/ZphsoBBmCj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>