<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladies4trump @POTUS please President Trump, do us all a favor a fire all Obama staff immediately, they will never be loyal to you or #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brithume @Charlie4Trump @nytimes the Dems need to approve @POTUS cabinet picks then he wouldn't rely so much on him. He's very smart man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@americanistrump @jmdonsi you need to remind all these #fakenews organizations of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KazmierskiR @vivelafra and so very thankful for @VP and his lovely wife and their Christian values they espouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KazmierskiR @vivelafra finally a POTUS that understands &amp; LIVES meaning of #Prolife ! Awesome. A long time coming, so thankful for @POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you remember when EVERYTHING @Walmart was proudly sold "made in America"? I do. Sam Walton rolling over. @POTUS @realDonaldTrump #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews the legal citizens living in these cities &amp; counties shd b able 2 vote whether r not to have it - not dictated by demo gov/mayors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VivaLaAmes @BasedMelGibson @TruthFeedNews I find that hard to believe. I saw Drew Carey @ one of the balls interviewed by Fox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikandynothem I can hardly wait! Looking forward to real change!  #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian I hope he bought her a one way plane ticket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DavidMuir @ABC I hope it's live interview. #fakenews #MSM can't be trusted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @POTUS @TheDemocrats in my great state of LA you have to show ID to buy beer, cigarettes, liquor, etc why not vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilasLongshot @RichardTBurnett @Deplorable_Left I never realized there were SO many stupid people in U.S. that you'd think were educated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian that's good for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity the first of many visits I'm sure over the next 8 years!!!! Thank you for all you do to keep America focused on real issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP fire her NOW @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricSpracklen @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse thrilled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burghseyeview @ceci8775 @Reince @FoxNewsSunday @POTUS Chris Wallace is democrat in tank for HRC. @FoxNews needs more housekeeping to #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepsi @nickmangold #BoycottPepsico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@childoflight4 @realAngeloGomez my favorite line in his speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDonaldNews I liked Ed Rollins. Will miss him. He must be retiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian @brianstelter @PressSec they did that so they (@CNN) could splice &amp; edit to their benefit. #DishonestMedia #BoycottCNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePatriot143 republicans, @realDonaldTrump supporters just don't act like these crazies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler boycott all of them. Not just Judd, any actress, actor or professional singer like Madonna, Cher - I say boycott them ALL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet such a good roll model for younger girls to follow in this domestic terrorist's footsteps. #LockHerUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow that's what they commonly refer to today as a "domestic terrorist". #LockHerUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetatertot2 from the bottom of my heart I say "thank you". â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriotGinger @BizNetSC @TeriGRight time to defund lots of things, UN one of them. #DefundUN #AmericaFirst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuvMyAmerica @greta @MSNBC I too love @greta but just cannot bring myself to watch anything on @MSNBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @melsherwood @HuffPostPol @JamesOKeefeIII rise above this foolishness, youre far better person than sore loser @melsherwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revjtcauser she is such a beautiful lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ARnews1936 @amlookout I believe you meant to say "classless". Chris Mathews is a moron and needs to resign. #Inauguration2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @tekarceben doesn't look like she needs anyone's help. Such a beautiful, classy lady. Not what we're used to lately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greta she has my sympathies!  Lol and I'm from Louisiana like he is. We aren't all that crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP think how proud we are today &amp; just imagine how much prouder we will be in 4 more years! God Bless @realDonaldTrump our #POTUS ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JGilliam_SEAL @NatEnquirer aren't all their articles full of "errors &amp; non- facts". No surprise there my friend. ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelpollak time to #boycottABC following path of lowly @CNN #FakeNewsMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkeyes agree. She is such a beautiful woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SagiOrli @tekarceben awesome. Gives me such joy to see this turnout! ðŸ˜ƒâ¤ï¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ðŸ˜ƒâ¤ï¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricTrump praying for you &amp; your precious family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me I didn't just see John Boehner @ #Inauguration2017. How dare he?? Biggest sore loser -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteTrumpPics never been more proud to be an American!  #TrumpInauguration #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr gave me chills, one of the most beautiful things I've ever watched, wished I could've seen in person. Best wishes. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GJBALDACCHINO @BossyCowgurl84 unbelievable!  Knew @CNN was terrible but this takes them to new low.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @SpecialKMB1969 stunning, absolutely beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews same polls that said @realDonaldTrump would never win election. Agree polls are phony &amp; rigged. Every 1 I know excited for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SupportDonald @realDonaldTrump I wouldn't trust ANYONE that served in Obama admin inc CIA, FBI, housekeeping, valet parking, replace all!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedNationRising @LeahR77 I hope @realDonaldTrump lights up White House red, white, &amp; blue his first night 1/20. BHO never used those colors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derosi6aolcom @Littleone619 @ConstanceQueen8 @TruthFeedNews @TuckerCarlson ditto. Made my day when I heard the new. #MakeFOXGreatAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBloom451 they are using same polling methods that indicated @realDonaldTrump would not win election. Shameless MSM. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flaunttnualf @StefanMolyneux I live in Deep South. Cannot remember race relations being this strained since '60's thanks to BHO &amp; admin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrieksada @JeffreyCOwnby thank you Toby Keith for your courage &amp; patriotism. All Trump supporters need now to show appreciation to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAGA3X @Charlie4Trump they've graduated from protesting at rallies to this nonsense. #SoReadyFor2017 #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ish10040 @DianeHauschildt @USHeraldNews I guess he will add this to his list of accomplishments now! So sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery @nypost so sad. You can give PETA credit for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlverezAmanda @CarmineZozzora @VoteTrumpPics @AppSame @nia4_trump @PrisonPlanet @Cernovich @seanhannity and haven't held real jobs 8 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmSteveHarvey @realDonaldTrump thank you for being open minded and willing to work together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @FredFleitz because he's an idiot with a boss that's even more of an idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConstanceQueen8 @TruthFeedNews couldn't be happier. @TuckerCarlson SO deserves it. Love his show. Don't have to change channel anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wikileaks @FoxNews @realDonaldTrump needs to not only #draintheswamp he needs to clean house @ #CIA and start over. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepublicanChick @ahernandez85a @Rep_Hunter @acipollo @RepAdams rip that thing to shreds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich a very smart, well spoken man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to #confirmSessions for Attorney General because he wants to #ProtectTheBorder https://t.co/dZTUo8lOYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStick2013 McCain needs to resign. Obviously he is not interested in working with @realDonaldTrump and can't be trusted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStick2013 he needs to resign NOW - today. He has only made matter worse for @realDonaldTrump and true GOP. He's a RINO and needs to GO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @DonaldJTrumpJr  I hope @Sen_JoeManchin is the catalyst @realDonaldTrump uses to bring parties together. Seems good man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CR @DonaldJTrumpJr @BrianHDarling he has to be to allow himself &amp; his family to be the target of ridicule &amp; slander. So sad. Stay strong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoneColdTruth @tekarceben yes resign now if you can't be team member]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Italians4Trump @BreitbartNews McCain needs to resign now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow time to clean house!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MEPFuller @billpostmus no don't believe that. Keep the faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4Freedom4ever @DebAlwaystrump led and encouraged by RINO John MCCain!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends @TomFitton clearly this administration uses serious drugs or is just plain stupid. Probably both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePatriot143 clearly he was delusional when he said that! Where's he been past 8 years? That's right, on vacation !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CNNPolitics that explains a lot!  Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BluegillRises @BreitbartNews @nia4_trump @donlemon @CNN what a Moran !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamVTV I stopped watching her long time ago when she started attacking @realDonaldTrump and taking up for Hillary every chance she had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatDollard @DebAlwaystrump @SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump this is prime reason there should be TERM LIMITS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankLuntz @DebAlwaystrump I think that's the most profound thing you've ever said!  Totally agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheChrisSuprun @realDonaldTrump you're just trying to "make a name for yourself" by skirting your responsibility as an elector. Shame on U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VivaLaAmes @Kotcha301 @Walmart @TruthFeedNews I've seen it all. #boycottWalmart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ish10040 like mother like daughter. Apple doesn't fall far from tree. When that Apple feel it landed too hard on hits head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GopAaron please just go away already. You LOST. #Trump Won!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP probably so he can swear his sorry self in for a 3rd term! Talk about revolt in this country. @realDonaldTrump better get hold it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angels8000 @vivelafra I pray when @realDonaldTrump takes office he lets his DOJ seek justice for this young man &amp; give family closure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow she does hate @realDonaldTrump.  Thanks @TuckerCarlson for staying the course &amp; sticking to your guns, stating truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bocavista2016 @realDonaldTrump that is the funniest thing I've ever read.  Hollywood could take that 1 line &amp; make millions #fakenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAngelle and we ALL know you're a Godly man. Mathew 6:33 look it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAngelle gov Edwards has made many enemies. No way he will win re-election. You were so close last time. Perhaps that's part Gods plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAngelle disappointed with outcome. Lord has something better in store for you!  Please pray about running for Governor! You'll win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian talk about #fakenews this is it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anne19brown @POTUS for those that voted "SAD" or "4 More Years" - Are you kidding me?  Obama worst POTUS EVER hands down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vivelafra @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews love me some @TuckerCarlson so refreshing skip Meghen Kelly &amp; wait for @seanhannity - he &amp; Tucker are it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @realDonaldTrump do you remember when Walmart was all American made? Now investing $1.3 billion in Mexico. Shameful. #BuyUsa #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKerik @MailOnline @realDonaldTrump wake up America. @realDonaldTrump needs to rescind that deal ASAP no good will come of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Team_Trump45 thank you Lord!  Time to let @realDonaldTrump &amp; @mike_pence  #MAGA3X and forget about this nightmare of the last 8 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian love @TuckerCarlson he's so refreshing &amp; straight shooter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ just to name a few of his accomplishments!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee she's a lot of both!  Thank you @GovMikeHuckabee for your service &amp; commitment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @Lrihendry passed up all favorite Kellogs cereals yesterday with good heart! #DumpKelloggs #BuyPost #BuyGeneralMills #MAGA ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>