<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@labuzamovies Milo At Altamont will be where the final seal opens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Milo starts showing up to speeches with Hell’s Angels we’ll know it’s really the 60s again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbysoave good I’m glad we understand one another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbysoave no but robby these stories are boring and unimportant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reactionaries gonna react. https://t.co/2RMToUEVsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member when all the crazy civil unrest led to Nixon losing in a landslide when he ran for reelection?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that’s a booting https://t.co/mYPEKk2ZFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States is really getting just about everything it deserves, in every sense of the phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smug is right tho. https://t.co/bUoBbJfC55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FigDrewton That’s good though: https://t.co/BtyKAS7EMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that the bobcat was in the zoo the whole time lends more credence to my theory that WMATA has actually tak… https://t.co/9aBqMOP3tt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duranni1 He knows his audience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComfortablySmug Did you show your #altcenter solidarity with #TeamMnuchin today? https://t.co/O6RPVQD1lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zandywithaz I usually put both on a hotdog: some ketchup and some yellow mustard. Now that’s a tasty sandwich!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zandywithaz put ketchup on her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zandywithaz That dog looks delightful. Of course, all dogs are delightful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zandywithaz dogs: is there anything they can’t do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“its” https://t.co/Uk1I1HKYln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vjmfilms It actually sounds to me as if it will be from the plot description.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Beyonce news is the best pop news of the day,” the people cried.

God thought about this, then cracked His knu… https://t.co/8fclXLPlLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Two, whenever Trump’s not on the screen, all the other characters should be tweeting 'Where’s Trump?’"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass @lachlan the best part is you can’t even taste it because you’ve had like 27 beers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanzilberman If there’s one thing I know it’s 90s rock lyrics. If it was on DC101 it was in my brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanzilberman It’s unknown to us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass Has @lachlan never heard of Jumbo Slice I mean wtf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can’t know this.

He can’t know this because I don’t hate Joe Buck.

Joe Buck is great.

https://t.co/K5Xq1R2fX4 https://t.co/mYaiRhPDrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComfortablySmug @Batee555 She managed to win 3 million more votes and still lose. That’s some amazing incompetence right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Batee555 @ComfortablySmug You know what second place is, right?

First loser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Batee555 @ComfortablySmug and yet she failed, spectacularly, just like all the other failures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[goddammit now the lines at chopt are never going to end https://t.co/l9vTxpVFPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass @crousselle yeah that game was way harder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your mom is officially on notice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass @gabrielmalor My friends and I “rediscovered” this in HS and wasted 100s of hours playing it. It’s in my top 20, definitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crousselle @KevinWGlass if you are bad at video games maybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass Battletoads at 81 is some bullshit. Top 20, easily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass Also, no TMNT? Man, that game *defined* “Nintendo hard."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass That list does make me want to play Castlevania III, though, which I’ve never done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(review coming friday same bunch time same bunch channel)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose it’s a waste of effort to complain about retconning in the RESIDENT EVIL movies, but by God complain I shall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel I hope Ollie is enjoying a delicious slice of pumpkin cheesecake right now, laughing at all those idiots at the Zoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanWurtzel fucking quitter talk that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinWGlass would also be very wmata-like tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, the National Zoo is just giving up on trying to find that bobcat? When did WMATA take over running the zoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz @SethAMandel @cjane87 I find it hard to believe that anyone can be this wicked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjane87 @SethAMandel not my fault y’all are ignant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @cjane87 have you ever had it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjane87 @SethAMandel pumpkin cheesecake is better though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A failure equalled only by the movement to elect Hillary Clinton! https://t.co/leaOvYhhOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjane87 @SethAMandel “Hey, you want something that is rich and tasty” 
“no i would rather have trash fruit covered in dirt bread"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjane87 @SethAMandel your account is so bad you should delete it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow and i was told monsters aren’t real https://t.co/eLBSW7ACGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cheesecake &gt; pie &gt; all other cakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel what about cheesecake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to think, before Trump Iran’s government had such respect for the United States. https://t.co/KqvU2Sk2ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(No offense, but if you think Babs is a better actor-turned-director than Mel, you’re a gd lunatic who should be in… https://t.co/5DntWNZFjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Popehat why are those mutually exclusive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamMnuchin #Solidarity https://t.co/KXkDXFGOM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm okay with suspending the Senate rules if that's what it takes to get the EP of BATMAN V SUPERMAN into Trump's cabinet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtLOL I have the PS4 version though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow always someone on twitter who wants to be wrong about how i am right all the time https://t.co/L6SaOujwx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, though, attacking anyone for anything on Twitter is stupid. Don’t be a Twitter Jerk. https://t.co/OLcVanxpa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, but people on FB rarely have any decent insults either. Brevity is the soul of wit(hering scorn). https://t.co/XEqzZdvOAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting in fights in FB is even dumber than getting in fights on Twitter. I blame the lack of character restrictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I basically only use Facebook to post pieces I've had published and harass Neal Dewing. https://t.co/Nb4FgfcqRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KFoleyFL I mean, RE 4, 5, and 6 are all basically just action games with a horror veneer. This one is very moody/scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KFoleyFL You definitely will not like this one then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KFoleyFL It makes me sad to think about all the wasted pixels floating off into the atmosphere like so many chlorofluorocarbons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j1ri_ It’s already passed; just took me a night of playing to get used to it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resident Evil: Biohazard. It’s fun, though I kind of prefer the shoot-em-up RE games to the survival-horror RE game… https://t.co/s3WHIv9hnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started playing a video game for the first time in 18 months or so. There’s that fps-induced motion sickness I missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being nicer strikes me as a liability, tbh, so I’m glad he only seems that way. https://t.co/aHvNhSzik9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, this nomination keeps looking better! https://t.co/AgmzDCNm5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unfortunate SCOTUS noms have devolved into pure power politics since Bork. But when 9 robes become philosopher kings it's unsurprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faceyouhate @astromarko mother of God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats will filibuster; GOP will go nuclear; Gorsuch will be confirmed. This is a rather obvious sequence of events at this point, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was wondering why you had stepped up from Hobo Chic to Marginally Presentable today. https://t.co/aBJjTBqrvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glenn__Kenny So you're saying there aren't many people in LA who will dig Gorsuch? I find it hard to believe originalist thinking is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Achilles himself would be like "nah I'm cool." https://t.co/edd0t9glr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wait until he revives Press Your Luck with drone strikes in the place of the Whammies. https://t.co/OwpAMyjQHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Father to a murdered son. Husband to a murdered wife. Commander of the Armies of the North, General of the Felix L… https://t.co/MVLx4s5HXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoganDobson I'm hoping we get a Scalia-like pick, but I've always been a doubting Thomas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My main takeaway from all the Uber angst is that I'm not going to have to worry about surge pricing as much in the short term.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjciaramella @DavidRutz wow did you know he was a reality tv host]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they should get seth rogen and amy schumer to do it that campaign was a huge hit after all https://t.co/UEmas3rcSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and yet no pulitzers have we won

bias is real https://t.co/f6OsThh2B5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComfortablySmug The fact that people consider small businesswoman Ursula a villain in LITTLE MERMAID is gross. Are contracts meaningless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComfortablySmug @RonWFingers @redsteeze @morninggloria I think it is generally accepted that Prince Hans is the hero of FROZEN, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very little bit leakage on those https://t.co/lqMTQ1kjOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Popehat @EsotericCD @JayCaruso don’t do it man you will regret it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Washingtonian had any real reporters they would’ve covered this long ago. What are you covering up over ther… https://t.co/r7iVDZw9u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[meh, improvement is overrated; sick owns are forever https://t.co/p3IJnbp3lG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glenn__Kenny patriarchy wins again smdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@labuzamovies I’ll stop when you do what’s right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. https://t.co/mmlt2HM0Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is important. People on Twitter aren’t here to tweet about the things you deem important on any given d… https://t.co/Z917ArCpv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdispoto @jacko2323 @FreeBeacon of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[would be a good idea tbqh https://t.co/ELUHldFUl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbysoave @LizWFB @FreeBeacon I was surprised Pikachu went full-on-alt-right too, tbqh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayCaruso Exactly. I mean, I respect greatness, so Go Brady And The Patriots. But who he voted for has nothing to do with it either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Brady’s politics have nothing to do with the Super Bowl and should have no impact on your appreciation of him. https://t.co/JuY4fSAXHt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>