<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor wee guy will never kiss again. https://t.co/RjWnpPmSc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs offers 35 mil plus I think they would sell him, an I think the money he would get down south would influence him to go to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs I know, or could sell him for like 35 times as much. Be interesting to see, I like him an would like to see him stay, but if were]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs can't keep good players at the club unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs but then say he isn't as consistent an not scoring as many goals, his evaluation will go down. He's been brilliant for us, but we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs aye I've seen few tweets an Facebook posts about it, would be mad no to accept 34 I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elliot__Blair that's amazing a could just imagine him grouching ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docccs seen a lot of talk he's away to Chelsea for 34 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really struggled getting up this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need 10,000 pound an a ticket out of here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaylzKHM need something. Need to find a dentist up here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A need summer just now, need that feeling when you walk of the plane an the warm air hits your skin, unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno if you got jackies mention mate, she asked someone to tag you @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/A6bkmEKk7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need someone to go to the cinema with in Edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to watch supersonic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squeakk_ it's like one of the only ways a can eat it ðŸ˜‚ chicken on the bone is the fear ðŸ—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyamcX ahh, yeah probs of on part time wAge you don't needs to pay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moyzi they wouldn't let go for less than 40 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moyzi yeah it's a bold estimation, but probably because of the potential there Celtic reluctant of selling. Sure it said on sky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyamcX aye god knows then, id google an check or phone them. Might be due a nice rebate if it's been going on for a while ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moyzi not worth 40 million, good player with great potential, also won French under 21 to. But not worth that estimation yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyamcX aye am sure that's the case, sure it's not national insurance your paying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyamcX a thought you didn't have to pay tax if your in education?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisdom tooth is growing in an it's honestly so sore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, have a good day! ðŸ’ƒ @ohhiindia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisdom teeth are so sore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What takes normally five minutes has turned into an intense ten minute walk cause of the ice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisdom teeth are growing in a it's agony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cant stop watching this, so so creepy https://t.co/RnXEymty8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottJohnstonnn a never knew they actually had prawn in them until like last month same as prawn toast ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came down like two hours hours later asking if a wanted to join an stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in the apartments  where a stay are having like a wee party an stuff an like a burns dinner, didn't make the cut for it tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_LaurenNicola that's mental, especially not that much ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_LaurenNicola no wayðŸ˜‚ that's like the worse looking pizza in the planet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhood1 didn't know that,it just seems worse cause it's getting publicised more cause it's USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is starting to Remind me of a man from Austria. Who marginalised a religion cause of his own beliefs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A use to think trump was a better candidate thought some his ideas were ok. But that's to far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps ban on muslims is one step to far. Adds fuel to the fire for these terrorist organisations to attack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hate Edinburgh. Like actually have zero pals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two absolute gents there, brilliant sportsmanship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer an nadal, two greats of the game. Great to see them both in a final.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A need friends in Edinburgh. A want to do something today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A don't care how fresh you feel on a Sunday by staying off it. Sober weekends are horrendous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird on the voice atm is so unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I do is eat out. Needs to stop waste so much cash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible for Many clouds, brilliant horse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met a girl in the EE shop from glengarnock today, first time ever, she apologised for the train stopping there ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoneColdRab brutal, it's when a go to bed am up and down all the time an the half the time a don't even need it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoneColdRab a think I might have this, gen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much racing on today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmah93_ @JoshEvans_ feel sorry for you Emma, according to josh your always getting ready... that's his excuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorMcfadzean that use to be a good couple of months for me to be down that, you can never win mate ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshEvans_ you on your phone again while on holiday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental Craig Gordon's carer nearly over an now he could sign with Chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanyadomino @chris_mcfadzean @chrissybiy someone did it to Corin to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanyadomino @chris_mcfadzean haha they get recorded aswell ðŸ˜‚ so the person can here what you said an stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandyrobertsan @haymarch_callum aye it is man, none of them have that many decent shops, more than often your going for the scran haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandyrobertsan @haymarch_callum ad say silverburn now, upped its game over the last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potato scones are the ultimate breakfast item]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzzing that it's Friday, only been in work for a four day week an I'm desperate for a couple days off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger just seems so much happier and more chilled now, pressures off him an he can enjoy himself more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish folk are the best at like everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #SCOvIRE RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too https://t.co/pp1bOiAfO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be quite easily the worse picture My eyes have ever seen https://t.co/drkvjCaZ6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRoberts19 that series of unfortunate events is meant to be good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AimeecGraham14 aye is it haha, doesn't have a clue lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wee pig out of moana is to cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing gets your more excited thank thinking about summer, especially when you have plans â˜€ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great result, especially for broonys 400th appearance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haggis gives me the fear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amackenzie93 so good init! #georgemichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See people that comment here n videos an that with a fake story thinking its funny, it's not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhood1 aye people protesting making it so much worse cause they didn't get there on way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@not_annemarie still it was a vote, an America is meant to be democracy.. if it was other way around people wouldn't complain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyaaaholly I don't know if a like them, a only ever eat the caramel ones haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact you can now buy a box filled with maltesers celebrations is so good. Just need the 2l Capri suns now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Result doesn't mean you should then go an vote again. Same with trump. All these people protesting. He was voted in by the Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I want to stay in the E.U having another vote is going against everything we're meant to support, just because you don't like the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I WILL start the gym this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diana__doll haha that was always the worse when your parents said that, it was worse than them being angry ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elrow in Glasgow be a bit mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diana__doll still drinking, poor show. Only Tuesday to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sounds cold outside today, can't be fucked at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jayesophine uk fits into California 1.74 times. Always find it mental that over there you can fly for 6 hours an still be in same country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good few days off, but now back to reality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When's made in Chelsea start back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diana__doll unless it's this weekend then you'll have no chance ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A check my bank thinking ill have a decent amount of money init, an every time a go am disappointed, always less than o expect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMccutcheonx yeah it use to be my Sunday night viewing on sky 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMccutcheonx the new ones are class with Steve mcgarret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @r4ch0 have a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshEvans_ ðŸ˜‚ can't even ride a bike now cause my hip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how good a feeling it is knowing a don't need to get up early tomorrow an go to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dunlop_paige it's brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@that_craig_kid cheers bud! Hope you weren't to rough this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinPeterOneil thanks mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So brutal when your birthdays coming to an end cause you've got to wait a full year to the next one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ewanmcqueen_91 cheers bud! Hope your well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsjackthomas aye well am talking back when they were both in there hay day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsjackthomas aye man especially with the elder wand to]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>