<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA okay perfect!! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA is this the route that from chapel hill to city?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@absoluteradio please play bohemian rhapsody. ðŸ˜Š We are on the rainy M4 on the way home to Bristol after weekend with family. #requestshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so so good to have my family back ðŸ’œðŸ’œðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The radio station we're listening to played #closingtime bang on 5pm. Had to resist going full on #andybernard on my colleagues. #TheOffice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bus driver casually mentioned his breaks weren't working on the journey in today. Great. https://t.co/dCUbPtRmbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've found the perfect way to get my love to make the sofa up all nice, hide  his phone under the cushion and only hint slightly where it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it acceptable to go to bed at 8pm? #SoTired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I've asked my love to contact the photographer for our wedding. I'm betting he won't do it until I've asked at least 7 times?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to build a pillow fort with my love today. I want to sleep all day. #adultsgonewrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am disgusted with people - mainly Donald Trump and whoever left a used tampon applicator rolling around the bus. #grossversionsofdodgeball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love genuinely asked me to lay on his side of the bed to warm it up before he got in, who on earth does he think he is?! #princess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emilyylime05 cross trained on Amadeus now but definitely miss AA xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emilyylime05 oh no :( can you swop some time off and take a holiday? Please let me know if there's anything I can do ðŸ’œ works ok -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's doing it... he's actually doing it! Miracles do happen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emilyylime05 sending all my love. Is there anything I can do? Yeah, better then they have been! How's work been? Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked if that was the last round, it clearly says "round 1" at the top of the screen.. he said yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've gone and gotten lunch jar out of his bag, it's like having to ask a small child if they've done their homework!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to bed at 10.30, if it's not clean, he's not getting fed..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's started another round, he keeps singing "you are my favourite" - not sure he's trying to get out of the jobs or he's talking to the tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe if I stick the jar under his nose, he'll get the hint?! Am I letting all women down giving him subtle clues to what I need him to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He currently making noises at the tv whilst playing #RainbowSixSiege - I refuse to do his jobs for him. #ishallnotbebroken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still see the plates on the draining board and someone hasn't moved from the spot I left him in...an hour ago #fianceproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing how long it takes for my love to do the two small jobs I asked him to do tonight. Put the washing up away &amp; wash his lunchbox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA any idea where the 36 city centre 0744 is from Chapel Hill? It's 10 minutes late again!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, you know, off to ballet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBusnews morning. The 36 from St Anne's is almost 20 minutes late (city centre) again. Can you advise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite bit of this weekend. @SLSLSLSLxxx making Forrest cry by telling him she's eaten all the dinosaurs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do is sleep. Can't I just hibernate April?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yogfest I could, but I'd rather not be banned for future trips. America is my favourite country in the whole world. I hate being broke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yogfest ha - I wish I could, I'd give anything to go. It really sucks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dors5881 hey lovely, just money stuff. Life stuff. Regrets. Wish I could go back to BA or AA. Ugh. Hope you are okay honey xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My entire family are going to Florida for two weeks... without me. I can't afford to go and it's made me so sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He chose @POTUS and Darth Vader...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I chose @AnnaKFaris @prattprattpratt as I look up to them, though we don't have much, I'd like to give something back to them and bless them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatting to my other half about what famous people we'd have at our wedding in December if we could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, is this your work @joelneill? #buckspot #wheresbuckie? https://t.co/SHjUUZ2fwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA 36 city centre from st Anne's - just shown up. Been here since 7.35 ðŸ˜¡ some kid has been here an hour..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA morning - so once again 36 city centre hasn't shown up ðŸ˜¡ there's people been here for an hour and no bus. 3rd day running.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA also has your 36 city centre changed its route? Definitely going the wrong way ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA from chapel way (36) to city centre. Surely I can get refunded for this? I'm gonna be late again :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA morning! Second day running bus is late :( yesterday was 0744 was 20 minutes late and the 0808 today is currently 10 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA  bus is here nearly 15 minutes late. Do we get any refund if the buses consistently are late or don't turn up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA the 36 Hengrove Park went past about 5 minutes late but the 36 city centre no sign of :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA can you advise where the 0744 no. 36 from st Anne's to City Centre is please? ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA your bus is late again and I'm going to be late for work... again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wanna know what's happening Twitter?! It's 10.18am, I'm at work and on my second glass of Buck's Fizz, that's what's happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I draw the line and patience runs out when someone full on sneezes on my arm without covering. ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is only half of what our bosses just sent to the office for Christmas. There's 4 of us in today out of 6. https://t.co/aPa8O8AwiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1998:
- Don't get in strangers' cars
- Don't meet ppl from internet

2016:
- Literally summon strangers from internet to get in their car]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelneill @DaniHell_64 was this the work of you guys? https://t.co/D4ANNZ2Xyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulCaudell @666amit apparently Camden food market is the place to go. https://t.co/hnZETmGroD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlight of the day: 74yo old aunt with a metal chicken she bought from Squires, asking Forrest if he wanted to touch the cock repeatedly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBSA your 0744 bus left at 0741 this morning. I know it's marginal but meant we missed the bus. I'm gonna be late now :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBusnews sorry, it was a Bristol bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstBusnews the bus I usually get left 3 minutes early. Meant I missed the bus and now I'm gonna be late :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the 3 boys to do the fireworks. First one, falls over and almost sets fire to my bro in law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get engaged, catch finger on door, finger swells, can't wear ring for 6 weeks ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a baby in the office, I repeat a baby in the office #ovariesexploding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Em_Smith1 he just asking me over a cuppa. True your brother style ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Em_Smith1 maybe ðŸ˜‰ excited though xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I've got an excuse NOT to eat that extra biscuit.. https://t.co/dTTcFJIGo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum just referred to milk as 'cow titty' - she's definitely still on the morphine @bethybobthorton @SLSLSLSLxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixUK are you not showing the new Once Upon A Time? ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could go back and punch 21 year old me in the head right now I would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even at 25 + vat (cough), this struck a chord with me. Great article from a great bunch of people. https://t.co/hdxjNjijrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday. I need dinner ideas for tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it the weekend yet?! I need to tidy the house but I also want to sleep. #adultingproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, @prattprattpratt and @AnnaKFaris are a great example of couple goals. They seem so down to earth, funny and clearly so in love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had 1 hours sleep last night because of my anxiety. I have hit my awake limit and I'd give anything to go to bed. Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonterrey @KrisRochelle @thedancemyth @listener what time are you on stage tonight please? ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see @listener tomorrow and @mewithoutYou on Sunday â¤ï¸ #goodweekendvibes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw @AladdinLondon tonight for my birthday. The Genie killed it. If only I could be as talented as those guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 meetings with 1500 people to book. Me, the only travel consultant in the office. Thank god for @xbadchristianx to keep me sane. #madeit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PokeVisionGo does this work in the UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWOA definitely,I don't have much money and wanted to give him the best day possible.Do you guys think you can do something to help fix it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWOA but staff member where to do so wasn't helpful. Then it started raining so gave up and drove back. Sad, I'd heard really good reviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWOA we've travelled from Bristol and barely got on anything, wanted to pay for another experience so it wasn't a wasted journey but when I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took my other half to @CWOA for his birthday &amp; it is super disappointing. Apart from our giraffe feed this morning (our guide was amazing).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morrisons thank you! I appreciate it! I'll DM now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morrisons Hi Taz &amp; team, did you send anything? Nothing has been received!! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morrisons hey Morrisons, where's my compote? And 2 and a half berries? Disappointing breakfast ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRocketSummer id really love to send you the money for the cd because I know being a touring musician is hard. You guys are a blessing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRocketSummer I don't know if you'll read this but your wife did the sweetest thing today. It honestly made my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what's my favourite thing ever.. When people only pretend to like you when they only want something ðŸ–•ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicakeogh see ya there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to Bristol after two amazing nights of saying goodbye to the band of my youth @ffaf and now back to adulting ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/XOmXWqMRzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fairlady1111 @getreading I know. 3 hours now to do less than a mile. Not happy bunny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@getreading it's taken me 2 hours to do less than half a mile. I'm late for work. This is a BAD start to the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YodelOnline Hi Amy. It was my other half @benthenoise that has the tracking number. I don't think he's had a response yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm getting paid for taking pictures of my receipts with @ReceiptHog &amp; you should too! Earn more w/ my code:glol2869. *not spam*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YodelOnline We're having real issues getting our package. Please could you advise asap!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airfrance it's okay! I know (working for a travel management company) little things like that do get noticed. Sooo my reward? ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @airfrance - I know it's no biggie but you have a spelling mistake on your website. Little things eh? ðŸ˜‰ https://t.co/bOrHQ5fgiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving is stressful. ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmythsToysUK Ashley at your Slough store is a complete star and a credit to your company. She was polite, profession and so helpful!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just cried at Pitch Perfect 2. I'm broken. Send help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to start my new role and a massive exciting challenge. Time to build something great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a cup of tea, we have no milk #britishproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen. Life is not promised to be easy, I've had my fair share of shit and not where I want to be but God is good. https://t.co/sCaaMJUxEh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>