<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey update.   I returned from missing 2 games with a lower body injury.  We lost 4-2.   Got a helper.  #contributing #always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It my father's 80th birthday today.   Happy Birthday Theo!   You are truly the best!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now following @POTUS.  Here we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I broke all of my New Years resolutions within the first 2 hours of the start of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston - we have a problem. https://t.co/LLd93VtA9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was flying in this thing earlier today.   Great ride. https://t.co/EzSpItGjSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Tsawwassen Mills mall. This place is huge.   I feel like I just walked 18 holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@HuffPostCanada: Toronto luxury home sales soar almost 100% in a year https://t.co/G5CoN3QHYI https://t.co/HDvNmKSAWu" Ya.The ex YVR buyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently getting reflexologized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction:   It does NOT feel like spring out there.   If you don't like the weather wait 10 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C. real estate data show sharp decline in foreign investment after tax https://t.co/DZkW9AeHw4   Brutal news.  Harsh stats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Yaletown salted sidewalk.  No ice.  No snow.  That's messed up. https://t.co/w0JlEINGnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK 2017.   Look out.   I'm serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Big Feet for an hour and a half major league rub down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually noticed a real difference in the amount of daylight we got today.  Seems much longer than just 7 days ago. #RightDirection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a hard time believing that it's December 30th, 2017.   I remember the millenium like it was yesterday.   Time is flying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[En route to see @KaseyMicaela @Kendall_Titch and @J_Titchener.   Good times ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflecting on the death of George Michael I remember when the video for Freedom came out.   It had all the top models of the era #straight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Christmas Eve day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shortest day of the year is almost over. From here on in we gain a minute of daylight per day. This is a good thing for many. Me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very happy with my haircut. If you want the same magnificent results go see Nancy at Black to Blonde in Kits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently getting my ears lowered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League update. Playing later tonight. Same team where we tallied up between us 121 PIMs in a 39 minute game.  I'm prepared.  #tinfoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League hockey update. Down 3 zip last night.   Ended up tying it up at 3.  Lost 4-3 with 1:20 to go. #FirstWorldProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like poutine right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shout out to my mother.    She's celebrating the completion of 78 years of existence on this planet tomorrow.   I adore her. #KeepGoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.   Played last night. We were down 4-1.   Climbed back to 4-3 but lost. I had a goal and a helper. #McDavid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 12:12 on 12/12.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new https://t.co/oiQhFU8aqW is out.   Compliments are welcomed.   Insults...not so welcomed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what people in Alberta, Sakatchewan, Manitoba, Ontario, Quebec, N.S., N.B.,  P.E.I., NFLD and Labrador think of our 'snow storm'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big snow, little snow.   Little snow, big snow.   #Snowgate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a snowflake to be seen as of yet.   #BCStorm2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Yukon has tremendous potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flew back from the Yukon tonight. The airport is so simple.  Went through Gate 1.  Flight left 15 minutes early. Great people at Air North!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to head to the Yukon tonight. Tomorrow I will be attending the swearing in of the new Premier @klondike_silver   #InGoodHands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. https://t.co/Ra1nQaljSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.   We beat The Outlaws 4-2.   I had to hit the showers early with a game misconduct.   #Canadian  #OhWell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under 10 days until the launch of the new https://t.co/oiQhFU8aqW.   I'm half excited and half nervous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Scorpio_F6: #Scorpio spread joy and laughter wherever they go." As a Scorpio I have to whole heartedly agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where I was this past weekend.   A winter wonderland. #BirkenheadLake https://t.co/NHIdilV2hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey game update. Quite the tilt last night. We won 6-2.  There was also 121 PIMs. Shout out to Nick for representing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like hurricane winds out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a windy one out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Cowboycerrone: Hey @arielhelwani https://t.co/tkQtAvg39E". What did the other guy look like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it for daylight today?  Really? Now dark until tomorrow morning?   C'mon.   It's only 4:40pm. #harsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Horocasts: #Scorpio can't deal with someone that never show up on time or make promises they can't keep." I have to agree on this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Lifeldeas: I can officially say that  are definitely an Extremist. https://t.co/nmyHMw7I1N" That doesn't look too hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shout out to @klondike_silver on being the newly elected Premier of the Yukon.   Great guy. He will not disappoint.  Congratulations!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The supposed super moon. #DoesntSeemThatSuperToMe https://t.co/ARgB8Yyhov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Others went to war so that I didn't have to.   Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump protesters just rolled by. https://t.co/arP5EGKNZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though shalt not panic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary is going to bed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was the most amount of daylight we are going to see for months.   #hack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is last call tonight? #DST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is going to be a new President in the United States on Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe that we are about to lose an hour of daylight this weekend. Do we have an hour to lose?   It's dark enough already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The baseball season ends tonight.  Isn't it a summer sport?   And isn't it November?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game tonight. Lost 4-2. We had a great start to the season.  Now on a skid. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Movember still a thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's November.   Good luck to all this month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted to have a 30 minute nap.   It turned into over 2 hours.   Woke up groggy. Then saw Wonder Woman and a dinosaur together.   #Halloween]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey league update.  Had a game last night. 10pm start. Should have had 2 goals and 3 assists. Ended up with 0 points. L 4-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like a Friday to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Canucks game in Punjabi.   It's kind of interesting. It's like being in a foreign country. #CBC #HNIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fur protesters just wrapping up another protest.   Ridiculous.  And they are all wearing leather shoes. https://t.co/XtHPg3ut31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at @TheKeg.   Absolutely delicious prime rib is being consumed by me.   Thank you @TheKeg !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Breathing the air in Beijing has the same health risks as smoking 21 cigarettes a day." Lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.  Up 3-1, then down 4-3, then came back and won 5-4. We are 4-1 after 5 games. #TheShow #BecauseItsTheCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@NEWS1130: BREAKING: Wind warning is ended for Metro Vancouver #BCStorm : https://t.co/WrmDPBmQip"  That was the tail end of a typhoon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading out in the #BCStorm to go play beer league hockey. #TeamPlaya #brave #fearless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fur protesters are back at it.  And now they have duck calling whistles.  All during the #BCstorm.  Clowns. https://t.co/4CU1emY1x4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Hillary delete 33,000 emails after being subpoena'd?   I would kinda like an answer to that one.   What was she hiding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@GlobalBC: Drinking and starving is the new trend among Canadian undergrads. https://t.co/LzwCCu6GVe" So glad that I'm an overgrad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@NEWS1130: Samsung Note 7 recall to cost at least $5.3 billion
https://t.co/Wau9vRzq1V" Still lovin' my BlackBerry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put together a land assembly tonight.  4 houses in a row.   Already have the Buyer.   This is the next level of real estate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The calm before the storm. Literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: People tend to confuse being mean with being honest."  Agreed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was just 10:10 on 10/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey coma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@WhatTheFFacts: In French, a walkie-talkie is called a talkie-walkie." Everything is backwards there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@WhatTheFFacts: Alaska was sold to the United States for about 2 cents an acre." Too expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Is Your Cat Depressed? 9 Signs... https://t.co/E7kPjTAStA"  I'll be honest with you...I'm not a big fan of cats....at all.   Period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @BlueJays for relieving stress tonight.   By doing that you will be creating a whole lot more stress in the coming days. Good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to be a hero?  #Jays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this day in 1994  I moved here from Toronto.   Happy Moving Anniversary to me.   #Oct2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League game result. We won our 4th game. 3 and 1 now. First place.   #ItsEarly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@ScanBC: #Delta crews are on scene with a Cessna that crashed at the end of the runway at Bounday Bay Airport. #CZBB" Rough start. #PullUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed up a new listing tonight. 1600 sq ft 1/2 duplex in Kits north of 4th.  In the quiet part. 3100 block. Shows well.  2.298M. Call me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horses in the bike lane.   Is that a violation?   #YaletownProblems https://t.co/djWKrl3LSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo shoot today.   New pics coming for my soon-to-be released new website.   Thank you @kevinclarkphoto. Great job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League game result. We were up 2-0. Then down 5-2.  Then we tied it up 5-5.  OT solved nothing. Off to a shootout.  We won.  6-5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game today at 3pm.  Attendance expected - 0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's Landlords have arrived.   Great. #RoyalsVisitCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@BradyTrett: Slo-mo of MacKinnon's hands on the OT winner. No words. https://t.co/JDdAWL9pQK" Beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: People with smartphones unlock their phone around 110 times each day." Absolutely ridiculous.  #ThatsProbablyMyAverage #yikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Quote_Soup: Love conquers all." You need some cash too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Quote_Soup: You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdoch" Habits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was crusin' beside a Delorean today. Quite the rig. #BackToTheFuture https://t.co/XX0Os8RWmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New website coming soon.   New photos coming soon.   Stay tuned.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>