<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoSeamGripe yes go to https://t.co/D58TdtZZ0r and sign up! we are being careful with our emails ;) as in not too many - ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved the #ProgressMeetup tonight! Thank you will send a lot of info - this was my awkward selfie as I left https://t.co/GsZ8QG4GUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank god for @Beyonce and twins. thank god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like a month of Trump, not a week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but now we need to organize https://t.co/6mZRVl7XTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gift giver you are queen in my dark dark world right now as I try and organize my #dnc member spreadsheet https://t.co/07ujoGKCUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what would be SO awesome is to have a current google doc for #DNC members that gets updated as they change.... but why make anything easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we acknowledge game here.... https://t.co/JSdn8HJnym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From a supporter: signed up at https://t.co/FhrlpPVyfw few days ago and I have gotten 20 emails.  This site is ridiculous.please change this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanCalovich @IsaacM74006 we are opening up the DNC platform to people not companies to donate - small dollar donations move races]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsaacM74006 you must run!! Good luck to you too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope every SINGLE senator votes no on devos - there will literally be NO REASON for a yes.... am watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[call time baby - call time happening now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeSco42149142 @TheYoungTurks @YouTube not the corporate wing....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShoenSteven @TheYoungTurks yep I get that sometimes, curse of the name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with love https://t.co/DpeBojIvyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[members of congress please get on FBlive and show us how you are fighting to #StopTheMuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blizzarding outside @ WeWork Manhattan Laundry https://t.co/tgC0ktOcfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganBurak @TYTPolitics @NomikiKonst @JordanChariton Megan shoot me an email liz@lizforvicechair.com and thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of our best hopes right now is @SenJohnMcCain - who knew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SAGawards would love to see more celebrities wear some protest tshirts and jeans and head to the airports now. thank you @kalpenn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhoWhatWear @chrissyteigen sorry I love you guys but please you should flag the refugee crisis - women who love fashion care! #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movement has started see ACLUs amount raised - we must keep fighting https://t.co/eMfatTt7lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jZv6bgwe1A loved #DNCforum thank you Houston!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No hate no fear refugees are welcome #nobanbnowall @ The White House https://t.co/jcCmlZkde9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now the White House - #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/QvcWLvI3ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am only using @lyft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just landed #DCA saw families crying and holding each other - this is not who we are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headed home - Houston was amazing #DNCforum - we signed up 100 folks to help, get information and take action - look out for a survey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is real life, congress needs to stage a sit in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profpeaton sign up and we can put you to work!!! https://t.co/2uadippEj6 and more thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are Americans and all our welcome - congress stage a sit in please https://t.co/LK98aEQxWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can't see his wife - interview was scheduled Valentine's Day they were so happy. It got cancelled this morning https://t.co/KO2dnunZ4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.katie and @CD_Menefee signed up through @RefugeeAssist  to help get people out -all lawyers do that now https://t.co/0iCg5Hh3l2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every member of congress should be at their airport now - I don't care why- get there and help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamenta @HillaryClinton sorry you feel that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamenta @HillaryClinton #LoveArmy come with us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers trying to find out names of refugees on last flight in @iah they need the names to petition and get them out - where are we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@houston keep going @DFWAirport are you guys letting people out? https://t.co/dG65rOOH6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes @cerafinah you're right @iah https://t.co/1r1fDMRhEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. Heather is here @iah only one family so far. @realDonaldTrump stop what you're doing https://t.co/USNeVdIXzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.headed to @iah jeans are needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in case anyone was confused - no do not ask for permission..... #DNCforum - just do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everyone has a lot of advice for candidates,  but never forget why you ran in the first place -to fight, we are coming @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanasmith looking forward to talking about how we can open up the DNC to all the movements out there - #DNCforum there are more of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToluseO see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankBruni see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobbyCervantes see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeneps see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubycramer see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daviddesola see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gdebenedetti see you there - millennials are running for vice chair - speak with us, we are fighting #DNCforum https://t.co/JwA21pC8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And %}*{€{? Just got real. Let's do this #DNCforum https://t.co/69d7cNfeQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok @PatrickSvitek will be at the forum today - we are running for office baby! I'll be looking for you: https://t.co/eglLE3IAuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6IRMXSxtz3: Change that Matters watch it live! Im on 1.50pm CT #DNCforum  https://t.co/tjtagJdfZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieLevin I'm telling @Rosejackson3 to send me all her democrats today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send them to me!!! We need them tomorrow at noon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met with some incredible people living in Houston through @SarahLabo and they are ready to take action - we are just doing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I'm saying is it was pretty darn good crawfish #DNCforum in Houston https://t.co/6D7n4Osh8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Houston right #DNCforum https://t.co/FeBc610PIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zakouts84 can you change back your avatar to Hudson? I'm sure he has a resist tshirt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are coming  https://t.co/9hURJQEPVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LindseyGrahamSC is on fire  https://t.co/E7xrhgTvwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Crowdpac 'swamp' office now officially full and we got all the @OBEYGIANT posters from @womensmarch https://t.co/EL8PERxxjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the little things in life .... https://t.co/UbBIeQH751]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we are on again Houston flight 7am slightly later here we come #DNCforum https://t.co/ZrsbMb35yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes to all of this - though living with a scientist (physicist) myself, we may need to give them some charm training https://t.co/plqZKoE1ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothypmurphy @MotherJones a lot of what you're talking about is playing out in the Vice Chair race and I'd be happy to speak with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley @joss we ARE @runforsomething!!!! We are all running! We have to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DNC flagged some items, so I added them verbatim - many many thanks to the Secretary's team for taking the time! https://t.co/wMzkXVzJq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VOVatzC9RG this is just everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Run for Something: A strategic plan” by @runforsomething https://t.co/BPvzvoU7KO - this is why we'll win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TomPerez_DNC @EllisonCampaign @Harrison4DNC @wethednc @jehmufordnc @PeteforDNC #rayfordnc we are running #DNCChair https://t.co/DBoiqLAig3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[winter already came, now we're just in a f*** blizzard. GoT referencing hard https://t.co/VWGuxRJ74B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The men currently running for #DNC Vice Chair @BlakeforDNC @AdamForDNC @RickPalacio @MitchCeasar and how it works https://t.co/DBoiqLAig3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The women currently running for #DNC Vice Chair @latoiajones @mcbyrne @RepGraceMeng @MariaEDurazo @LornaJohnsonMSN https://t.co/DBoiqLAig3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we talk about how much Candidates are raising for #DNCChair -transparent? - because most of that should be going to build our bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “A super sexy subject: How the DNC elects Vice Chairs….” https://t.co/j2UiYNiMWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikalyoung not at all!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikalyoung not at all - would love you there - can you fill this out? https://t.co/zL856oUujS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for everyone offering to support and help! we are ready now to take action so please sign up here: https://t.co/ykzfaB25Ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flippable_org actually Georgia needs a new Voter Protection person - think you can help with that? let me know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can help me with a crowdsourcing project today or tomorrow - to help bring transparency to the DNC please message me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a HUGE fan of @sethmoulton and what he's fighting for - he's not afraid to challenge democratic "rules" and he… https://t.co/YA3s20WOb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to @wethednc for inviting me to #demsincolor tonight and meeting @Koran4sterling - @IdahoDems r lucky https://t.co/ic4Lpuabvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atima_omara  are you kidding! Eating with @Koran4sterling - can we talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #demincolor forum but also please note 3 millennial women running for vice chair were all in the audience @latoiajones @mcbyrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This terrifies me - media keep hitting with facts that's all. Regardless of what they say  https://t.co/mU3vguuAPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaywardWinifred working with the Internet and amazing people online who want to help open up the DNC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music to my ears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing sending you member names now. I think we have to open up. But this means social media if they have it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes all this https://t.co/yZOK3SrPnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpydyrrHeath ok - set up a pledge page so you can see if you have support  @Crowdpac can help thats step 1! https://t.co/cgVZKPf6tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcbyrne @OHDems I loved "rise up" - generally I hate emails. Looks like OH is crushing it - did donors resonate with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OHDems @mcbyrne she got the "Rise Up" one - completely agree - it was awesome and clear what you needed. did you raise good $ from it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamSeder hi sam - I love that you are covering the vice chair races - we need to bring attention to them! thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hmcghee this is what we talked about https://t.co/CdBXfkR4Su]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>