<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki4Him Think about it. Til now best they had was "Infidels! Kill the disbelievers and kufaar" Now it's "They hate muslims &amp; bar from US"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki4Him I honestly don't think you realise the damage this will do... He's handed #ISIS a huge propaganda victory on a silver platter ðŸŽ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikePenceVP @Bryan700 Sweet Jesus Tapdancing Christ... #backinyourbox #Veep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it bad I'm hoping Chinese Navy hands @realDonaldTrump his own arse if he tries a blockade (with no injury to US Marines/Sailors)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's required here in @Ireland To be fair https://t.co/Vd0GSkkNPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carol_xox Pretty much. Also (shocker) @DermotBannon is butting heads with the homeowners #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes OMG @realDonaldTrump will you ever GROW THE FUCK UP!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyOfHedon I've kind of moved on now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenoconnell @williamspat929 Jesus will ya let him deliver the bowl of shamrock?! Also May said fuck all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FancySparkles @TheAnonnMessage I got that, I was simply wondering why a secular group such as @GroupAnon would resort to religion...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAnonnMessage WHAT?!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyOfHedon I live in Ireland. @realDonaldTrump has no jurisdiction over me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tchalladaisy Basically...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repealthe8thplz I'll be interested to see if this actually happens in any big way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiara_keane Told my girlfriend about #strike4repeal said she hasn't heard of it and when I said it was on Twitter she just rolled her eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillWtroyer @mikd33 Well @BarackObama had to deal with CONSTANT refusal to cooperate from the GOP on almost everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Which has NOTHING to do with the fact that you lost the popular vote by about that margin right? #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyOfHedon @piersmorgan FFS bullshit or not PEOPLE ARE ENTITLED TO THEIR VIEWS! This is a democracy you cretin ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan You don't have to be that nasty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost a lot of respect for @mcgregor_ewan for this silliness https://t.co/iEKSIWZr6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgregor_ewan So go on and engage with @piersmorgan and challenge his views. It's this sort of unwillingness to engage that led to Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Have you read the article? She said nothing of the sort! https://t.co/zO8Vn5IofQ - via @xychelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews N4 interchange Westbound where it joins after Chapelizod. Happened around 18:15 both drivers were out talking and all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews Seems #DB66a crashed into a car ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassbwell Surely the Twitterverse has helped too?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OverheardDublin "First and last time I buy that fish, it was so FISHY!! ðŸ˜·" ðŸ¤£ðŸ¤£ #OverheardConversation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcorway We'll have to agree to disagree there man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcorway Couldn't give a monkey's what he loves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcorway Well a lot of the Irish public are interested to know for various reasons, that's what it is to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcorway What's the problem? Yardstick for @realDonaldTrump commitment to US-Irish relations also @CaitrionaPerry is a National Treasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @MrTommyCampbell I dislike Trump but to be fair - one is a secure line whereas the other is not. Obama had the same two phones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danfrekincucino @rolandscahill @realDonaldTrump Not yet he hasn't...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Combat1Wombat I wouldn't have even responded to that @NicoleArbour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InternetHippo @Phonycian Maybe 10 year old children should be off-limits though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah lads come ON like... #repealthe8th #Strike4Repeal #WeWontWait https://t.co/Z5ssYK8fo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briandelivers @tiara_keane @MrHoppy_ He tweeted. Lack of engagement, verbal abuse of those who don't hold our views led to President Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiara_keane I understand your point, but (Devil's Advocate for a sec) I see some holes. What if a man agrees with you? He can't legislate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrHoppy_ @sarcastrophe420 @briandelivers Mate if you want to be treated like an adult, don't be so childish... Christ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briandelivers @tiara_keane If you pair actually tried ENGAGING @MrHoppy_ and explaining where his argument has holes you might get further]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiara_keane Good point but you KNOW there are those who don't classify abortion as "basic healthcare"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevie_Z @SarahPalinUSA I was wondering myself - that doesn't count as "soaring stock" at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassbwell I would get on it but I disagree with ANYONE being punched because of their beliefs, no matter how nefarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@13spencer All fun and games until he somehow finds some nefarious way to ruin them or otherwise have them taken off air]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls and @SeanSpicer are excelling in their new roles bigly #Spicerfacts #alternativefact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_P_Williams @realDonaldTrump He didn't write that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump More of this Mr. President. Less of the other. Pity you didn't write this tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholasPell Cop on @NeilMooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@november17 @Treadstone71LLC @realDonaldTrump I know exactly what he'd say "You're disgusting"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@98FM FFS how quickly people forget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJTFOIR @CENTCOMArabic @iraqicts @USEmbBaghdad @Iraqiairforce @Defense_Iraq Anyone care to translate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilmizzirish OK then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @ikebarinholtz I quite like Piers and I know neither of you have heard of me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt He already did. I'm too lazy to link but see the speech to the CIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carol_xox Couldn't agree more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JOEdotie Really not cool whatever his politics...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibyaLiberty @Home_Halfway @TSG_SiLent Note this person is also a member of US Armed Forces so @DeptofDefense could take a look also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibyaLiberty @Home_Halfway @TSG_SiLent He didn't delete it he just blocked you. I've reported the tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSG_SiLent US Media and @POTUS keep telling us the ordinary US Serviceman/woman is decent... then I read your tweets... @DeptofDefense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brendinater @maevehiggins @RossOCK I have and let me tell you they are lovely! A bit too lovely...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President never gave a gift of nine luxury cars to John Gotti associate Robert LiButti #SpicerFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec @seanspicer "The sky is actually yellow. You've all been victims of mass colour-blindness. PERIOD" #SpicerFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razormind To be honest I could never really grasp the point of #ethereum - did #blockchain technology no favours though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razormind Nah it's dead. Especially since it had to hard fork which incidentally exposes a potential flaw in block chain technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razormind What about people who are genuinely allergic to gluten, coeliacs like my gf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Not just for your family, nor even The US. Do you know how worried the rest of the world are now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DefenceForces If the unthinkable happened to a fellow member of Nordic Battle Group would we need to get involved? https://t.co/cVzGUlo0L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's awkward. I hope for Barry's own sake he doesn't wake up... #StrikingOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SligoChap @MaiaDunphy @FLOTUS44 I think pepper spray or mace would have been more appropriate ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ObamaFoundation @BarackObama What a lovely video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Am I allowed to say I dislike you intensely yet hope to visit USA again soon or are you gonna close border to me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholasPell I hope for their sake you're right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrTrunney Well that was uncalled for... #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katenash @LayBeattie Yeah I'm really unhappy about this too #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeanfromPa I thought Michelle Obama was very classy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah lads - trash talk @realDonaldTrump new @POTUS but this trouble on the streets setting fire to limousines etc. is stupid #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MenonTalks77 I'd have jammed mine into his fucking neck, twisted it and pulled it out. Let the cunt bleed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MenonTalks77 He's giving them away as he goes as souvenirs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What about the rest of us around the world? ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone who can lip-read tell me what @realDonaldTrump is saying to @BarackObama right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilmizzirish He literally told the rest of the world to fuck off #AmericaFirst Watch how the stock markets react... #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@todayfm They were handing over the nuclear football...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're American this sounds great. If you're not... Ay Dios mio... #Inauguration #AmericaFirst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's raining in Washington DC. Even God is crying #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilmizzirish I saw those military officers and I hoped it was a coup. It was actually them handing over the nuclear football #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God was that the lad delivering the Nuclear Football? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go... #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer giving a big fuck you to @realDonaldTrump ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonsnowC4 He's finally reached his "Oh shit what have I done?" moment #noclue #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Home_Halfway I hope you're right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump's face though ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld @ReaganBattalion I feel so bad for that kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieMcCormack Can we leave the ten year old kid alone? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@domjoly Leave him alone, he's ten!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pundamentalism I wish one of them had bayoneted the cunt #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Barron Trump being made to get back a bit by his older half-brother and half-sister #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Fun car journey so... #frosty #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell ya what, I wouldn't want to be @SecretService right now - security and logistical nightmare! #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol @BarackObama taking @realDonaldTrump by the arm - body language still says "I'm still top dog" #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well... Was it just me or did it seem a little... frosty between @MichelleObama and @MELANIATRUMP? #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looting and people smashing shop windows in Washington DC - cops using water cannon and pepper spray #inauguration]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>