<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone asks me that question at customs, there is going to be trouble. https://t.co/dBqh1Ry4M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Staff Rethink Tactics After Stumbles https://t.co/AU4myMUjwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[84 Lumber Journey https://t.co/WcG94xoKMn via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did a Dr. Seuss WWII Political Cartoon Criticize America's Isolationism? https://t.co/YH0Hq5m3KQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @realDonaldTrump You made all my artsy liberal friends give a shit about football #riseup #fighting5th #u&amp;thePatriotssuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up from Georgia Resistance https://t.co/1VV9evoVIs via @privy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All those upset with Berkeley bc peaceful protest makes the point better were SUPER impressed &amp; convinced by the women's march, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Like others I want to know how to get paid for protesting as I have been doing it for free. Do they have health insurance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got to see Arrival.  It was really, really good. Also I identified with Amy Adams' character very strongly #smartwomensavetheworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The anarchists are the ones punching Nazis. Your guys are the Nazis. #goteampunchnazis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is enough, I guess... https://t.co/M0XteC2wji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too. #sfwritersresist https://t.co/g2O7R7RTst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WE THE PEOPLE https://t.co/z7mYtcz2pS via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packed room again, more than last time even. We are picking up momentum. #dekalbdemocrats… https://t.co/avOQyjuOBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally LOL'D at some of the comments. https://t.co/yyEHDQQFi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fortnight of Trump https://t.co/ybbeIf8G4q via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potus Good job saving us from five year olds. Idiot.. #ImpeachTrump #ImpeachPresidentBannon #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepHankJohnson Not ten days in and he has already broken the law multiple times.  #ImpeachTrump #ImpeachPresidentBannon #DefendtheRepublic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov @CustomsBorder You didn't have control over it before? What were you doing? Quit stalling and comply with the court order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg The Lysistrata gambit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nnedi Right there with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascists go after the most vulnerable first. This is a test. If you aren't outraged, you failed. #NoWallNoBan #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nasty Weather" by Juliana Finch  https://t.co/OHWZD43ohR via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potus @realDonaldTrump @seanspicer  Why did you shut down the White House comment line? What are you afraid of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ClimateMarch in April. #LGBTmarch in June. #ScienceMarch tbd  #BlackLivesMatter ?  #NoDAPL #Sovereignty ? Come on, everyone can play!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson You spelled "inheritance tax that only affects the super-rich" wrong. Piketty says only way to save capitalism is raise it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theodoragoss @Slate Yes. You clearly don't understand what is happening here. You're not even "next"; he's already attacking the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I guess that'll make you a posse comitatus grabber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course they aren't.  American taxpayers are. The question is, who is going to get paid? #CorruptTrump… https://t.co/hqHlE9Why2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats No, but I sure would like to see you put up more of a fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potus will profit from DAPL. #CorruptTrump self-dealing from the White House week one #NoDAPL #NoKXL #divestdonald #showusyourtaxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson @sendavidperdue  6 generations of my family have been educators in GA. DeVos is not qualified to be Secretary of Education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson @sendavidperdue Support Georgia entrepreneurs and keep the ACA. Protect Georgians with chronic illness and keep the ACA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson @sendavidperdue I called both your offices today. I'm diabetic &amp; if I can't get insurance I can't start a business this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanBarton1 For a second I thought you were talking about me and @mightybattlecat  I think we are likely bedfellows. Er, friends :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first job was working for Greenpeace. #truthismoreawesomethanfiction https://t.co/aUtL9cTngX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's somewhere for the people who attended the #WomensMarch to put energy #NODAPL #itsallconnected https://t.co/htJVq0P3F4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myhairisblue what uterus-havers do with theirs. Doesn't matter if you id as man, woman, or genderqueer, if you can get pregnant YOU DECIDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myhairisblue Having pondered this a little more, I don't agree that it excludes trans ppl. It excludes non-uterus-havers from dictating /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[54, white, rural, lifelong Republican protesting Trump. &lt;3 https://t.co/XlyFSHRmav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myhairisblue I know trans ppl are in serious danger too. We can talk about all of it, both/and, but only so much fits on one sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myhairisblue Restrictions on abortion could literally kill me. Can I talk about that without checking with everyone else for once?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lsarsour did a tremendous, magical thing and now the Islamophobes are scared &amp; on the attack. #ImarchwithLinda any day of the week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wrong."  And that's "millions of women who marched." https://t.co/8cXdMZuW0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a 20 year old supermodel, my dog is  well-behaved, and my house is always clean #alternatefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #dearassailantinchief nm I found the answer here https://t.co/y0rDJCZcF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear a crowd chantng the name of their Congressional district? #JohnLewis just walked by. #pickedthewrongfight #district5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People hooting and hollering and we aren't even to Decatur yet. This is going to be fun. #AtlantaMarch #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #dearassailantinchief Maximizing Profits for Insurance Companies Again https://t.co/UmVz50d9Az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[men get approval for the same thing we did that got ignored. Do what you'd like to see done for you: listen, amplify, and give credit. /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep in mind it's maddening for WoC to see us get a positive response where they get negative or none, just like it's maddening to see /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND...Do more planned civil disobedience. Because optics. Remember we didn't get the vote by being nice. #goodtrouble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'll be like we are super heroes with "charm police" as a power. USE IT FOR GOOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No arrests yesterday is prob attributable to numbers &amp; % of middle-aged white women there. Answer: we need to come out for ALL the protests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta March #womensmarch https://t.co/Aaqu1iJfOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AtlantaMarch #womensmarch https://t.co/AhHwa0X2Xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my brotherTony's signature phrases. https://t.co/N7REkojrOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-abortion guy with bullhorn shouted down by a women chanting MY BODY MY CHOICE and LOVE NOT HATE MAKES AMERICA GREAT #AtlantaMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crossing Marietta St passing the Omni. Sign says "John Lewis for Pres" #WomensMarch #AtlantaMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinseighGreen I just passed the Ferris wheel #AtlantaMarch #womensmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AtlantaMarch #womensmarch @ Center for Civil and Human Rights https://t.co/LiTvg7ndXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AtlantaMarch #womensmarch https://t.co/bY0JIEOlpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/W4DfP0fwkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many people showed up that the streets and sidewalks are wall to wall people &amp; we are moving very slowly.  #AtlantaMarch #womensmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AtlantaMarch #womensmarch https://t.co/vCSwp6cB9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd chanting "NOT ONE STEP BACK" #ATLANTAMARCH #womensmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of signs name-checking #JohnLewis and the #5thDistrict #AtlantaMarch #womensmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AtlantaMarch #womensmarch @ Center for Civil and Human Rights https://t.co/3mHVKTHVqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is definitely the biggest protest crowd I have ever seen. #AtlantaMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People hooting and hollering and we aren't even to Decatur yet. This is going to be fun. #AtlantaMarch #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Eastlake station. Now standing room only and people are singing "America the Beautiful." #AtlantaMarch #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MARTA train also full of marchers, despite the pouring rain. Maybe more than I've ever seen. #AtlantaMarch #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kensington Station full of people in pussy hats and carrying signs #atlanta #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMamatas HELP US SCOTTISH TWITTER YOU'RE OUR ONLY HOPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drove through Mirkwood (ie Ponce west of Decatur) on may way to Mordor. Wish me luck. #district5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So why black people defined by black urban poverty? If you assumed Atlanta was really a hole bc majority black, you are part of the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people are not defined by white rural poverty, which is either invisible or "othered" onto Appalachia. That is a different problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not knowing anything about black history or the black middle class leads to not knowing anything about Atlanta. The reason is the same. (4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More music, art, and dance come out of Atlanta than you know. But also 100+ year old black owned businesses and the intellectual centers (3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Atlanta is great and prosperous not IN SPITE OF its essentially black character and culture, but BECAUSE OF them. Music &amp; art, yes, (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being serious for a minute...Trump is relying on racist ideas about #inners to slander #JohnLewis and the #5thDistrict (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primediscussion @jkrelldavis Ding ding ding. But there have been black owned businesses and a black middle class here for over 100 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnitedConsulting How many of your contracts are in the #5thDistrict ? How do you suppose they feel abt #JohnLewis being called names?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kssturgis62  Hush. You don't live here, you don't know Atlanta, and you sure as hell don't know John Lewis. Stop embarrassing yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From my terrible sojourn on the west side of Atlanta Friday night, amid drunken revelry and loud music… https://t.co/OW2tZnC7du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH THE HUMANITY #district5 #nopenottiredyet https://t.co/IfABrhzt3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mere mention of #JohnLewis ' name just got a standing ovation here. #atlantaliveslewis #pickedthewrongfight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @gaffe_tape I had to wait in line for my vegan cheesexake today in #district5 #prayforus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating sugar-free cheesecake at a vegan bakery while a music video is being shot across the street in #district5 #weareneverlettingthisgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When people visit Atlanta I take them to the King Center, Fernbank, the High Museum and Mary Mac's...all in the 5th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep Mr. John Lewis' name out of your mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retired UGA professor Judith Ortiz Cofer dies; remembered for literary talent and teaching | Online Athens https://t.co/3BiZmS4oVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait...Mombi? I think I know what is going on... #EmeraldCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbc I can't believe you would run ad aimed at chemotherapy patients. #opdivo is horrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion piece by George Chidi https://t.co/Z7iLuaL9UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Christmas at Ground Zero  https://t.co/QITkYuPOpa  #dearassailantinchief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter Witch:  Milk, cinnamon stick, pinch of cardamom, warm then add an ounce of Strega. You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keppa85 @caseyo4 @NateSilver538 That was just to maintain what we already have while reducing. Now contemplate how much increase will cost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #dearassailantinchief Amendments and Oppressions  https://t.co/kBfIIQycxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Republican Forms of Government https://t.co/DvOwjgJOxH  #dearassailantinchief #republicansagainstdemocracy #Constitution]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>