<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS the refugees are already stringently vetted prior to getting their visas and you know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump not one person from the countries you have banned has killed an American citizen on American soil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews crazy should work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @joe_warmington do you remember that your country has a constitution and that you are not a king or despot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP24 the hypocrisy is staggering.  Typical Conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scott_tobias well the swamp has been refilled now it is time to damage other things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deepgreendesign I am a very proud Canadian.  Even more so now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deepgreendesign thank you. I think I did it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deepgreendesign thank you. I will look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deepgreendesign yeah...no. I have a Samsung.  It just seems even more important now to proclaim one's citizenship.  Thank you anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deepgreendesign dumb question.  How do you get that Canadian flag by your name? I want one and can't figure out how to do it?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RCdeWinter @throwitinmyhat are these creeps going to be allowed now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithboykin @CNN he is either paying them or they are very stupid people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scott_tobias these people are insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsbie let him do it on his own time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy oh no. Some village is missing a lot of idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @hardball @NBCNews @MSNBC @ABC but clarify clearly that they killed no one on American soil and Obama did not place a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvalis this sounds like one of Trump's incomprehensible speeches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seedrooster @kbeninato @chelseahandler isn't protest part of your constitution? Much like the gun part you guys love so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbeninato that is absolutely no excuse. He wanted this job now man up and do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS are you still talking about yourself in the third person?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldThumb @DaveMosher he didn't ban refugees from Saudi Arabia or Egypt where he has business dealings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @joe_warmington what about the bad hombres who have actually killed Americans! Saudi Arabia and Egypt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel @RonaAmbrose I thought they were always taxed because they are part of your salary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntoniaZ @realDonaldTrump @TrumpDraws @selectall this must give Americans sure how pride in their president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpDraws at least he spelled horse correctly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonaAmbrose do you think it might have been more respectful to those who were murdered in Quebec to wait a day or two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple he is the only Conservative that I would even give a moment's thought to voting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 by affected, does he mean tortured, demeaned, deprived, and murdered? Is there a happy genocide? I think my head is exploding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Gilmore @nytimes he probably needs him to look a bit smarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LTEJakee @mikd33 @realDonaldTrump of course it is religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump many of them are now running your country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders or Russians hoping the deplorables and despicables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo @chriscaple good to take care of the important things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 how do these insane people justify this? Muslims were murdered while praying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntoniaZ not to mention stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip she has the same IQ as Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saletan @chriscaple she has been around Trump for way too long. She is incoherent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul @chriscaple he probably wouldn't have won without Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you are the one who appears mentally unstable and likely to start a war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotAltWorld @guardian he has the intellect of a gnat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costareports you lost that title when nobody stood up to Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell @throwitinmyhat is this the KKK  David Duke?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomsoncbc damn. That would really have him wringing his tiny hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_scottreid @POTUS oh sure. Throw me to the wolves. He will come for you next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomsoncbc @CBCAlerts are there more people than for Trump's inauguration.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpHotels the Trump brand is despicable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenMaryWatson @joeharris @realDonaldTrump @POTUS respect has to be earned. He is a waste of oxygen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @joe_warmington and you have made it more of a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiObaro good for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobRae48 my God. Does Cheney have a conscience?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple @realDonaldTrump was that necessary? ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evelynne24 @radtoria @JustinTrudeau and you would rather have a racist, misogynist, lying orange guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TexasSheri @TomBullington @JustinTrudeau not the 3 million dead people who voted for Hilary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanniAndrew @tayfeh oh but he will. You are OK with his persecuting others but when it is you, you will want help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS when are you sending back the Statue of Liberty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanniAndrew @tayfeh another Trump troll. You might care when he turns on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tayfeh I am sorry but Canada is better anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digby56 I wonder if they remember Timothy McVeigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanBrendle I will never forget the feeling when it exploded. It was terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple you scare the he'll out of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS truth is gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ipoliticsca worried about the ramifications to their reelection or real concern for the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple Oh!!That makes me sad. I didn't give it much of a read as I figured it was just more hate from Trump minions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple Really?  I am having a lot of difficulty telling what is true and what is lies.  I hate to think it is true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Min_Reyes I don't know how anyone could work with a man who is so bat shit crazy. I tried to think of a more elegant term..but no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple this sounds like more crap from Trump followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoungDems4Trump @joe_warmington @kinni00 then how can you be for Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RajuAjo @Peggynoonannyc @CBNNews I have known a lot of people who proclaim their Christianity who were evil, backstabbing liars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peggynoonannyc @CBNNews and nobody pretends to be a Christian ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogueNASA @OrrinHatch why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robyndoolittle it is so easy to take a stand on an issue which you will never face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxBusiness @joe_warmington @VP especially when he is obsessed with numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@v12hockey @ddale8 but he has books on the presidential desk and...wait for it...papers!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 obviously a rather dumb person. Much like Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 the man is a moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I love reading your information but the print is so damn small! !! Am I doing something wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougSaunders @robyndoolittle do these guys only know the part of the constitution pertaining to guns? What about free speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters does he mean starting today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders his daughter should too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer when you know you are outright lying you should do the honourable thing and quit.  His credibility is gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_warmington @politico come on Joe.  Nobody has been this bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacleansMag he can't save himself from himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthugrantham @tonyposnanski @DISKKANE2008 @POTUS good luck with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @chriscaple call them out on every lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I was trying to not hear him but did I hear big ly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisrockyoz @ozlifeadvice he is an amazing ,charismatic, intelligent man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinNewmanCTV @CTVW5 @TrumpInaugural I am in Japan.  He has 2 hours here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisdonovan @Scott_Gilmore Trump doesn't have the class of a gnat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson @MrIanMacIntyre too late!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@berngiacomazzo Daniel Dale has been fact checking Trump crap for the past 18 months. What rock have you been living under.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddCTV @CTVNews I plan on sticking my head under the covers a d hoping it doesn't happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 does Godliness mean cheating and adultery in their world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple he seems to be aligning himself  with dictators. Sadly, America's choice may destroy the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenAtHome most women I know look at him and want to throw up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters it is like letting a fox into the hen house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX @ColinPeters isn't that conflict of interest in countries that are sane?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @wzzm13 what is the matter with these people?  Are they suffering from dementia or just plain stupidity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscaple from the little I have read, he seemed like a good, honest man.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>