<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The St Patrick's day visit will go ahead, and I sincerely hope @EndaKennyTD speaks as gaeilge during the entire shamrock bowl ceremony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeannedesutun how did you avoid seeing Star Wars all those years? Need to avoid a dominant malign cultural phenomenon. Asking for a world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBrillQuill @BBCNews just four short years away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebrillquill so close! Derry's old Waterside railway station bought by Translink https://t.co/OU0h8aw3fW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. https://t.co/GhDuEAqika]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried moving to the country. Now I spend the savings travelling to Sydney | Brigid Delaney's diary https://t.co/T7PoHf3O3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start as you mean to go on - the thin-skinned buffoon has nothing more important to do and is baited by a tweet yet… https://t.co/GtZLjssahq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Making Plans To Go Completely Legit After Vice Presidency https://t.co/NdjdNhtR5w via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccourtvolta as soon as we get back from Florida!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last hope is that the embodiment of flatulence with a rotting pumpkin for a head will never complete the oath because he keeps adlibbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The Canadian businessman who sponsored 200 refugees https://t.co/s48hWOtidD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwoovo Daredevil - I almost got thrown out of the cinema for sitting upside-down in a futile attempt to make the movie enjoyable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I see #JimmysHall I'm reminded of how little Ireland has changed - cf @exchangedublin #tg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will happen to the Kurds? https://t.co/BDQ6DKpxVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[more books coming: https://t.co/nwlM9BS3Yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my food-baby just kicked...

Hope everyone's enjoying this ridiculous time of year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccourtvolta I emphasised the one word the players never hear - character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Why a disabled person was assaulted in an Indian cinema https://t.co/5IJN1hBR8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting Ireland's groundbreaking Women on Walls at the RIA https://t.co/ruvY3vmIw2 via @rte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialism for the Rich, Capitalism for the Poor: An Interview With Noam Chomsky https://t.co/FI5zHhEUFd via @truthout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - E-cigarettes major concern, says US https://t.co/KNLSUJUvK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccourtvolta no way, I'll have a new, protective stomach lining of chocolate by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The abandoned mansions of billionaires https://t.co/G4j1WbKStK via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secrets of life hidden in enormous caves https://t.co/2N7rSKKOo1 via @BBC_Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rare fish swims upside down https://t.co/el8NzYApi1 via @BBCEarth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nation that hates to be late https://t.co/1PvUhv9m9Y via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The European country that loves being sad  https://t.co/vPxujzfhu2 via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Four major cities move to ban diesel vehicles by 2025 https://t.co/gGgJYNKesV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccourtvolta thanks!! Looking forward to your cooking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A museum of 500,000 oddities https://t.co/afaVVB4ZqJ via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Martin Shkreli: Australian boys recreate life-saving drug https://t.co/6B6YbTHsvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The World Has a Playground Deficit” by Christine Ro https://t.co/LZupH25JRb @ctd_dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s Time For a New Kind of Power Fantasy” by @leighalexander https://t.co/kZPuYKqmAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honourable mention for @DublinTenants during the Secure Rent+ Tenancies Bill in the Dail #rentcontrolsnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universities accused of 'importing Sports Direct model' for lecturers' pay https://t.co/IkPJEMczha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q6 Ireland has new engagmnt structure called Public Participation Network for voluntary groups to have a voice -slow progress! #CityLinkHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q6 cities are complex organisms, government can't know enough about needs of citizens so we need to talk to each other more #CityLinkHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuhitApp @CityLinkFest or customers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuhitApp pretty positively afaik #CityLinkHour https://t.co/FZ9u1ldqYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q5 decisions need to stay local+be open to all input - give communities time so they don't feel ambushed or railroaded #CityLinkHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityLinkFest allowed people to see process and progress through local authority bureaucracy transparently! #CityLinkHour Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CityLinkHour Q3 favourite public space is Marlay Park - green, quiet, meadows, paths through woods, sports facilities+gigs -mixed uses4all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityLinkFest a small town in Spain had their mayor field+followup complaints&amp; Qs about public domain maintenance on Twitter! #CityLinkHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityLinkFest so many to choose from... Dublin's public spaces are grey, smallish and surrounded by traffic. Parks are gated closed at 6pm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityLinkFest I live in Dublin and I'm at a meeting of @DublinTenants - a group working for fair and affordable rents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bystander's Guide to Standing up Against Islamophobic Harassment (and Other Types of Harassment, Too) https://t.co/Pz0Kt8Ccx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Indigenous Activists in Norway Got the First Bank to Pull Out of the Dakota Access Pipeline https://t.co/Y6PLIpOoRj via @truthout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can we exercise a choice over? Nothing else is worth worrying about. https://t.co/mFq8b4kvNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Your Insecurity Is Bought and Sold https://t.co/XGGWXZxonM via @IAmMarkManson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 130-year-old play that makes sense of our times https://t.co/iilzdxGTnL via @BBC_Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than Coffee: New York’s Vanishing Diner Culture https://t.co/zXdd2Ti8Gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... though that reads like a call to stop him reading, which may not help...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add 'Bowling Alone' and 'Angels Of Our Better Nature' - Stop Trump Reading List https://t.co/XlzaK4K9SX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 50 Best Ambient Albums of All Time https://t.co/dbi05Wieaa via @pitchfork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to love walking at night. So much easier to think in the quiet air. The joy of walking in cities at night https://t.co/f1UiO4HbOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasgow University offers a Simpsons philosophy class – and it makes perfect sense @aintnoquillo https://t.co/F9wKen7ZMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grief comes in five stages. But when it comes to Trump, I can’t get past anger https://t.co/PFZPwpXm9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article 50 claimant Gina Miller: 'It isn’t safe for me to go outside' https://t.co/cul6LnlaOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Hundred Thousand Unwelcomes. - https://t.co/9rBoZWdtmO via @wearerabble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gurgaon: what life is like in the Indian city built by private companies https://t.co/NNRgPHVCxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - In pictures: Gang City https://t.co/Erq8yCiBm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelSkolnik @evapaterson can't wait to see what Carson has planned for 'inner cities'. Pyramids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the world rot at Europe's largest tech conference https://t.co/nLqcTpdhMy @fitzsij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensational coelacanth discovery https://t.co/gwQPnICch1 via @BBCEarth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The British island at the edge of the world https://t.co/W0pnzsCpz4 via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Monkey News has taken a sinister turn - 'Monkey attack' on girl sparks deadly clan clashes in Libya https://t.co/s9Dn0IY0Zc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Nixon’s 1987 Letter to Future Candidate Trump Predicting His Win https://t.co/1RlEAbhNtR via @NYMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heiress quietly shaping Trump’s operation https://t.co/vZrnBfbvke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver mayor on housing crisis: 'I never dreamed it would get this intense' https://t.co/0JYwIULfND #RentControlsNow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman creates registry for white men (until we figure out what's going on) https://t.co/zd8frNY76a via @HuffPostWomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The current housing crisis is not an accident #rentcontrolsnow https://t.co/TcoDsYTNMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trump poised to violate Constitution his first day in office, George W. Bush’s ethics lawyer says” by @imillhiser https://t.co/juw62FPcfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World’s first blue wine goes on sale @nina_panag https://t.co/hWIfG4NjR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBrillQuill @TPM this could be the proof we've been waiting for - he's clearly part orangutan and hates everything Harambe stood for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitzsij #getinthefuckingsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitzsij @edgalligan was it for this...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harambe was set up! HOW HIGH DOES THIS GO @TheBrillQuill https://t.co/9Vpsd0xoAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it a green? Is it a plaza? 

No it's a #collegegreenplaza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philosopher who predicted Trump in 1998 also predicted his 1st act as president-elect: https://t.co/LuzTgI6nMz via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Day 1 in Trump’s America” by @sokane1 https://t.co/u7sNaVJZvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Parks and Recreation’: Leslie Knope Writes Letter to America Following Donald Trump’s Victory https://t.co/Aj5gArIMHI via @YahooTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moodysimon @guardian it could take a while, and it may not even work, but the sleep will do us all good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India’s crackdown in Kashmir: is this the world’s first mass blinding? https://t.co/bCbxkBq1z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly hey - no more complaints about educating people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_Sheridan @Pidge @niamhsquared exactly what every Baltic state is thinking right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O little town of Bethlehem PA, how still we see the lie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ghost town surrounded by ocean  https://t.co/7bBtNUlMRy via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope Fuckface von Clownstick never gets his Twitter account back https://t.co/a99f5MLDmO @thedailyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: 50 Years Ago, Sugar Industry Quietly Paid Scientists To Point Blame At Fat https://t.co/YM5E73p6VB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fending Off Loneliness With Cups of Tea https://t.co/HoLhMT72ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[November non-surprise - No criminality in Clinton emails - FBI https://t.co/LlY94xK4Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctd_dublin @LionraHq I'm way behind the curve, so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen this @ctd_dublin @LionraHq ? https://t.co/lREG7YZPD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US’ one-million-acre secret  https://t.co/5EBQsStBUD via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely fucking magnificent! Never thought I'd see Ireland beat new Zealand. Wow. Fuck the haka. Brilliant! 8! #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBrillQuill @officialjaden hopefully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinTenants what's your smallest violin? https://t.co/BPgsmTt7xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13% of Dubliners deficient in vitamin D https://t.co/2VhqLeBEMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and Dublin Bus, Bus Eireann and CIE to begin replacing polluting diesel vehicles with clean electric transport. It's already available!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also need Coillte to speed up the shift to broadleaf trees and diverse forestry, from N American and Scandinavian pine monocultures]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>