<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that was good. Carlton impressive (been a while since that could be said). #AFLWBluesPies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Collingwood going to score 5 goals in the last quarter? Um, no. Game over #AFLWBluesPies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on a sample of Americans I've spoken to this week in my work, nobody voted for Trump. They all deny it anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilgherrian @wwos  now why is this news? And why would anyone care? Except his wife/partner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eithne52 whoever said it looks remotely good, except Trump and his fellow lunatics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does the TV industry get a 3 month holiday each year? Seems old fashioned and not keeping with the times to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What quality TV choices do I have now with no #BBL06 to watch in the evenings? The TV guide suggests slim (non-existent) pickings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countries with insane, dangerous idiots in charge:
1. North Korea
2. Syria
3. Much of Africa
4. USA.

Others?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s_bridges of course, shit scared of losing all the racist votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 #lastfm artists: Laughing Clowns (15), Metric (8) &amp; The New Pornographers (4) via @tweeklyfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miranda_maybe so the argument is that the market is so distorted by neg gearing that it can never be unraveled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm, titanium dioxide sounds entirely natural as part of food. Apparently causes cancer. #9News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any chance of Klinger getting a game for Aus in the T20 games vs SL? #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scorchers really don't need to take risks batting now to win. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be easier to build a wall around the White House to keep the world away from President Dickhead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clutterbells @c0nvey @washingtonpost just more confirmation  (as if it were needed) that Trump &amp; supporters are delusional cretins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLW_Mole he is an idiot for many, many more reasons than just that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to take a McCullum special for the Heat to win. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janr572 exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deniseshrivell @MinhKular haha! "Trump supporters" and "educated" are mutually exclusive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair chance we have player of the match already, 7 overs into the match. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stars must be booked on early flight home. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some spell by Mitch Johnson here. 3/0 off 2.3 overs #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshtpm @RichardTuffin yeah, but that's because Trump supporters are too dumb to use high tech stuff like the Metro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jill Meagher: need to reform bail laws; CBD deaths: need to reform bail laws. Q - why not do it properly before these bad things happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaKorras @nranews ah yes, the answer to everything for the idiot part of America.  Guns, and electing a moron for president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProvaxShill @AngelaKorras I don't know about that.  The fact he got elected says a significant % of Americans ARE in fact complete idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 #lastfm artists: These Immortal Souls (12), Died Pretty (2) &amp; Angel Olsen (1) via @tweeklyfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin absent on Saturday Night Live https://t.co/vKyrO0sJGE via @newscomauHQ Maybe figured real Trump is parody enough?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinhKular @abcnews what odds she has a health "crisis" preventing her appearance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnLeft2016 @SpudBenBean no matter what people thought of Hillary, electing Trump was not the sane response. Completely nuts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Americans who voted for Trump. You may not have liked Hillary or Obama, but how in any sane way does that make Trump the answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLU @RichardTuffin maybe they should invest the effort into challenging the 2nd Amendment? That's the really stupid one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee what is it with Republicans and hating women?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do Republicans mostly look like angry, middle aged or old white men? Oh yeah! Because they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News @cjjosh of course based on his accuracy with crowd numbers, his personal fortune probably really amounts to $7.50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has buyer's remorse set in yet amongst the Trump supporters?  Has it hit Vlad yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NekoCase @shelliav1 what makes people look bad is that the voted for Trump.  That, above all else is confirmation they are morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's really sad is that the things women are fighting for in #WomensMarch even need to be fought for at all.  Pitiful they have to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress @MinhKular I think the first 4 words were all that was needed to generally summarise Perry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @love0ntoast you forgot to mention the dickhead president the Trump inauguration delivered; unlike the Obama one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vic_Rollison at least when they're worrying about stuff like that, its less time for them to spend on breaking good things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually why award runs for leg byes (&amp; byes) in any form of #cricket #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest of the world on Trump: arseclown, village idiot, dickhead.
Americans: yeah, let's make him President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meg Lanning out off a definite no-ball. Missed badly by umpires. #WBBL02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stupid really is winning in the world at present. It's depressing, really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now we officially have President Dumb, leader of the stupid world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Vic bail laws need changing. For violent &amp; repeat offenders, I think presumption should be strongly against bail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ceburns2003 @stinginthetail who follows him in the first place? Certified morons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @MinhKular @mandurahmail descends into farce? I'd suggest she starts as farce and goes downhill from there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear TV channels, any show you promote during sport broadcasts, I will refuse to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renegades innings is sort of dying in the arse. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not watching Trump inauguration. At least I can live in denial that Americans really are stupid enough to vote for him for a few days more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ok_lyndsey @MinhKular @cporterwa presumably not that govt agencies are invariably grossly incompetent at IT stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts @Billablog @DavidLeyonhjelm ok, what did you think was the context then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nqc_jono @BrissyDan there is that!  Should have sent him a mock premiers' medal/ring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe except for minor crimes, bail should only happen if court convinced 100% that accused unlikely to reoffend. Presumption arse about now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh looky!  Melbourne driver was out on bail.  Maybe, just maybe, bail needs to be harder to get for habitual criminals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrissyDan @nqc_jono of course if the Broncos want him, no doubt he'll sign for $100k a year on their salary cap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrtonymartin most things Malcolm says make no sense, so it is plausible he commented without understanding what it was about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#channel9 referring to Vince Colosimo as screen legend may just be overstating his fame just a smidgen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe just maybe if the family violence had been dealt with more seriously the driver in Melbourne today wouldnt be out to run people down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there normally guys just hanging around Flinders St/Federation Square with baseball bats? Normal daily occurrence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACurrentAffair9 "most of the footage is too gruesome" BUT we'll be glad to show it as soon as we think we can get away with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep yes! He is an arseclown. I'm sure Hanson got him on board to make her look sane &amp; reasonable by comparison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsPraxis available.  whatever an "available" is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man dead in suspected croc attack at Cahill's Crossing in Kakadu https://t.co/xr6lQXQ5lU does this count as suicide? or just terminal stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing that footage of the guy doing donuts, my main concern was to hope the horses don't get hurt. Am I bad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelBkr @RichardTuffin some aspects of poor implementation do need review. Whether Prod Comm is right for that I don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Prudent_Kazia @davidbewart @mefergus the companies won't need to spend as much on their tax minimization schemes. Saves $ = more profit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police urging people to stay away from Bourke St area. Now let's see how many dickheads go out of their way to rubberneck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if Leyjonhelm is stupid enough to delete his tweet then deny ever making it?  Or blame hackers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miz_Rosenberg disappearance of Harold Holt, Australian Prime Minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpwoodhead out in the real world, where such things are taken seriously, he'd be fired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisGarry7 @7NewsQueensland wonder what that cost?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoachHead7 and how many get called incorrectly?  But the 2 in this game were well over the line. Ump obviously not concentrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe teams would fix their no-ball bowling if the penalty was, say 10 runs each? #AUSvPAK #cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how umpire missed calling that a no-ball on the field. Wasn't even close
 #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steph_Philbrick one thing we can be confident about is none of them will find a need to do more than $6750 travel a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFMEU @MinhKular no doubt Parkinson has called it deliberate rorting and not inadvertent, or because grey areas in the rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeckeringBoy @MinhKular @newscomauHQ at least there's one thing the government can do well - creative expense claiming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's going on @Centrelink with #notmydebt ? Are they nasty, vindictive pricks or just incompetent idiots?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9/41 is like old times for the Sydney Chunder. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well bowled Ish Sodhi. 6/11 #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Thunder's season is about to die, after they've limped through right from the start #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely to claim something is official to claim expenses it must be primary part of travel reason not some incidental reason to justify claim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noeltowell @MsRonnyB @canberratimes i wonder if calls not answered can truly be counted as "handled".?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robin_her @SandiHLogan @seearjay maybe he could be minister for Alzheimer's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100 as if there was ever any doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young guy driving BMW. My automatic assumption is drug dealer. #rbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need to drive for x,y,z reasons". Well, mate, you should have thought about that before driving pissed. #rbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumitaguchi @Pollytics gravity may have a problem with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this guy on #rbt is fibbing about only having 2 beers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bogan on #rbt is too dumb to have ever got a license to have had disqualified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessMattie1 i wondered when it turned into the home shopping channel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandiHLogan @seearjay not much point Arthur having all that experience when he seems to forget everything he's done or been told]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAviator1992 @MinhKular @TurnbullMalcolm your challenge is to find someone for the ministry with a lilywhite expenses history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut @seearjay and that is sure to be a crowded race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSassyRed added profit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gibbot5000 obviously too many underemployed journalists on the payroll]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>