<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[what a bummer about Rob Schrab no longer directing The Lego Movie 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@en_cohen I thought the same thing about the 'out of nowhere' thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeah that's exactly what I was looking for, actually. https://t.co/wrbCLJM2Gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTWritePretty @JacobQKnight 5 Tricks The Killer Klowns From Outer Space Would Perform IRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobfreelander @Elrickane anything that results in more additions to my watchlist and potential discoveries is good news to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard the latest @SYNWPC yet? Listen now, on @acast: https://t.co/CaKA8swB7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elrickane @bobfreelander @PureCinemaPod oh good lord I need this in my life! Can't wait to hear this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gem of the week on @Spotify imo: @drgnkingDOM's new record out now on @LameORecords.

https://t.co/n03lfaLPPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@70s_party something something... farty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregGLeGros @Superstamp yeah we're all stoked on this. I think we talked about the trailer when it came out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AchinglyChic the "Then it made headlines..." image tho haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Releases on @Spotify for Feb. 3rd 2017: https://t.co/On42tbdYCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@father_daughter @TheGreyEstates two-fold because if I don't mark them all as 'read' then I'm like eeauughhhh nooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonasdowney it was tooooo hard. I need to put more work into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yckmd_ @tmbg Thinking maybe I should do two power hours, and split the discography down the middle...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drafted a @tmbg power hour: https://t.co/sScGYXqFWb

This one was hard as heck to sequence; I don't think I did the best job, but I tried!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamgently yaaaay
the peaks on MR are amazing but EV is on-the-whole more well rounded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Budget_Bytes haha, that's me with "Special K Nourish: Coconut, Cranberries &amp; Almonds" 
good lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric Version &gt; Mass Romantic

&lt;/hottake&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good lord that new japandroids song is terrible. what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new mamo makes a great morning https://t.co/7nWqiL2lKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieinto added Al Tuck! There's no Ghendarvas on spotify, either unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Coastal: Glory Days of CanRock: 
https://t.co/Ftee73t9un

What's missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard this podcast? @tinyengines are absolutely one of the best labels in the game right now. So stoked ab… https://t.co/UNibmPIJS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathisms @SYNWPC @jeffkarpala that is amazing. thank you for spreading the word and also thank you both for listening!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilygagne oh damn. I'm kind of pumped for this, I'm rooting for it to be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for some tunes? Here's my list of 45 albums from last year that I loved a lot. 
Check them out: 
https://t.co/REeYlhUhWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterfeitJns thanks for sharing! I love love love your album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rljd I love this lots and lots
please keep doing this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Superstamp absolutely. I know just what you mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Superstamp thanks dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is that a wolf in your mouth
or are you just happy to see me? https://t.co/Kf14Dej8N0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieinto thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lighter note: for a time, this album was instrumental in calming me down. 
https://t.co/HU7IXlWSZy 
I would repeat it all night. Sooo good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfacenoisepod ahh that's good. I waned off my first prescrip and it all came back so I'm on a combo now that seems to be better for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfacenoisepod no no hi jack away! thank you for sharing too. I really can relate to a lot of that. simple pleasures becoming hard. sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiarabella thank you!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiarabella @ChrisGethard right? the second season couldn't have come at a better time for me, and watching the streams was so amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfacenoisepod ah dude I 100% understand that feeling. sometimes movie theaters are major triggers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfacenoisepod man! sending love your way bro. that sucks. how are you these days with that tho?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And also by donating to @endstigma, as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway. I want to be more open about it all this year and hope to help the bigger conversation about mental in some way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to contribute to stigmatization by bottling it all up. I don't want people to be scare to talk about it, like I was / still am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the first I've really spoken about it. I am on a better combo of medication this year that has made the problems way more manageable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally went to my doctor and went on meds; they weren't the right ones for me initially. I was afraid to tell my parents? And friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a bad nite on the couch. I called Emma, and she taught me to rub my fingers on the couch and focus on the texture to stop the attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drank alone in my basement a lot to try and self-medicate; a mistake. Watching @ChrisGethard taping-streams helped me cope in a major way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2+ years ago I started having panic attacks at night; like my heart would explode. I couldn't sleep in my room, I'd go to the couch instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year, I'm going to try hard to get better at not bottling my anxiety/depression internally while also calling for de-stigmatization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normwilner any meta tags on those photos for location? might be able to track down the location of the church in the photos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FullStopPress @SYNWPC What's the controversy? Haven't seen the movie, and haven't been spoiled either...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tederick there's a @mamopod twitter? huh ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tederick @mamopod please actually make this the new mamo logo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tederick holy crap that is adorable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy the entire @blacknumbers catalogue for $25 and all proceeds go go American Civil Liberties Union.… https://t.co/fQHoCcjKa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazygamereviews Now, if only I could find some video or screenshots of OFF-SHORE FISHING! Heh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazygamereviews Good lord. I had your video paused because it flooded me with ICON memories. I bow down to you, sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazygamereviews Here's an obscure Oddware for ya: Unisys ICON aka the "Bionic Beaver." Seemed exclusive to Ontario.
https://t.co/21U0SZEYZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really into the new one from @MENACE_BEACH this a.m. And that new @ThrowingSnow holy shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New music released this week; lots of good stuff! Playlist: https://t.co/pw8F6p0uX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quasi releases a PWYC protest-comp feat. Doug Martsch, Corin Tucker, Stephen Malkmus, Carrie Brownstein and more.
https://t.co/ukvVBXMwZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewMcWeeny Have you revisited Poltergeist III lately? The special effects in that movie really stand up tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has gotta be an online archive somewhere of vintage TV GUIDE magazines, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[p.s. no shade on Virtual Insanity and Deeper Underground here because I love them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[were people this excited when jamiroquai put out an album in 2010? IDGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewMcWeeny holy moly I am excited about this project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great dude
great gear
great price

great new podcast?
THERE CAN BE IF YOU WANT THERE TO BE! https://t.co/KJEhoFsiLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard this? Because it is damn good. https://t.co/bvSXmYsYyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbaWaterhouse @SYNWPC right? looks prettttty great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theyshootactors @mitchberghini but guys what about all the GURUS out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruthless People (1986): ★★★½ Bette is physical-comedy perfection in the final Zucker-Abrahams-Zucker collaboration. https://t.co/IA1mCpQK6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never understood why CAKE got such a bad rep; here's a Power Hour of their music to convert the unconverted: https://t.co/kBK510hr6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hahaha 
well this gets tweet of the year from me https://t.co/7m14UpFJqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criminal Law (1988): ★★ A promising thriller that ultimately disappoints as it ulravels further and further. https://t.co/xFjfwjsQB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firstborn (1984): ★★★★ Well-observed and acted family-drama from Michael Apted; unfortunate finale, though. https://t.co/YxmY0ZM8lF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreatwayGames  thanks!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillSloanEsq where jason gets really upsetand kills a guy because he is making fun of him without realizing he's listening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaseyLyonsSYNW pfff what a snob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you listening to this great show? IT'S SO DANG GOOD https://t.co/5afrHrPq4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doug_Tilley i like music it's pretty cool I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so excited about there being a new Grandaddy album. Holy shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for @Spotify playlists? I made an organized list of mine, right here: https://t.co/JCCL6S0ThF https://t.co/p0gUNnmYkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREAT PERSON GETS WONDERFUL JOB
THIS IS AWESOME NEWS
CONGRATS MATT!! 💯💯💯💯 https://t.co/6suwpo7A5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just a friendly reminder before they went disco, The Bee Gees were fucking incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithcalder this is... fucking awesome?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonbrow definitely. check out @CounterfeitJns' album from last year for something a bit noisier but still entirely bad-ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonbrow fucking great band! Love both their albums so so so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I could only have one food for the rest of my life? That's easy-that pizza from the cover of that one Tiger's Jaw album. No question."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samatha Bee killin' it already in 2017
https://t.co/iPREmLgC4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruculentTexan @DrewMcWeeny ooh. this seems like it could be a good fit for what was in that teaser for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brokencircles @TheGreyEstates Amputations is a mf jam. Everything on Something About Airplanes, really. Their best imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakeg99 @adamgently it's very, solidly, good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I want recommendations to add to the list please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On weekends, I often reach for thrillers of varying quality &amp; entertainment value, so I started a @letterboxd list: https://t.co/M4ZT6nR52d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tederick whaaaa what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Young Americans (1993): ★★★ Intriguing, mostly successful, British / American thriller starring Harvey Keitel. https://t.co/BQWzNkgYgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great episode of @80sAllOver; they're way harder on TIME SQUARE (1980) than I expected though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence (2016):  ★★★ Didn't fully do it for me; thought-provoking and beautifully shot, though. https://t.co/3aYjCL9h5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeclouxJ @PeterKapow @WillSloanEsq @jessehawken @theyshootactors I remember enjoying The Island at the time... as derivative as it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obeseball monster truck with a monster inside 

SIGN ME UPPPPP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>