<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Republicans weren't going to let Hillary Clinton have a SCOTUS appointment? Ever? https://t.co/Pl4pYZEUpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A CNN producer files lawsuit after being detained in Atlanta due to Trump's executive order https://t.co/WBNFH5NQny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats win huge in Iowa special election, but we don't know if there's a 'Trump effect' just yet https://t.co/QdlP3doD4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Dept. of Labor quietly takes down their Wells Fargo complaint webpage—Sen. Warren busts them https://t.co/N3aDqbBajU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House retaliates against CNN: No Trump officials will appear on the network https://t.co/yAen3vhcDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The president of the United States of America was just told to pay $6 mil for trying to scam people https://t.co/LaVuPHi0bA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PEACsandiego Live on E coast w 25-yr-old Timneh &amp; 22-yr-old Senegal - adopted last one @ 10 - sweet as molasses! Thks 4 your work &amp; B well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New website showcases seeds of a brighter future https://t.co/zXyEhSwhVW via @ensiamedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian oil exec found dead after caught bribing Donald Trump to lift U.S. sanctions https://t.co/6VeN86kzJ4 via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PEACsandiego Thk U 4 F! Note that https://t.co/NJNq3kSZ9v was written to encourage adoption. ASPCA endorsed! (FYI, I don't get royalty!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this for real? https://t.co/DCdyilyr2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adopt, don't buy! - parrots have long lifespans &amp; many need good homes! Earning trust of mature parrot more rewardi… https://t.co/WQVRIr5alQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This little piggy didn't go to market! https://t.co/9K5EkurmEM #twins #mellizos #vegetarian #Vegetariano #iartg… https://t.co/E2l0yNNQ4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joint Accounts https://t.co/pzbYlLQeQn #224 in Kindle Store &gt; Nature Writing #birding #aging #Immigrants… https://t.co/QQmzQFEugR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ONE more vote needed: Betsy DeVos's confirmation is suddenly on thin ice. Her defeat would be almost unprecedented. https://t.co/peWYWSPgZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Not the America I know’: George W. Bush's daughter wants you to remember his speech on Islam https://t.co/6YEz20Jh9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘This was the worst call by far’: Trump badgered, bragged and abruptly ended phone call with Australian leader https://t.co/Vxv8RseeAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Assured Cost of Clamping Down on H-1B “Genius” Visas" https://t.co/9HOHYsxATT by @Blakei on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman wins "Nobel Prize of mathematics" for first time in history https://t.co/uxP3GxtBdg via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CA lawmaker demands proof of Melania Trump's immigration status in protest of Trump's exec orders https://t.co/ouyLvJDJcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell demands Democrats treat Trump's Supreme Court nominee like Republicans treated Obama's - REALLY???https://t.co/SBzGozhoM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions' Embrace of Racist Law One More Reason to Reject His Confirmation as A G - Southern Poverty Law Center https://t.co/wLGs5F2WJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysterious intruder rattles GOP lawmakers https://t.co/AEO4EO6c9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance from within: Federal workers push back against Trump https://t.co/5YMSQH86yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build an Autocracy https://t.co/hLSt1JRJdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acluct Willimantic Police Department is in compliance with posting of forms &amp; policy on website. Please correct report. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jihadist groups hail Trump’s travel ban as a victory https://t.co/gfvUs8eyks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s hard-line actions have an intellectual godfather: Jeff Sessions https://t.co/n5O8VohdBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your police department following CT’s complaint rules? Find out on the @acluct statewide survey results page.  https://t.co/MEIOZvpiGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainbow-Arcoiris https://t.co/bZ5r8Wf3u2 #bilingual #nutrition #childrenfirst #salud #saludable #ellchat… https://t.co/iOruPyfxgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact-checking Trump’s claim that his refugee policy is similar to Obama’s https://t.co/3y5nwPKwO9 via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on the 7th day, Trump violated the first amendment prohibitions against a state religion https://t.co/NfORQ2hyeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard Dean has it right. The time for action is now. "You are being left behind by your base" https://t.co/q6BsH5QHxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans who oppose, support Trump refugee order https://t.co/MMSgSZ7Irp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird sisters - Hermanas raras https://t.co/0YavY35km5 #ellchat #langchat #Kinderchat #kindness #iartg #Tolerance… https://t.co/9pSkDqYbZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garrison Keillor: Trump is what he is, and God help us now https://t.co/MGWGOaf6r5 via @tulsaworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Trump executive: I knew he was ill for last 35 years https://t.co/lhCYF2QFbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's why it's fair—and necessary—to call Trump's  chief strategist a white nationalist champion https://t.co/ms8vl0NxWF via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of Trump's executive orders aren't actually executive orders. Here's why that matters. https://t.co/TAU927Qpx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the rookie federal judge who halted Trump's refugee deportations — to save a Syrian https://t.co/WcAwGqAH5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions multiply over Bannon’s role in Trump administration https://t.co/41VMGDjW9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Post: A Writer’s Perspective on Value of Bilingual Books for Children, Families, and Schools https://t.co/u4fyBCp8IO via @BeckMonkeys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cherry Tree - El Cerezo: REVISED EDITION - EDICION ACTUALIZADA by Delia B... https://t.co/sz9T64iyuS via @amazon #iartg #kindness #kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic Nun Explains Pro-Life In A Way That Will Stun Many (Especially Republican Lawmakers) https://t.co/jifRAZVEjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Beware hate speech, says Auschwitz Holocaust survivor https://t.co/t0E4GdUEFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Perry Is Terrified. Why Aren’t You? https://t.co/6AN8UbtJFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s statement marking Holocaust remembrance leaves out mention of Jews https://t.co/Mx6Cavn3Ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's stunning first major interview as president, annotated https://t.co/fh8aPGkaNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not enough - must persuade republicans to oppose! https://t.co/I2F4eGwVYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Crony Cabinet May Look Strong, But They Are Scared - https://t.co/gTrwD6OlNx https://t.co/jBgi1n8RKL via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Crony Cabinet May Look Strong, But They Are Scared https://t.co/XPCjfiiQdu via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's appointees don't seem to be signing required ethics pledges and don't plan to https://t.co/mW2PcFTQ7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monkey Cake - Torta de Monos by Delia Berlin https://t.co/3JRZhCfXfQ via @amazon #iartg #ellchat #langchat #bilingual #bilingue #humor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“How to #StayOutraged Without Losing Your Mind” by @MirahCurzer https://t.co/i4kB4dy7DK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TrumpBeat: There Is No Pivot https://t.co/PIfGjIK91F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia treason arrest seen as tacit corroboration of US intel https://t.co/X0znh0xpdM via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Doomsday Clock just advanced, 'thanks to Trump’: It's now just 2½ minutes to 'midnight.' https://t.co/Ku3tAi4Iz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nation's top scientists can't get through to Trump - and they're alarmed https://t.co/QaMpWwMzTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's stunning first major interview as president, annotated https://t.co/s8TV534bwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims about inauguration crowd https://t.co/XVy59N9Zph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signature needed: Tell the Senate to oppose anti-worker Puzder https://t.co/8b8V0a44ER via @CREDOMobile #p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand with the ACLU and take the #PeoplesOath to defend our rights under the Trump administration: https://t.co/CP3gSfafS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxMaxsilva1946 max, it's fake news - pretty sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TALES OF EVA AND LUCAS by Delia Berlin , Hailey Quercia | Kirkus Reviews https://t.co/USPWv9qsCJ #kirkus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome the Weirds - Bienvenidas las Raras by Delia Berlin https://t.co/JjEeYgzFRe via @amazon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman: Info in classified CIA doc would trigger new election in other countries https://t.co/jLmEUSDoZ5 via @huffpostqueer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRANSCRIPT: ABC News Anchor David Muir Interviews President Trump - ABC News - https://t.co/Zdb7qv2jMB via @ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned https://t.co/bkB9PgYugr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true, correct story of what happened at Donald Trump's inauguration https://t.co/mvOfPPVRFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Access to #patientcare could be in jeopardy. Tell Congress to protect hospital funding &amp; patient care in your state. https://t.co/pkTOGfq3A6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DIET - DIETA https://t.co/9K5EkurmEM #Health #fitness #LetsMove #iartg #Kindergarten #Kinderchat #nutrition… https://t.co/Tp4UyZNENx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FEMA Under Trump Fails To Help After Tornados Devastate S.E. The Incompetence Is Showing Already. https://t.co/q15Yls8OHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a fan of him, but not illegal as long as he only voted in one. https://t.co/fPFoObhxMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's only 14% - it means 86% of his voters see thru his lies - amazing! https://t.co/eZiqItp6WD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elementary... :-) 
Bilingual kids' books with positive messages at https://t.co/rAuucKAQk3
@retobilingue… https://t.co/EvUfetfOS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions is a champion of voter suppression - paving his way with lies: https://t.co/04SA9L2WG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put all your eggs in one basket! " humorous, entertaining, moving and provocative" https://t.co/8fCvrPL9Oy… https://t.co/GqUdGmMUjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump calls for 'major investigation' into voter fraud @CNNPolitics https://t.co/FcVU2pOPvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no JUSTICE without TRUTH - Wrongful accusations lead to repression &amp; witch hunts. Expose lies. This is sha… https://t.co/E1t8s6GOEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s disregard for the truth threatens his ability to govern https://t.co/ASrepOoNZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The true, correct story of what happened at Donald Trump's inauguration https://t.co/6CKqgPrjSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United States Senate: Do not confirm Betsy DeVos as Secretary of Education. https://t.co/nFB1Aqfs2X via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the difference in how Trump and Obama greet WW2 veteran Bob Dole and his wife https://t.co/LoHvpPAcTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump claims standing ovations during CIA visit, but intelligence officials tell a different story https://t.co/VnZIGuSyBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainbow - Arcoiris https://t.co/bsbTVZVps9 #nutricion #salud #HealthyLiving #bilingual #ellchat #Kindergarten… https://t.co/gmHjdZ8pPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Eat a Rainbow: Cómo Comer un Arcoíris : Babl Children's Books in Spani... https://t.co/bsbTVZVps9 via @amazon #cocina #nutrition #ell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herding explained... https://t.co/0nLbXB4W4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump's staff is lying https://t.co/9hTuxGJ18h via @BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about #alternativefacts: 
80,000 illegal ballots cost Hillary the Electoral College :-) https://t.co/41Koa0VFxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump thanks the FBI director accused of helping his campaign" https://t.co/fmhmiZNAHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIGN NOW: Tell @SenateDems to protect access to health care &amp; block @RepTomPrice's HHS confirmation. https://t.co/gPy1Uu9ckQ #Medicare #p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration just told a whopper about the size of the federal workforce https://t.co/ZGUntTvlNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's bridge-building eclipsed by false voter fraud claim https://t.co/OECDVPn7Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without evidence, Trump tells lawmakers 3 million to 5 million illegal ballots cost him the popular vote https://t.co/7bQBpEHgba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich Kids Stay Rich, Poor Kids Stay Poor https://t.co/cldhaCKeUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My closest Swing District is NY-19, won by only 26,000 votes. Find yours and help swing the House left in 2018: https://t.co/tkF88izMvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promised to resign from his companies – but there’s no record he’s done so https://t.co/2K4QdEjC0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Underestimate Catastrophic Impact Trump Administration’s Policies Will Have on People W Disabilities https://t.co/jbIALW9yNW via @aclu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mutual Funs: Selected Essays by an Older Couple by Delia Berlin https://t.co/0vHvoej4dR via @amazon #birding #nature #iartg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump takes to Twitter to weigh in on Women's March, TV ratings for inauguration https://t.co/ZkTtWCrRBQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>