<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnycarroll77 on the to do list https://t.co/i4aie4zcjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Postvox hi folks, is this a temporary closure? Where are uncollected parcels gone? https://t.co/WCpEiZMY3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donna_cooney1 @Postvox hopefully temporary, would be a huge loss locally, anything residents can do let us know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donna_cooney1 @clontarfIE permanently or temporarily ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuthbertable  if VIE is the legal entity then it only lodges abridged accounts. See pic. https://t.co/baoTSUqwRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KZapponeTD will it also include rights for current adoptees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly Christian Slater and Winona Ryder in heathers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely interview with Ken and Linda, so eloquent and such strength. Please support @feileacain1 if you can https://t.co/6NntBkbHuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never finishes at three #SherlockFinale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I appear to be viewing more of Teresa Mannion than I ever wanted to #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure which of them I love more https://t.co/CRtBcmCwGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not seen #eastenders in many many years. Flicking  channels and "I tan easy" by Sharon ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@citybin only if you agree pineapple has no place on a pizza! Source of the wager attached https://t.co/0gmnlqMey7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@citybin hi folks, can you advise if pizza boxes can be put in the brown bin. Settle a bet! Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orbyn I remember a girl in school using a sports sock. Didn't realize for ages why she was walking around with 1 knee sock on &amp; 1 bare leg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggyvaneijk good god please tell me this didn't actually happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the idea behind these, ðŸ‘ðŸ» to @PositivityPack https://t.co/QEtUXPVVZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaCeistAgam Leo would ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #plagarism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaCeistAgam no words to describe how epic a burn this is. Kudos ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 also John "cheated" on Mary with Sherlocks sister. Now that's weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 he was, as we say on DNS, bet down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aahhhhhhhhhh Sunday can't come fast enough!! Epic!  #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love her ! #sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men have ginger beards #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally you'll reach more people than I ever will ðŸ‘‡ðŸ¼ðŸ‘‡ðŸ¼ https://t.co/lVGS4fLOHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh to be a fly on the wall #trump #russia https://t.co/6jD8QmjY22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sligo, Dublin, Athlone women sign up ! #womenscouncil #genderequality #nationalstrategy https://t.co/mb1t8oucHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry Laurence Llewelyn Bowen, where is he now (and his flouncy sleeves) https://t.co/k7kZhzs7Iu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unusual day where I am favouring the Sindo over the @IrishTimes for once  https://t.co/0Cg0J8VybB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe or BOI you can pay by text ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe depends on the bank and your internal rating. Just go into a branch and it's limitless once you have funds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeannedesutun no but they let me dress up as a millennium milk bottle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI a friend of mines accounts been merged with someone else's but they seem unaware. This is more bizarre ! #browsonfleek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StandardIssueUK my mam thought "senza una donna" was a charity song and "send us a dollar"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TescoIrl It's a 15 min drive, not worth it. You might get in touch with the store to do a full shelf check at a minimum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stop watching https://t.co/iee3WtOd86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TescoIrl hi, bought this today in Artane Castle, D5, only noticed date when unpacking ðŸ˜” https://t.co/9FeLX7lA3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 probably a red herring but hey it'll make us watch the rest (cos we needed encouragement)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMillican75 The Affair on catch up. Getting interesting !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sherrinford...only just copped. Slow on the uptake! #thirdbrother #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For an army surgeon he's kinda crap at treating gunshot wounds eh  #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Mary quite contrary #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnycarroll77 at least you know better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn to help prepare ! https://t.co/G7Mrs6Fe9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why didn't anyone get me this for Christmas!? Love photo books https://t.co/yOsIplJPRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn you can't not! Freeman said it's the darkest yet which is hopefully a good thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes I liked the clothes. And the popcorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eh hello they just murdered someone ?! #JonathanCreek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah here they've murdered the actual story, what a daft adaption  #witnessfortheprosecution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CarrieFisher #RestInPeace #badass https://t.co/XO1DLrNREz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaiaDunphy sadly it seems to have become part of Christmas tradition for some people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjbm1969 absolutely nothing. Nothing. No leftover screws. No, no, not here, no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BootsHelp hi folks, dm sent re purchase made today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pipsypie @sharonledwidge meaghers on baggot street, d2. Also online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @AerLingus trying to check in using app but won't let me reset password? App issue or me?! https://t.co/vu9lI9vMZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 @catspjs13 @bbcpress @BBCOne hips!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry second the hauck, Amazon or Boots online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry you can also rent them from "sling libraries". They're like jeans, everyone finds a perfect fit. Plus it's addictive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toucanbox oops! Too late to go searching in the bin ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syqau @CherylReynolds a simple google would advise the contrary #untruthteller https://t.co/WiRuPaGHAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toucanbox what are the token stickers for ? Should we be keeping them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toucanbox by Conor age 3 ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/pAnul7G1Nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry the swwwwwwish ! Love â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurphyEoghan does the working group cover commercial  and/or spsv insurance ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time! Hope the establishment of the database etc happens expeditiously https://t.co/2Sn734uvtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avocaireland super thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avocaireland hello :-) would you be able to tell me the measurements of the small lambswool throws? Can't see it online. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 noes! I'll miss her https://t.co/KbvVhL5ayM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soundmigration assume you've seen this https://t.co/VPLSfOJrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soundmigration @lstwrd the most benign interview ever! Disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live with my own hero everyday #preemiepower #WorldPrematurityDay #wpd2016 https://t.co/wVgKSS4pKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianneReddy @andotherstories 9th December. See you in the queue!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneRabbitte thanks for replying; I will be in work unfortunately. Will see if can record it on tv, fingers crossed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneRabbitte hi Anne, is there an agenda for this tmw or could you update me afterwards? Eager to hear progress https://t.co/EXDCDrZHax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KZapponeTD morning, can I ask what the agenda is for tmw or when we can expect "progress" ? https://t.co/oGx1Kpe8XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyCarer is this it ? https://t.co/PFdto90C5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djjennygreene thank you! #epic #wheresmyglostick https://t.co/qqGKc57EIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cocomairead @giftgrubmario @jduggantodayfm @cupidkelly the Barbara Streisand info way upsetting ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the mam of a 33 weeker, thanks @cooper_m for a super interview with @IrishNeonatal. People really aren't aware of impact on parents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianneReddy dull response. Flogas. My bills are way cheaper. And they answer the phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michlawlor still laughing ! His face ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just asked for directions by a random guy, opened his phone to show me the address, except he was on a porn site not maps ðŸ˜‚ #erections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop the world I want to get off #Trump #whathaveyoudone #watchthedollardrop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @ek_mccormick since when? "The father or mother of your father or mother" not an extension of to suit an end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How quickly can I get to Chicago #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe nope, not yet, driver can't see your track record. There's talk of a cancellation fee coming in though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DromeyElaine @CoraSherlock in the same way they use photos of full term babies to pursue their goal of scaremongering &amp; exaggeration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoraSherlock abortion leaves many women feeling healthy, mentally strong and safe. It can also be "care". Two sides to every coin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI de nada. I had an early baby so became aware of them that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI I know ppl who have had excellent pnd support from them, and also trauma counseling post early/preterm babies. Unsure prebirth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI seriously though, what's the motivation? They're not the prettiest thing in real life so not sure even the best filter can help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've voted for #Heaslip in the IRPA Try of the Year award 2016 https://t.co/aeBTQjDjVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI this! https://t.co/V9VdwBjdnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Charities_Reg really would have benefited from a free text section as well. Have lots to say but can't say it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colmogorman if you fancy a quiet beach day head to Mandrem. Beautiful spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProLifeLegend @DromeyElaine @RebeccahLouise I think you mean your tweet is the lie. Bull. Total bull. Young and ignorant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he does that to Stella then is left alone with the doc and solo guards? #comeon #TheFall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisnMc16 @SarahJayBee I would pay good money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoChaela @daithigorman @RudyHellzapop @AnGobanSaor publicly available info - healthy donation pot https://t.co/WX34q7hBL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithigorman @RudyHellzapop @AnGobanSaor company directors are as attached https://t.co/kOKsX2MSSB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>