<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[No. Inaction across most Departments will do that. NAMA + health + education... etc.  Wake up. New radical thinking… https://t.co/CUcp0hte5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't give up. Been there. Fantastic officers from across all of PSNI helped us. Humans helping humans. More… https://t.co/wMs9S84Bzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope. I'm patient ...but not infinitely  ..... https://t.co/LFnymIiAQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing you on YouTube doing your vlogs @THE_NEURO_GENiE https://t.co/8IBFImwfRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super - who should we chat with @CDC_tweets ? https://t.co/zNoedkz7na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only if co-written with you ! https://t.co/Hwe1guxBLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true, internet surfing during class is not so good for grades https://t.co/B20QnWxhBX via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should gifted students go to a separate school? https://t.co/xbwQU1BaNK via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a child's humour reveals about their psychological well-being https://t.co/0UqevobMjA via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What your brain structure says about your personality https://t.co/CDMBG2Tcvw via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @cearta 
Brexit ruling brings short-term clarity but long-term uncertainty https://t.co/MlO0AXwCzT via @IrishTimesOpEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great - let's chat in a little while ... OK? https://t.co/GYeGCgxoGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myself and @NoelPurdy would be delighted to share our research and applied practice regarding bullying and educatio… https://t.co/UPl1IFU02d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope those rules have had some thought put in to them ... and that they are logical. If you need a scientific vie… https://t.co/hNq7i5tYH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiringTheBrain This is why I find it hard doing my type of research with "dirty test tubes" AKA humans who differ… https://t.co/9E7o0iQ2e2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration Week special: "Gaslighting" goes mainstream https://t.co/7xYQMe5TGS via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging Reform "Success" and "Failure": The Gary, Indiana Case https://t.co/fe8HRLzjGA via @CubanLarry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the simplest questions that are the hardest to answer by simply saying yes or no. https://t.co/mhyM9wc191]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sagely advice from @NoelPurdy
@Aoife_m_ @COSiorain @luciecorcoran @purpleph @NIBPS @22Q11_Ireland @IDTCD @mccartpm… https://t.co/tixaISN7QG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Fall for This Sophisticated Gmail Phishing Scam https://t.co/X3zdswXpha via @PCMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fergbreen or 0871300177]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fergbreen I need your no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fergbreen free for a call?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps they can draw those lovely, rich, colourful, straight cause-effect lines between neuro explorations and edu… https://t.co/Dc7yV8RdUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrietta Lacks’s Family Brings Awareness To Cervical Health Month « CBS Baltimore https://t.co/FKKG74KlzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22Q11_Ireland 
Better outcomes for children with SEN is the key goal of new model – Minister Bruton - https://t.co/B5d74D0ma8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with 'microaggressions' https://t.co/hybmYLWW0M via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why learn spelling or maths if there's an app for that? https://t.co/xMT9L3WX1t via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, join the queue . . . .   :-) https://t.co/5KLEd3eiQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was me ok!  You didn't stop by to say hello  :-((( https://t.co/szZNk8YCBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top airline launches programme to help passengers with autism https://t.co/W2gl54j8zs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A serious one this time Grainia. This time, the new negotiations will bring the skeletons and naked tribalism out o… https://t.co/AwN32scj63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulation of Dopamine During Social Media Use In Adolescent Rats - McSweeney’s Internet Tendency https://t.co/iQBw5wR9RD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiringTheBrain  Some Lab Lit - https://t.co/1esMK028PH  -  HT the fab @DynamicEcology peeps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I had deduced that . . . https://t.co/Ri6keK4Wwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philosophyire 
The rise and fall and rise of logic – https://t.co/FrnIHWdGQV via @aeonmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Can fMRI Tell Us About Mental Illness? - Neuroskeptic https://t.co/Kg1OK3CCwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electroconvulsive therapy: A history of controversy, but also of help https://t.co/0xWfqPEiHG via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting online trolls with bots https://t.co/A7mkXweoHE via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's missing in the teaching of Islam https://t.co/Y2CeKcKlNq via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etiquette and ethics of reviewing Banerjee A - Med J DY Patil Univ https://t.co/hw7n5ZsqYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luciecorcoran 
Europe calls for mandatory 'kill switches' on robots  - CNNMoney https://t.co/ABlAdICpX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcampbelltcd 
The Concussion Diaries: One High School Football Player’s Secret Struggle with CTE | GQ https://t.co/3gy07L8Trt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drones delivering packages in cities won't take off – here's why https://t.co/lQyxoSLwBN via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to talk to your dog – according to science https://t.co/C2MJ0ErdVi via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schizophrenia may cause type 2 diabetes, new study finds https://t.co/vAiNx0BfPv via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all cuss, so why shouldn't judges and politicians use the c-word, too? https://t.co/uqM4Mz4fYt via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lives of Nuns: A Reading List https://t.co/9Q9H6IfUqM via @longreads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Life of John Prine, the Mark Twain of American Songwriting https://t.co/HL9Cf4XRPR via @RollingStone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you give me that in plain English  ??? https://t.co/CiVmNPyTxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope. Not possible. 
I'd dare to say that @philosophyire couldn't convince me that roast beef is musical .. or that… https://t.co/TlRvLD2hU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes - and can't find Alasdair on my list ...? https://t.co/RJjM8h9MfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introductory psychology textbooks accused of spreading myths and liberal-leaning bias https://t.co/O8qTloTKCM via @researchdigest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmaefarrell No. "Grab" sounds too rushed and, well, "middle class". No, "one" simply must take time with such matters. #wehaveservants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22Q11_Ireland for Brian T. Wilson  .... is he on twitter?? https://t.co/9intotPOT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmaefarrell Hope all is good your end Emma 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOALIBISBOOKS Crime novel His Bloody Project put Scottish writing back in the spotlight – here is what's next https://t.co/PTTYeAbJbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision and Blindness https://t.co/gpVoQVIVFS via @HuffPostEdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a test title https://t.co/tSKk53bh8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subject choices at GCSE may exacerbate social inequalities, study finds - Centre for Longitudinal Studies https://t.co/PtV26egjZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelPurdy @JimGamble_INEQE 
I wonder if she has our phone numbers? https://t.co/YzPrQ0j082]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22Q11_Ireland hard at work sampling eateries for #22qalliance conference https://t.co/Bw1Rug1FcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Image of the Day https://t.co/AloGwQqKPo via @AaronJBarlow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all that counts can be measured. Not all that can be measured counts. https://t.co/uSA9JXPRUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s time for science to abandon the term ‘statistically significant’ – https://t.co/SM53jGD8Kj via @aeonmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been meaning to go for ages. https://t.co/Stq8La8BXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The survival time of chocolates on hospital wards: covert observational study https://t.co/unfQxoEIst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course not. No grandstanding as yet. Independent mediator not called on yet. Hope Mr Mulvey is available ... as… https://t.co/36mHTmBmxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we not do this - on Twitter - as an academic community - cross-disciplinary?  #screentimeevidence https://t.co/gXYRXJ5Iwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenge every signatory to point to 1 meaningful piece of research- then we can stitch the story of "evidence so… https://t.co/1D4jPSgZdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't you all just point to the evidence and research that's there &amp; not just use your "name" to say we need ev… https://t.co/2WSAfouAv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we decommission the wheelchair icon in 2017?  And the dress / skirt? And the trousers? Can't we just "grow up"… https://t.co/yOVRn0FGsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give you a compliment and you want to arrange a chat about DEATH. I'm calling Rebus ... and Big Ger! If 50p ain't… https://t.co/GW5Y1UwudA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be able to say that they are 20 years old in 2017 says everything you need to know about @NOALIBISBOOKS… https://t.co/1kahfX2CnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd pay for the privilege of entering @NOALIBISBOOKS and seeing David and Claudia - the essence of all things great… https://t.co/GughlhPxuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aoife_m_ @TheGriefGeek 
https://t.co/hTAxTOASXz Adolescent Pregnancy: Past, Present and Future Trends and Issues https://t.co/rZthYAcin4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news!  @NOALIBISBOOKS @SchoolofEdTCD @FrazerPat @James_A_Magee https://t.co/Rkzwcp2gVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His statue was missing recently in Dublin - the sign read:

The boy's outta town
He's gone on tour with his mammy
H… https://t.co/3du5cYh8wn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Said Ireland . . . never.  Why?  'cos it doesn't affect men.  Oh, and let's keep taxing those things we can't speak… https://t.co/hyn25IeW2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@301N @cearta Looking good! More of this please :-) https://t.co/5suJPRjwZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@missmarymcgill: Revolution not resolutions. #NewYearsEve #nye2016 https://t.co/0vney9bBTF"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - WATCH: What Happens When a Bullet Hits an 'Unbreakable' Prince Rupert's Drop https://t.co/236Rh7NBta via @ScienceAlert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diametrically opposite to Alexithymia in psych. Linked to cognition - dysfunction in emot awareness, social attach… https://t.co/SYVpCmQ0Mb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22Q11_Ireland As we know, wider than this - exited from wider care issues etc as now an "adult". https://t.co/O7EoDmdU7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catheri45282137 No - none. We think the family originally came from Co Roscommon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catheri45282137 Why??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess we better bury this story . . . 
Female doctors save more lives https://t.co/nwDqz8euLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profsiobhanon 
Origins of Happiness? PAA response. https://t.co/SODW6wImoD via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I meet lots of Repeal 8th peeps. On chatting - I find that they are actually "pro-birth" - pro-life is a totally di… https://t.co/Re7bAgmjUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profsiobhanon Hope you typed that one-handed with Prosecco in the other. North Derry is very cultured! Keep up the good work :-))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profsiobhanon 
Origins of Happiness? PAA response. https://t.co/fPwAZ8V0JA via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ok if you are from the North. No similar acknowledgement if you are from the North and live / work in the South… https://t.co/uMgB4OI2V2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingstoneJim Watch the YouTube clip ...  It's not about the nail.  Sums up all marriages  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingstoneJim Hope all are well and warm there Jim. A lovely time to have with family ... love your juvenile sense of life and craic  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingstoneJim A rejoinder not suffice in this case! Glad the geese are safe. I could walk the dogs with that thing &amp; not leave the house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But ... are you pro-birth . . . or pro-life ???  Two very different things!  Too many "repeal" peeps don't know the… https://t.co/YUboJfrelV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoibhinn_ni_s @joeboating @Mark_MathsEd @mmeureka - for engineers, it's just the wrong size. For psychologists, le… https://t.co/he20IxsCae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's flying? You or Peter? Reply will determine my rejoinder  :-) https://t.co/JcxU9O6LjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna take you out for a long walk &amp; chat - and come back alone. In 2017, I'm taking no prisoners. Will introdu… https://t.co/zTmD2qLv23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a RSPCA before a RSPCC ... 

But - why would we promote a robot species to replace us at the top of the food… https://t.co/kNmeF4kNLu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>