<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bouchelolz @_L_M_C_ He's also on local radio. The daft racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's the spirit, Donny. Now wipe your arse, flush, and tell President Bannon this to his stupid face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@momentumtrumpt1 @janhopis 'Hells Angels, Texas Chapter' avatar, 'PC World, Bracknell Branch' IRL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zoella I hear you, Zoë. We need to rise up against people who spew hate about Curly Wurlys. Punch them right in their faces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Law-enforcing judges are the worst type of judge imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAmitie @realDonaldTrump A lot of people are saying that he wears diapers. Maybe a health thing, maybe a sex thing. I don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner Conversation ender / "that was almost good" endorsement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradweslake Interesting (and encouraging). I'll read up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madgoat69 @Chris_arnade My concern is that it's too late. Election is won, focus now seems to be on dismantling democratic structures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madgoat69 @Chris_arnade I don't think you can - especially not with the safety valve of 'fake news'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews I'm going to make the same comment twice. 

You know - like in the movie "Groundhog Day".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_arnade Pro-Trump will only become anti-Trump when it harms them personally. Same goes for Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_arnade It's impossible to reason people out of a position that they didn't reason themselves into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews I'm going to make the same comment twice. You know - like in the movie "Groundhog Day".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay_Beecher My 6 year old told me that they sing "Ba ba black sheep / Lee Rigby was good".

Are you calling my child a liar, "Jay"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebGorka Who's going to run Al's Toy Barn while you're pissing around in the White House?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwensDamien Used to be in The Bill. Hasn't worked since 2002. His Wikipedia page has a 'Personal Life' section spanning 4 paragraphs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why do you wear diapers, Mr President? A health thing, or a sex thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @realDonaldTrump Trump does things like a tsunami? You'll never get a job in politics with cruel jibes like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexJones @Bro_Pair A Russel Crowe effigy made entirely out of ham.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JumpVote Did the left steal your chin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower Nabbed (cc @ALS_Fanzine) 

Also, typo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TopTopPundit @2010LeeHurst We all lose, Lee. All thanks to #torture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TopTopPundit @2010LeeHurst Meanwhile, the real terrorists just wanted his demands met. Those demands? Get Lee Hurst back on TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2010LeeHurst You killed my baby, Lee. They think it's all over, Lee. IT IS NOW, LEE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2010LeeHurst You torture the terrorist. He tells you where your baby is, but he's wrong because he wasn't the terrorist after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer Today on Republic Airstrip One;

Polls = truth
News = lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Obama would've had it done by Wednesday. Lazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @YouTube You sound like a hospital radio DJ who only got the gig cos he's terminal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump Not so - that's the encore. 

"One more song, Mormon Tabernacle Choir!". Some say they're still there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It was 9:00 ages ago here. You need to make American 9:00 earlier. Lazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DVATW Spreading the blame ahead of the inevitable collapse of Brexit, hoping that the weirdos go after the judges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @Bro_Pair @Target I heard it was 1.5 millions gallons of cheese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer @realDonaldTrump Get a haircut you curtain-y soft shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin - "Control the media. Restrict the internet. Repeat. Distort. Dismantle. Only then can you lie, because now y… https://t.co/JYftkOAMt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeardedGenius I keep on waiting for a dastardly master plan... then he's an idiot. Again. He'll become impeachable… https://t.co/1JVN7iZdlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohhoe @directhex I'm several hundred loops in and your hypothesis holds up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohhoe @directhex Come for the punch in the face, stay for his mates running away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xV_krampus Putin. Actual Putin though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xV_krampus I'm not American. Just an interested spectator, watching the death throes of a superpower. Enjoy it. I will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xV_krampus @FeliciaBGomez Trump supporters have jobs, you said. 

Obamajobs. 

So far Trump has just sat around waving. All talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xV_krampus @CNN Yeah. The same, but from a different angle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeliciaBGomez They've Obama to thank for those jobs. 

What a crowd-pulling, job creating legend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine's a hell of a drug. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History.
#Inauguration https://t.co/0E1s93usrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like watching Formula One. Incredible boring but you can't look away.

Just in case.

#Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DVATW You should consider a combover. You've such a nice face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeahsCousin 
19:01 - Grief.
19:04 - Outrage about joke. 
19:18 - General joke acceptance.
19:43 - Alex Jones conspiracy theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boynamedshark I hope the Pope sees this, or else he might forget to obey Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail "Somebody's gonna love you" sounds like dialogue from Deliverance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton @JamesMawFFT 
"Joey Barton would never post someone else's quotes on Twitter without permission."

Friedrich Nietzsche, 1879]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a piece I call "Trump on Twitter". https://t.co/7TuW8C49IN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They've made their bed, Donald. They should lie in piss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No steam without piss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No nothing... so... something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @LifeZette This might be a bad time to say it, but you have a double chin in that photo. #fat #piss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wee, the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janhopis That, when combined with .@-ing, is worse than actual Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail Then there's this. https://t.co/H5MM6E03gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vornietom Not a movie, but Generation War captures the "this is normal, right?" mood of normal Germans pre and during.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsgorrie Yes. A working class theme park for people who are terrified of their bin man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianPilton All the best for 2017 Brian']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeahsCousin Which is to say, it was ace so well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonNRicketts So deferential to the source material too. It's his own and yet it's what we know too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themichaelowen @SpeySingleMalt 

THE SPIRIT OF THE WARRIOR COURSES THROUGH ME. 
https://t.co/IwgBfRZkn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bruciebabe Sensitive little Slush Puppy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bruciebabe @H_L_Thompson @hrtbps I'm saying you're fat, Bruce. A fat, processed snowflake - a Slush Puppy, if you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bruciebabe @H_L_Thompson @hrtbps After you asked billions to do so, you wrong un.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPDeacon ♬ Red &amp; white &amp; blue (passports), defo no black or brown. I can sing hard Brexit, sing hard Brexit, sing hard Brexit too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonNRicketts Oh, man. Hope you're able to wring out every last drop of joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminholgate @freddiedeboer @Glinner That's misguided, perhaps, but I wouldn't put it in the same category as blackface.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminholgate @freddiedeboer @Glinner I'd argue that a kid wearing it at a music festival does so cos it's beautiful and "spiritual".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freddiedeboer @Glinner Great article, btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freddiedeboer @Glinner It's about intent, no? Blackface is typically an insult, whereas an Indian headdress is worn in reverence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goddersbloom We should sell the Queen to the Saudis. It's the only way Godfrey, and I commend you for suggesting it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch This article says as much about you as Mair's bookcase said about him. You are unintentionally fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gergilroy Remarkable that this is the case in a sport with video replays. A blind eye in HD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRebellato I have the best phrases. So, so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRebellato The fraud thing won't matter to his followers (see tax evasion), but the theatre thing makes him look a bit pearl-clutchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itvfootball When did Frank Lampard come out of international retirement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy It's almost as if he thinks widespread riots are needed in order to make America great again. https://t.co/um37lB85Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys @saveciaranmurph Succeeded by Treefingers on Kid A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dempster2000 He used to play a dad on Hollyoaks, but then came the "allegations".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw The Bootleg Paul Dickovs in Camber Sands a few years back. All the hits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Redknapp @Betsafe @AlanMcInally @OfficialPDickov "Official Paul Dickov".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Corbyn and McDonnell were firemen, they'd refuse to tend to a burning orphanage because Amazon have a product called the "fire stick".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss4trump I pity you when the penny finally drops. It's going to be hard landing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss4trump 2 days in; Clinton won't be locked up, Obamacare won't be repealed, Mexico won't pay be for the wall. 

You were tricked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss4trump Lobbyists will. Even if Trump wanted change (spoiler: he doesn't), he's not competent enough to make it happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss4trump It's adorable that you haven't worked out that you've been swindled. You'll get nothing he promised. It's already unraveling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss4trump Dear turkey, enjoy Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage Fuck off you Toblerone-shrinking cunthouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMB @MeCookieMonster Why do you hate our war dead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hrtbps I'm in Latty, OH. I've amended the ballot papers to read "Don't mark an X beside the candidate you do not don't want to lose."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giantpoppywatch I've increased the #respect by appx. 25% to atone for his lack of #respect to date.… https://t.co/Jht0ezEoNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giantpoppywatch @DVATW Why do you hate our soldiers, David?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogerHelmerMEP "We will fight them on the beaches. But not on our web-sites BECAUSE WE CAN'T BE BOTHERED." 

Think on, Helmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWRichardson I'll be singing 'Canyonero' all night now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acjimbo There was a brief moment in time where racists and homophobes hide behind allusion. That's gone now, and the Mail reflects it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PaulHayward @honigstein @DaveToffy The players will be doing it because the FA instructed them to do it.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>