<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Your brain is chronic but the mental illness doesn't have to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @EENet_news for yesterday's workshop on mental healthcare evidence. Awesome to see the direction we're moving https://t.co/tXzLLQ4mgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AllenFrancesMD I've been using this as an example of why these criteria fail us. Especially the "distress clause" https://t.co/sOSfcPBZt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verylightnosuga Yeah, it's a really common compulsion. I hear about ppl doing it all the time. Weird and sad that awareness is lacking here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drs "unable" to Dx man with thoughts of harming self/others, calls cops to confess repeatedly... That's textbook OCD
https://t.co/RMmDndjRbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharmarkedesign I don't think the criteria should place such a burden on the individual to prove their story. I don't remember yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @EENet_news today codesigning evidence priorities. Awesome to see lived-experience, effectiveness, and accessi… https://t.co/kwkId5n6mX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hero we need, although we surely don't deserve her. @jk_rowling is saving Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engaging in compulsions to chase safety always leads to more of the suffering you were trying to avoid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharmarkedesign Thanks. The article brings up great points. We have many inaccurate assumptions about memory and emotions even if no PTSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packed house at @CivicTechTO tonight. Awesome to see so many ppl getting engaged in projects to support their commu… https://t.co/t0eyCf57An]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article oddly fails to mention what residential Tx facilities are like. Invest in community-based help for youth: https://t.co/kHqz5PlspN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAd23281707 Thanks, Scott!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigots take away space from others out of fear and weakness. With your actions, you can give space to others from a place of strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigots give cover to violence through their words. You can give cover to love and kindness by speaking openly about embracing diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our illness-first approach to diagnoses fails in these situations. The label doesn't matter. Is there anything heal… https://t.co/SyFLRaNgJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unable to access therapy, kids sink deep into Botox and self-loathing compulsions:
https://t.co/LhvBW50Ozw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lewis_EDM Sounds like a good time to step back and cut out compulsions like that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where we are. In which direction will we step? https://t.co/ZSm291IlE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength is sticking to your values in the face of fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reacting to fear by causing harm to those seeking safety has a long, sad history: https://t.co/ymCBUMicr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTheatreZen Enjoy those steps ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["unable to distinguish between what feels good and what's true..." Check out these prescient words from Carl Sagan: https://t.co/NKArYWbPhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Thanks! I'm glad you're finding it helpful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 It helped me to approach things like this as just any other fear. OCD loves to latch onto fears about values/recovery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meditation is great for handling pain but if somebody's hitting you with a baseball bat, don't forget to tackle that source of the pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OCDtreated Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First chimera created: https://t.co/ShGnE3BZIN That's good, right? Not like it was a fire-breathing monster with a snake for a tail...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's that word for somebody that only eats fish? Plastictarian?
https://t.co/RsdDOpO2E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a story to share of navigating mental health services in Toronto? Visit https://t.co/ir7DxjURhs to share / help others #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes your coffee binge to finish your PhD thesis look like a pleasant afternoon tea:
https://t.co/I5V4Rgjk81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For recovery, shift the focus away from fighting #OCD and towards doing what you value. OCD is only a tourist. Your values are here to stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeborrahS Exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't separate centuries of systemic racism from mental health issues in FN communities. #BellLetsTalk about that. Not just about bandaid$.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balance one day of talk with 364 days of action. https://t.co/f1Xc6XUvdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are life saving, evidence-based treatments for overcoming mental illnesses. You don't have to "manage" or "cope" w them. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, what has ten legs, is vapid on the inside, and won't be part of doing anything interesting or fulfilling in li… https://t.co/L6MgNaMYta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foerstk Non-searching is a great way to have a balanced head even when society is upside down :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this factual fact + a picture of a polar bear and ice. Remember what they looked like so you can tell you… https://t.co/5x6Sl2Br04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At what point will Orwell's "1984" get moved to the non-fiction section? https://t.co/ihd4zSCaVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need to go searching for an imbalance in your head when there are more than enough imbalances in society to fuel anxiety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antipsychotics are one of those things you don't need to get your kid started on early, especially for off-label us… https://t.co/6gmouowD7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team of scientists that have never seen a sci-fi film create semi-synthetic E.coli to take over the world https://t.co/2EuTou4WDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OCD_Guy_UK Yeah, it's unfortunate that's what they actually mean by "chronic"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It helps to approach recovery from a place of wholeness. You're not lacking. There's nothing to get. Only things to give. #mentalhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When somebody says OCD is chronic, that's not about the illness, it's about the treatment--what they've chosen or what they can access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's lying at the CIA about inaugural crowd size is a study in compulsive behavior (w/ so many layers of irony)
https://t.co/MlcKIrEHhB *]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howiemandel When you're speaking about OCD, it'd be great if you could mention that lots of ppl cut out the compulsions and recover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our mental healthcare system is so effective at creating advocates for system change: https://t.co/8wGBDjNtg4 (that's not a good thing)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verylightnosuga Thanks, Ally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imaginexbc @paulm_taylor The leader we need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Write a note to yourself about what you would never do. And when you come to the line, don’t cross it." https://t.co/kjQcqRYHe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mauty Sure, Mike. Send me a msg through the contact form on my website: markfreeman.ca and we can set something up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever journey you're going on, certainty won't be coming with you. #mentalhealth #recovery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a heavy squats @crossfitYKV these stretches from @yaboymillhoy help me walk from my desk to the fridge again https://t.co/6LUJYPlSxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to get a particular feeling and hold onto it, the only one you'll ever get is anxiety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A doctor shares about his fentanyl addiction and the tumultuous road to recovery:
https://t.co/3k1KgCOSic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a computer could tell you when you'll die, would you want to know? It's no longer a hypothetical question:
https://t.co/l67kjN6pHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see studies happening here in Canada on preventing mental illnesses:
https://t.co/rLAA78m2al They're not inevitabilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A look at the impacts on mental health care access if the #ACA gets repealed:
https://t.co/vLPTotHF3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rockstar engaged patient hiring primary care physician on the cutting edge of patient-centered care: https://t.co/SEoEbUByJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is now nobody walking on earth that has ever walked on the moon.
https://t.co/EcVJ4VHepP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organize as effectively as those who love war. #MLK https://t.co/faN22FHh2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On tarmac for 90+ min. Attendants give us free earbuds. But the plane's entertainment system is down. Gift to control sadness causes more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Yeah, find what works. It's like playing music--sometimes you play a note loudly, other times quietly. Be flexible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Yeah, meditation is a good example. Try to keep things flexible and light. No need to get stuck on one technique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 I approach all thoughts as the same. Could help to not see em as other thoughts. You can have any thought n return to present]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The psych sector needs to innovate. The old one-on-one, 9-to-5 only, sit-on-wait-list-for-9-months-for-a-bad-therapist model is very broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadigel Oh, that'll totally happen. The old one-on-one, 9-to-5 only, sit-on-wait-list-for-9-months-for-a-bad-therapist model is very broken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatrist diagnoses patient without meeting him. But is that surprising w/ the way DSM criteria are designed?
https://t.co/GyhhUFWORk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental health care and guns. One is a right, the other is not. The consequences are entirely predictable/preventable
https://t.co/oypJbzWm3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope. Not even anger about snow (snow rage?) is an excuse for your violent compulsions.
https://t.co/6cOh4Ldf9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah it's Friday night but grab a drink and cozy up by the fire to listen to these two chatbots argue w/ each other
https://t.co/FCItAtof6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsayzv Thanks! I'll share it around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selection from the top 30 under 30 list: https://t.co/n4XvOKzmXq Strive to be ranked the best person that feeds you breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our abuse of nature is making it go crazy.
https://t.co/aVUAFDGngB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwame_mckenzie Thanks for the clarification!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "...report found zero correlation between time spent working and career progression." https://t.co/3Tr7KWYIRy Go home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feeling you're feeling is a feeling you can feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have 39,000 students... The reality is 13 people cannot meet that kind of demand.” https://t.co/ebmNZlfWIT Ye old therapy model is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwinkleeT Yeah, it's passed from hypothesis to myth: https://t.co/8VXLNrZKuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneC70 Ah, it's sad because it's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental health dialogue in Canada is way behind the times. Chemical imbalances? More psych beds? The 80s called, wants it's broken ideas back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petergoffin Great to have dialogue but still important to dissect info critically. "Chemical imbalance" approach is now widely seen as myth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwame_mckenzie Did they quote you accurately here: https://t.co/mS6ta9BEAl What about evidence of over-prescribing? https://t.co/lAnZBbAiSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To help with your mental health goals for the year, imagine you're a pirate making your new year's resolutions... https://t.co/8c1eHFkQfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpollock03 Thanks for the recommendation! I'll check it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Told you so. Your brain is just a glorified spleen that excretes imagination: https://t.co/CxyMxGDqAI You are not your farts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheriff0604 Judging thoughts as intrusive or bad or wrong is the problem. Doing that naturally leads to more compulsions, as you've noticed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 2016 didn't kill off hope, right? Well guess the literal what: https://t.co/6F899R4W7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will we stop equating beauty with value?!
https://t.co/dFrL5R5J5p It's the soul of the camel that matters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Any time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Yes. Your brain believes you should know. But you're teaching it that NOT knowing is the ideal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Yes, and do things knowing you're uncertain. Enjoy doing the most important things you can imagine while not knowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 So it's about accepting thoughts and living by your values in a way that directly contradicts the fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 I'll confirm that belief and worry even more. Instead, I can agree that I'll be embarrassed and do the action I was avoiding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 If I believe being embarrassed is bad, my brain will worry about ways I might embarrass myself. If I react to those worries...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 There's a bit more to it. It's important to show your brain through actions that those old beliefs aren't useful. For example:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highviolet91 Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see that Ontario will begin publicly reporting wait-times for mental health services: https://t.co/1x52JzLf9b]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>