<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: New York Times 'is still lost' https://t.co/s7TfFchIXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The Daily Show’s’ Muslim Correspondent Hasan Minhaj Tears into Trump’s ‘Muslim Ban’  https://t.co/RZcjGctQpH via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Protest Against Muslim Ban and Anti-Immigration Orders https://t.co/slaCNqEaEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau says Canada will take refugees banned by U.S. https://t.co/lgyjsHgmew via @NewsHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Muslim ban excludes countries linked to his businesses https://t.co/r468BadLrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Gwyneth Paltrow, women should not put jade eggs in their vaginas, gynecologist says https://t.co/7w4LTYfR32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Prelude to President Trump’s War on the Free Press  https://t.co/vZhQRf7mLh via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just what we need https://t.co/vFV4Uf6uqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little bit Limey and a little bit rock n roll... https://t.co/borQp61zgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A right nice promotion, innit? ; ) https://t.co/RhuN4T2PkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Annoying Business Jargon - In Photos:Most Annoying Business Jargon https://t.co/2VICnMmlLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gynecologist secretly photographed patients. What’s their pain worth? https://t.co/PdIi5L3zaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Why stop at cheddar? Experiment! Ham-and-Cheese Waffles https://t.co/AdOyQa5GdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg @dbennettgroup When the time is right, I'll make it to Birmingham.
And that time... could be any time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi forces fight IS at Mosul University, take areas along Tigris: officials https://t.co/nARnn2sYSr via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... does this mean he's not interested in the U2 Joshua Tree anniversary tour? https://t.co/BEy4DVpdwa via @timesofisrael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Meyer: Tipping Is a Hoax That Fosters Inequality https://t.co/6XhXK3b3OZ via @Eater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our one true lesson from the Holocaust https://t.co/J6onsMGl0D via @timesofisrael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The consequences of not vetoing the Israel resolution https://t.co/OTjkwrY9Za via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't that the truth! https://t.co/98mkUoySQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Foreigners Among Istanbul Victims, Attacker Still at Large  https://t.co/VibamFwSTA via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, we will start 2017 with this guy as our president. Ugh. https://t.co/LrVwO1MXAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The death of Carrie Fisher and Debbie Reynolds is sad, no doubt, but why is that news item featured more often than… https://t.co/5c9NtYx1lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 10 Oldest Languages Still Spoken In The World Today via @culturetrip https://t.co/9ZAj2fDE5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eater  other countries have been using this technique for a long time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ishmael12345611 Merry Christmas, Ismail. You are a beautiful soul. Your videos and words have brought awareness to the tragedy in Aleppo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An appropriate use of the word "tragic" https://t.co/enbNCcotSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajplus Wonderful!There are so many  who have no way to post a message but await evacuation to safety.They are in my thoughts every moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Yes, this  is great! Thank you! https://t.co/uCk2zjsT8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg Really wonderful. France, Spain, Italy all have very similar versions.
I first tried the French version… https://t.co/jyqGGdh94I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
I missed this yesterday. I love salt cod... especially when pureed with garlic... served on toast poin… https://t.co/UsqYQT85wW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takeout-Style Kung Pao Chicken (Diced Chicken With Peppers and Peanuts) Recipe https://t.co/fEMRfmyB3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, assholes, these are wild animals.Don't approach them.Don't feed them.Don't let your kids taunt them. https://t.co/heh0JArrT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMSBites 
Really amazing product! Have you thought about perimenopause and menopause markets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revchristopher 
Go Robot Chicken! https://t.co/0VHv0vTVXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One More Thing to Throw on the Grill: Oysters https://t.co/F46pYKaX3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg @scbaird 
very cool https://t.co/2hJCH0HUvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A Brilliant Trick (Borrowed from Cornbread) for Crisp-Bottomed, Flaky Biscuits" on @Food52 https://t.co/GvQP3LgATV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Centuries-Old Form of Public Cooking That's Making a Comeback" on @Food52 https://t.co/cUgepZ2eTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg   Haha... very funny . So right on! https://t.co/OJ7Mv8KNGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipster Suffers Allergic Reaction After Eating Pork That Wasn’t Pulled - https://t.co/4xwnqjh5JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[County Fair Season Means Pizza Cones and Footlong Mozzarella Sticks https://t.co/PBMancHkwP via @Eater_DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aguachile: Mexico's Most Vibrant Ceviche That Isn't Actually Ceviche https://t.co/amHiy941h2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, You Can Walk Around With Fried Chicken Attached to Your Phone https://t.co/nnkOTeYMCW via @Eater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A culinary tour in ramla https://t.co/X3eOSLnsj5 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why People Who Like Spending Time Alone Can Connect With Others More Deeply https://t.co/yfLo3uK3JK via @lifehackorg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Insult Like the British - Anglophenia Ep 12 https://t.co/CAUoeWixL0 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Wow, how cool! Exactly the kind of thing I love to do! Send pics, please! https://t.co/Zz72x6Gjix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Girl Scout Cookies Are Coming; Tim Kaine Eats a Po’ Boy https://t.co/GkQqUGDBYz via @Eater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Stroopwafels Are One The World's Greatest Cookies https://t.co/wmB2wpd0ig via @HPLifestyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Boston, some areas bear brunt of opioid overdoses https://t.co/20PES4OlAv via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Make Lee Anne Wong&amp;#8217;s Loco Moco https://t.co/PMqBok7AYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niihau, Hawaii’s ‘Forbidden Island,’ is closed to outsiders https://t.co/8WASxKn6Tw via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Geoducks https://t.co/r1boWIgmfX via @Eater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubin’s may not have served its last knish https://t.co/BQ7DQ6t0fK via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks scrumpdillyicious. https://t.co/gQGJeg1mys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Five Guys, I've been with you since the beginning. Now, everywhere I travel, there you are! 
https://t.co/lnHw1Ak8fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Are Pulling People Over to Give Them Free Ice Cream onFood &amp; Wine https://t.co/m49HZkurjq via @foodandwine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice in Wonderland Restaurant https://t.co/LmhGrm759n #Architecture via @niume_official]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: What You Eat Changes How You Think onFood &amp; Wine https://t.co/b9JbivJUsr via @foodandwine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Where is "just behind the beat" located?
Is that near Manchester?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJemaineClement 
Bored? I'm so bored, I'm reading your Tweets. Bored. https://t.co/sacewCw5U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg @dbennettgroup 
 Can you convince them not to call it "foodie village"?Surely they'll regret it in 2026 https://t.co/E2shaZ5xKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Oh, yes, I watched that as well. Oy. https://t.co/Yg0JR8aZko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Lame. He didnt even have the steak with Whiz because it "put him off". https://t.co/wCnLRuhtKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbennettgroup @kevin_fegg 
That IS ridiculous. Poor dog. https://t.co/puwyk63Ut7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbennettgroup @kevin_fegg Oh, please, it's obviously a saxoladle! Sheesh! https://t.co/Ke5ODr7mfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg Oooo... "I want to go to there" - Liz Lemon (Thirty Rock) https://t.co/MstrPi1Lw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg haha! Indeed! I loved that book.  Did you enjoy it? https://t.co/Y4ZyNBtN3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg Hubba hubba! I work for an Ivy League... where is my Steve McQueen? Oh, right. Missing factor=Hollywood https://t.co/ut90G6fZXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNIBoston Went to Uni tonight. Unbelievably good!Everything was
 p h e n o m e n a l including service!
Thank you!! https://t.co/ECkTOgU8vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enough already! https://t.co/wbzckVISGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg  And you're doing a fine job embracing the world around you.Twitter on, my friend, Twitter on. https://t.co/hOkaxi8AAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful sammich https://t.co/GCVscd1Kj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaws... one of my favorite movies! https://t.co/0fUcQdiiaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg very much want to go to  basque region of spain. Been on my list for awhile. https://t.co/wWbqHftRiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And how! https://t.co/lQSiBp8Snf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha. Oh, yes, my love of food and alcoholic beverages is mighty impressive. I think I'm in good company. https://t.co/WT5jXfYzaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like lagers (especially sour lager) but like IPAs and amber ales too! https://t.co/DnG6Y3DAwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool! What did you have?  Camden Hells? https://t.co/zdc15Tp527]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg @dbennettgroup 
Oof! How dare you expose me to that! https://t.co/131yegWo5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg  The FOOD festival looks great! https://t.co/FiL4wRqqdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course Roxy's in Boston is on the list!

https://t.co/CLH0OWTJlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg nothing better than potatoes roasted in duck fat!  Deeelicious! https://t.co/ObOGbYUAdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Workers Find 19th Century Underground Shipwreck in Boston - ABC News - https://t.co/Wv2E0eZpct via @ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clam Shack rocks 

https://t.co/xNiHX5ag6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg @dbennettgroup 
Mmm... crunchy! https://t.co/T6xRhfEuds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! For the dad I never knew well enough! https://t.co/VxoZko44Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HgEaLovBir Rhubarb Upside-Down Cake @beardfoundation https://t.co/HgEaLovBir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats on working toward a healthier lifestyle! That's exactly why the studies are important. : ) https://t.co/PNZJBEChgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg True. I happen to know some experts who are not ! : ) https://t.co/QThZZsI8zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg  healthy debate! https://t.co/OPhk8uFTKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg  The idea is that we shouldn't be terrified of eating fat, right? And we actually need fat in out diet. https://t.co/1qwz0wrDDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_fegg 
Have a happy Monday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iv38 
Friendly. Fun. Easy to chat with, but... every culture has their good and not so good, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iv38
 lot of Irish culture in chicago, too. Had quite a few Irish(real Irish, not Americans with Irish ancestors) friends there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton and Sanders reminisce over drinks on 'Saturday Night Live'  https://t.co/xiHo406rXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iv38 hmm. They are all so different.  I appreciate each for what they offer. I probably like boston and dc best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iv38 been a while since I lived in DC. Lived in Atlanta and chicago before boston. But I do still miss DC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iv38 
Grew up in Washington DC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>