<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tauranga's new Labour Party candidate revealed https://t.co/QI6cu3ltYS via @nzherald.  All the best @jantinetti - you will be awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come join us at #hīnātore to explore Pacific navigation and 3D print your own waka https://t.co/QNXdrthmIZ… https://t.co/Yvlb1lnrn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting more girls into tech https://t.co/OR8j3ceIYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free learning programmes @Te_Papa Hīnātore | Learning Lab school programmes | Te Papa - https://t.co/lv1UTQmQAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bigdlinz talking to #mefnz17 about understanding barriers to paticipation - context is museum but easily could be schools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you make it to the end - video on sensory overload as shared by autism nz https://t.co/ULgFGPHJVJ #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Sensory overload is like being stuck in a disco 24/7' - autism nz #mefnz17 https://t.co/oT3Z0l27P7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do we cater for all our learners and their needs #mefnz17 https://t.co/NLPAqmAd1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO important RT @MindShiftKQED: 3 Ways Schools Can Be Supportive of Students' Mental Health ... https://t.co/OicPx7u8Lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@danmilward at #mefnz17 #hīnātore talking gamefroot and games in education https://t.co/fxEmx5o3DI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gamefroot as shared by @danmilwarhttp://gamefroot.com/ #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tpack framework https://t.co/IFx3AFGs8s #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[holoportation as shared by @sirmattrichards https://t.co/V6gyec30kZ #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tilt brush as mentioned by @sirmattrichards  https://t.co/7YKn7TDYk2 #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sirmattrichards  giving a shout out to @knowclue for the #hīnātore lab video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sirmattrichards of @Te_Papa #hīnātore talking about the research between the learning lab #mefnz17 https://t.co/Q02aF0ArGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Education inclusive website has awesome resources to support educators 
https://t.co/iwyr0FiUAw #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[congratulations @FalknerKatrina - so well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nlouwrens have you seen this new pi resource https://t.co/lV7D7MwUtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[arts for all, fab resource from arts access aotearoa #mefnz17 https://t.co/F5d1r04jRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melbourne Museum Autism Friendly Museum Resources including social stories #mefnz17  https://t.co/sr5s8BRw6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the idea of sensory maps that highlight high sensory spaces and low sensory spaces -perfect for mapping out visit #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inclusive programmes allows access for all, at all times  #mefnz17 #udl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listening to Adrienne Leith from Melbourne Museums talking abt making museums accessible for all  #mefnz17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Museum educators' forum 2017 about to kick off at #hīnātore #mefnz17 https://t.co/SB1cepAnMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reframing the Debate About Screen Time to focus on what we do with the device  https://t.co/xupVQ92Eiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous new @Te_Papa Bugs resource for ECE &amp; Primary https://t.co/Z2ajrvaOln #ECE #ecechat https://t.co/Bw4WUzjT5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lucky seven: Apple’s original iPad made its debut seven years ago Friday" https://t.co/HjXfCDuBVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final days of Slice of Heaven Exhibition at Te Papa.Great responses to the What would you stand up for today to mak… https://t.co/NOZ2nrCyXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An awesome array of school programmes available at Hinātore | Learning Lab at Te Papa. Check them out https://t.co/lv1UTQmQAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating a high-tech Learning Lab in a museum https://t.co/jm6MGbpwMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A modular drone that turns into a hovercraft! Check out @Makeblock Kickstarter https://t.co/okNnpcSTSY #airblock #programmable #drones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nlouwrens See this:  https://t.co/dE6ffsXejX  Think it could be great.  Hope all is well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome learning opportunity with @Raspberry_Pi &amp; @FutureLearn - Learn about programming starting Feb https://t.co/dE6ffsXejX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helzie Thx.Hadn’t seen this. Not quite sure what to think - seems limited in terms of exploration. Will have to find out more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft tutorials available in Te Reo for 'Hour of Code' https://t.co/IHr6hYqWzj Tumeke! @wawaro81 Will be a fab resource.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mountains Moved: A special feature on the week that shook our beautiful nation. via @NZStuff https://t.co/Sk4FbKAE4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nurturing te reo Māori language skills in ECE - Kia Ora Wellington Playcentre https://t.co/USFcnXUu2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring our working theories this morning at the Wellington #corebreakfast with @kerynjdavis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all about achievement challenges today - join @carolynsenglish in 20 minutes.  Online, free &amp; just for you  https://t.co/l96FojcL3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School principals hope an internet group's new powers will mean fewer cases of online abuse. https://t.co/tsBuGJUxuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to make robots as smart as humans is to teach them to learn the same way we do. https://t.co/b8cf4YEGeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the Connected Communities session today?  You can watch via the recording https://t.co/r2jnsU3Uqk #cenz16 https://t.co/xnAmZt9cP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome opportunity to talk CoL’s, inquiry and collaboration #cenz16.  9.30-10.00am https://t.co/l96FojcL3n https://t.co/E6ya1KMc8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview piece with @sallyannw on STEM and CS in curriculum https://t.co/To1A6FOlPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love how technology can bring us together. Joining in from afar for  @coreeducation farewell to @Wrighteze - nice to be in the virtual space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ and AU Careers with Code - new edition out now in print and online https://t.co/85OLjJjYtY @RefractionAus #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does your Kaahui Ako reflect your community and New Zealand asks @carolynsenglish #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding where students are, where they have come from helps us work together to support them #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working from principles - we need to have vision and purpose for working together #cenz16 @carolynsenglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to late to join @carolynsenglish for Working from Principals, underway now https://t.co/l96FojcL3n #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Working from Principles’ - Why work together starting today at 9.30.  Join @carolynsenglish from 9.30-10.00 today  https://t.co/l96FojcL3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @carolynsenglish for the second webinar in our CoL series. Starting in 20 mins https://t.co/2yBLPUAfhE #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, just finalising up from the competition and winning video released later today.  Others released soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited to attend "Smithsonian Learning Lab Webinar: at Connected Educator Month 2016. Come with me?  https://t.co/VrOebsYmsd #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephcamp1 @coreeducation @nlouwrens @fivefoot3 how is this: https://t.co/1zYYjcdGEz will also send through another later today :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Learning Tools Help Educators Create More Inclusive Classrooms https://t.co/tXx5EPF6rV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catspyjamasnz @kimtairi @HotereBarnes Tumeke!  Along with the other suggestions, this site might be useful:  https://t.co/4wrwmfBNhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great post #uLearn16 reflections 
https://t.co/f4KCFNXTv7 #cenz16 https://t.co/wtyLwh1Sol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share your story about getting started with games in learning https://t.co/ABR9AOig5t @BronSt #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about how we can create challenge, goal setting, contexts &amp; agency for learners in games @BronSt #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good game design is something educators need to understand more about @BronSt #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful learning is socially constructed - shout out for ece  @BronSt  #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The conversation and discourse around the game is as important as the game itself @BronSt #gamefulpraxis #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As teachers we need to know what our learners are engaging without outside the school @BronSt #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communities of practice essential to support teachers understanding  of the role of games in education #gamefulpraxis @BronSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BronSt talking games in learning #gamefulpraxis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out about #Weltec by @fivefoot3 and getting started in games for education #gamefulpraxis https://t.co/52DNMPK0LJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing @dianagracenz todayat #gamefulpraxis but know her input is here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[awesome hero up gathered for #gamefulpraxis https://t.co/LTNiR0Lpdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived for #gamefulpraxis - exciting day ahead with @BronSt @fivefoot3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the fantastic Connected Communities webinar today, the recording is available https://t.co/OtDjDm2kmY #cenz16 #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not too late to join @carolynsenglish italking Connected Communities with a guest panel 9.30-10 https://t.co/oKBtaOWtNi #cenz16 #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @carolynsenglish in 10 minutes talking Connected Communities with a guest panel https://t.co/l96FojcL3n #cenz16 #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @kerynjdavis for the next CORE Wgtn breakfast - The power of research thinking to transform teaching &amp; learning https://t.co/Zvq22ycpPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fantastic keynote from @virtuallykaren - let's make a difference for our learners. Ngå mihi Karen #cenz16 #ulearn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The deliberate, intentional practice at the heart of being an educator @virtuallykaren #cenz16 #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DianaWilkes thanks! It has been fantastic  to see so many connected conversations #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have had fun bring #cenz16 to you RT @TarnzC: 1 more run from the Connected Crusaders #ulearn16 ... https://t.co/Hw4t650GWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annekenn Am almost thinking not only do we need a #notatulearn16 I think we need a #atulearnandwatchinglivestream ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is the biggest staff room in the world - @nzvh #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nzvh talking connected leaders and building plns https://t.co/mqnFBLnRgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think, Collaborate and Act Globally - Geoff Wood #cenz16 #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 https://t.co/iyLyTmnP9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story of Over the Back Fence with @nzkauri https://t.co/anjw03YDOH #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nzkauri sharing his story about connecting through collaboration #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 https://t.co/TbBaa0ivze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerriattamatea DM your address, I have a few small #cenz16 goodies to post to you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have new appreciation now for designed learning experiences.  Thanks @catspyjamasnz #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to have empathy for the user when designing learning experiences @catspyjamasnz https://t.co/QdhKOUtaYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on in &amp; join the live streamed Connected Conversation featuring @catspyjamasnz @nzvh Geoff Wood https://t.co/IiW8fSDjPb #notatulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@catspyjamasnz taking the stage and talking learning experiences #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 #cenz16 https://t.co/ClJopFh1W8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catspyjamasnz Kia Ora Joyce, so great to have you as part of this series and sharing learning experiences #cenz16 #notatulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those #notatulearn16, join @dwenmoth @MichaelFullan1 as they talk Coherence - is it possible?  More info https://t.co/JeyJn9LqyT #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hekiaparata address visually represented #ulearn16 #cenz16 #notatulearn16 https://t.co/dhROY1n6Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerriattamatea See you again soon #notatulearn16 #ulearn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nyssa76Jones I @MissesArtech Indeed. We need more diversity but making it ‘pink’ is not the answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful words and provocations from the wonderful @whakaue2 #ulearn16 #cenz16 #notatulearn16 Ngā mihi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eMPOWERedNZ @AmesburySch   @whakaue2  What synergies - hearing the same message here in the livestream panel #ulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the aspirations you have for your child - @whakaue2 #notatulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are we going to nourish and grow each person we teach? @whakaue2 #notatulearn16 #ulearn16 #cenz16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The transforming learning and assessment will be taking questions over twitter - starting thinking and sharing now #notatulearn16]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>