<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCFilm2017 @dannytheleigh @prevengemovie an incredible feat from writer/director/star @alicelowe and producer @JHandorf. Brutal stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are currently only 114 MPs currently working I would ever consider voting for. And even some of them I wouldn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage indeed. You still need to quietly withdraw, pen resignation to EU parliament, get in the sea, end it all, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack nonsense. It's all about the snake wang. #AASW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewheatleyclu1 @FreeFireMovie I think I agree. I just love Sam's face on the other one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure if I prefer this or the faceless version of the @FreeFireMovie poster but Sam Riley's face makes this… https://t.co/dkfLd8iko7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shudder_UK I may have to invest in a Roku or a Chromecast, but it's yet more kit amongst the retro consoles and laserdisc player... Plex?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shudder_UK fantastic news and many thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shudder_UK are there any plans to develop an app for the PlayStation 4?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MondoDan last shot of the house, it implies the second option, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MondoDan I agree. (Both about the meaning of the last shot and film endings in general. If you watch who walks out of the house in the...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack appreciate it. I'm sure someone's written it up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack I'd for sure be interested in the deleted scenes. I'll look on line and see if they're subtitled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack sounds tasty. Extras?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London friends. This is what you've been asking about. https://t.co/lbF5H6Sdi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MondoDan yeah, it's great. Plus, Still a little ambiguous right at the end. I mean *SPOILERS* is it all three of them or just the two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack I watched it on Amazon Prime but I might buy the Blu anyway. I love physical media and it's certainly a keeper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack Oof. Lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MondoDan It's rare I enjoy a movie that much when I see the end coming so clearly. Gorgeous photography and perfect tone made it a gem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I'm a bit late to the party on this one but I just got round to watching Goodnight Mommy. What an amazing, beautiful horror film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first instalment of my Xmas gift from @JHandorf just arrived. It's gonna be a good/fat year. https://t.co/KnByQErsfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris_osbyrne @mr_wheatley or this. https://t.co/cmlwOOK0RS either way, this is one of the times you're allowed to play music on the train.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camillard I agree it's unfair to tease the kid but if he's actually homeschooled then it's less of a joke and more of a wish...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 @JHandorf there's a few listed in the second image. @zoflower  has all the knowledge, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the crazy brain of writer/director/star @alicelowe and the miracle enabling mind of producer extraordinaire… https://t.co/IOwKvKPZ6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah you say you've experienced DV/R (I've no reason to disbelieve) but you say this: https://t.co/MjB6TAp2S6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah @HuffPostWomen you're so angry &amp; quick to name call. I'm confused by the disconnect between your statements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah  I'm glad you don't experience it but don't demonise the experience of others. https://t.co/aHRFgLQffS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah Not sure what a cowardice troll is but nearly 20% will have been sexually assaulted, statistically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah how about these women, recent enough? They deserve what they got, in your opinion? https://t.co/ivOr38PIJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFinnemore his reaction is this because until a moment before the photo she had no arms and they were all inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cjgodiva @DKhanna77 @TarekFatah Sounds like victim blaming. Was the fate of Mary Ann Nichols, Anne Marie Burr etc due to their actions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack checking the spelling on imdb shows me there's still a few I need to watch. He really is very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack Le Corbeau is great, if you've not seen it. https://t.co/jraCmWiVCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slippery_Jack Clouzot can do no wrong, imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely morning working with @TobyAmies on promo for @prevengemovie (starring @alicelowe, produced by @JHandorf) video up soon, I'm assured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm happy to help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm 
#10 in space. 
#11 With Freddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm 
#7 starts in lake, hypnosis plot
#8 On a boat. Stephen King's Pen. 
#9 most gory, uncut in Canada, body swapping, Kane Hodder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm 
#3 3D, finds mask
#4 "Final Friday" Corey Feldman and Savini
#5 Not Jason. Mental asylum. 
#6 "Jason Lives" ends in lake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm maybe the following potted Friday 13th catalogue will help.
#1 the surprise ending. Saving FX
#2 no mask, wheelchair down steps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm they're oft maligned but for me they're the pinnacle of 80s studio horror. &amp; only franchise to successfully relocate to space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm we watched #6 on the 13th. Campy fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig's first pub Sunday lunch has gone well. https://t.co/MDXWYYJ5aX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillaRestal I have looked. I find no proof of what you claim. It sounds like you have no proof, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillaRestal @clairecircuit @rosehip300 can you show me a source for that? Or even that there was a spike ahead of the referendum?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillaRestal @clairecircuit @rosehip300 and the fiscal plummet just happened to coincide, to the day, with the referendum results?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillaRestal @clairecircuit @rosehip300 presumably by "sky" they meant "pound". They were correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ace new poster for the great @prevengemovie written by/starring the fantastic @alicelowe and produced by the magica… https://t.co/DpVunFZAEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp it was indeed. Also: https://t.co/L06m1QmL37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp aw man, that stuff was great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHandorf film and a pizza if you're back early enough? https://t.co/OgJQF8KL0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 the Pig like that but punctuated with brief comas. Like someone trying to level off their PCP with smack but overshooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp my pillow is 3D! It has no depth but does exist for more than a single instant, which is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 I'll let you know, 'though I suspect a 3 month old French bulldog would be utterly useless in a post apocalyptic wasteland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines well now I know what he's going as for Halloween: The Rocketeer! (Pigateer?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig has a new job. It's very important and he's taking it very seriously. https://t.co/s4hnGFfXno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 ooh, that's a kind offer. I may just take you up on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 😂 Like you weren't going to anyway. I think I got about 8 out of the 13/14 there are. The trick is look for yellow wires!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremythomas666 @Playdead so good. Just found out about the alternate ending. Not like I wasn't already playing through again anyway...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't think @Playdead would be able to outdo Limbo but I just finished my first playthrough of Inside and they did; it's a beautiful game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the @bbcnews @Channel4News et al agree not to report on anything @Nigel_Farage says/does? He should be denied the oxygen of publicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamHoopFilm such an amazing film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first day back at the workshop is my first day away from the Pig. Soon he'll be big enough to come to work, thou… https://t.co/MO3NX9is52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_wheatley Amazing films. Only watched Blu 1 from my Arrow set; have yet to find time for a full rewatch. Beautiful from what I've seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkwilkins it's a Sumac Martini. Recipe by Yoyam Otolenghi. Absolutely bloody lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingredient two ready. https://t.co/x4vfGtBxS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkwilkins seven, I miscounted: Orgeat syrup, a vanilla pod, allspice, a clove, ginger bitters, Angostura bitters &amp; lime juice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six ingredients to make ingredient one for tonight's opening cocktail. https://t.co/K2ALkSVNo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig has a new hobby. #notacrime #alsosomecrime https://t.co/qf1tAic0Xr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines @SarahDobbs ha ha. It's a film that works well on that format. The grain suits it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahDobbs @cjlines it's worth the dig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahDobbs Haunting of Julia aka Full Circle: https://t.co/kp4tGlaioh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone I know selling a car? Reasonable boot space, mostly for the drive to work, occasional kit hauls to set. Mine has had it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TriciaWhatley he got his way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig mistrusts the big hand. https://t.co/Z8mtc8rvkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig votes for another day on the couch. https://t.co/sMJCaLHmB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines that's totally what I meant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines well, goat can mean "greatest of all time" or a lecherous old man. So maybe the film is the cake and you are the goat‽]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines it is a more fitting title, though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig has had a very tiring Christmas break, apparently. https://t.co/xpUF3nxafu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines ooh. You're in for a treat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjlines does that mean you've not seen Eastbound and Down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewheatleyclu1 thanks, and a happy Christmas to you, too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel go back to 3250bc and put a Rubix Cube in the hand of Ötzi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel @LeightonJimbo I dunno "I've got a time machine" is a pretty good opener...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewheatleyclu1 @_Val83_ aw, thanks guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@qipodcast is there a word for homonystic nominative determinism? Homonative determinism? https://t.co/QOJPQM51Hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig's sleepy tongue doing its thing... https://t.co/dswiVo4oTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel @YouTube "just"? This is now on my Xmas viewing list for sure. Thanks for the link!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel I've never heard of On The Eighth Day. I wonder how it holds up, compared to Threads (which is a masterwork.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pig is not especially impressed by his first foray into baths but that's what you get when you insist on walkin… https://t.co/VZy0EdJeG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New development: The Pig now sticks his tongue out in his sleep! More on this breaking story as it develops. https://t.co/tknd9yXFvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting article. I have my own non-existent childhood film that I'm rewriting because I remember it so vivid… https://t.co/TEs0lSmkZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No pigs here, just this average sized potato. https://t.co/SJsrP8Nr3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Livsdarling That said, having tried to eat in the constant company of a puppy for the last week it deffo makes for hard-mode meal time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Livsdarling Get takeaway delivered to work. 

Maybe kick it up a notch and combine it with a service like this:

https://t.co/AZ1bVyUzSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michskie1 thanks. That's very kind of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itchynads ooh. Hello. I didn't know about this at all...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaDelPizzo video of The Pig coming tomorrow!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>