<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Now seems like a good time to repost my take on how @realDonaldTrump alienates even natural allies! https://t.co/qeZ5hIG4lA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Republican power-play must be resisted or the rule of law itself is at risk." https://t.co/PQRhJ1Lu0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good summary of the 6-8 o'clock hours https://t.co/M5mbhMTL5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump doesn't have the temperament necessary in a President. https://t.co/t4Ew5hnYH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump jabbering about fake news at a #BlackHistoryMonth event flanked by Ben Carson &amp; Omarosa is a liberal meme come to life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't make this stuff up: https://t.co/ULEZpS5yGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllAboutFi Those are "alternative" trains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically @HillaryClinton's talking points. https://t.co/1xXhgnWt3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snark aside, this is an absolutely insane rule change for a party that railed against the @ClintonFdn for years. https://t.co/NEsOPOwQPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump transition email shows initial effort to oust all inspectors general https://t.co/SnRyI7DsBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. Just as an oil executive is confirmed to lead the @StateDept. https://t.co/NEsOPOwQPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why on Earth did @EPN think any of this would've gone differently? https://t.co/d3AuCl8lrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts: #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/tuDbctEylM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deleted my original tweet for obvious reasons. Pity that ppl feel the need to embellish an already tragic situation. https://t.co/S5ETMhmQyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JordanHupp1 By that logic, was FDR's interment of Japanese-Americans not discriminatory because not ALL Japanese-Americans were detained?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JordanHupp1 So it isn't a ban, even though:
1) the president called it a Muslim ban
2) applies to Muslim countries
3) excludes non-Mulims?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not cool that this guy may have been less than truthful. Still, Trump's policy is inhumane. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/k3pzsOe4Lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A Totally man! Racist memes are hilarious, and the key to a successful future in Republican politics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo I do, actually! I put my @AmericanU education to good use helping Dems and refugees!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Your tweet is as heartless as it is anecdotal and irrelevant. https://t.co/NlQimsakuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Glad we clarified that you have no argument. https://t.co/OE9IAPl7k6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@putoguey @K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline  Ah, two tweets. Is that you, @austin_cirillo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Nice attempt at a sick burn! https://t.co/yplMPRYv4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline  @austin_cirillo Ah, so the facts are wrong, but you FEEL that the points are "true."
Millennials ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo @NewYorker But, hey, the data don't support CIS's long-held biases, so why not ignore it?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo (which, by the way, I think is a cheap out. There are data available) https://t.co/y07bAWWr0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo The source literally admits there's no way to calculate off-setting… https://t.co/TTLCVHn0Uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo I did. The Center for Immigration Studies is a right-wing think tank. Not credible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo A word of advice, always research before putting your name out there https://t.co/brbi7oVcZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo The piece demonstrates a remarkable lack of knowledge about US refugee policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo They come to the US for permanent resettlement, not to take public assistance forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Literally ALL US-bound refugees were, in fact, previously living in a "neighboring country."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NCBlake @K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo This point makes no sense. Refugees come from those other c… https://t.co/xckQSw7lZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo If you actually want to do this, that's only the second dumbest point after citing cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Citing Russian propaganda to make an easily debunked point doesn't bode well for the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Alexander_A @TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo K. Alexander, you simply must know that the facts here don't jive! https://t.co/5uyHk383pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the press corps are honoring this OTR request, why? https://t.co/OtfaGgDzic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEagleOnline @austin_cirillo Also, sourcing from @RT_com is just silly! Vladimir Putin is simply not a reliable source of information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheEagleOnline Hey @austin_cirillo! Your facts are bad: Paris attackers were EU citizens not refugees #NoMuslimBan https://t.co/XKObefT6Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine that... #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/kSWST3RxPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wheresrosinow @DeceitinDrugs I'd imagine the relative quality of American healthcare may also play into the calculus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(obligatory reply where I clarify that this is a joke) https://t.co/oSFFJiLmci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, this is all just a distraction. What's @realDonaldTrump about to announce?! #resist https://t.co/9028RrC6kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey look, @realDonaldTrump submitted a brand new business registration in Florida on January 3, 2017. Huh. https://t.co/9pgo9iqGE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be a pretty effective way for Trump to:
1) Feed the far-right
2) Save the US government almost no money https://t.co/iQjgEdSr2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @HouseGOP is running scared. https://t.co/e8U6W8bw40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JordanHupp1 The "90 days" mean nothing if CPB took away your green card.  #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/kLklZR70p1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting that whenever I have a tweet that picks up some steam, the troll accounts all seem to show up together. https://t.co/Lf3D7GfS0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet somehow, the @WhiteHouse is openly touting Gorsuch's "own political views" to justify his nomination. #SCOTUS https://t.co/Pbox2tboFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workers At @Trump Hotel Vote To Unionize https://t.co/OPSXCZA15g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["us" #FireBannon https://t.co/CcyzQyjKyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But @nycsouthpaw, you must understand that they're aren't discussing the @Trump Organization! They assured us they… https://t.co/5kN6o8Ae0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump security’s use of force questioned https://t.co/zCeXdNzerx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trans-Atlantic Mood Sours as Merkel Refutes Trump on Euro https://t.co/SylbLEDusF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bipartisan group of federal prosecutors backs Yates https://t.co/dK6NqlxvXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me it's "not a #MuslimBan." 
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/Y2MmbYin3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Are The 'All Lives Matter' Supporters Now? https://t.co/Um2BXoPpe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why exactly is the US Embassy in London RTing #SCOTUS tweets? https://t.co/EbhzVOdBYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator Hatch: Trump doesn't seem to have separate Obamacare plan #SavetheACA https://t.co/q7bM7TeEnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a renter. Otherwise, I'd love to! #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/6rZYVGkPtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Washington Correspondent’s Own Refugee Experience https://t.co/NdlMci1FXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @kenklippenstein also exemption for Middle East Jewish folks. https://t.co/i6slDJ4vZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell your Senators to stand against prejudice and fear-mongering. #NoMuslimBan https://t.co/Qqkg1K82SP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch on Merrick Garland: "grossly mistreated ... among the finest lawyers of their generation." #SCOTUS https://t.co/Tpom6UgG9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executive Order Separates Badly Burned Iraqi Boy From Family #NoBanNoWall Boston https://t.co/oUWXVO1DWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow this promises to be remarkably normal compared to the baseline for politics in 2017. https://t.co/pqphD5RjdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMINDER: @Reince Priebus claimed green card holders aren't affected by the #MuslimBan. A lie w/ blood on its hands. https://t.co/4KwB3aOkFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is a US citizen and aided the US military. @realDonaldTrump's Border Patrol refused his family entry. https://t.co/aPRfSRF9FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact check: True
#NoBanNoWall #PelosiTownHall https://t.co/JtsY3lz5eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics matter. Real lives and real issues have been irrevocably harmed by the @GOP's refusal to confirm Merrick G… https://t.co/Sx52uIdBdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come for the @StarWars references, stay for the passionate defense of the United States of America. 🇺🇸 https://t.co/VodDdbOmdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They were in the wrong place at the wrong time. Naturally they became heroes." - Leia Organa, Star Wars novelizati… https://t.co/nzNe7CDCMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The world's doors were closed': Jared Kushner's grandma on refugee life https://t.co/C9y6FOShld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell, @DonaldJTrumpJr? #MuslimBan https://t.co/geQU9luKix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Washington University Student Barred From US Amid Trump Immigration Order https://t.co/40brKQnNch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court will examine partisan gerrymandering in 2017. That could change the voting map. https://t.co/GjR8PpDyq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snarkytoes @zagush A good question! We don't know. https://t.co/u4riNZWihg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kurdish family headed to Nashville sent back to Iraq after selling everything they own #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/8fTJRAAzrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds detain Katy High School student from Jordan following President Trump's immigration ban https://t.co/2DCHb9umoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories of a simpler time, when LED signs caused silly mass-panics instead of the @WhiteHouse. https://t.co/Ikkni2IEgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's not a #MuslimBan, then why is a man NOT from one of the seven affected countries being detained?… https://t.co/J9Y1tIFfSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@zagush I'd argue firing Inspectors General is a much worse precedent. They, by definition, cannot do their jobs under political pressure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats decry Trump threat to fire inspectors general   https://t.co/dTonH6BUB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand transparency from @realDonaldTrump. Sign this petition: https://t.co/JTbEnSCRip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall gaining converts in the @GOP https://t.co/rNpbTMKxXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not good. At all. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/4qY9mWZTWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh, really? https://t.co/83vwgjFBOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos appears to have plagiarized quotes in official responses to Congress. https://t.co/tmFvLwhl0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Ignored All of Obama’s Advice—and Now He’s in a World of Trouble  https://t.co/4pnOL6WOgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no editorial justification for his objection" https://t.co/9tRuJsLhcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are new signs Republicans are going wobbly on the #MuslimBan https://t.co/mTL1dbk1W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(tbh, we don't know if that's @SpeakerRyan or not, but it does kind of sound like him)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh shucks, @SpeakerRyan, that was some locker room talk right there! #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/b9liqpHsU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sacking acting A.G. raises new questions about his respect for the rule of law https://t.co/BtDIUL4WPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look, another nominee with plagiarism problems. Is no one at the @WhiteHouse vetting these answers? Malpractice. https://t.co/wOganDXeOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerRyan opposed the #MuslimBan months ago: https://t.co/jZkRdoLE9n. Now he's running interference for the… https://t.co/UEJD45ivG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next puff piece on @SpeakerRyan's much-vaunted Catholic faith should address this issue. You know it's coming. https://t.co/3Vdko2LTfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerRyan is not a moderate. He's not an "independent" check on @POTUS. He's handed @realDonaldTrump the reins.… https://t.co/hVFSj3eo1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of people affected by @realDonaldTrump's #MuslimBan: About 90,000 https://t.co/fcBrUqkncb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @FBI has quietly investigated white supremacist infiltration of law enforcement https://t.co/0mwN7xiM4x]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>