<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant reality check on ASEAN centrality by Richard Heydarian  #TrilateralNSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will Trump's US or Australia or Japan do when there is a security crisis on Korean Peninsula? Good question  #TrilateralNSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaired a bracing discussion this morning on how Australia, Japan and others can cope with US unpredictability #TrilateralNSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troubling. Is this how Bannon really thinks?  https://t.co/WPAJW0uU40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Withering words from Eliot Cohen after week one of president Trump - worth reading in full https://t.co/8A7NkDUdla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Australian who thinks it is business as usual under Trump should read this. https://t.co/8A7NkDUdla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james_acton32 James can you please follow me on twitter so i can DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the next India-China war might look like via @htTweets https://t.co/NNuK6xKR7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid global uncertainty, time to study national security - enrol before 6 Feb https://t.co/y2cfGPRD7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[huh, the  world is as angry as it gets? it could get a lot worse  https://t.co/jxiRslDP6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad times for American diplomacy  https://t.co/Fy6OVN4m8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US spies fear allies will stop sharing intel under Russia-friendly Trump https://t.co/DCICxmJO9J via @POLITICOEurope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's never been a better time to study how to ensure your nation's security ... https://t.co/y2cfGPRD7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is US intelligence community still investigating new National Security Adviser over Russia communications?https://t.co/ZIronKuFDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ANU Currently reading Australia must do more to influence US political decisions: policy paper | ANU at https://t.co/7A5PCP98wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Trump mean for Australia's security? Inaugural Policy Options Paper from @NSC_ANU  https://t.co/WRo7lJwFXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corrective to Tom Switzer's odd piece in today's @smh - it's not only the left that opposes Trump https://t.co/DJWvwrGA3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This damning new assessment of Trump is from US conservative and strategist Eliot Cohen https://t.co/DJWvwrGA3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely right - Australian compulsory voting a safeguard against a Trump movement here https://t.co/jXwIRv8phq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why US allies now need to count on tempering by congress and Trump's cabinet  https://t.co/tK7wWjGWKe via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should US allies do about the new Trump reality? Look to each other. Do not panic - but do not relax https://t.co/WRo7lJwFXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intercepted Russian Communications Part of Inquiry Into Trump Associates https://t.co/2pDmDzZKKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid Trump uncertainty, time for Australia to diversify security links with other Indo-Pacific democracies https://t.co/WRo7lJOhmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's alliance bigger than any one president - but difficult times ahead. Outlook from @NSC_ANU https://t.co/WRo7lJOhmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian foreign and security policy wakes up to Trump
- don't panic, but don't relax https://t.co/WRo7lJOhmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't panic, but don't relax - how US allies should handle the reality of the Trump presidency  https://t.co/WRo7lJwFXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bookgrocer with a good book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump inauguration - #surrealityTV #Inaug2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow the ANU National Security College will release its first ever Policy Options Paper - what Australia should do about Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But not Australia https://t.co/ddf0au1rlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud that @NSC_ANU and its Futures Hub had a role in this important scan of the global future  https://t.co/iqGl1CLGbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[grim and useful view of the future - the US National Intelligence Council's global trends report is out  https://t.co/GFyIVwdNu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s News Conference: Full Transcript and Video https://t.co/VK8Ywn8c5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which basically confirms that it does https://t.co/U69rBm6URU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia says its spooks don't collect compromising information. That's a relief. https://t.co/UVw2zJ2Lu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Received Unsubstantiated Report That Russia Had Damaging Information About Him https://t.co/YwlIwnRCOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More to come - report on Russian efforts to compromise Trump. Would explain a lot https://t.co/wvIief961B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany probes Russian fake news campaigns in lead-up to elections - no democracy is immune  https://t.co/CLtgvkRobD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troubling mix - a nuclear first use policy and submarine launched missiles https://t.co/0a1gCHmERS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wackileaks - how the US right fell for Julian Assange - and why we should now see him as he is  https://t.co/HrnIdCnYxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['badly mishandled the MH17 plane crash controversy'? An odd way of saying shot it down https://t.co/tN0WwXz5aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmGarcia what and they give nothing back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence is America's edge in seeing the world. Why is Trump starting presidency with self-blinding? https://t.co/5O6lMVVASG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence is America's edge in seeing the world. Is Trump beginning his presidency by self-blind ? https://t.co/5O6lMVVASG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perilous and stupid - damning definition of Trump's treatment of US intelligence community https://t.co/5O6lMVVASG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump trusts Putin and Assange but not America's own intelligence professionals, then who can trust him? https://t.co/pYsth1evL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To US intelligence analysts - don't let Trump's disparagement make you quit, the world needs you https://t.co/wPTzBmomp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still find it surreal that Assange and Trump are so mutually supportive - yet this is new reality  https://t.co/nJsXEK3EIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newsworthy. Trump meets a dictator he doesn't like  https://t.co/rx2tlSdShS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymooners 'forced' to splurge $1600 after Sydney NYE fireworks dream goes wrong - what a pathetic non-story  https://t.co/iBsmlMBmjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This graph gives the lie to absurd claims that Japan is 'militarising' https://t.co/zeRm10pUYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of intelligence analyst America needs if it is to cope with a Trump presidency  https://t.co/NvjAHnaP5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great role model for coping with the tough geopolitical times ahead - and it speaks truth to power  https://t.co/AfNzit8stC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolton breaks with Trump line over Russia cyber hacking of US election.  https://t.co/nNeEn6Mhnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Russia recruited elite hackers for its cyberwar on the US  https://t.co/wmEm2ggPUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expelling 35 Russian intel operatives a good start. But next US Administration needs to sustain the pressure  https://t.co/FjBa33efDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's on https://t.co/kFjPXaO69Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a Christmas rest, I have lots of reading lined up on how small and middle powers can protect themselves in a troubled world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how many Assange supporters realised that Wikileaks and its help for Trump would help make this happen https://t.co/tvaq118O1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enrol to learn about national security in the Indo-Pacific in first semester 2017 https://t.co/VTa076rPcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 16 new @NSC_ANU Masters alumni - a new generation of expertise in national security https://t.co/hzG8oc0bFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-China drone incident a reminder of risks ahead - nuclear-armed rivalry underwater @lowyinstitue https://t.co/0MVMikXQUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Striking front-page photos of Russian ambassador's killer - doesn't anyone think these glamourise terrorism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to teaching Masters course on national security in the Indo-Pacific in first semester 2017 https://t.co/vZ0Alof7HB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing and chilling that more Americans don't seem worried about what Russia tried to do to their democracy  https://t.co/48zjdZM4Q3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astounded at how Trump can keep undermining US interests by rewriting history of Russia hack  https://t.co/u7Akf98YW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian interference: Donald Trump threatens to wreck US democracy. Republicans are helping. https://t.co/XmjcRXRU9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting with America: Mike Green nails it @lowyinstitute https://t.co/IsVNze3n8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Officials: Putin Personally Involved in U.S. Election Hack - When will Trump face facts? https://t.co/KLf8ejGvUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Russian cyberpower invaded the US election - don't assume something like this couldn't happen in Australia  https://t.co/QRHpd2GC7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to involving @NSC_ANU in generating insights for #fpwhitepaper - process launched today by Foreign Minister Bishop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will be flat out listening to intel briefings if they take his advice and let him know every time 'something… https://t.co/U1CfvPN6Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading A Very Expensive Poison by Luke Harding, recommended and chilling reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @teaandscones666 @the_intercept so why not support a bipartisan commission to get to the truth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason to study national security @NSC_ANU - Professor Paul Cornish to teach cyber and intelligence  https://t.co/7c563KlMur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget Nixon to China. What will Trump to Russia do to nascent Beijing-Moscow axis? Still, hard to see silver lining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All democracies are vulnerable to foreign interference - time for new safeguards after what happened in the US https://t.co/wnINX3miGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s get the facts right on foreign involvement in the US elections https://t.co/wnINX3miGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Message for President-elect Trump - intelligence capabilities are good for the USA https://t.co/2d52Yug2M2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jabinjacobt @EvanLaksmana @ics_delhi the implication being that a pro-Chinese foreign policy would be somehow 'independent' ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Cyber Kangaroo can defend the internet of things  https://t.co/hpggIe6qOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's mixed legacy on security - my interview on ABC Radio @NSC_ANU @ANUmedia https://t.co/Y2U9Etx7Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia is under cyber attack today - thankfully this time it's just a (very serious) game https://t.co/qjV02U61G2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia will have to deal with tomorrow's cyber threats today - thankfully this time it's a game @NSC_ANU  https://t.co/XFFDocd4bS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why China should heed the lessons of Pearl Harbour https://t.co/KVOIhBWRSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping I was right in Feb when I suggested our Defence White Paper could weather the travails of Trump  https://t.co/NzK994VYHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharp insights on Australia's cyber vulnerability by NSC_ANU expert Roger Bradbury @ANUmedia https://t.co/Sp4NpgT5Ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to Sharif: "Amazing work, visible in every way". Not so sure this applies to Pakistan's strategy toward India https://t.co/LzVniZSg6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump had every chance of a good start with the world's largest democracy - no longer it seems https://t.co/LzVniZSg6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news: CNN anchor dumbstruck by Donald Trump voters convinced of mass voter fraud https://t.co/spvzAaiAKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing I'd do to revolutionise science in Australia https://t.co/AD262K7oiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring story  https://t.co/cwADXBPNU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in a career in national security? Study with @NSC_ANU - information evening in Canberra tomorrow https://t.co/rbynSO5j56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to study for a career in Australia's national security? Information night this Wednesday @NSC_ANU https://t.co/y2cfGPRD7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian propaganda effort helped spread 'fake news' during US election, experts say https://t.co/93KFPCHH5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaoulHeinrichs thanks Raoul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read. Seriously powerful demolition of Wikileaks' war on democratic institutions - a deeply inconvenient truth https://t.co/V5pH4WAOaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great insight into a successful diaspora community - Indian Americans https://t.co/e00NHjIRjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see so many @ANUmedia academics in 70th anniversary of Australian Journal of International Affairs https://t.co/MLhJFGjH4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured to have an article in the 70th anniversary issue of the Australian Journal of International Affairs https://t.co/MLhJFGjH4m]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>