<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TitusOReily can you call someone a soft cock ? #AFLWBluesPies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalphyHeraldSun or most north melbourne games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly i bet nrl would like a crowd like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedonoghue lucky @crickettas played guys in form or we would have been in real trouble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor actually surprised it hasn't been done before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor do you think it will help for the next tour of UK , worth a try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor Are they being used in all the shield games ? had more swing than Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brentcostelloe @HurricanesBBL @WINNews_Tas hmmm whats happening there ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedonoghue @DivaBay22 @Dyka355 saw that Boyce took 5 against Clarence the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theroyaleditor @MailOnline 36th in line, gee alot of things have got to go right or wrong depending on which angle you are coming from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertEllul @Simeon_TW @plalor Very good point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertEllul @Simeon_TW @plalor Doran coming off an avg or 4 in the bbl and only 24 in 1st class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertEllul @Simeon_TW @plalor but replacing him with someone who got dropped for his keeping and batting performance in the bbl ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simeon_TW @plalor equally as hard to explain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMercurySport @Stubboir @themercurycomau no funding for grass roots football for 15 years ??? absolute disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@australian so that makes nbn redundant before it really starts ? Great way to spend billions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theroyaleditor if this is true why doesn't it getting reported more, or does the world media like to bury this typ… https://t.co/odNybTD7JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedonoghue @Dyka355 extremely difficult to work out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themercurycomau surely now is the time for state government to get rid of most of the states councils and have about 4 to 5 max]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themercurycomau the last thing anyone would need is the Hobart city council looking to do anything anywhere near them. #hopeless #muppets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@White_Adam @BBL heading north,south,east or west ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@White_Adam @BBL when ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simeon_TW not just this summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Maddison , class palyer, needs an innings, haven't seen the best of him, he's got talent Yea yea yea #BBL06 #willheever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SENNews @TheRunHome I thought @KP24 has been fantastic for our game and I don't support @StarsBBL . I hope he comes back next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craighall01 @rohan_connolly @damonheraldsun @theheraldsun I'm with you on that, those guys will carry this with them forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7NewsMelbourne probably unlucky he was in court this week , would have been let out last week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommorris32 Paine move from uni to North ? Hasn't kept shield this year, Doran is the keeper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarfSerious @bowlologist @MarkHoward03 @tensporttv need the dude from the Brownlow to carry them out too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportmeister_ got Ben Dunk to who plays as a batsman too, plenty of keepers,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportmeister_ shield cricket that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportmeister_ Na plays for Uni. Jake Doran keeps at the minute, have McDermott too who made 130 odd in future league today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportmeister_ Paine hasn't kept for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsMelb @9NewsAUS a very big problem, happening too much and need to have their licences removed, some can't walk but still drive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solskjaer025 @White_Adam Paine can't get a game now and has not I think all year, maybe even last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsMelb do this in New York - 5 year min - max 20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsMelb nothing will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vomited quite a few times up there in Queensland, know what McCullum is going through #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomsteinfort they are good, real good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theagesport @theage I like it, cricketers glad they don't make bats though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnewsAdelaide what an arsehole wanting to grow food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughriminton @DavidLeyonhjelm What a Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor horrendous, no respect for anyone here, they treat it as a God given right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pierik_AgeSport @theagesport @Bombersteve @SMHsport @theage add a Waugh there too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor @australian agree so wrong but an amiture compared to Tony Burke 2 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitch Marsh -12 @CricketAus #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must say the comedy factor of Mitch Marsh in the @CricketAus team is quite good. #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving CH 9 commentary, I was the same as Maxwell, had all the shots just played the wrong ones #AUSvPAK #cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdferg26 @shanedonoghue fucking awful, absolute rabel, the only leader is not the captain. Big changes needed. Need to exit some Paine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedonoghue @HurricanesBBL @crickettas the poorest field settings you will ever see. #overhall #newblood #gotridofwrongkeeperbatsman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lithgowflashman maybe captain needs a spell, 3 behind square on off side when clive bowling, horrendous field placements  #amiture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lithgowflashman is this now about 8 losses in the last 10 ? Someone needs the arse. Captain, coach or selectors, maybe all 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomfoolery3145 @ajsmiddy appetizing, I suppose in some way your lucky @crickettas @BlundstoneArena had anything left !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a positive note for the @HurricanesBBL no one actually good enough for national selection for any country. #BBL06 #Hurricanes #chinup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ICC @manuz05 @BLACKCAPS is that Burt's boy ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarfSerious @Uz_Khawaja Tipping Ian Chappell loved it #oldtimer #irememberbackin73 #mybrothergreg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcgrandstand @GerardWhateley Warner trying to save his spot from #Lynnsanity #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffLemonSport may well have been better served wearing the old New Zealand one day get up #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcgrandstand Wade may well have been trying to keep in an impending rear exit - hense the crunched over slow moving exit #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBaum I believe the Sydney test is produced by the NRL, plenty of back slapping too by NSW commentators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarfSerious lucky it's the cart and not the old school stretcher. #oldschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simeon_TW @themercurycomau funny only said at the game would have liked the odds beau Webster to bowl the second over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simeon_TW @themercurycomau not the first time at that ground, other hurricanes games have been investigated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfStitch bet punters are quing up for this sale $17.99 each or 2 for $40 #bargin https://t.co/DN9T1RjKLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannygreenboxer @PerpetualLoyal cracking pic, not mine but passing it on https://t.co/McF3jWoqSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachelolding @smh waterside suburb of Hobart "Rokeby" that is a very long bow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmaxcricket thrilling test cricket - great pitch - no wonder test cricket is going down the drain,with this pitch its not even a contest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[curator at @MCG doing a sterling job to kill off test cricket with this shit pitch. @abcgrandstand #boring #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowlologist does he have the ability to AVG 20 / 30 in test cricket? Bloody handy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildOatsXI @PerpetualLoyal you both need to be back next year to knock over the big American coming back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcgrandstand how come i have not heard the ad nauseam comments on the shit weather at the mcg like you do at Bellerive Oval ? #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plalor nothing like reading the old melways so both you and the drivers know where they are going #oldschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Swannyg66 not a bad thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiecox1969 clean hitter of the ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAPathway @ShaneWarne Tip 1 plenty of sun screen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@936Hobart whisper is that Coles pulled out at the last minute on Glebe Hill estate shopping centre late yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@australian i know politicians are dumb but surly not so dumb as to use their own phones #prepaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danbrettig what a great idea,playing 4 day matches before a test series, brilliant, who would have thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeonCompton other clubs doing what Sydney and a couple others have done for years . More structure and discipline. Better leaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty i just cant believe it, he strikes me as trust worthy, honest hard worker, just loves the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kanecornes id sleep in a tent to play in a gf with sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsSyd absolutely   terrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajsmiddy a pull shot when your 6/120 trying to avoid a follow on and innings defeat ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly bit of a @redbullracing  @danielricciardo moment #ausvsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agerealfooty and punters reckon richmond took a chance on Yarren !!! This was a bigger gamble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFLTasmania more boards than @mickfanning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7NewsMelbourne and again everyone else pays for an minority - wont make any difference. stay out of peoples lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brisbanelions love the p r of clubs this time of year with "pb" being done, of cause every club will get pb's with 2nd yr players #hype]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latimes may never have been asked, presumptuous prick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brydoncoverdale had a good 50 over series too, may have turned the corner, hitting the ball crisp again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billshortenmp employers are not trying hard enough to get employees??? Pretty much sums you up #joke #noidea #morehandouts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pierik_AgeSport @theagesport @SMHsport @_TheTonk @ChrisBarrett_ was nasty, hit very hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rdhinds great to see shield ground's serving up day 3 wickets on day 1. Can only help our cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly @Jesse_Hogan @theage salamanca would have missed you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly maybe Sam Whiteman from WA and he is English born so might be ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarfSerious they will be ok, retire back to their million dollar homes and cars and not give it another thought till the next test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TitusOReily They were lucky, got the best of the pitch, weather,better hotel rooms,eye fillet instead of chuck steak, virgin not jetstar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBaum be careful what you wish for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rdhinds thank god for the full day of rain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MickMCG34 bowling to the pitch conditions perfectly]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>