<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to @replyall's episode #86 Man of the People by Reply All en route to work. I'm obsessed.  https://t.co/Hw6G6Q7MPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it more agressive or pointless to tweet at ppl/companies u want 2 work for? Was thinking "pls hire me I admire you greatly and can write"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I've ever wanted in a podcast. https://t.co/npdbOg9hbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to go to the gym and watch Netflix on the treadmill but wifi is too slow now so I'm listening to political podcasts... #bodyandmind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My journo friends must listen to this, lots of smart people. Let's do our job. https://t.co/fp2dDHhlDL https://t.co/fWdapNBlzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or maybe we're the daughter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all the Dad in the library reading a strawberry shortcake comic to his daughter rolling on the floor screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girly_Juice I love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends who flu together stay together? @HollyIsWyder 🤢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today a therapist called me spunky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girly_Juice I've thought about this before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're a nerd and you love the man." - my boyfriend after I said I didn't feel bad that he got a ttc ticket for not paying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At sea if the boat sinks the captain dies. That's why I want to be a passenger." - Josh, 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I see perfect winged eye liner on someone else and I cry to smear the feeble attempt I made off my face. Teach me pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went on vacation without telling my roommates and came home to a stupidly ugly couch in the living room. I have been replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was denied health insurance and I'm more confused than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One time I got up at seven and then died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever drop a blueberry in your kitchen and then just think "oh well"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girly_Juice yuss I'm in!
improv soup for the soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I move forward knowing the irreparable damage I've already caused to my schnoz? Also who has a tissue all of the time anyway? Hanky?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My grandma told me if I keep wiping my nose with the back of my hand it's going to change shape and be upturned and ugly by the time I'm 50.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I moved into a house without a laundry machine three months ago and I think I've only done laundry twice and who knew I owned so many socks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you there, God? It's me, Steph."

"... new phone who dis."

💔😫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT CHRISTMAS UPDATE. My brother's Chinese Zodiac sign is a MONKEY not, as previously reported, a rat. I'm so sorry for the error.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I eat one carrot can I have another five Christmas cookies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not ungrateful just thought it worth revealing that I cried in my last three improv classes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone ever yelled at you for asking "would you like some spaghetti?" not enthusiastically enough? Yeah, me neither.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UGH I just dropped yogurt on my knee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look it's a picture of my brother on an elephant."
"Oh, the rat."
"What?"
"His Chinese horoscope."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My to do list is as follows:
- laundry (crossed off)
- grad school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so excited to buy socks and then go to improv class. Also a kid just stood up and peed his pants and I need a tetanus shot (unrelated).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K but HAVE you ever had peanut butter m&amp;m's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my bebs @ The Monkey Vault Movement Training Centre https://t.co/lXO34FBS1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyIsWyder you and this random guy on the other side of the planet would get along https://t.co/GCe8z0OtHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyIsWyder Holly this is so gross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've never felt terror just google "sea turtle throat"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vibin with the weird kid at the back of the class who also walked into the wrong room and decided to stay because you can't fake fate brutha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girly_Juice I LOVE ALL THAT IS YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @HollyIsWyder what are you doing tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesketchersons of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered that @HollyIsWyder has also never seen Borat and this is probably why we're best friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who says *something no one says*."
No one. No one says that. You are the one person trying to prove something no one thinks. (Me to myself)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working at circus on the weekend:

Kid: Are you a kid?
Me: Uh, nope!
Kid: Why are you so small then?
Me: Well... okay you got me there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh it's gettin real https://t.co/XuwylTgeMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenBeauch you know it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a kid flailing and sobbing on the floor of the library while his nanny tries to put his pants on and I feel a strong connection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just applied to be a professional cuddler because I've been told I'm v snugly and I was denied social assistance so this is my life now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm frightened, friends. 

An American Tragedy https://t.co/HoIP3xSLfH via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I can think of is grade eleven world history when I learned that all nations fall. And that I wanted to live in Portland w my mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just hit my funny bone and I'm genuinely distressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tolstoy was a prophet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Can we make a musically?"
"No buddy, your mom says no screen time on school nights."
"Come on, be cheeky."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My new biggest fear is teenagers." - Lila, 8.  Same dude. Same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:
"Are you going to be watching the election?"
"Yes, we've ordered in Swiss Chalet."

Should I write a book called "Schoolyard"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just don't want to be cold or go bald."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just looked in my garbage can and all I saw were granola bar and bandaid wrappers and I guess that's how last week went.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so terrifying and solidifies my choice to bike always even though someone could shove me off my bike I gues… https://t.co/Xjsy6h29CN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteDeCourcy anything for food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's got all the elements. You know, fire, electric, water, fear, surprise..." Ronan, 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw my first Sunday Night Live last night and was thoroughly impressed and delighted! Big laughs, sexy band, cute smiles @thesketchersons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids are soft and sweet and snotty and so loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is much, much too early in the morning for noisemakers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenBeauch blasphemy. Also then how will I tell yours from mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't find a pencil. I also can't write in a book in pen. I have three pens. I need to underline this quote. I'm so stressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, I can't come to work because there's an acid cloud on my block and I've been cautioned to stay inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is more colourful and harder to see after midnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in denial of my freckles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids are nuts ya know. Straight wily almonds. How do we ever calm down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got tipped $30 to teach a beb to somersault because the parents realized it was nine am and I'm here for another twelve hours. Bless you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked into a bank branch today and have never been more well received in ma life. Bring cookies everywhere you go, I guess. Ppl listen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ErinSylvester it's heaven. I hit up Hot Oven bakery on roncy. Also one near Runnymede. So worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered almond pretzels. Welcoming winter weight gain with open arms and mouth and wallet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteDeCourcy don't u know it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took the day off kids to put cookies in bags and curl ribbons. Not sure about the future but heck I got free lunc… https://t.co/tZT3EMy9j2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously how much power do librarians have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes you have to 'yes, and' your own catastrophe." I pay for improv instead of therapy because it feels more socially acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's easier to behave when we know who we are to each other." What I learned in improv last night. What I am applying to ma lyfe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom: I know why you spend three hours a day wiping noses, it's so you have time to write. 
Me: I still can't pay my rent. 🤑]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just applied for a job with a Haiku because I'm running out of ideas guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just spent $20 buying the kids ice cream because I'm running out of ways to make them love me is this what parenthood is dear god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The job market was so dismal I had a better chance at surviving by scraping by as a fringe performer."a Dad to me. As I wipe his son's nose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At four thirty in the morning you can eat as many granola bars as you want/can because what happens after three and before five isn't real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S1:E1 "Downer Ending" of @BoJackHorseman is an under-thirty-minute encompassment of all I am and fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gracious Bitch: A Memoir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Openly weeping in public because I'm allowed to feel sorry for myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Writing is a hellish task, best snuck up on, whacked on the head, robbed and left for dead." MacDonald again, right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you look closely, however, you can see that they all have the thing in their eye. The result of an accident or a gift." AM MacDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calcium magnesium. Chamomile tea. Something put me to sleep, please. Back rubs? Dry reading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the eleventh hour, the self-doubt begins to creep up on you. Fear not, though, we can only bring the best we can. And that's gotta b okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's no unqueasy way to go out of this world." - Drew Gray, of a bio-crematorium. Idk if you want to google it or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird that things are only gross if you notice/ know about them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I basically aspire to be all that is Don Gillmor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A  Poet Self-Destructs https://t.co/wZKwUR7YNm "Art is nothing but loose ends." Amen brutha. This one hit me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kid gets kicked in the crotch, decides 2 hang low w me 2 recover and read. 
"My book's about lego ninjas."
"Oh, that sounds cool."
"I know."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They keep coming up 2 me and saying 'weird species.'"
"Huh, are they playing a game?"
"Idk"
"Wanna hang out with me for a bit?
"No thank u"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Board-Game Theory https://t.co/2Dxqm0gRtc my bffla works here too "in the world of games, failure is necessary to success." Awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What plagues me? The infinite number of "Subscribe Now!" inserts that fall from me like breadcrumbs leaving a trail. I already subscribe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, two big wins last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyIsWyder wtf what the actual f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet dreams to all you lovers and poets]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>