<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweedy151 @PennyRed, If you believe social justice is bullshit, you're alt-right. Plenty of normal people think marginalised people matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf, If it brings you actual joy, it's not clutter and you shouldn't have to get rid of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanderkoogh, try Sharon at https://t.co/lnaJTgsJ7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: rivalrous (thanks to https://t.co/Zkd8ifn0UV )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Krisjohn @cueballAU, I've decided to form or join a group to pressure current/future Australian governments into imposing sanctions on USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cueball_AU, b) Address the global threat it represents; c) help US citizens, both non-financially and... d) financially; e) fight fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cueball_AU, So what can us foreigners do to: a) raise awareness among others in a way that's empowering,  not just worrying; 2/...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cueball_AU, So, it's obvious to me that you're one of the few people outside USA who recognise Trump's administration as a calamity. 1/...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: contour  (thanks to @reemansell)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played #Thunderstone on 2017-01-19  https://t.co/RGpCEkJXFy #bggplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@summerbrennan, Me too, and I'm a straight man who has lived in Australia all my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, ultimately, real charisma only comes from inside; must b learned/grown. Then you can be popular &amp; powerful, young padawan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, Remember that it's possible to fake charisma (surgery, clothes, makeup) and people may believe it for a while...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PsychoSting, Are you going to @Genghis_Con?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: substandard (thanks to @V_garpend: https://t.co/uK4CoXHiQR )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny4ashley, Happy birthday! Don't forget to masturbate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: prevail (thanks to @ashedryden)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, I know someone who did that once, with a car-load of crushed aluminum cans. The container refund money paid for the fuel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLadyLycan, Growing old disgracefully is an art form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaiTalks, Hi!  Can you please DM me your e-mail so I can keep you up-to-date on the Web site restore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondie_6E, Messy. Stay safe! *hug*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strange_Animals, "TAKE ME TO YOUR LEADER, EARTHLING"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strange_animals, I DON'T NEED DRUGS ANY MORE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastasaurus, You are doing so much for people. I'm in awe of the effort and heart you are putting into everything. Courage is infectious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondie_6E, Nice hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glipschitz, Telstra claims it was ordered by the Federal Court of Australia. Their message quotes "Section 115A of the Copyright Act 1968".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strange_Animals, "This is OUR plant. Bugger off!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: entirety (thanks to @toastasaurus: https://t.co/jvoqgugxIv )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a mall santa scaring kids with threats of coal or rotten potatoes. It's almost like we train kids to fear Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashedryden, Seems if anyone is stopped for something like this, then the EFF might be of use. Maybe not at the time, but PR help after?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondie_6E, Does this mean that if I send you selfies, you'll Photoshop santa hats onto them? Coz if so, deal's off, babe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashedryden, Sounds cool. What's it about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, Maybe you should stop growing meat plants then. :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: lucrative (thanks to @blondie_6E: https://t.co/WpeNSwO6Gb )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dril, Yes, but what is your opinion on people making veiled references to my wife's asshole!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorLudlam, Just found out you've taken leave to deal with stuff; I'm thinking of you. If you ever want to talk about anxiety, I'm here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, It's a kind of arsehole solidarity moment for many of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, Would it be fair to say that until Ferguson (and similar brutalities) and the election the US didn't really know itself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, Indeed. I'd argue there's been a lot of improvement; just unevenly distributed. I think a lot of progressive people don't realise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, Sadly bigotry, ignorance and xenophobia are a massive part of many sections of US society. Change takes vast amounts of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, Yeah, but fortunately I'm seeing more action and discussion than I am disillusionment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, I snorked near the end of the list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kessily, Holy shit, that's grand. Did you do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: solace (thanks to @reemansell: https://t.co/siiHoNj5Xh )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hipikat @shrydar, I wrote a wrapper that takes care of this.
https://t.co/sa2TSc2j24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian, What have you been smoking? I've never even HEARD of two of those languages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The contents of robots.txt doesn't matter.  Here is an example site the triggers the issue: https://t.co/jf4EXd6ZSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VladimirToncar, Hi.  I've found a bug with sitemap_gen.py where it fails during robots.txt parsing with "KeyError: u'\u2713'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: aphoristic (thanks to @warrenellis' newsletter: https://t.co/GWQ4Rg9GKe)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek style impulse drive, here we come!
https://t.co/eYTMA0S3wt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Measurement of Impulsive Thrust from a Closed Radio-Frequency Cavity in Vacuum", by White, March, Lawrence, Vera, Sylvester, Brady, Bailey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Further info: https://t.co/Q9AFQCC4rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect that Newton's third law of motion needs to ask itself some very hard questions.
https://t.co/UNKfsiyk3G
#science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf, Can I tempt you with the Open Exocortex Project instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaosmanor, Moooove on, cow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c8ters, Oh wow that wig looks just like your hair in your profile pic! Twinsies! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf, To avoid having to use external tools, I made this: https://t.co/Qs7GlJjjY8
Yay Makefiles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strange_Animals, fucking hipsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: Salzburg (thanks to @PennyRed: https://t.co/Ws6GnBqs7X )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondie_6E, Am I allowed to call you the Slutty Power Ranger??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scroeser @karun777, A hard read; crystalises a lot of the thoughts I've been having. Good call-to-action?
https://t.co/0EKaUe8xQA
#antifa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf, Better that than hallucinations brought on by sleep deprivation. Hallucinations are not graceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@errbufferoverfl, You're a wizard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pcaffin, It's worse for us than you think. Malcolm Turnbull had nothing bad to say about Trump, so our leader thinks our paths are aligned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hipikat, Interesting. Why do you think they wrote that in advance? And statistically, it's going to happen right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freakboy3742, Replying to an old tweet to see if you're still looking for phone answering services that will follow a script?  I am too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kagij, People probably said the same thing about Abbott.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @BrownesDairy, I bought your Mango Passionfruit yoghurt and my girlfriend thought it was "pretty bloody spectacular". Good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump won. Game over.
#election2016 #fascism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaxy424, WHAT WAS YOUR SECOND INSTINCT??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: jest (thanks to @ShannaGermain: https://t.co/aDbAa8TIYM )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OaklandElle, The biggest problem with Trump is not what he will do, but what he is happy to encourage in others. Orders of magnitude worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pypikat, It's like someone decided Unix was too easy, and thought "how can we make this like a cross between VMS and a Warhol painting?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksylor, Was there a traffic jam (a.k.a. gridlock) outside? X-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilMsTangent, That's the awesomeest 5 pictures I've ever seen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondie_6E, Can't you just stay home and jerk off to Garth Brooks records? :-)  PS -- How was the tractor ride?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaxy424, Wrong! *unzips and pretends I have a sock fetish*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pirate Parrots (meet them here: https://t.co/dm9YgNzFEI ), Absinthe, clothing and fine jewellery stalls, prizes for best dressed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steampunk Pirates &amp; Fairies Ball is tonight! (Rigby's bar, Perth CBD)
https://t.co/MJOsPD9zNN
Burlesque &amp; DJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Pirate Parrots who will be at the event: https://t.co/dm9YgNzFEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fluffygutss, Oops, I didn't read far enough ahead! Hope to see you next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to the Steampunk Pirates &amp; Fairies Ball this Sat. night (Rigby's bar, Perth CBD)
https://t.co/UiEnUlrvw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strange_Animals, totally #badass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mad_Harri @Orientdan, No such thing as reverse racism (i.e. towards white people)... it's not discrimination if directed at the privileged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strange_Animals, I like how "an ambush predator" is as specific as you can get, because no-one has ANY DUCKING IDEA what that thing is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, I dare you to snort coke out of my butt crack on my 69th birthday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian, Whereas most Muslims think of IS as a bunch of blood-thirsty, divisive blasphemers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian, Well no, most real theocracies are plagued by cronyism, pork barreling, ego stoking, graft, etc. but at least they do religion well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgefwoods, It's like a circle-jerk where no one will look each other in the eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian, I think it's problematic to call IS a theocracy. More like a military dictatorship lightly garnished with the trappings of religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed, Thank you. The world needs to hear about this clown car in a suit, this coke-addled, asinine shitfight pretending to be human.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've been eating too much chocolate when water tastes savoury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: precarity (thanks to @PennyRed: https://t.co/Jv2cjGDxpH )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@V_garpend, But why? You're beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashedryden, What is problematic about the Red Cross?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinkSarcophagus, god damn, that fuckin thing's fatter than Eric Cartman. Have you considered using it to take over a sumo wrestling gym?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: intelligible (thanks to https://t.co/8FnoJApmQE )
#Django #Python]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: oneiric (thanks to @warrenellis’ newsletter: https://t.co/GWQ4Rg9GKe)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAEZnet @Genialgenius, correct site: https://t.co/ruCZ4jMQKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WordOfTheDay: verklempt (thanks to Joshua)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>