<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayKodaline Hey Jay, would be great to meet for a coffee, really liking your content on YT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really excited to be bringing a campaign between @madisoncawley14 and @ParamountIRL to life next week! https://t.co/Glhc7rvBUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaCusack Incredible story, booked my first lesson at Weston last week, good luck with everything!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but if you call yourself a 'social influencer' and you have 19 subscribers it takes away all credibility from you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@intercom really make the customer experience online much easier. Beautiful product]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiosracht @Ryanair Soon to be Norwegian Air also hopefully!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiosracht @Ryanair Would be the absolute dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiosracht @Ryanair Would have loved to see what they would have done do them if they were allowed to acquire them as opposed to IAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love this company https://t.co/6c2W3RXlkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its absolutely incredible to see how different we consume media today as opposed to 8 years ago https://t.co/RcJ6tWELqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JWT_London Hi, can we DM? Looking for an email from somebody at JWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stphnmcsweeney @MrNiallMcGarry No idea on data, but for sure we delivered engaged, educated users, its up to the app to retain them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stphnmcsweeney @MrNiallMcGarry @YouTube Those downloads were unincentivized, so no giveaway etc which is why it is more impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrNiallMcGarry This 'influencer' campaign we did for a fashion app got 14,000 downloads in 24 hours. That is value https://t.co/uOpOeNY69Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrNiallMcGarry In Ireland, most of the 'influencers' have no influence. They will die out. Creators, with real influence, won't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHarryMcC Massive respect to you guys for sending something! Its easy to not acknowledge the effort of some amazing people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a Dublin air traffic controller on now that sounds identical to Liam Neeson 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its absolutely amazing how nowadays everybody's work mainly revolves around computers, as opposed to 20 years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosie_mansfield @oisinkim Thank you Rosie!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronguthrie @PursueCo Thanks a million Aaron!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you check in 3/4 days early for a @Ryanair flight, they always allocate you the middle seat! Better off checking in the day before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People not being active on email is absolutely killing me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tracy_Keogh @ChristineBohan A year since you wrote that! Thank you Tracy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is superb: THE FUTURE OF CITIES https://t.co/IpUbNgw6s3 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tracy_Keogh Leaving your phone and laptop in the office - no tech at home, works for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tracy_Keogh I feel like I'm at home here Tracy!! Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seanopry55 Hi Sean, do you have a business email I can reach you on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Hi, I need to change my phone number connected to my personal account. What do I do? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat file for $25bn IPO. Meanwhile, in popular culture in Galway.. lol https://t.co/h4mjBEwJX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also props to @AIBBiz for sponsoring + new branding looks great @DigitalWeekIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @DigitalWeekIRL for a great weekend - had a super time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail How much does a one way ticket to Cork cost at the station?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail It says the 6pm train to Cork has spaces but I am trying to book and no green seats are coming up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing a campaign for an app and we've crashed the whole thing after 20 minutes. Impressive but annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ambrose_Cooke Please check emails asap - thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be heading down to Cork this weekend to speak at @DigitalWeekIRL - should be great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wearebroadlake @WebSummit Have a super time guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmberVenzBox Hey Amber, whats going to happen to @LIKEtkit with this IG update? https://t.co/dFBao7apPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Ridiculously slow wait times to speak to somebody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypoison Hi Emma, do you have an email I can reach you on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeekFitFreak Awesome feature on the show man :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Hi - can you reach out please when iBB is back up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lifeisgood Hi, have a question - can we DM please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thefaceshopCAN Hi, can you pass me on the details of a PR/marketing person please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of @mcnfreedom acquired for $60m. I'm of the opinion it is worth nowhere near that. Will cease to exist in 2 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemmaCostello4 Hey Gemma. Would love to chat about Fáilte Ireland's use of social influencers if you are free for a coffee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryhand I have no idea how posts get so much traction and carry so much weight, as opposed to FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not usually interested in politics but am very impressed by @DonnellyStephen and what he preaches! https://t.co/VZVvdCpiJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anouskaPB Hey Anouska, building a management agency focused on the travel 'influencer' space - would love to chat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuedeBrooks Hi; just to let you know the email in your YT bio page doesn't work - probably are missing out on oppo… https://t.co/pbf3LU8Imm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brother_hubbard @wearedesigngoat Thanks a million!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brother_hubbard Hey, wondering who the designer was that did the logo for Sister Sadie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso Not a hope can you justify $35k for 200,000 views. About $15k maximum, still good money (for the 'influencer')]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So awesome seeing @CaseyNeistat get so excited about planes lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shows like Jeremy Kyle set the standard for atrocious television]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveandRobotsHQ Super. By far the best brand I have come across! Will send an email - thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveandRobotsHQ Absolutely in love with you guys' branding! Would appreciate if you could let me know the designer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iabireland Okay super - have signed up for the waiting list. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think they should ban horses and carts in Dublin city centre. Absolutely stinks + they are seriously slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iabireland Hi, are all of the tickets for the Digital Upfronts event gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@followupcc Your product has turned very buggy and unreliable. I have paid $320 over the past 14 months in my subscription. Going to cancel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BingChen @YouTube A change like this should make creators doing brand deals more acceptable in the eyes of the audience (which is superb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BingChen @YouTube Brand deals &amp; merchandise are usually the other main sources. Any other revenue generator creators should look into?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMXCI as long as there is demand for short/viral content, it will be supplied. Demand is increasing also as attention spans decrease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMXCI Learned from @garyvee: 'The market is the market'. Clever people may think the content is ridiculous, but millions engage with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super response from Freddie Wong regarding @YouTube's controversial stance on monetizable videos https://t.co/hMMHxkCL6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find it really interesting listening to marketers speak about 'influencers', buzzword after buzzword, most have no clue what is going on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMXCI And many people have built up hyper-engaged audiences here, so income from this will be a nice supplement to overall earnings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMXCI Not a chance. Its an incentive for people to post video content on Twitter. Short, viral content is v. shareable on this platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMXCI I think they can turn it around by making changes like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see Twitter coming out with a monetization program for its creators. Great to see the 70/30 split, also. https://t.co/YiAEx5Euep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayNolan Hi Ray. Running an agency doing influencer marketing for travel/hospitality businesses. First of its type. Would love to chat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tracy_Keogh Thanks for the advice &amp; for listening Tracy, I'm excited!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely great to hear Ireland's Best Young Entrepreneur is back. Thankfully, I am old enough to enter this year, as opposed to last year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tracy_Keogh will let you know how my experience is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a reasonable, easy place to eat in Dublin, that is not mcdonalds, is torturous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryhand @Con_Keppel best article ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sl_heavey I did, kinda regretting going there now though!! Great to see you too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryhand They are insanely nice! Roommate works at Facebook so unfortunately not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distribution of content is almost more important than production - influencers can be a super way to distribute https://t.co/Bcw0XBo4JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@summeru4ia Hey Summer. I may have a brand deal that you could be interested in. Do you have an email?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Wonderful. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Hi, yes it is set up as an International Beneficiary. Need to get this sent out, can someone call me please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB It says 'Fully Authorised', along with the other beneficiaries (the ones that appear when trying to send a payment)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Please let me know or if you could get someone to call me at 0857700099 I would appreciate it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB The beneficiary I just created is not appearing on the list of beneficiaries for an international payment. Thats my problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Got that fixed. Now the beneficiary is not appearing when I try to send a payment, even though it has been successfully created. IBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Got it fixed. Created the beneficiary. Now the account I just set up is not appearing when I try to send the payment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Hi, trying to create a beneficiary to send urgent payment. It says: Technical Error. Please contact support. ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehappypear How many hours of sleep do you guys usually get?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kog_x thx for the love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty nice when you complete a week-long marketing campaigns objectives in less than 30 minutes.. Bang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB Was just curious as I haven't seen it from corporate accounts before - thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskAIB How come you guys have to put #ad at the end of your posts now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGapYearGuru Just came across your channel Jess, love the content :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not uncommon for people to spend their whole life waiting to start living." —@EckhartTolle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOCDStories Hey guys; you have a really cool cushion that says 'not all those who wander are lost'. Where can I find it? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrReidWilson Have been finding your writing tremendously helpful - thank you, really appreciate your understanding of this space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite quote when it comes to working with YTers + what influencers should focus on with their audience is 'Relationship over reach'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westlife are actually pretty great]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>