<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I just completed the Soak meditation on buddhify - https://t.co/RW0jwST98Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Culture Jam a Populist in Four Easy Steps 
"Press pause on the siren song of polarization."
https://t.co/QLVk8ogrkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news is ... the bad news https://t.co/H6Pe5CvK7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very thoughtful piece albeit rumours of its death may be exaggerated; I suspect there's still fight left in the p… https://t.co/0JUIazoZFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Internet and the Tragedy of the Commons via @GPFutures @JCE_PC be interested in your thoughts https://t.co/q2MJkMBzgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, interest rates and Chinese panic: Why euphoria could turn to a credit crunch in 2017 https://t.co/igCwQjcw8o via @telebusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OffTheTracksNZ not to be confused with this https://t.co/takAC3LJtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had every celebrity moved to NZ yesterday, they'd be safe now. Happy New Year! #2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaz_murphy This was the cartoon! https://t.co/v2CQNTkulr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newsthump And before the ink was even dry on this piece, Debbie Reynolds passes ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artist who made Sgt Pepper montage of 2016's dead celebrities hospitalised with exhaustion - https://t.co/XTOM1PJcZa via @newsthump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper making a call by tapping a public phone when I didn't have 3 x 2cent coins https://t.co/SrltYMM1Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonNRicketts @RobJStewartNZ @YouTube And now we need someone to pay tribute to George paying tribute to Freddie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @pmbillenglish just two? Is 50% an aspirational upper limit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insanity. The scope for creative compromising has been legislated away, leaving little prospect of resolution. https://t.co/S5mKBhwF5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf How wonderful for you David. Welcome to the chaotic bliss of parenthood 💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler @simonpnz PS Nearly 20 years ago they used their studies of generational patterns etc to predict Trump or a version of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler @simonpnz The Millennial Generation was coined by Howe &amp; Strauss in their incredibly prescient 1997 book The Fourth Turning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPlunket And at Jville Countdown too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thoughtful perspective on the US Election and its implications https://t.co/v20CadjXqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @charles_finny I thought it was our Big One. Hate to think how bad Cheviot must be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not liking these after shocks much either #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @charles_finny It felt much bigger than the Sept 2013 shakes. I'd be v surprised if not similar damage in Wellie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG if that was centred near ChCH it must be huge. I'm in Wellington and thought it was our Big One - it never stopped. #nzeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were many of the current protesters outraged with the prospect that Trump might not respect the result? Or is that what gave them the idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On cultural shadow, Trickster Trump &amp; hope for positive, transformational, change (in the long term at least) https://t.co/8Oxyt8K7eK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that thing where the US curbs civil rights but it's ok becos of 911 &amp; terrorists &amp; it's not like any Pres would ever abuse power...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Crap. https://t.co/y0QJxhocuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excellent read "Civility ... is simply the ability to disagree productively with others while respecting their s… https://t.co/r2L3UIIAsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BondSolon @Searchline03 @EWI_Global @NEWAExperts Yes I will be there. Coming over from NZ. Very excited too! #ExpertWitness conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey  @DomPost you've got a profile piece about the new Kapiti Mayor. Only thing missing is his name... https://t.co/Ec4Fxw4G20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyJones_ and you got to work with her too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina what, and no purple??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smalltorquer @EricCrampton I'm not sure. Eric, are law  changes proposed in light of recent Tenancy Tribunal rulings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smalltorquer @EricCrampton with increasing % of middle class renting for longer, logical to expect a "rights" shift from LLs to tenants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton If there is in fact a correlation. Many foreign investors may simply prefer empty properties. Easier to flick in a hurry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @CNNPolitics @Eugene_Scott Ironically it wld be LESS competitive now had the DNC allowed more competition in their primary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS how do they cope with the later books? They're pretty dark. I'm not sure how my 6yo wld go. Movies definitely not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary vs Donald, digested: the second US presidential debate in five minutes https://t.co/yvj4YoVxH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raybon Kan: The burqa - a mistake we made to get here https://t.co/uAcXvL9htK via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sue_Cleaver @connor9mcintyre That's terrible!
It's only thru childbirth that we women come close to experiencing this ghastly affliction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @robhosking ... Try explaining that to the 6 year old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @robhosking My husband is older than most Dads. His father imported kitset TV &amp; they watched only static until TV arrived in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @robhosking I remember when rich people had a second TV that size in, like, their bedroom. Rich RICH people had a colour one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackgorman Wait a minute, box? There was a box?  Well that does explain a few things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why a President Trump will probably be ok in one simple sentence https://t.co/XOz1a9zPcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely it's not too late for #warren2016 https://t.co/Gl7jnsLwU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How could these two ancient institutions, the Democratic and Republican parties, cough up such human hairballs?" https://t.co/Od0rxO689Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConversationStr @RealGeorgiaT You guys are so powerful. Next week you should discuss the possibility of @martinhancock11 returning #spider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flaming_nora TOYAH!
 Who is just one degree of separation from ... SPIDER!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BGCraven @dpfdpf Maybe someone's trying to provoke a denial. Like those misreporting Michael Schumacher's health succeeded in doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz it's time to bring back depositions or something like it. Current practices not transparent and undermining faith in the system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cest_chienfou We studied the White Paper during my Constitutional Law class that year. Wait, didn't it pass??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AKA the Orwell Was Right Bill. Total overreach. Why not have us all micro-chipped and be done with it? @JCE_PC https://t.co/8sBV7HnYE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't too late for #warren2016 https://t.co/dyQSx8gZ9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutomaticEarth Here is Part 2 - the insidious disempowerment of cash https://t.co/6E6WgZ9k0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFMauldin Are you familiar with Nicole Foss' work? You appear to be on a similar page.  https://t.co/kKW5XZyQrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicole Foss is back at @AutomaticEarth. And well worth the wait. Pt 1 of 4 @bernardchickey https://t.co/qZ1rbaT1ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dame Lowell Goddard's letter to the UK Parliament is worth reading. https://t.co/BFpGkVoORZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ For preparing reply submissions??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan would be fab to have a single Sub Hub that accessed all of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan If the US Election is anything to go by, that is no longer a liability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan Yes, it could curb your free spirit. On the other hand, it would channel all your skills. I think you'd be awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Melanie_Skelany @RaybonKan @nzherald Raybon, please go into politics!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raybon Kan: A man with enough names for a relay team https://t.co/Eg9fGUtlcw via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Marginal Buyer Holds The Pin That Pops Every Asset Bubble https://t.co/BnmVuLfMni via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V thoughtful piece from Colin James on migration. 
More Kiwis left NZ than returned last year, albeit fewer than b4  https://t.co/s9oVImZCD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IR_Tyler @RMoneynz I used to work for Justice Goddard. 
She's a good woman. Sounds like she was handed a hospital pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell @DomPost @NZStuff I was sure the #DavidJones opening was tomorrow. Just as well I wasn't actually invited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @TheDemocrats @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton Wouldn't solve problem of finding a new acronym for First Bloke tho #FBOTUS anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dean_knight The CJ probably secretly sees herself as Diana Ross anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @greg_a_cole Kevin May's potential impact on British fashion cannot be overestimated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ here y' go ;) https://t.co/tT8uwDupsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our suppression laws need to adapt to the times too.  https://t.co/k94GPUHoAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver's housing crisis and the fear of seeming racist. 
Sound a tad familiar?? @PhilTwyford @bernardchickey https://t.co/mNqZtd03Lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack yes! We both have milestone ones this year too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack and mine!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zerohedge would a bailout of Italian banks trigger the run on Deutsche Bank derivatives which IMF thinks could collapse global fin system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These scams are getting increasingly more sophisticated and difficult to spot  https://t.co/fKUnOSGxhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMF: "Deutsche Bank Poses The Greatest Risk To The Global Financial System" | Zero Hedge https://t.co/TUKVujDKX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Geoffrey Palmer QC, ex NZ PM &amp; Constitutional Law Professor, on #Brexit https://t.co/WnSdeC1Eph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Lawyer - A New Era of Witness Performance https://t.co/z6uli51o5Q via @legalempower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had it been murder not manslaughter, 17 years would likely have been the minimum non-parole period, not the total sentence #Moko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisBramwell Cf 17 yr non-parole period imposed for "sustained brutality against a vulnerable child" if there had been murder charges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW BLOG: Experts - preparing to be cross examined on the foundations of your evidence
https://t.co/rXXbfr9qbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experts - Preparing to be Cross Examined on the Foundations of Your Evidence https://t.co/UebGyp3W1o via @legalempower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As @JohnFMauldin recently noted, if you've read The Fourth Turning by Howe &amp; Strauss, #Brexit is not so surprising https://t.co/txMOn0l1R8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin And not surprising if you've read Howe &amp; Strauss' The Fourth Turning about cycles of history from generational perspective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was one long shudder, Wellietown #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's safe to say there mb a little buyer's remorse between now &amp; Oct so will David Cameron take Boris down with him? #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because we don't bother with commercial TV or radio, I'm oblivious to whatever it is Mike Hosking  has apparently done to offend #justsaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a decent shake #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Te Papa do know his medal isn't included, right?
Peter Snell's historic singlet sells for $122,500 https://t.co/gonwAGP5Sz via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @AmbroseEP is voting to leave, albeit reluctantly, then #Brexit has  now moved from possibility to probability. https://t.co/7QglMsxlgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostInPoker @bernardchickey @SenWarren It's still a long long time until November - especially in this race!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it too late for #warren2016  https://t.co/2Hhvgi9mPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bernardchickey @SenWarren Please remind me why, oh why, Senator Warren is not a presidential candidate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana In a couple of years she'll be right back at him with "but what if broccoli is my Disgust, Daddy"? #mixedmoviemessages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is no #Brexit, will the UK Supreme Court win in its defence of the Magna Carta, Bill of Rights 1688 etc? https://t.co/P1H7ROyGfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bernardchickey @PhillipsTane @HamishMcKay @MattNippert @ToddScottNBR I'd like to subscribe to one news portal that hosts all my fav media]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>