<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 8 Taken for college project on non-English typography, bag made from newspaper @WikiCommons https://t.co/kKlViWrKWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 7 A very pretty shed on a farmyard. Ireland looking its green and agricultural self @WikiCommons https://t.co/b5LMJxEMdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 6 Some idyllic Limerick countryside @WikiCommons https://t.co/MoRPB3SwRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 5 The last of the agricultural machinery! A manual pulper @WikiCommons https://t.co/FJonTjAtMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays 4 A manual horse-drawn hay buck rake @WikiCommons https://t.co/IHHS4diMf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 3 a manual harrow (@EileenONeill5 we think!) @WikiCommons https://t.co/F4TPBJwJvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#100commonsdays day 2, an Irish horse drawn plough, painted and displayed in a garden in County Limerick https://t.co/FS7Bb2DK5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decided to give #100commonsdays a go! A challenge to add photograph to @WikiCommons every day for 100 days, day 1 https://t.co/wmz1MSCjgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do the cats all prefer my side of the bed? #cats #catnap #catsofinstagram #bedtime @ Dublin,… https://t.co/DiRZiZhOMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always nice to get a free cookie! #morrisonhotel #dublin #cookies @ Morrison Hotel https://t.co/Gnd7dtaKIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Featuring a picture of the inimitable @tcdlibrary https://t.co/nVvXHPYI8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antinbath your garden looked fabulous! Especially your shaded/cool area, looked very atmospheric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Monty Don and Big Dreams Small Spaces, but it just makes me pine for my own garden #gardendreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye #hipster #cat #decoration until next year! https://t.co/LYlBMPxhOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year new diary #newleaf #batman #adamwest https://t.co/dzAJcwI4px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snoozy #grumpycat face @ County Dublin https://t.co/DTsg96VLwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mad new year's here in Castle Gregskull! #catsofinstagram #cats @ County Dublin https://t.co/pkatHjX0LU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domino hates the #hoover but she loves that it finds all of her #toys #cats #catsofinstagram @… https://t.co/Rtq3QcR5NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great jamming #christmas #homemade #jam @ Costa Del Finglas https://t.co/T2BylRGHQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EileenONeill5 my daffodils and other spring bulbs are already coming up! It's a good thing the balcony never gets frost 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EileenONeill5 unfortunately it got a bit dark! Mostly clearing away leaves and pulling out faded annuals https://t.co/IH14LxdDcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to attack the very neglected #balcony #garden just having a fortifying #cupoftea first! @… https://t.co/AtamM5lJbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asking a ghost do ghosts exist, nicely done Ardal! #irelandwithardal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My word, the man in Ireland who looks after the Padre Pio's relics is called Pio after him. That's something else #irelandwithardal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 15 minutes in and there has already been a willy joke, amazing #irelandwithardal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A night to be tucked up tight, according to Star cat #catsofinstagram #catnap #snooze https://t.co/0iosJAJwyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last but not least #christmastree #zingy #drwho #christmas #pratchett @ Costa Del Finglas https://t.co/Jyz9iX3pOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More #christmas with #christmastree number 2 #paperchase #lego #ghostbusters #tinytree @ Costa… https://t.co/zz7eAABzoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's being to look a lot like #christmas #christmastree #tree #eyore #winniethepooh @ Costa Del… https://t.co/3qGac8I71z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcdlibrary bit of inspiration? https://t.co/e7m2DiileT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoylanPat fantastic, thank you very much! If you follow me, I can send you a message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There now, very interesting! #HSTM https://t.co/HzTV0TBhVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out you can fit most of the US in that basket of deplorables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto hadn't even dawned on me. Terrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto on the other hand, he is friendly with Putin, so who knows what nation they'll nuke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really don't want to have to see a nuclear winter, thanks America...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoylanPat I've been doing initial research on the Eblana Theatre (Busaras), and your name was mentioned as someone to talk to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very different from the previous winners, Custom House never looked so good! #WLM https://t.co/W3c4HjWxY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this might be my personal favourite! https://t.co/7tTJlQQSWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhdelaney @americasstudies I'm only interested in lazy blogging ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been planning to do this too, although I struggle to think of what to write about though, or maybe over think it? https://t.co/ri8lgUoh26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sorry to hear this, I was just using some of her work to improve this @Wikipedia article… https://t.co/3Q5JuH26C7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneBlair will do, would be fascinating to chat about it properly some time. Looking to do some oral histories in the future too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneBlair &lt;3 when I saw "memory keeper" in your bio I knew I had to follow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneBlair Hey! It's "The rise of the citizen curator" I'm interested in how people are curating things online all the time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well can't sleep, more #writing it is then #phd #research #insomnia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you there! *lifts mug* cheers! #research #conclusions #phd #curation https://t.co/ybjbKkB78l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My drum teacher taught me the same lesson when I was 15 :) https://t.co/rDUXAntBmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling hear hear! To all those fuzzy ones and foxes everywhere :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling This is when I run out of cats! I miss this little lady everyday, Cass was my spirit animal :) https://t.co/MxVMQVCwtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This needs to happen more, Ireland badly needs to be part of this kind of conversation! https://t.co/WrkChoTBU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling POOFY KITTY!! *squee* back to sleek kitties with Star https://t.co/G7cL5h0ShG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling Oh, it's like that?! I give you the magnificent Loki! https://t.co/GJYQlA0sTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling Ah, the needless shirt ripping, brilliant! I think my Domino could win that fight! Here she is merc… https://t.co/jTs7Oes44v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angryearthling Oh now, that's a challenge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am genuinely struggling to think of anything that is more futile than wrapping pine cones in yarn. https://t.co/E70mJIx7VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I slightly mad for wanting to pursue more oral histories? From museums, galleries, theatres, to gardens they fascinate me #phd #ponder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a fantastic resource! https://t.co/oqFFPvyXIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are things that make writing a #PhD easier-knowing that eventually it will be over, &amp; getting kind, encouraging words on your writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desperately need a punch line: "A citizen scientist, citizen journalist, and a citizen curator walk into a bar..." #phdchat #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm presenting at tonight's event! https://t.co/cGQQgxZTKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark of a cool sister? One that indulges your nerdy interests! @aisoneill1 @EileenONeill5 #StarTrek50 https://t.co/Fg3UL4bqkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wittylama I'm with you on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthFCarden @NMIreland I love the little stickers used on objects, tiny circles of beauty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't dust bunnies more akin to dust caterpillars, in shape? I've never seen a bunny shaped dust bunny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarlathJudge the colours are lovely, all those jewel tones. I think you could keep going back to get it in different lights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarlathJudge Love this window, by a wonderful stained glass artist Catherine O'Brien https://t.co/ZsRLSxebaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to be heading a @Wikipedia lunchtime workshop at this! @WikimediaIE https://t.co/8nEW9A5Ick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto will we? I think we should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto @startrekeire @USSCuchulain @Octocon @wexworlds are you tempted? I'm tempted...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to keep tweeting and RTing this until it gets to 10000 euro! #donate #crowdfunding #cats #Dublin ttp://tinyurl.com/htnlr4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizmaybury thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccawatson @beccijeffers @exchangedublin @mhdelaney @lizmaybury @nuckpang throw this a RT? https://t.co/8pIQacQfDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on people! #donate and give this a RT! https://t.co/8pIQacQfDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some amazing rewards here - and all in aid of the cats of Dublin!! https://t.co/eEEMA8jfEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the torrential rain here in Dublin acting as a sort of pathetic fallacy? #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to help lots of cats and kittens? Come show off at @phibscatrescue pub quiz Thurs 23 8pm, prizes and raffle! https://t.co/c8KBq8NX2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminAhr @CutForTime there are fantastic movies with Meaney, but they might be too Irish. The Snapper, War of the Buttons, Intermission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminAhr @CutForTime very important that Colm is pronounced Col-um, pedantic Irish person, sorry #GreatestGen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a Toq card is awesome! Birthright are a great couple of Worf episodes #GreatestGen @CutForTime @BenjaminAhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done sir. https://t.co/tN3HjlRDiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How wonderful! https://t.co/3M1uYSmM40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krelnik good to know! Just a random poster I spotted in my local. Some of the language was definitely a red flag...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has my skeptic senses tingling... https://t.co/t43RvreaYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CutForTime @BenjaminAhr or live streamed broadcast as you guys watch it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CutForTime @BenjaminAhr I love it as it was the first ST film I saw in the cinema. Special episode or a bonus series as premium download?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying out the Black Sheep for tonight's @DublinPubhD nice and cool anyway! https://t.co/BvOnHtq9sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminAhr @CutForTime It does have the most epic of villains though, and features ad-libbed final words from @WilliamShatner himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So finally remembered my password, too lazy to change it again, what have I missed in the Twitterverse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminAhr @CutForTime but as an idea for special episodes, maybe watch some of the films? TNG ones of course...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminAhr @CutForTime Still shocked at your derogatory comments about Generations in EP:37 best movie EVER!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaunoboyle @TheMuseumOfLiz that's me alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sannahirvonen it was lovely to meet you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish museums need the power of pizza! Museum staff need to share experiences with the public #MuseumNext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thoughts on the consistency of experience and feeling in relation to @IMMAIreland #MuseumNext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Particularly love the idea of fostering a "culture of invitation" #MuseumNext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonybutler1 @IrishMuseums writing up at the moment, but drawing on citizen journalism and science, trying to formalise citizen curation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling out privilege, I think @fionakearney is my new hero @IrishMuseums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonybutler1 @IrishMuseums really enjoyed you talk, studying citizen curation in my PhD so it was a joy to hear about Derby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IKEAIE how many different accounts are going to tweet me! Dublin.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>