<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday feeling kicked in already ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets bought, bring on the hibees ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously unfit ðŸƒðŸ»ðŸ’¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewescfc happy 21st mate, hope it's a good one ðŸ’š https://t.co/Ic9QbNV9Ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liam smith couldn't cross a road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12th feb part 2 https://t.co/BHfkcdc5vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some bastard chored my charger on Wednesday come in this morning and someone took my extension lead. Scummy bastards ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbieEwing04 happy birthday bro, hope it's a good one ðŸ’™ https://t.co/IiQv1G0h45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ibiza all booked up with the boys, something to look forward too ðŸŒ…ðŸ»ðŸ‘½ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno how I manage going out the whole weekend all the time with only working 3 nights a week at river island. Take me back to that life ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not going to win games with a midfield that has no pace about it. Kitchen or Nowak can't play both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearts are pish. Such a boring, negative team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 year left till I can retire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canny help but smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary how much me and immy are in sync these days #Imfeelingit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewescfc that celebrated his birthday everyday of the week in boomerang ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewescfc stay with me for the rest of my life ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would do anything to go back and relive the first year in Maga. Honestly never stopped laughing the whole holiday ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiefchasi @ClutchLikeRomo that's disgusting mate. Have a word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to stop leaving college work to last minute ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMcCannn7 happy birthday mate, need a night out soon ðŸ» https://t.co/B6e2SEL5ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craig__berry 4 more days till Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should be over all the butterflies but I'm into stu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Sunday sesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loud eaters infuriate me, not hard to eat with your mouth closed ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 hours to go ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to get this holiday booked, going to be some laugh ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairmcgowxn honestly mate last time I seen him was entry, need to put in a transfer bid to get him back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immys got a wee meter in cav and cunts pay into it to talk to him for 20mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some sell out that empty seats everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressed to the max ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desperate to get away somewhere sunny for a few days ðŸŒ´â˜€ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MCowatt such a great tweet ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyhmfc1874 happy new year bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImranAli_7 have a word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanCampbell09 the robster is disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanCampbell09 what are you all about. Get to Luckies now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cantley will be president of Columbia ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGaffer1902 congratulations mate! ðŸ‘¶ðŸ» need to have a catch up soon ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taganbrown_ think so mate you going to Luckies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taganbrown_ happy birthday mate, hope it's a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myracingtips what happens with wincanton mate race void?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanfox98 thistlecrack mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanfox98 nah mate Antarctica de thaix was strolling it favourite had already fell. Seen might bite though sore one ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your horses is clear by 20 lengths and falls clean on its face ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last thing I'm wanting on Christmas Day hanging out my arse is my 50 odd year old uncle screaming Henderson to deliver in my ear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First present I opened silk sesh with immy and tubby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freddyheron goal machine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeMcGregor3 happy birthday my man, see you later on! ðŸ»âš¡ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImranAli_7 skint mate saving it for tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyle_bc saucy Cantley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same old hearts away from home ðŸ˜’ judge Cathro after winter break though once he's had time to get his ideas across]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick of going to that casino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bennthomson9 one and only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bennthomson9 Gordon be feeding the horses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bennthomson9 think of the closing party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 21st to my best mate @bennthomson9 hope it's a good one bro ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ» https://t.co/s2wjvDd5c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Gucci Ali @ImranAli_7 I've got best eyesight in Edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamRitchie08 still Â£100 up today mate could be worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamRitchie08 aye mate had 4 up could have cashed for Â£350 let it run for Â£900. Never backing Rob havlin again mate shittest ride ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorHendry happy birthday mate hope it's a good one ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One horse again for Â£900 ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulCameroni @NandosUK am no a grass ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ cunt took your garlic bread mate stick him in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than going out with your mates over the Christmas period. Few big nights to look forward to ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘¬ðŸ‘¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phoodle in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut @myracingtips what you think of this https://t.co/6rvQV1M42d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free the robster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Fridays ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/nng9wh4o3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice way to start the weekend ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/gFDaOB74Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyhmfc74 aye mate she held it up too much needed to be closer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyhmfc74 would have been more but one of them dead heat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyhmfc74 nah mate cash outs at 400, up already so letting it run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparkyhmfc74 @myracingtips this comes in 2500 in 3 days mate fingers crossed ðŸŽðŸ™ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myracingtips waiting on plus night for Â£1300, how confident are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads pickled ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another winner ðŸŽðŸ’° https://t.co/qAI7XCNXc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@partydoco @myracingtips first past the post]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c2Ollie @myracingtips 4 fold mate, all drifted before the off as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myracingtips smashed it https://t.co/0q9dyP07fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myracingtips waiting on boagrius for over a grand mate, what you think of his chances?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf is Apple Pay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon the JT's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanDowns_ shrunk in the wash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fuck you rangers the hearts have one the league ðŸ†ðŸ‘ðŸ»"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish Neilson and Crawford all the best. Grateful for the championship season and everything they achieved  ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who da fuck is dat guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@braaandonnn happy birthday bro hope it's a good one â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CD_15 me either every name I've seen mentioned is worse than neilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CD_15 only away form needs to improve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CD_15 @Ladbrokes Ben Cassidy could have managed the team to first in the championship mate. Saying that don't want neilson to go though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a man Patrice Evra is ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fraserwalker96_ happy birthday mate, hope it's been a good one ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucked my phone, nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moffat in the booth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DelworthHannah happy birthday Hannah, hope it's a good one ðŸŽ‰ X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freddyheron shite odds mate had to pick loads of teams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taganbrown_ thought it was fucked when Ronaldo missed pen and Latvia equalised ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Mr Betfair ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/cjdvyJvssa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England v Scotland not seen one two footer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope luckies is packed for the Scotland game ðŸ»âš½ï¸]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>