<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Job opening @hoxtonminipress.  Office &amp; project manager  https://t.co/KmQyeXYpCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farage unveils new £1 coin #2ndReferendum https://t.co/w1xEEqW66m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to our launch of 3 new books @HoxtonMiniPress tomorrow at pie and mash shop, Broadway Mkt 6:30-9pm. Free drinks https://t.co/8PYd8bTuCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New colourful photobooks from @HoxtonMiniPress on @kickstarter. Support the project here https://t.co/I9L8twzyzG https://t.co/fT1ThyNZXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andygreenacre_ @TelegraphMag thanks for the commission. RIP paul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My book on spanish hunting dogs nominated as one of best of 2015 by @humblearts. Thank you. https://t.co/Hu2lYWPO0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FastBailey @NewStatesman Thanks for pointing this out! Never saw it. Good dog Bailey!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yipee! My book on hunting dogs is a book of 2015 by @EveningStandard and picture book of week by @NewStatesman https://t.co/Fa6FV7GETp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see #paris so busy today . Vive la France https://t.co/ZiWrvzP52D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're not far from the events in Paris but thankfully safe. Thoughts are with the victims...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaFidalCam  hi Ana! Hope you are well!!! Thanks for the kind words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieKako81 thanks for your kind words! Glad you support animal rights too. See you at Usborne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouAmini thank you! @HoxtonMiniPress would love to know where you picked up your copy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to @HoxtonMiniPress book launch today, free G&amp;T, 7 Ezra St. Right behind Columbia rd,2-4pm http://t.co/3FTrLR3VgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installed a @nest thermostat in our home in winter and latest gas bill is now double last year. There's saving the planet..useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[East London indie publisher @HoxtonMiniPress is looking for an office manager http://t.co/G0MBDNny8h http://t.co/QlL7tkhGim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me on national geographic, innit -  complete with misspelled name

http://t.co/XmtrxQD3cJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Max_de_Winter thanks for sending your artwork Max! Hi to your pod!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@espanswick you are very welcome. Great to hear they arrived and are being enjoyed! Thanks for ordering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah! @kimptoncreative is there something in today's paper?@standardnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boycott Kerala tourism now that the government is brutally killing street dogs. Sign this petition: http://t.co/PBIYNypPvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signing copies of my new book in Paris tonight 530 - 730pm @Photo12Galerie come along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sqezekid we did yes! Book is being collected by our mailing house today. Thanks again for your support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction!! Launch starts 6:30pm (not 6). #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please come to my book launch tonight @TPGallery (just behind oxford circus - in the bookshop, not the gallery) for drinks and dog talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudioLegohead thank you jo!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cotton thank you Edward and glad you backed. Yes, netflix documentary - would be wonderful...all best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebRichterPhoto @theprintspace stick that lovely print in plastic and send it to those unpredictable sods. Good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 hrs left to support new book from Hoxton Mini Press: MAKERS OF EAST LONDON  @kickstarter http://t.co/HFkyU5I6VK http://t.co/Bb0PN2Op0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@espanswick oops sorry! Have followed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to my book launch @TPGallery of 'Where Hunting Dogs Rest' this Thur 6-8pm, just by Oxford Circus. Signed books http://t.co/wJqvFWbVhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwant2shootyou Come to the book launch to see the book, or look on my website http://t.co/k9mwKxYiO8 - show is on in paris at mo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Launch - where hunting dogs rest, this thursday, 23rd July- http://t.co/ybv8uQOBi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@espanswick hi Ellie. Unfortunately no! Working on it though. In meantime I can send you a paypal invoice if you DM me your email &amp; order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lesleyj28 yes indeed. Although I haven't seen it myself - am out of country! Hope it looks ok!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VortigernJamie the book is distributed by turnaround publisher services who will be able to offer wholesale rates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charliedennis oh no. Sorry to hear that. How beaten up is it? Do you need a replacement copy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@copperpower what wonderful pictures and beautiful dog! the pod is doing wonderfully well and rehabilitated- thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charitybevis thanks again for your continued support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tug that's great to hear! Glad it arrived safely. Thanks again for your support on @kickstarter !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kickstarter is there anyone there that I can ask a quick question about backer reports?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Kickstarter campaign for a book about craft ‘Makers of East London’ from @hoxtonminipress. Click to pledge http://t.co/HFkyU5I6VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please please retweet your outrage at the dog eating festival in china right now #StopYuLin2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in Paris come to my opening tonight, Galerie Photo 12, 6:30-8:30, looks fab http://t.co/sRLj5CMfn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to @HoxtonMiniPress 's fanciest launch yet tonight 630-830 Town Hall Hotel, Haircuts of Hackney, free drinks! http://t.co/6D9uPcv7Ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this poor fella injured in park...Waiting for rescue now http://t.co/YHUyQcSIxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hunting dog images in the most beautiful dog mag ever @Fourandsons Touched to be included http://t.co/62IZXrR1j7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francesemma @kickstarter thank you frances!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adoprecoce thank you for sharing. Less than 1 hour to go!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zebulon_ thank you so much for helping to spread the word! 15 hours to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamCMarsh @kickstarter many thanks for helping to spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Negation2010 many thanks for sharing alan! can't wait to get the book out to everyone next month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenisODonovan many thanks for sharing Denis. Only a few hours left to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aswanews to pre-order a signed copy on @kickstarter choose £32 reward here: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL for july delivery (only 16 hrs left!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slideluck @kickstarter thanks so much for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnePickering1 @kickstarter thank you so much for sharing. only 18 hours to go!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailydogtag many thanks for your support beth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aswanews @BarkPost thanks for sharing. please check out the @kickstarter signed copies for the next 18 hours only! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaRealitijd @kickstarter many thanks for helping to spread the word eva!! only a few hours left to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eliz_Orcutt thanks for sharing elizabeth. please check out the kickstarter as well. only 20 hours left!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TPGallery please take a look at my new project on spanish hunting dogs. only 22 hours left on @kickstarter!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markzware please check out the @kickstarter too. only 21 hours left to pick up a signed copy of the book! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JUXDITMel thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabaErcole thanks for sharing saba! please check out the @kickstarter too. only 21 hours to go! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madog_lu @kickstarter thank you! can't wait to get the book out to you in july!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@looklooklukala @kickstarter thank you anna!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrssizzledogs thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBoxxLtd @kickstarter many thanks for your support!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 hours to go. THANK YOU so much to everyone who has pledged and helped to spread the word!! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New photography book: Spanish hunting dogs - http://t.co/gjoveWQgmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BareReality thanks Laura! Hope to see you soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@theprintspace @HoxtonMiniPress many thanks for having us last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhotosbySooz @HoxtonMiniPress @theprintspace thanks for coming along last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigrstevenson @theprintspace @kickstarter @LDNtwentyfour7 thanks Craig. Great to meet you last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@looklooklukala thank you so much Anna!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkShenley @theprintspace @kickstarter thanks for coming along mark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreatorexDavid @theprintspace @kickstarter Great to meet you david. Thanks for having us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thanks @featureshoot for this article on my latest series: http://t.co/UT4v8inzbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogTreatNews please check out my photo series which aims to highlight the plight of the spanish hunting dog: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maydaypitbull thank you so much for your support and help in spreading the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftABit_ @kickstarter thanks!! we are over the moon with all the support! can't wait to get the books out to people this summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last chance for a signed copy of my new book on kickstarter. Support the spanish hunt dogs http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL http://t.co/LACxTzcmpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give your voice to those that don't have one, stop the chinese dog eating festival this month #StopYulin2015 http://t.co/FkieiO2hj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aruetzel thank you so much for helping to spread the word!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweetdogsb please check out the book on Kickstarter too - only a few days left!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustPetNews please check out the book on Kickstarter too - only a few days left!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hurleygirly629 many thanks for sharing. pls take a look at the kickstarter campaign too! http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sqezekid thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sqezekid many thanks for sharing! please take a look at the project on kickstarter too.. only 2 days left!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoggerJogger please check out the book on Kickstarter too - only a few days left!  http://t.co/4rMC1Rmztj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Hydrant please check out the book on Kickstarter too - only a few days left!  http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matt_James_I @The_Hydrant thanks so much for this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slhosking @kickstarter thank you Stacey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerryGilling many thanks for your continued support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JamFactory many thanks for your pledge and support!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calgarydoglife thank you so much for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aboutaccess @kickstarter thank you so much for your pledge and support!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahanndogs thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeelyFanForever @kickstarter thank you so much for your support!! Can't wait to get the book out to you next month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BarkPost only 2 days left to support my @kickstarter campaign. please RT: http://t.co/4rMC1R4YBL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>