<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[my mum: u hang up first
me: no u hang up first
my mum: fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[from my window overlooking the city, i can see apocalyptic sheets of horizontal rain flowing over wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today i saw a flat so unfurnished that it didn't even come with a stove top #why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemurraywriter hahha that would be perfect!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless S A M E. the flat hunt is killing me rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[legit everyone in my everton summer flat is chinese, which makes me think they just saw my last name and were like, yup let's put her here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[masterchef australia, but every time george calombaris says yum, it gets faster @bowenshi_nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-closes laptop- well, i sufficiently feel like i'm dying i think i've looked at enough flats today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mum: wow it's raining, why did no one bring an umbrella / me: well i live in wellington so i haven't seen an umbrella in 3 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whenever i see a wishbone outside of wellington: hello my lost brethren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not sure whether putting a blonde streak through my black hair has made it look better or just outed my true form, a 2000s emo kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonalSkehan thank you so much (and for the fab recipe as well)! 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire @bowenshi_nz  wish i could do delivery! i'm in auckland right now 🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me and @bowenshi_nz made @DonalSkehan's black forest pavlova. YUM 😋 https://t.co/tAobiCtg9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me @ every view since i came back from greece: where's the parthenon tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dad woke me up this morning for the market + in my dazed state i thought, what the HELL i dont need to be woken up, ive FINISHED high school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-rolls up sleeves- if there's one thing my mother taught me, it was to buy things from the back of the shelf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me in greece: i have bought too many clothes i must stop
me in italy: -buys clothes- oh no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jewellery store owner: this is yours -gives ring- and now this is mine -takes my credit card- ha just joking / me: ha ha ha -eye twitches-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if the olive museum is CLOSED on our only FREE DAY in sparta then what's even the POINT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fave card of the night @ClaudiaJardine https://t.co/QRT5QZ3aza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[an update on preparation for my next site presentation: i am watching other peoples' travel videos of ancient corinth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2poor2furious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-opens bag- -greek breadsticks fall out-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[day 14 in greece: it finally rains for the first time since i got here. well, i felt only like max 5 raindrops on my face but still, rain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i bought something different at the bakery for lunch today but it turned out to be just another variation of a cheese pie #thwartedagain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there's even annoying car window washers at intersections in crete!? wow, some things truly do cross cultural boundaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless -nods wisely- of course, of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-swirls cretan tap water in cup- yes. a smooth texture, though not quite the fresh undertone of new zealand water. still a solid 3/5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[forever lowkey sad that my mum made me play piano as a kid instead of guitar. maybe i will never become a rockstar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i briefly forgot what country i was in while shopping a H&amp;M and spoke fluent english at a poor greek guy. i am so sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[banana got squashed in my bag. bag now full of banana guts. traumatised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i was doing well with my conversation in greek with the cashier until we progressed past hello]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when i walk down the road + greek men try get me to eat at their restaurants, i feel like im playing assassin's creed + trying to avoid NPCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wondering which shop i should next drop a €100 note at #tourist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdveloso woke up before i could eat it D;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i also had a dream that i 3D printed a 2m high french fry. it was a wild night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had a dream last night that someone betrayed me (don't know why or how) and woke up really angry till i realised it was a dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaJardine: yeah we can inspire each other
me: everything is suffering
@ClaudiaJardine: not what i was going for but ok #bantz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[walked round the acropolis today and only cried a little bit. still can't quite believe it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun Fact - some flippin turkish commander stored explosive gunpowder in the propylaia (spoiler: it blew up) and thats why it's so ruined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemurraywriter aww you are the sweetest, thank you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the british school at athens, feeling very inadequate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got emotional seeing the acropolis in the distance today, might just do my site presentation on the propylaia whilst crying profusely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I JUST GOT OFF THE BUS AND WALKED INTO AN ANKLE DEEP PUDDLE, THEN JUMPED OUT OF THAT PUDDLE BUT LANDED INTO ANOTHER PUDDLE AAAAARGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[moving van guy: oh where are you going? / me: GREECE / moving van guy: OH MAN FCKIN SICK!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless HAHAH yeah, hey look when did auckland get a parthenon??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless yeah!! then land in greece and be like ??? how did i get here ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaJardine @alexa_ruthless i look forward to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me flying home to auckland: -creates extensive itemised list-
me flying to greece: -throws things in suitcase-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless i give that rock an 11/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me in greece: -points at ruin- that is a very good rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not a cat or a dog person, i'm actually a hayfever person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i had a dream that all the knives at work turned into meat cleavers. i was cutting lettuce with a cleaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloodGoblet all i'm good for hahha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i was falling asleep at a pub quiz cause i know nothing, then a classics question came up and everyone started shouting at me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: wow i am so keen to roast some vegetables
oven: -breaks-
me: wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone: -talking about something-
me: yeah that's cool oh hey did you know it's six days till i go to greece?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i accidentally cut myself at work but didn't notice it at first, so i just brushed it off as beetroot juice. it was NOT beetroot juice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaJardine something like this for greece but more interesting and longer and more greece?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my october 2016 [in seconds] https://t.co/QlEzUsJY4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have a bag of expired bread crumbs. should i throw them across the street and become the Pigeon Queen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[warning: if you talk to me in the next week, i will probably grab your shoulders, hiss GREEECE, then whisper the number of days till 13 nov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when will my concentration come back from the war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MakaroPress where has Polina Kouzminova been my whole life!? i'm loving 'an echo where you lie' so so much &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just took out my collection of plastic bags from my wardrobe and now i feel like i'm in a sea of suffering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the last 10 minutes of me packing has just been staring at empty boxes and feeling overwhelmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[time to apply for study link, ie. realise that i've forgotten my realme password and spend time answering questions about my childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my flatmate moved the microwave onto the shelf so now it feels like i'm making a sacrifice to the gods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classical Studies, aka Cool History]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i went opshopping and got a $10 Cashmere Sweater so i can go to the golf clubs and drink champagne every evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[glad to see countdown metro getting their priorities straight and stocking coriander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[strange. i seem to have finished my degree, somehow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[creative writing folio all printed, just one exam left to smash out tomorrow 🙃 https://t.co/OC7lkfDiZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collagen: A Love Story #CREW352]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my hair only looks really good rn because i haven't been outside in two days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when i leave my the 1975 playlist off shuffle and it descends from party tunes to ambient sound + im sitting there in the dark like who am i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you vs the guy she told you not to worry about https://t.co/DerCHJPBEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ME: time 2 study
email: 40% OFF ALL STOCK
ME: time 2 shop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless at first when i saw your tweet i was like, YESS, then my realistic self kicked in and was like, uh, get back to study]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless oh i wish i could!! these final hand ins are killing me rn 😵]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf wellington, get a grip on yourself #just6amworkthings https://t.co/EyfPaNMO8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how to cook with emma:
- dice onion
- cry
- keep crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY 220 is a very cold exam room]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the battery is running low on both my laptop and my phone and so am i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my friend: do you have internet in greece? / me: yah so i can keep you updated on my travels / my friend: o i just wanted to send you memes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless omg :o we've come so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tbt to my first year exam study plan. look at all that blessed TIME. i'm jealous https://t.co/DqqxfXXSbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dried banana chips almost taste like potato chips if i close my eyes and forget that i'm suffering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if i put my cress and coriander plant in the same pot, will they fight to the death? (that's how gardening works, right)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what a beautiful day to go to uni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannybultitude awww, no worries! poetry can be whatever you want it to be :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannybultitude this is fantastic. also u could try out prose poetry - closer to the structure of prose without the expectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nothing like watching hercules for the millionth time to get the feels going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes i trust the intuition of customers and sometimes they ask for ketchup on their whitebait and i wanna cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me with smudged eyeliner + a $1 frozen coke using the james cook hotel lift, walking thru the foyer as a guy in tux plays piano: yo waddup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[almost missed the train to work. i think that's enough running for the rest of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaJardine that is amazing. my life has been enlightened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaJardine i am way too proud of this tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[possible CREW352 science writing folio titles: "GABA receptors and other stories" "wtf is a prostaglandins" "opioids #ayy" "it's a metaphor"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>