<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalakaiFekitoa @RixterSm2 @LimaSopoaga @MaoriGC @Highlanders where's @bensmithotago he still hiding - or doesn't he need to train anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otago great that sounds good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnPhoenixFC shame all kids will be at school at 10.30 a.m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otago any idea when Castle St works will be completed outside CFI Building?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LimaSopoaga @bensmithotago @MaoriGC @MalakaiFekitoa hopefully he's NOT gone AWAL to negotiating an overseas contract!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otago hopefully the park bench is on the way for this little oasis created beside St David Lecture Theatre. https://t.co/c4lCUhGgwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3V3RTON1AN not much of a charge if the last 3 Prem games are anything to go by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LUFC @officialcwood there are even Chris Wood &amp; therefore Leeds followers in @Lovedunedin too which is in the South of NZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tom_Stevens1 @southern_united @NZ_Football @FootballSouth2 how many did they score? Good job Liam wasn't in goal or they wouldn't get any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvertonBlueArmy yep but it is 7 o'clock in the evening in @Lovedunedin so would be a bit sad if one was asleep https://t.co/MluTpbOIHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united @NZ_Football @Dannny_Ledwith @FootballSouth2 that's seriously cool. Will look for that this winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZ_Football @southern_united @WaitakereUnited yes Hope it's 4 in a row. Be good to keep the run going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united @WaitakereUnited gutted can't be there as travelling back from Christchurch today. Go @southern_united]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@odtnews hard to believe. Brighton is much better for families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iangriffin @otago that's a great idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosshoward8 @southern_united @WaitakereUnited gutted in Christchurch this Saturday so will miss it. Will follow here instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on feeding off the force | ODT @southern_united great article today on @rosshoward8 local boy made good  https://t.co/Tyg4x2BvVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to be the 1,295th backer on @BackerKit for Monkey Light Automatic: our b... | Thx @Monkeylectric! https://t.co/RCGAtiMnDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottd_sports @southern_united be great to continue to see the backflip from Eric Molloy well helped by great crosses from @rosshoward8 too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SkippersRoad to #BranchesStation wow NZ is amazing place to live. https://t.co/z6VQ34IV8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow #SkippersRoad you are amazing. https://t.co/XrxEilplmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out cycling in #TheGreatOutdoors near @LoveQueenstown today. Hot day for a ride but enjoyable… https://t.co/L7qW0X5FNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1993Chief great result and well played @southern_united]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TOTCHE @skysportnz the game is supposed to be live not blank screen. #fixItOrMoneyBack https://t.co/KEiRmC4Axf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skysportnz where's the #TOTCHE game gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beINSPORTS where's the game gone #TOTCHE missing off nz channels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iangriffin nope it's definitely yours as you have all rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iangriffin planning to watch it go out tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The42_ie @danny_furlong great to have them here in @Lovedunedin looking forward to next game this Saturday. @southern_united]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HULEVE 9.00 am in @NewZealand great time to watch @Everton live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottd_sports @serenawilliams would be a great dream attendee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlyEverEverton #hero absolute #hero @NevilleSouthall is. @Everton this isn't even a question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listening to Christmas music today and this from Third Day is one of my favourites  https://t.co/dzvbtRcdMz via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy at least it wasn't between Christmas and New Year as that's a different perfect timing - usually reserved for bad news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosshoward8 @NZ_Football @southern_united @TasmanU great game and a good win. Best player on park #14 classy runs and good crosses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancewiggs agree was easy...good to see opportunities for people who don't meet the habitual investor definition too, to be a part of fund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavershamTrain looks like a great team to keep the train running nicely. Big thanks to @handshorner for his efforts too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united on the way hopefully grab a win in the Capital today. https://t.co/QpLcTY7n1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancewiggs @punakaikifund @snowballnz I'm in, great to be onboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFC need to add @newzealand to the map. I'll be watching with my son Caleb who is @ChelseaFC fan on Sunday at 6.30 a.m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laxi9 @LearningLovers reminds me of this quote...... https://t.co/20D37Tapkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united looking forward to the next few weeks and the opportunities with the home games. @YellowFever_NZ https://t.co/ttjo5IB4hd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities to add some top scientists to those already in @Lovedunedin come join @Laxi9 @methylnick and others h… https://t.co/haJikpfYeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PED7 a little bit harder to forget it when your son supports @ChelseaFC thankfully living in NZ don't have to put up with so many Kopites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeff_cheshire @FootballSouth2 will put even greater meaning to winning/holding the Blair Davidson trophy now which @CavershamTrain hold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united finally a good result after @Everton @AllBlacks it's been a tough old day especially when your son supports @ChelseaFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeff_cheshire great obituary in ODT for Blair Davidson. Didn't have pleasure of knowing him @FootballSouth2 will be worse for his loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united feels like 10 minutes not 3 when you're following it on twitter. #WUvSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanBannatyne @nplumpton it's probably cheaper at Tesco than in NZ where it comes from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancewiggs typical...kind of article one would expect. Good opportunity for individuals to invest in Punakaiki.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlyEverEverton A very topical one at present ROONEY #COYB #FindEleven #SquadSearch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nznanjan @otago @Lovedunedin I think that the technical term is "rocks".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKeyMustGo   it's a good place. Been back here for 12 months and it's been great being here in Dunedin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otago looking stunning today. @Lovedunedin #DunedinIsGreat https://t.co/w1NhB03nml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day for rugby in @Lovedunedin for the big final. Go @OtagoRugbyTeam great news it's inside @ForBarrStadium https://t.co/GlRHg8b1I3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson classic. He's all ready for the call up to the #BigDance @AllBlacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz not sure politicians facing up to reality is possible. But wish they would though for everyone's sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighlandersApp looking forward to it. Part one of my birthday weekend celebrations. #theBig50.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united @HarleyRodeka @NZ_Football @CU_Dragons @ForBarrStadium great will make a plan to be there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DionWright888 hmm makes you wonder about your MEntr. now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_united @HarleyRodeka @HamWanderersNZ @NZ_Football just a shame its not at home in @Lovedunedin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dunedinisgreat great afternoon for badminton in @Lovedunedin Spot the Rhododendron starting to bloom too. https://t.co/74t6EDl2w8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DArcyWaldegrave Escape to Victory definitely for me but that is because I love football and I saw it when I was young and it has Pele in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic place and happy memories visiting Milford Sound with @realjourneys always a great time. https://t.co/ebrRA7Wn6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OtagoRugbyTeam all the way especially under the roof at @ForBarrStadium should make for a great game! https://t.co/q3npxZVajV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding peace and solitude in Doubtful Sound | https://t.co/8azkfYm5Ba  great place to visit with @realjourneys  https://t.co/abvQPrLUIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Dave - he's just shown me a #BetterWayToFly to Vancouver. Where would you choose? https://t.co/CoVs4ek6T8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samfromwgtn @KiwiLandingPad @kiwiholty I am sure that you would be definitely welcome and provide valuable input too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADInstruments @AllBlacks that's pretty cool. Enjoy the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The summer cruise ship season begins. #Dunedinisgreat #DunnerStunner all in @Lovedunedin https://t.co/2iLQ9vpg1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AllWhites great result @NZ_Football icing on top my son Caleb sets a new PB juggling post game of 354! Beats my 25 https://t.co/A9dTdZDIoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcarey70 not if you come from down under and support @NZ_Football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methylnick @Laxi9 one for you two. https://t.co/Al8f6Td0MH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TweetAnEvertonPic my favourite @Everton player @Tim_Cahill a boy from down under like me! Unfortunately not a Kiwi… https://t.co/Pm37Eb84yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a #dunnerStunner St Clair Beach @Lovedunedin https://t.co/UYMwTcMvZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConAnderson @jasonjo13723516 @CreativeHQ best we get a move on lads #VibrationAction https://t.co/f0wOlgkTcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConAnderson @jasonjo13723516 #VibrationAction https://t.co/7atTzraorx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenljoyce @Izzy_Njohana @callaghannz @CreativeHQ @the_icehouse that's great just what we're looking for our startup #VibrationAction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConAnderson @jasonjo13723516 might be an option for us. Need to look into this. https://t.co/XZpYXdA2Np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 Otago infantry killed in one month | Otago Daily Times Online News. A must see in @Lovedunedin @odtnews  https://t.co/2iOQgOQygV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otago student innovation for on bike storage. Mixing of old tech and new. https://t.co/32UXSzDuAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! @otago @Lovedunedin clock tower looking stunning with Spring Blossom today. Landscaping looks good at St Davids https://t.co/iLCupFsHPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matiuworkman they don't call @MitchellSantner flatline for nothing. All class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @charlielecomte whats the score?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see that @PacificEdgeLtd in The Fight Against #Cancer campaign featured in @USATODAY! Read about urine and… https://t.co/bGYl0Xwpfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConAnderson Friday this week. https://t.co/pwJ0MLzFPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lovedunedin @punakaikifund gutted not in Dunedin this Friday. https://t.co/pwJ0MLzFPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thoughts on clinical trials. https://t.co/8g2T4jcL13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realjourneys stunning as always - you're making me miss it even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple of likely lads @methylnick and @Laxi9 helping with @PacificEdgeLtd intern recruitment at @ChiasmaNZ networki… https://t.co/4iSbEvJFMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great campaign, well done Ian. https://t.co/C1aa8DJJYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @methylnick correct? #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to @methylnick this is my doppelgänger https://t.co/TxiacvU6IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting new glasses organised. I think they forgot something.🤓 https://t.co/POTzbQj55w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design they are really good, 100% better than the other signs that I see around the city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design did you do these? They look great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentDave_ does he have to pass a medical or is that later after he's injured. Do #afc give money back guarantee? Sort of reverse addons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Everton off to bed in NZ in next hour. Hoping to wake to good news. Hopefully it's all sorted or it will be long morning wondering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvertonTwatter @wilfriedbony hopefully he's on the way to @Everton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All help appreciated @ABIaucklandacnz for @PacificEdgeLtd  https://t.co/q46lyXR1Kt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>