<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent insights on #Brexit from Brussels from @OpenEurope's @pietercleppe on @BrexitCentral this morning! https://t.co/vniJGVyRjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you missed me discussing this week's #Brexit developments on TV yesterday with @JBeattieMirror, watch again here https://t.co/ZYQnDXpAsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating couple of Lab v UKIP battles in local by-elections in Rotherham going on today... https://t.co/9lvWdATq1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out for me on @SkyNews around 11.30am discussing all the latest #Brexit developments!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it last night: my analysis showing how every MP voted on the Article 50 Bill https://t.co/z9dYvGKywk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @BrexitCentral today, @DavidScullion salutes the 346 Remain-backing MPs who put democracy first last night https://t.co/bg4ufOmxCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did your MP vote tonight on the Article 50 Bill? I've done comprehensive analysis for @BrexitCentral https://t.co/z9dYvGKywk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulwaugh What about other frontbechers defying the whip like Catherine West and Vicky Foxcroft?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Labour front bench collective responsibility in tact or has it completely broken down? Will @CatherineWest1 be r… https://t.co/W16akLWZ2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SW_Trains A train with seats free just passed through New Malden at exactly the time the cancelled London train was due. Why?!??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are cancelling multiple London-bound trains from New Malden @SW_Trains, why not have faster trains do an additional stop???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flamin' Nora! It's February already! Where did January go?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why MPs should vote for the Article 50 Bill tonight: @labourleave's  @BrendanChilton on @BrexitCentral https://t.co/4CeihZSFNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are @BrexitCentral's video highlights from day one of the Article 50 Bill debate https://t.co/mAfk0eTpkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen out for me on @talkRADIO with @paulross on #Brexit shortly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A commendable acceptance of the referendum result from staunch Remain backer @wesstreeting during the first day deb… https://t.co/OtCFupkZCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear my MP @JamesBerryMP just telling the House of Commons he will vote for the Bill to trigger Article 50 tomorrow night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @matthew_elliott on his appointment as a Senior Fellow at @LegatumInst https://t.co/77uWH23ird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proceedings now under way in the Commons on the EU (Notification of Withdrawal) Bill; @DavidDavisMP is on his feet. Game on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to be losing @jordan_devi from the @BrexitCentral team today but delighted to be welcoming @DavidScullion on board as Deputy Editor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see former EU-backers @TheCityUK now embracing the "once-in-a-generation opportunity" of #Brexit https://t.co/813KUglK0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The warning from @theresa_may that devolved governments have no veto on #Brexit leads today's @BrexitCentral news https://t.co/qQd3NDrU0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All your #Brexit news for Sunday 29th January, courtesy of @BrexitCentral https://t.co/YY8KX6SvR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK’s relationship with Australia will be revitalised after Brexit, writes @matthewlesh on @BrexitCentral https://t.co/lJZYFvYNxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's your #Brexit news summary for the day, courtesy of @BrexitCentral https://t.co/ByalLoz5dC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour's Shadow Welsh Secretary quits as she refuses to back triggering Article 50 - even though Wales voted Leave https://t.co/nJERegNLAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's news on @BrexitCentral: Labour in crisis over Article 50 vote as May prepares to meet Trump https://t.co/8iOUWM6Apj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a joy to return here! https://t.co/xHa90L7r3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to returning to York to participate in the @PolSocYork #Brexit panel tonight alongside @LilleyPeter and @joecarberryUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour demand a Brexit White Paper to unite the party, but the PM then shot that fox: @MrTCHarris on @BrexitCentral https://t.co/IeWZCIynKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregHands @Starbucks The very first one? I paid a visit in 2011!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking now to re-read this taxpayer-funded Project Fear propaganda from the Treasury last May: https://t.co/qXZMw2QRns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read today's #Brexit News on @BrexitCentral for a full round-up of coverage of the Supreme Court judgment https://t.co/0fc3NIwxeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK must embrace Gibraltar more closely and not allow it to be a pawn in the Brexit talks, says @AndrewRosindell https://t.co/VzMdLuCKPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newjustine Charming! Given the referendum results you would appear to be a rare Yellowbelly Remainer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By @JohnPenroseNews on @BrexitCentral: Ministers should fast track legislation to deliver Article 50 Act within days https://t.co/yuLU3SOXlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Previews of today's Supreme Court ruling in the Article 50 case dominate today's @BrexitCentral news round-up https://t.co/sAHB4iGn2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Smith on @BrexitCentral: Anti-Brexit obstructionists in the Lords must be threatened with a Great Culling Bill https://t.co/iw7NmTdhf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not already getting the daily @BrexitCentral email, please sign up to keep abreast of all that's happenin… https://t.co/9PYDcpR8Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's your daily #Brexit news round-up courtesy of @BrexitCentral... https://t.co/yaB0O8UN27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @BrexitCentral @migrationwatch's Lord Green slams Lord Hague’s "simplistic" proposal for post-Brexit work permits https://t.co/FdODzfJ54I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomascoles I'm no longer there so ask @the_tpa - historically TPA prefers across the board reductions than complications to system...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your daily feast of #Brexit news is served up, as ever, by @BrexitCentral... https://t.co/oUH6gD7flZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @BrexitCentral @oflynnmep gives his take on the PM's Brexit speech and has a warning for Jeremy Corbyn and Labour https://t.co/AjT8T89fDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just caught up with @TristramHuntMP's valedictory Commons speech on #Brexit. Typically thoughtful and worth a read. https://t.co/JfAK4Y2r0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May has given us an achievable and realistic vision of post-Brexit Britain - @charbar1994 on @BrexitCentral https://t.co/w5xFqEN9Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gina Miller may have mischievous intentions but her legal case will help reinvigorate the Commons - David Abulafia https://t.co/0n4C9juHlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some encouraging news from the German finance minister leads today's @BrexitCentral news round-up https://t.co/qWp03chEXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How recently did it become a thing to take to the streets to protest against the result of a democratic election/referendum? Seems fatuous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had not clocked that the new @POTUS was teetotal. Imagine that twitter feed if it were alcohol-fuelled...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underwhelming for an inaugural address and concerned at protectionist  rhetoric. But then expectations were pretty low, weren't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asabenn @POTUS Er, it's up to 3.5 million in 5 mins!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presumably those tartan scarves are a nod to the new President's Scottish heritage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's #Brexit news on @BrexitCentral leads with Labour in disarray over whether to support triggering Article 50 https://t.co/kMjlq3vc4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased @Bromund of @Heritage writes for @BrexitCentral today about Brexit, Trump and deepening US-UK relations https://t.co/WMwpfXj6xs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very brave of Labour to select this ardent Remain campaigner to contest the by-election in staunch Leave-backing Co… https://t.co/CHxbhBDwWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with @michaelgove that @piersmorgan has been on fine form on @bbcquestiontime thus far this evening! https://t.co/HHJy6fxjvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The breakdown in collective responsibility of the Labour front bench over policy on Brexit is staggering https://t.co/FNaTYnHSMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of the 8,000+ tracks on my iPod, no fewer than three Christmas songs have been shuffled up in the last hour en route to the office!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's @BrexitCentral news leads with @LiamFoxMP confirming informal trade talks are underway with 12 countries https://t.co/i2Lpegf8nE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A @BrexitCentral tour-de-force as Labour's @AVMitchell2010 warns his party to give up its infantile Euro-enthusiasm https://t.co/ALOxZVgH8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More thoughts from me on @theresa_may's #Brexit speech in this week's @guardianaudio Politics Weekly podcast https://t.co/LTBVqPKkaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to returning to my alma mater, the @UniOfYork, for this event on #Brexit next week! https://t.co/1WB8zJlmIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bumper round-up of #Brexit news on @BrexitCentral today, following yesterday's speech by @theresa_may https://t.co/76hIFajU4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People should now unite behind Theresa May’s positive vision of post-Brexit Britain: @SteveBakerHW on @BrexitCentral https://t.co/Ar1M2QyH8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to @BBCr4today the cold weather in the south east of England today is coming from the continent - was it something we said?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A certain four year old is very excited about his new bed! https://t.co/eLIOtzkJNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to the first ever @BrexitCentral Podcast with @darrengrimes_, me and @matthew_elliott! https://t.co/0tUbdiYwaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @matthew_elliott's take on @theresa_may's #Brexit speech this morning... https://t.co/NLK3pk3Yyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists are trying to tempt @theresa_may into saying she was wrong to campaign for Remain at the referendum but she is not biting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must recognise the need to bring the brightest and the best into the UK while controlling immigration at a UK level, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All economic indicators since the referendum have been more positive than predicted, @theresa_may reminds @bbclaurak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The losers have a responsibility to respect the legitimacy of the outcome of the referendum, declares @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No deal would be better than a bad deal", insists @theresa_may (Very important that EU knows we're willing to walk away on WTO rules - JI)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A punitive deal to discourage others from leaving would be an Act of calamitous self harm for all of Europe, sad @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economically rational for all to have a free trade agreement: the erection of barriers would mean fewer jobs and less growth - @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vast majority want a positive relationship w/ the EU after Brexit. That's why we want a free trade agreement with the EU - @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a time for opposition for opposition's sake, urges @theresa_may. And it's not my job to fill column inches with daily updates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a comprehensive and carefully considered plan, says @theresa_may.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want an unlimited transitional status but there will be a phased process of implementation to avoid cliff edges, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The objectives provide a basis for a new strong and constructive partnership with the EU, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must work together more - not less - to deal with cross border crime and terrorist threats, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea of associate membership of the customs union is floated by @theresa_may who wants out of common commercial policy and external tariff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We want greatest possible access to single market with maximum freedom to trade in the EU &amp; the same for EU businesses here:  @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more contributions to the EU budget, promises @theresa_may. We may pay specifically to participate in some programmes, she adds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder from @theresa_may that BOTH sides in the referendum campaign said leaving the EU would mean leaving the single market]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I am proposing cannot mean membership of the single market" - unequivocal from @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also a pledge to protect and maintain workers' rights from @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resolving the rights of EU citizens here and Brits abroad is an early priority - @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When immigration get too high, public support falters. @theresa_may may says she knows you cannot control immigration with open borders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retaining common travel area with Ireland is a priority in and there will remain a special relationship with Ireland - @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Objective 2 is a Stronger Britain, says @theresa_may, emphasising support for the Union and involving the devolved nations in the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First objective from @theresa_may is clarity and certainty. Says final deal WILL be put to a vote in both Houses of Parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is one goal behind the 12 objectives - a positive and constructive partnership with the EU - @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are leaving the EU but we are not leaving Europe, emphasises @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The referendum vote was not a rejection of our shared values or a desire to turn the clock back to less peaceful times, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's in the UK's interest that the EU succeeds - so all should reflect on the lessons of Brexit, says @theresa_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Referendum was not a decision to turn inward on the world, says @theresa_may, reminding us of strong global ties around the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game on - Theresa May takes to the stage... https://t.co/6wsR9R7HBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An audience eagerly awaiting the Prime Minister... https://t.co/Cou6nIxu1B]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>