<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bungdan @salvadormom Is his taxes in there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heather28df @Freeyourmindkid No one takes Kanye seriously, not even the drugged out Lil Wayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamsFlaFan @WEMUSTSTOPTRUMP  Dear @realDonaldTrump you ignorant lunatic moron idiot. CA sends more $$  than it receives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @markevans08 the spineless worm @SpeakerRyan will not even go to voicemail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwunStJames @ROMANHO1 Oh please Darwun it  was a very humid day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder @ElizabethRowin Simple question. All Trump business entities lose money, but he says he makes money. How?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eggsmcenroe @now7grandkids Tell us how you really feel George  Nice !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey  ..@realdonaldtrump is compensating for his tiny hands, tiny manhood, tiny droplets, tiny mind, tiny fortune, tiny intellect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic @nytimes ..SteveBannon bounces @realdonaldtrump on his knees every morning, makes him sign, pats his head &amp; sends him to play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vet67Nam @MarkAgee Yes, the insane lunatic who started occupancy Jan 20th 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaZito That dar is wimmen talk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer You must be a little failed boy inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple question. All Trump business entities lose money, but he says he makes money. How? @WSJ @FT @MONEY @USATODAYmoney @YahooFinance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggrushko Clothes line failing, hotels going bust. Another bankruptcy? @IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer Patriots won with Alt-White players eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently @POTUS is a senile LUNATIC orange TWAT https://t.co/n8iPdaNjat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharypayton Nature Fresh Spring Water?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not call, but "other" people might https://t.co/30YQgQSV5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleyGirlNik @McConaughey There goes your tickets  sales. Never again, not even for charity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McKelvie @MelindaThinker ..@Foxnews just got into the printing business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs ..@realDonaldTrump is a senile lunatic puppet. The orange moron has no clue what transpires around him @teamtrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tragic_cal Trump University will print any degree for a small donation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP You will go down in history as commie traitor scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior @IBTimesUK He started as a moron then got even dumber?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul @markevans08 Trump is compromised. Massive debts, sex tape, money laundering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cupcakexx25 @Freeyourmindkid Biggest downgrade in the history of man https://t.co/aJR7mVaAvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Send one of your 120 bankruptcy lawyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptJaneway2017 @abuhena0044 I want to support you, but I wish to let the Orange Turd know every day that I despise his treasonous ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiberalJaxx Steven Bannon is an alcoholic, a racist, a wife beater. Nothing superior there.  @KellyannePolls @teamtrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @DineshDSouza Sleeping with your students is a terrorism Dinesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  A Trump supporter murdered 6 people praying in Quebec. Anything to say Orange fart, anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence When a senile lunatic @realDonaldTrump puppet is ordered by President Bannon to sign and SHUTUP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @bosslady2898 ..@teamtrump is the greatest collection of liars, incompetents, fools and bigots ever assembled. @MSNBC @maddow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrunoAmato_1 @jwyarnell The Trumps are a criminal organization. @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @IvankaTrump https://t.co/RkRnkjTE5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile No. Trump is senile. He repeats 5 stock phrases, has no memory of yesterday. Only greed and perversion keeps him alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jomason57 @YouTube @TheYoungTurks ..@IvankaTrump is a Trump is a criminal. Don't be seduced by her smile https://t.co/eFWaiAT5Dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @ThatGirlCA @MarkLandler ..@realDonaldTrump is managing Trump Inc. Only  the moron treasonous @GOP thinks Trump is playing golf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey The cowards should have done that a year ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind .. #OrangeHitler #OrangeTurd Lunatic, Toddler, Man Baby, Orange Peril, AssPimple, PeeMaster, Tiny Droplets, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithboykin @PatriciaBWriter I hereby declare that I was fully and totally in love with Barbara Jordan and Ann Richards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid Booooom ! Lies will destroy a yellow belly liar's liver  @BBCWorld @CNN @KellyannePolls @dailymail @maddow @StephenAtHome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlForsling Yep Day 15 and @realDonaldTrump is still shite @guardian @BBCWorld @Independent @DailyMailUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robreiner @RanchDressingTN Comey is a traitor @FBI Why sell our country to Russia?  @foxnews @cnn @NBCNews @ABC Why commit treason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @NaYaKnoMi SS agents will report pee parties @realDonaldTrump You hear that #OrangeHitler #resist @SenateGOP @CNN @BBC @ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Take a hint #OrangeHitler, GO AWAY you are destroying America  @SenateDems @SenateMajLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are one Orange Turd, not the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A so called judge will sentence you to prison soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbewart @DynaMoChen @nuzzel @rossprowd Crazed Aussie, bit by  a Tanzanian slime worm @australian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the depression supplied by the @gop criminals. @HouseGOP https://t.co/h09pFra4qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hired help lives in New York https://t.co/HIv2kmbbo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impeached the Orange Turd  @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/LxIKnMVDMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two visas for Russian pee professionals https://t.co/ZzjKFWuL5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackieFarnham @NaYaKnoMi You just can't make this shit up. The @houseGOP will legalize sex with sheep next. @GOP @guardian @BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamVTV Really dumb nut? Trump can fire a Federal Judge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He will resign when China calls in his loans and he can't pay. https://t.co/6qdtHKgxXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul @salvadormom It is creepy the the @GOP is willing to sell our country to Russia. @HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science rocks the spirit. https://t.co/iI6puXPCXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandadeibert @CatStaggs Very French avant garde cinema!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid Poor @LizDellaPiana I feel for you. But we kept telling you all of 2016, @realDonaldTrump is a lying scum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes @salvadormom Trump's business is Ponzi scheme of debt. Not one individual entity shows a profit. @SenateFinance  Money laundering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@balthsbart @RonHall46 @homemadeguitars You made my might. I am logging off now !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There a villa in Russia with well dressed women who drink a lot of water waiting for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorist shot dead in Bowling Green @KellyannePolls #BowlingGreenMassacre https://t.co/l6oJvV36Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkbl @Freeyourmindkid Here kitty kitty. I know real cats smarter than you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iveygirl08 @abuhena0044 @USATODAY to conduct his business. Trump never left his debt ridden Ponzi scheme business behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder @ThomasB00001 Good ! One parasite down @IvankaTrump https://t.co/fBI9m5jSWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kswills Men say God tells men how women must behave. Amazing that God never tells women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kasparov63 @abuhena0044 Those record productions have been happening every year since Stalin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozzy4873 The only cure for that is Russian urine therapy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlumniUSC Proves that Steve Bannon is @POTUS &amp; the orange lunatic toddler @realDonaldTrump is just a senile passenger on the Nazi bus. @BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WewillvoteTrump Now you are into nonsense. I can't believe I took you seriously. Bye !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WewillvoteTrump No! but don't confuse religion and national politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WewillvoteTrump A little knowledge is dangerous. One sided knowledge is useless.  Separate fact from fiction, enemy from friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 Nate you get to the babbling bullshit quickly. Thanks !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USARedOrchestra @KevinDarryl If Baghdad Spice @PressSec says 109 it means he reached into his colon and pulled tha… https://t.co/OVuqi3Yj1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WewillvoteTrump I spent years abroad. I am not an expert on any of them. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiberalJaxx  If @KellyannePolls says millions died in Bowling Green then millions died]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@australian Sorry Mate, we will, get rid of the Orange Turd soon enough https://t.co/6rQXK3mSCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WewillvoteTrump @puppymnkey Are you afraid of one LOUDMOUTH fake Imam. Get some man balls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress @JoyAnnReid Trump is an egomaniac surrounded by virulent racists &amp; flattered by Putin. PUPPET @realdonaldtrump PUPPET #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @ElizabethRowin ...@realdonaldtrump is tired. He needs another pee pee to recover. @teamtrump @foxnews  @POTUS @CNNPolitics @BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Picassokat @now7grandkids .. @realdonaldtrump is lying orange FOOL. The idiot LUNATIC is senile. Every day his tru… https://t.co/PEOFEOrw7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFallows ..@realdonaldtrump is too DUNCE to understand what the TPP meant. China should call in his debts &amp; break his Ponzi debt scheme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @politico here, shove this reminder https://t.co/JnKEItaRi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Donnelly @LiberalJaxx Those froggies need the swamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teamtrump is the greatest collection of assholes, liars, incompetents &amp; perverts ever collected @guardian @ABCPolitics @MSNBC @France24_en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @LiberalJaxx ..@teamtrump is the greatest collection of assholes, liars, incompetents &amp; perverts ever c… https://t.co/AOtinmDU3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WE WILL NEVER LIKE YOU. WE WILL NEVER RESPECT YOU. You are an insane lunatic clown. @guardian… https://t.co/9aWmEbMlcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS  Please STFU Kellyanne. Barack Obama rescued us from the @GOP failure. @realDonaldTrump is a parasite taking credit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @realDonaldTrump it is Day 14 and you still behave like a lunatic toddler clown. Why?  @teamtrump @PressSec @BBCBreaking @POTUS @NBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwardsDaily @BodhisattvaKat Dear @realDonaldTrump the whole world thinks are a lunatic idiot. @teamtrump @foxnews @senategop @cnn @bbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those Executive orders keep coming. Idiot senile lunatic @realDonaldTrump signs anything Steve Bannon orders him to… https://t.co/RYsx2XtDJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImaHillFan @Honey17011 Every single one of those slimeballs is https://t.co/lkETTt2AOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Picassokat @ramaxe1965 Even @realDonaldTrump's  supporters know he is a moron; but the promise of a "white" country seduced them. @cnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @RebelJournals  Numbers clearly visible on the truck. No one walks out the motor pool with just any truck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert @ThomasB00001 Pence has to ask Bannon https://t.co/KLMBXYBMmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meakoopa @RcarltonRb First you made me laugh out loud, then I was reminded that polite does not bring change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristieRabago If @KellyannePolls says Muslims massacred Americans in Bowling Green; it happened. Trumpettes believe it happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiggsWayne @yodaquoter Pump up the Muslim hate #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @ElizabethRowin We need to know why Republicans are selling our country to Russia @nytimes @SenateGOP @SenateGOP @SenateDems]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>