<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep reporting on the early days of the Trump White House. We might be in for a heck of a lot of leaking. https://t.co/vgDKdbFt4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrifying images. @abcnewsMelb @abcnews @abcnews24 https://t.co/lai9fu5Cdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I didn't predict in 2016/17:
1) Trump wins the primary
2) Trump wins the general
3) 3 Doors Down plays Krypt… https://t.co/NejOoX8YlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road is blocked at Sutton Rd in Sutton, east of Canberra, ahead of #MulligansFlat fire. https://t.co/AFAAg5vKCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SumishaCNA Can't go past their Roti Bom &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly from Aranda came home to this enormous gum tree in her children's bedroom. Thankfully no one home at the time… https://t.co/ICdAGj0s1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantWPhilpott Hey Grant, hope you're holding up okay! Have just flicked you a FB message re a story we're working on today - thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are definitely on the verge of the zombie apocalypse. I, for one, welcome our new mice overlords.… https://t.co/3Fti3GVS1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supergran41 @abccanberra It doesn't seem like anyone was inside, thankfully. A few people cleaning up the smaller stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few more shots of damage around the area, including a very badly damaged car. #Canberra https://t.co/XBW6nkf7WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trees torn up roots and all on the lawns of Parliament House in #Canberra https://t.co/7zXQTS6S7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road linking Old and New Parliament Houses cordoned off for obvious reasons... Note the downed traffic sign.… https://t.co/Bkwf79HulL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some pretty significent damage from downed branches at the Aboriginal Tent Embassy in #Canberra https://t.co/pL27FvM9Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0DanSmith @tomfed Phew! Though I did notice a Freudian slip of sorts when Reggie said "And man, what games?" What games indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomfed @0DanSmith Yup, March always seemed like a tight turnaround. What's the pressure to release early (other than imminent Wii U death)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0DanSmith @tomfed Yep, bizarre. At least they had Luigi's Mansion for GCN launch... and how hard is it to make a Mario Kart game, really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomfed @0DanSmith Literally the only one I saw was 1, 2 Switch. Mario as a holiday release is especially disappointing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key thing that struck me about the #NintendoSwitchPresentation is how few games seem deep in development. Not a great look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot say I was expecting Seth Meyers to deliver this interview at this exact moment. https://t.co/qOZ0jgj2Cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patcronan @SkyNewsAust #knowyourcompetition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't take my eyes off the emojis streaming along the bottom of the screen. https://t.co/BC3Ja8bWpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 30-year-old man has died following a single-vehicle accident at @Summernats at Exhibition Park in Canberra. #summernats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewpettifer Hi Andrew, hoping to get in touch for a story. Mind following me so I can flick you a quick DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlkiraReinfrank @tomlowrey I agree... Except I side with Lowrey on the Turkish Delight. Get that outta my face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomlowrey @AlkiraReinfrank Their honeycomb is consistent, which is more than you can say about those abominable Crunchies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police say the vehicle fire at the Australian Christian Lobby was "not politically, religiously or ideologically motivated". #canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@verge writes on the wild west of Talkspace - the therapy app blurring the lines of regulation and liability:  https://t.co/sdtX9aPtoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In North Carolina, Republicans are working to diminish the power of newly-elected Governor @RoyCooperNC: https://t.co/phjBnmPxAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Transport_CBR's new ACTION buses are ... wait for it ... blue. Light rail vehicles will be red. There's 20 new bu… https://t.co/l4eR3Dd4Ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@markparton: "Madam Speaker, you might have to get me out of this mess." (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@markparton finishes speaking in the Assembly: "I wish I could go to a commercial break ... so I don't know how I close this now." (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JadAbumrad Gazi, Lucy Liu, MoVida... Brunch at Top Paddock. Ice cream at Gelato Messina. Burger at Huxtaburger. Literally everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ACT public servants told to swap Freddos for mangoes under impending chocolate fundraising ban: https://t.co/GqxWbUdnXE #actps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Naked selfies' used as collateral for Chinese peer-to-peer loans. Interest apparently reached 30% per WEEK: https://t.co/ZBkz9pme6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 36-year-old Canberra man has been refused bail over child pornography offences heard in the ACT Magistrates Court. @abcnewsCanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a fascinating insight into the work that goes into obituaries long before the subject dies.
 https://t.co/BNqGEl0O8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Behind The Lines 2016 political cartoon exhibit has launched at @MoAD_Canberra. The inimitable cameraman Andy K… https://t.co/H6rdtwGSD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to reading this! @BenSmee @TheNTNews https://t.co/7LosXRupY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an exceptionally good read. https://t.co/gRviAuT6Lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend. #moreton #nationalparks #visitnsw #southernhighlands https://t.co/VvKtXPAIQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMichaelZavros Most welcome Michael! Was great to see the piece, and I always love an excuse to head out to @PortraitAu!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingenue_meg So I'll just quietly keep my fingers crossed and hope it outperforms every other video game movie ever. Plleeeeeaaaaasssseee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingenue_meg I know CGI movies never rate but I don't know how I could watch any live actor play Nate *or* Sully *or* Elena.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingenue_meg I've just started finding time for A Thief's End again and jeez I love it so much it hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JB_AU @AppleSupport This was sent to the ABC Breaking News alert email via "MessageMedia" too ... Methinks hoax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the team, Dan! https://t.co/cMuqfGAf61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sonya_gee Was "big fat poo" always on the mug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NateSilver538 gives an interesting look at how differently the punditry would reflect if 1/100 voters switched R&gt;D https://t.co/cCxeUseNzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where so many people are opting for spin and gloom, these guys are honestly evaluating things. Compelling listening. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's @keepingit1600 is a sober reflection of how so many people got the election wrong. Props to @jonfavs, @jonlovett &amp; @TVietor08.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems to be contention here, but crazy if true. Fewer polling places? Lack of enthusiasm? Turned off by tone of cam… https://t.co/ERgd7SspAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CLewandowski_ on CNN blasting Clinton for not speaking tonight, furious. @VanJones68: "Corey, you won. Corey, you won."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johnpodesta: "Every vote counts ... Go home, get some sleep." No more tonight. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyCJD Not that long in history of constitutional amendments I guess. 27th Amendment proposed in 1789, adopted in... wait for it... 1992.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyCJD It's all theoretical anyway because two-third majority in the House seems impossible, let alone ratification by 3/4 of states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyCJD Congress could theoretically flip in 2018 given incumbent disadvantage, but Dems defending more seats/Reps have a GOTV edge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And of course the only way to get rid of it is a constitutional amendment - surely impossible in a country this divided. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the second time in the modern era, we're set to see a popular vote/electoral college split in favour of Republi… https://t.co/z8MTDYpXvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those hanging on every tick of the @nytimes model. https://t.co/uCBctARa0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef Not counting partial returns, only pre-election projections and called states. Probably better for hyperventilating types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TomMcIlroy 538's model only based on pre-election projections and called states - partial returns not counted - so it's holding steady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, how about those forecast models predicting 98%+ chance of a Clinton win? #electionnight ping @NateSilver538]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the first time Trump has been ahead in a forecast, ever? @nytimes #ElectionNight https://t.co/viGB7rxhfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously taken with a grain of salt, @nytimes' live forecast is ticking on a knife edge. Case in point: 272 to Tru… https://t.co/jMsoGxpliQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holed up at home watching #ElectionNight. @nytimes has THE most nailbiting live forecast ticker, especially Senate: https://t.co/aDHaqmLi1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very cool. Also a terrible system to emulate in 2016! https://t.co/PaLcCfmfKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arisharp even if less so than years gone by. Say what you will about revolving leadership, I think we get better representation. (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arisharp Even though this US cycle is an anomaly I still take great comfort that our elections are much more policy-focussed, (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arisharp And even though our elections sometimes feel presidential, the Westminster system still feels like it wins out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arisharp It's a good question. Our partisanship is so much less pronounced too - far fewer party registrations, much higher 3rd party vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arisharp I suspect Australian politicians might do the same if they had that kind of public personal support... but none of them do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingenue_meg I looked into this a while back - the E3 visa is super generous if you're using a degree, otherwise it's tough. Sending my ❤️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a terrible story. Awful to hear the impact on @MelbChargers teammates. Excellent work @Jess_Longbottom https://t.co/fdZjZj8j0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STRAIGHT TO WORK: @ABarrMLA's new Cabinet will focus on a "progressive economic and social agenda". @abcnewsCanberra https://t.co/hp45auRVSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martin_J_Miller Right at the top, first under Andrew Barr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environment and Climate Change have been separated, with @GENTLEMANMick taking the former and @ShaneRattenbury taking the latter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The contentious portfolio of Gaming and Racing is no more. It now comes under Regulatory Services, to be held by @Gordon_R_Ramsay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the new @actgovernment Cabinet. Newcomer @Gordon_R_Ramsay gets the all-important Attorney-Gen, Dep CM… https://t.co/vnruozTEMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First sitting of the Ninth Assembly. @ABarrMLA elected Chief Minister, @JoyBurchMLA elected Speaker.… https://t.co/k9512eshAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ShaneRattenbury has taken up Labor's offer and will remain (the sole) Greens Minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoyBurchMLA will be the next ACT Speaker, with the Greens supporting Labor's nominee in Parliamentary Agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New @CanberraLibs leader @alistair_coe: 'I am honoured by the trust that my colleagues have put in myself and… https://t.co/FdooZcyFFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alistair Coe is the new @CanberraLibs leader. @nicolelawder is the deputy. @abcnewsCanberra #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @CanberraLibs are meeting now for their first post-election party room meeting. Leadership to be resolved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammshirley Expectation on Labor's part. Greens very much still mulling over whether to take up the offer or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor's also endorsed @JoyBurchMLA as its nominee for Speaker. @ABarrMLA says she's qualified for job, and it's Labor's turn for the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACT Labor emerges from first caucus meeting. @YvetteSBerry elected Deputy, @rach4kurrajong and @Gordon_R_Ramsay zip… https://t.co/CF8Dx1vRpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ending my #actvotes coverage with a brilliant view of #Tuggeranong. Looking forward to more reporting in the Ninth… https://t.co/hLQ075P4v8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Hanson's most likely leadership contender, @alistair_coe, says talk is for another day. 'Today is about honourin… https://t.co/lzGxT3Ch2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the party's strategy on light rail, @JeremyHansonMLA says "the politics may have been wrong ... but the policy was right." #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JeremyHansonMLA on leadership: "Whether I stand or not is a decision I'm yet to take, and it's something I'll dis… https://t.co/x3DmCUhZff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the crowd thinned at last night's #actvotes Liberal HQ, the party came to terms with yet another election loss: https://t.co/DHdwb5AuMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flanked by his wife, Fleur, @JeremyHansonMLA thanks volunteers for an "effective campaign". #actvotes https://t.co/UkUeFvqi3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanson: The Canberra Liberals will continue to be the party of integrity in this town. #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanson says it's very difficult to form government. He's called @ABarrMLA: "I have congratulated him." #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanson thanks his Deputy, @alistair_coe. Says he's led the fight against light rail in Yerrabi, even if it's fallen… https://t.co/E9xoMWdYeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal members fairly muted following ABC's call of a likely Labor win. Still plenty of people here, mingling.… https://t.co/nbHPWWpeLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd starting to fill out here at @CanberraLibs HQ, Antony Green calls a likely Labor return. #actvotes https://t.co/VpqjejSjVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record, I followed @JeremyHansonMLA's lead and snagged my own #democracysausage. Couldn't possibly report o… https://t.co/7ud0F4UM2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The inevitable #democracysausage gets a thumbs up from Liberal leader @JeremyHansonMLA. #actvotes https://t.co/4YssLUWMYl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>