<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY PARENTS SHOW OFF BABIES NOW! https://t.co/YhmE4y9tN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@livhritz @vandervonodd I want to know how she does that becuase i NEED IT FOR A COSPLAY AAAAAAH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GAMING_PRODIGY9 @Lotus_Lila @megturney well she is an adventurer , so like why not? (this is my first ever armour build it's not gr8)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GAMING_PRODIGY9 @Lotus_Lila @megturney All good bro! It's Fiona the human from adventure time but as a warrior! designed by Nasuki100 on DA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotus_Lila @megturney MORE CAPES! (tHANK you!!!! )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotus_Lila @megturney I got this cosplay thing down pat! &gt;:3 https://t.co/RNVMhzWw53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotus_Lila @megturney ALL THE CAPES!  if it doesn't have a cape in the design, ADD 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megturney i see this gif and i shudder as i add 3 cosplays with capes on them ^^"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameTheRobot You're fine babe! &lt;3  Love you more!  xx Just don't forget to come see me off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri learned this one the hard way.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameTheRobot WOO! finally got somehting to do while i'm packing! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameTheRobot You know it! &gt;:3 i'll get the good camera tonight :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @BlameTheRobot  i wont be sleeping tonight! https://t.co/M3nOGvuLXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameTheRobot then hurry up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameTheRobot woo!! I hope the sore back from E3 Was worth it! :D  it looks AWESOME!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairie_Tails And i thought I was making a big move haha  xD (just moving to auckland on monday)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairie_Tails Death by Glue in the eye (sailor neptune) XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yay.... hot flushes.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holding onto this guy as long as I can. https://t.co/zUoBuoU1DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe i talked to @MikeDirnt on The Edge.... I'm sorry for crying but I'll see you guys in May!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGingerMinj A-FUCKING-MEN!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm 21 and mum wont let me watch friday the 13th...................(little does SHE know)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri First step into becoming a cyborg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmberLPortwood Me at the Bar XD HA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do i tell my friends i've basically stopped eating ^^" .....actually...how do i tell my family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmLindsayJones Still gonna call her Jellybean~ &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO is it possible for obama to come back????????? like.... after ww3?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nodame_7 you could say its shaken me in all the wrong was haha!!!😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nodame_7 yup! Moving to auckland, my last day at pumpkin patch is next saturday so i'm looking for work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got my letter from PP today... moving to auckland in 13 days..... I'm terrified ....and excited......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalesButt well Helloooooo Mr Moriarty~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier why :(((((]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote a review on @JamberryNails #Marvel and #Disney Nail wraps!This was so much fun, https://t.co/aLjlEIhszd …… https://t.co/JN7cFyAMwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmLindsayJones  If they're gonna be a little bitch about what you want to do with your baby, then they don't get to come to babys 1st bday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh GOD i hate when people ask me to make kids cosplays... they're made of stretch and don't fit and are expected to cost $20... i WONT DO IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this was very much a bad idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SupaFitz You are working on a casual basis. they will give you the job seekers support though you'll have to report if work and get paid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harto Does someone need vodka and coke minus the coke???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyleroakley Busy or Messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilllindsay is the best way to stay entertained at 1am while being sat on by a cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 YOU ARE OFFICIALLY TERRIFYING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness I just found out @HyndenIsHere  Is gonna be at dunedin armageddon I'M BRINGING BACK THIS BABE! SO EX… https://t.co/efE7r8J3q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheriiart You're welcome love!  I seriously admire your talent! xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheriiart They're both adorable oh my goodness~ &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong Keep calm and blast them bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri Limit my cosplay munchies!when im working on shit i munch and i don't even notice until 10 bags of chips are now on the floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri Think of all the places you can put scraps and rolls of worbla and foam and shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasSanders I'm hiding under the christmas tree cause the rest of my "family"s here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Armageddonexpo I don't have any other money to go boxingday shopping sooooooooooowhynot right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I just realised the Live Action Phoneix Wright movie  is a christmas movie.... best...christmas... EVER!  HAHAHAAHAHAH @CapcomMobile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a risk with my Christmas outfit this year and created my own design for Lady Lizzie that i hope… https://t.co/AFDxBeKOJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sKWAD This was probably one of my favourite groups to be apart of this year!  Thanks Ceecee for organising it! &lt;3… https://t.co/AkkuNmtrlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So obsessed with my friend Tiinos Music! Check out her first single 'Sober' it's honestly amazing!&lt;3 #Music #NZMusic
https://t.co/AaSeh1j5Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im pretty happy with my christmas lizzie #cosplay for todays picnic !! https://t.co/Bo4jY5E97b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God i'm scared for what i've made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 episodes of Show by rock and NOW realized im watching season 2 Thanks @Crunchyroll .... (Help....how do i find season 1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri BUT I AM CRYING I JUST FOUND OUT MY FAVOURITE SHOP NO LONGER STOCKS SWEDISH FISH MUCH CRY :'''''''''''''((((((((((((]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite False eyelashes are being discontinued...RIP ...We had fun....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I freaking love these people so much .... Im coming back soon I promise :) https://t.co/Y8IjsBDWsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got to go out and spend time with these babes in #grieferbelt Cosplays! Created by @KalesButt xoxox &lt;3 https://t.co/VgW1qyPn9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love these guys~ &lt;3 they keep me distracted and remind me I'm not alone~ xoxox https://t.co/GsF4bj1tha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theodd1sout lol XD is it even a good website?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri I HAVE A SPARE ROOM AT MY HOME PLEASE FEEL FREE TO COME STAY SAFE OVER HERE! RIP america]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rialisms I hope you had a super wonderful day!xoxox and Thank you!xxx I'm going to email the fluff out of @Armageddonexpo s Gmail hahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness it's so beautiful o-o https://t.co/VWdtnGcaiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMichaelTatum Kill him..............with a cactus .........covered in rusty nails.........and fire....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY @Rialisms :D I love you and your Talents You're amazing! Love from this girl in New Zealand! :D (Com… https://t.co/b5QXZkvwl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter where you are, You can always find your wonderland~ https://t.co/3UPKH39CMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really do wish i could go back to school sometimes...... but i don't use my principal for a comfort item....oops https://t.co/SNESil8VSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rialisms I nearly lost my father 3 months ago to a heart attack...I hope this donation helps...I hope you're doing well @marchimark xoxoxox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2013 - 2016 I'm so happy I remade Meyrin! &lt;3 Thank you @Rialisms for lending your voice to my favourite Maid! https://t.co/AMWvHeQqVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what It means to be a servant of the Phantomhive manor! @JMichaelTatum @Rialisms @iantweeting https://t.co/aUxf143RB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Sunsa from @WellingtonZoo and He is officially the most well behaved Red panda ever! Cute keeper too~ https://t.co/aVva2WqklC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LONG LIVE THE GOBLIN KING! &lt;3 R.I.P #DavidBowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong Kill it with fire..........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharypayton Atleast you're working it!  Mini Payton has good taste!!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never had more fun than I had in my #Harleyquinn #cosplay , I can see why she's so popular! https://t.co/gPD3CUZMps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong YES!!!!!!!!!!  I HAVE NEEDED THIS SINCE I DISCOVERED THIS THEORY!! :DDDDDDDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Halloween comes pranks hehe Cy got BB Good~ @kharypayton  @GregCipes https://t.co/SeH3w3qOW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CristinaVee It was lovely meeting you too!!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CristinaVee Thank you for making me the happiest Homura ever! ignore the tired smile XD https://t.co/Pzgf6B23fR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HyndenIsHere my mum always used to give me "Rescue Remedy" and tell me to stay in a dark room for 30 minutes and that seemed to work for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...ithink i forgot to send in my timesheet last week oh no.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HyndenIsHere About right... i have nearly all the Harley pops..none of them stand properly....-sigh-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong I'd be worried bout the way your puddin loves ya harels.... it's not..really good for ya babe.... Ivy though~ xoxo :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megturney Who? the fluffy one or gavin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong oops...BYYYYE EXISTANCE.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yay more heart break ^^"  He still wants to go to lunch and sing with me...... this is fucking torture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition to keep our Kate Sheppard pedestrian lights #KeepKate http://t.co/fj33RPzkJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HyndenIsHere knows not to tick off Starfire! but do you? (I'm in love with this shot AAAAA &lt;3 ) http://t.co/zQjbGQlHtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is such thing as loosing your motivation to work...most of that is when your boss is a cock......i can't wait to start my new job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the 26 mill going to wards #changingthenzflag i could actually get like 52 million Chicken nuggets from BK at the moment........c'mon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheenaoum she will rip off your face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glam_And_Gore we probably will XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can not wait another week to shoot my #Starfire #Cosplay from #TeenTitans ! So MEGAPUMPED! http://t.co/ckifwjQ64r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatPatGT Good on you matpat XD nice going XDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharypayton @redbubble This is totally amazing but with the brightness down i totally thought he was waterbending......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyleroakley does tyler collect anything? besides dust and hairdye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mooore patterning~~~~ shocka when you find you don't need as much fabric as you thought you'd need XD #Cosplay http://t.co/gFpGCJRP98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharypayton with tula, much important . yup so much important :P]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>