<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump #POTUS Why Nobody Cares the President Is Lying https://t.co/8oqiyj5Cgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now #Trump is attacking his government's lawyers. An adult should cancel his Twitter account. https://t.co/u1ZdJJmdOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is #US coming to when #POTUS can attack judiciary &amp; misrepresent tight visa screening already in place. #Sad… https://t.co/0aYwinsQRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRake Don't know if it is tonight or next week that SNL is doing an extended piece with Alec Baldwin that will drive Trump nuttier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRake Trump did graduate from university, he can't be as semi-literate as he appears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRake Thanks for that. It's stunning. I Tweeted link to YouTube of it. Let's hope it isn't as bad as it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth listening to all of this! Uh-Oh: Does Donald #Trump Know How to Read? https://t.co/LAH1Ro81Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Bush-nominated federal judge who halted #Trump's executive order https://t.co/WvMRBcI0zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump illustrates fake news, a term he uses for anything he doesn't like. No evidence of support for… https://t.co/m24M8nWR3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there no Republican lawyers who find it objectionable for #Trump #POTUS to show disrespect to a judge, let alone George W Bush appointee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Has there ever been a #POTUS who has brought such disrespect on both his office &amp; those of other #US institu… https://t.co/vehmurO3R6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotuslander1000 Whisper 3string of neighbours &amp;see what comes out. No evidence for malicious theory to cover Lib hack/theft #bcndp #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotuslander1000 Nah, I think CC has deep Russian hackers reading #bcndp computers like they hacked US election. Equally credible :) #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helps BC Libs 2spin disloyalty in @jjhorgan #bcndp but no evidence not a Watergate, hacked computers or found files https://t.co/4iVACCYIli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric #Trump’s business trip to Uruguay cost taxpayers $97,830 in hotel bills https://t.co/KWKPIyhavK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump’s rallying cry: fear itself https://t.co/3NZ9JtHUKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must be #fakenews that #Trump could finance "The Wall" with surcharge of $2 on every taco sold in #US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great cartoon, political junkies like me have trouble stopping constant monitoring of train wreck. Please be boring… https://t.co/r6acgxxGf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump #POTUS #resist #TrumpMuslimBan Watch for more inane Tweets https://t.co/wWZd2YC9ZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marchaslam1 You convinced me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marchaslam1 Did they bring their on videographer at taxpayer cost? Only Premier photo-op @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only does #Trump #POTUS make inane Tweets np but he retweets his own inane stuff. https://t.co/OYrL7A5sav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keburman Should have read Greens turning green with envy rather than celebrating strong environmental leadership by electable #bcndp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keburman Read @keithbaldrey where he discusses @jjhorgan come 2 environmental awareness moment, celebrate it #bcndp https://t.co/X2q0lrxNx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endorsements are impressive as is article by @keithbaldrey on #bcndp enviro emphasis https://t.co/X2q0lrxNx3 https://t.co/Jye8YvaJiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch as AJW turns green with envy because environmentalists applaud #bcndp @jjhorgan Plan. See @keithbaldrey on ND… https://t.co/y8eGJrUuwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcpoli #bcndp Here's Christy Clark's climate action plan, expensive photo-ops in Paris while emissions in BC rise: https://t.co/jpNO24e3cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BCNDP climate plan "shows real action," say environmentalists  https://t.co/jlsTzCtIsz via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestBench You'll see gov &amp; Lib front ads on all channels &amp; platforms, more on @GlobalBC b/c of audience size. #bcndp must win spending less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's piece on nasty folks behind those badly done TV ads attacking #bcndp @jjhorgan https://t.co/j9cWW6L0F7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestBench All depends where Lib front group focuses ad buy. News hour cheaper than sports &amp; drama where you see gov ads #bcpoli @GlobalBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestBench Can't blame @GlobalBC for ad time bought by BC Lib front group. #bcpoli #bcndp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcpoli #bcndp EXCLUSIVE: Who is John Horgan? Meet the man who wants to be B.C.’s next premier https://t.co/xGEFp4G47j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what BC Libs internal polling is saying that their surrogates are already running TV attack ads against #bcndp @jjhorgan #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternatefacts #Trump @KellyannePolls claim of a 'Bowling Green massacre' https://t.co/oTlCCdhs1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Government reveals more than 100,000 visas revoked due to travel ban https://t.co/QfoCBKQOEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts in #Trump's #alternativereality #Sad https://t.co/hiU2MrxPdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you love how 3 million more people voted for #Hilary Perhaps #Trump should try to govern for all. https://t.co/vjc5RGysxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually Arnold has a great idea. Switch jobs and make America safe again. #Trump https://t.co/tUueerwYOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stirling Yah, it's your friends that frequently cause most trouble. I plead guilty to having independent opinions - free at last :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stirling Don't think it hurt to have Libs promote #bcndp plan, prompting Tweets from @Tzeporah  Libs want distraction from #bcndp Plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stirling Interesting side story if it was a "leak" rather than careless handling of documents or hack. Story as spun has no evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stirling Horgan made light of it b4 Shaw story with emphasis on "leak" rather than on substance of Plan. However, he'll turn cheek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Stirling Give me 2much credit, Libs have been spinning "leak" all day to make it story rather than substance of Plan. #bcndp #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robshaw_vansun Important lesson from US election is cost Trump nothing to push back against media, #bcndp should stop putting up with BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robshaw_vansun Point is your opinion should be on opinion page, not disguised as news. #bcpoli #bcndp #falsenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lotuslander1000 Alternatively a copy could have been carelessly lost or a computer could have been hacked. No evidence on alleged "mole"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robshaw_vansun Story is contents of #bcndp Plan, not Liberal stunt on leaking it 90 minutes early. Their stunt did nothing to lesson Pla.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like biased coverage that belongs on Op-Ed page. Shame on @robshaw_vansun #bcpoli #bcndp #fakenews https://t.co/wjZTeea1hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoodfordCHNL Weaver's green with envy as environmentalists complement @jjhorgan &amp; #bcndp while criticizing Libs #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoodfordCHNL Did Green Leader also say he envies @jjhorgan for having @Tzeporah endorse #bcndp plan? #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Fleming Very clever of @jjhorgan to get BC Libs to promote &amp; distribute #bcndp Climate Plan. #bcpoli Love response from @Tzeporah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain says Russia testing U.S. in Ukraine, urges #Trump to hit back https://t.co/1TNG1PBPDa via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUST READ #Trump Opinion | Steve Bannon's first major play is shaping up as a full-blown fiasco https://t.co/rge5boAUgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold responded in video: #Trump asks for prayers for Arnold Schwarzenegger's ratings at National Prayer Breakfast https://t.co/Am67Z2VmoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice from Arnold to #Trump Swich jobs! https://t.co/UZJO4DflqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘This was the worst call by far’: #Trump badgered, bragged and abruptly ended phone call with Australian leader https://t.co/8ivyXaBNaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S.-Australia Rift Is Possible After #Trump Ends Call With Prime Minister https://t.co/9mn6dVNTQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election is over but #Trump #POTUS prefers to campaign since governing is hard. https://t.co/J6KPjq9cSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cdnpoli Nice (ugly) list of promises broken by @JustinTrudeau on #CBC tonight but can't find clip on https://t.co/CJCwBThnkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dignity of office continues to fall as #Trump #POTUS uses 142 characters to articulate #US foreign policy. https://t.co/NYe5nVFLs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next #cdnpoli election anything @JustinTrudeau says 2b contrasted against video of solumn promise on electoral reform. Lost credibility!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch #GOP balance who can dissent while maintaining enough votes to confirm! #Trump #POTUS Time to demonstrate bal… https://t.co/aOJ0lFGdkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NorthVancouver @NorthShoreNews Looking forward to @JonathanWNV responding to https://t.co/wBqFTc15kH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very scary! #Trump #POTUS #Resist https://t.co/0sPbCH0egi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't he mean FPTP gave him power so why change the system? #cdnpoli https://t.co/oKS8PHeOL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Hobby Lobby Ruling Means for America https://t.co/J4ynP5J5js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markcritch Just in case anyone thought @ezralevant wasn't a pile of s..t #cndpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long will #GOP roll over as #POTUS #Trump behaves like #Putin https://t.co/0nsUrysJBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words matter, especially when spoken by people like #POTUS #Trump as they can influence weak minds like: https://t.co/rIxEgPQnsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS is a class act. Time will come when he will need co-operation from the people he slags. #Trump https://t.co/eJMDP6cCiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #GOP Congress lacks guts to balance powers, they might as well resign &amp; declare #Trump dictator. #1930s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least he hasn't taken off for Costa Rica https://t.co/nKldmDAQfW #mnpoli #cdnpoli https://t.co/s5KesencMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad even @washingtonpost hasn't updated story that alleged shooter was white #Trump enthusiast, see… https://t.co/aJfWWaZ2nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump fires acting AG after she declines to defend travel ban @CNNPolitics https://t.co/oiT3jra01u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet to read any major #US news site getting facts right on alleged Quebec murderer, read: https://t.co/77Ic4ad9tN @CNN @FoxNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, #POTUS just re-Tweeted his own Tweet. Must be really happy Yates has integrity. Stop Sessions co… https://t.co/ZHTMbfKB6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope enough #GOP Senators have guts to deny Sessions ratification #POTUS #TrumpMuslimBan https://t.co/nkeXqg1txR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS #Trump #TrumpMuslimBan If not blinded by #alternativefacts @SeanSpicerWH should pay attention to this. https://t.co/H2P1gHuqrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes it even more important to delay or deny ratification of Sessions #Trump https://t.co/sldYbxvYZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS #TrumpMuslimBan This should produce interesting Tweets from #Trump https://t.co/PJFSw6PBfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS #Trump #TrumpMuslumBan Someone should give @SeanSpicerWH the background on the alleged shooter. https://t.co/0Ka3FtzgVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS #TrumpMuslimBan He's just getting started, watch him destroy jobs! https://t.co/1kAeCzSCry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#POTUS #TrumpMuslimBan #Obama sets record straight after #Trump claimed similarities https://t.co/pPMIYtkMxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How #Trump’s Rush to Enact an Immigration Ban Unleashed Global Chaos https://t.co/9bbZVUiutU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump is more delusional than anyone can imagine. #TrumpMuslimBan https://t.co/PloJ6UUxHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legreg1 For gross payments to individual physicians, see the MSC annual reports https://t.co/4nL8FqVtHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting to go on air in 10 minutes @CBCEarlyEdition #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly shooting at Quebec mosque reported @CNN https://t.co/4m22DGotDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colinfreeze It's a parody account! #fakenews  @rodmickleburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday Jan 30 at 7:40 AM I'll be on #CBC 690AM @CBCEarlyEdition filling in for Moe with @ColinHansen #bcpoli #bcndp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcpoli #bcndp BC Libs have $ to pay Premier extra $50K, now converted to expense claims, but they're using our tax $ for pre-election ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcpoli #bcndp Good BC gov acknowledges "not all children have an equal chance" Sad it's not doing enough about it https://t.co/qzrmmYYY9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite bagging record amounts from corporate donors, Christy Clark is using tax $ for saturation pre-election ads. Vote her out #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to friends who say the news is too traumatic to watch. Thanks to #Trump &amp; #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days late but #US #Trump administration finally trying to sort out chaos it inflicted. #POTUS #TrumpMuslimBan https://t.co/SqMnWIiUUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bizarre for #POTUS to post to his personal Facebook page a reaction to #TrumpMuslimBan &amp; more attacks on media!… https://t.co/6jqHX5gMsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is the last time a sitting #POTUS behaved like this? He's dangerous &amp; unstable. https://t.co/XoCMAt9LLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump #TrumpMuslimBan White House Official, in Reversal, Says Green Card Holders Won’t Be Barred https://t.co/6IbmfCEOuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does #US military view political hack #SteveBannon as head of NSC. Take nuclear codes away! #POTUS… https://t.co/zrM92KH2cW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>