<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro someone running a Keeping Your Mouth Shut course would make good bank from me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From nuclear weapons to apartheid, NZers are known for our moral compass and punching above our weight. Our govt must denounce US actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shiflett or in the case of Trump, pick zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelchup me too. We can still make noise and support those doing the hard work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelchup the world is more interconnected than ever before. It's only a matter of years, if that, before the repercussions hit us at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester car design is amazing. Glad to hear you're OK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secvalve Dunning-Kruger says we might not be able to do that.  Hard to know what you don't know, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyavw combinations of code paths such you'd need thousands of files to test them all. In that case, focused unit tests fill in the gaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyavw if you're able to test all the functionality with black-box then you're fine, but for a complex system there are too many 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyavw these sort of black-box tests are good, but you might want to also supplement with unit tests if the system you're testing is big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyavw the longer the better! make them readable so anyone can look at the directory and work out how the code works, it's documentation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyavw I've done this in a couple of projects, e.g. to test an email message parser. Named the files after what was being tested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshForde @samjarman @moskoben agreed measuring is important, but you don't have to quantify your work/velocity using agile points though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatDudley turns out we have to relearn them once every three generations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WellingtonICT "Hmm, look. There's nothing written on this purple post-it either."  "Hmm, yeah, you're right."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amirmohtasebi @samjarman I know a couple of companies that are high in happiness and low in productivity. It's correlated but not strongly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman both are management problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman in my experience, if devs are working slowly it's either because the process is broken or because they're overfactoring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman estimating software build times is hard, and people feel more comfortable using a meaningless number than just using their gut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman who cares if you've shipped 100 points if your customers are less happy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman super common tho. Metrics like customer satisfaction, customer interaction, support tickets or revenue are actually meaningful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman every time you use points to track velocity, a kitten dies. Don't kill the kitties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman points are to estimate work in progress/future work. If you're using them retrospectively, You Are Doing It Wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms I'm on season 4. Can report improved feels. Also listening to the west wing podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn and if you can't, it's because you don't want to, and you should shut the hell up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn it believes anyone can spend the time necessary to learn a language, learn the codebase, submit a patch, and deal with the politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandofsky Slack's official app on Windows takes 2.5GB with 7 teams loaded. I'm blaming Slack more than Electron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms or biking in general. Not an expert but it seems NZ got it wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this talk. Seriously, if you're a dev, take the time to watch it. It will inform the rest of your career. https://t.co/U47TMSwY5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesslynnrose how do they handle failure? I think this is the canary of culture. You can ask for examples of failure in an interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torshin no probs, we'll flick off the "completely bullshit weather" switch when you come up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms can he do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms my only hope is it'd take an act of Congress to defund vaccines (I think?) so hopefully it'll just be a lot of hot air]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white guy (me) explains hiring for diversity with some reasons why it's important for a company's success. https://t.co/xoxEsw2q13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman I'd watch that talk for the explosions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman CFPs have been open for a while now! Are you writing one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got my ticket. It's going to be a fantastic event! https://t.co/XbAsIlunCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soundasleep @aurynn  I found Chef frustrating and a bit heavy handed too. Happy to share my Ansible recipes for Rails apps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinkelly isn't that what Twitter is for? Hope you're feeling better soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've reached that point where coding isn't as exciting as it used to be -- what next for you, software developer? https://t.co/IbPc7xMyf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @kenbier very exciting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenbier @sanityinc because colours were tied to pay bands at Powershop, we didn't make them public, but maybe that's changed recently?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms haha I love the word "squicks"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms if they were courteous, they'd put down the seat and lid, so you'd still have to lift the lid anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler I think this is a great reason for me to get myself up to Codemania, always been meaning to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler hmm, I can definitely see the argument there. If there is a scale, people will put themselves on it based on years. Hmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler The spectrum is a way to distance "seniority in age" from "seniority in skill and value", because the latter is what matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler maybe I'm not clear; it's crazy that years has anything to do with pay. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler yeah, with so many factors making up being a good developer, it's hard. But HR needs titles. Do you have any ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior? Intermediate? Senior? A proposal for a better way to name software developer roles.
https://t.co/s2P1BOsUKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to publish some more software developer career articles this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms hey, there goes the "that's why voters chose Trump as their president" line we were reading about yesterday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinkelly I don't think my VM has ever reached the jump back operation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn she opened my eyes and so many others'. It's a better world because she is in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amirmohtasebi I think that happens for any popular technology. The more mass-market, the lower quality the average build is going to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @merxplat not a shabby idea. My Food Bag for flowers, basically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merxplat that is a superb idea. I'd so use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms the Internet is basically the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms I don't think anyone has. So bizarre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmei how would you respond to someone approaching you, assuming it was done in a respectful way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_sim @Pseudony_Ms Has journalism been reduced to clickbait headlines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can confirm: role is awesome. Love building happy teams and shipping? You should apply! https://t.co/KCaxzMbUEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @mtishy @andrew_jackman yeah, it's ottermatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc you don't think you're taking it whey too far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc now you're just milking it for all it's worth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @andrew_jackman can't help it; when I see a bad pun I flounder all about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @andrew_jackman don't try the fish, it's poisson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse there's this fear of elitism that goes with it, but as long as you're paying a fair price, I think everyone wins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse I found that too. Decided to spend more $ paying people to do the things that were less important for me to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pavsaund @aurynn @cerebralideas I don't understand it well enough to explain in &lt; 140 characters! But I have a draft article in the works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @missbassethorn @fauxparse @widdnz @mexisme @nz_brian everything in cycles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jedsoane if you have no luck, try @connectnz on Adelaide Rd. Their repair centre seems to have lots of spare parts &amp; they are super nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missbassethorn @fauxparse @sanityinc @widdnz @mexisme @nz_brian I'd put good money on a nice dumb terminal solution to pop up this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_brian @sanityinc @missbassethorn some are suggesting going with a 12" MacBook and using a server for heavy lifting. That's tempting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanityinc @nz_brian @missbassethorn not so important in an office context, but people seem pretty unhappy about the battery life too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse I gave up and went for Spotify/Google Play Music. Both work offline good. GPM allows uploads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse we need to have a talk. Friends don't let friends iTune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_brian most of the piece rests on the assumption that "business" drives the process. That's not a prerequisite of agile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatthechelz @kellective in any relationship, there had to be a baseline of goodwill. There ain't shit you can do if you don't receive that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatthechelz @kellective it's OK to be intolerant of intolerance, and it's OK not to be nice to people who aren't interested in being nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dhh talk about a conflict of interest that is only disclosed at the end of the piece, though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatthechelz I've seen people spend all their energy being friends with pricks, and having none left for their real friends. Or themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_brian while "Lineage" is a better name than "CyanogenMod", I guess they wanted to maintain that awkward mouthfeel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse * also works for backpacks and on crowded buses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericwastl thank you, thank you, thank you for AoC! I enjoyed it so much, and really appreciate the huge amount of work that went into it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shoelessgirl hate to say it but I'm with FiL on this one. Although I am aim for a minimum of two allsorts in my mouth at any time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shoelessgirl not being a douchebag matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_o_bot to reference them! I'll write some posts these holidays. Merry Christmas to you too! 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_o_bot I don't have anything written up, and even tho there are millions of posts about these topics, I don't like any of them enough 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanya be sure to leave 2017-Tanya a nice comment to make her feel better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse 'cond' statements also raise/throw/crash if nothing matches, whereas ruby 'case' doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shoelessgirl happy 3 months, SH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shoelessgirl couriers really are ripe for disruption, they frequently do a horrible job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soundasleep better than two hours after boarding closes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn so yes. There are always decisions to be made in any complex system, and without structure the loudest and most aggressive will rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanya if you have no luck on twitter, there are a bunch of webpack peoples on the JS.nz slack group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman we should just skip webpack next: copypaste libraries and write our code with single-letter variable names all in a single file.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tech world goes in circles. I'll be happy when we've moved π radians from this particular trend. https://t.co/yUZsjwOmFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew @rnz_news we used to be 18 hours ahead, now we're 9 months ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ootoovak I've not seen it before and would like to give it a try!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>