<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjharris85 @bbctrust Why not debate whether the BBC should spend public money on down-market programmes that should be funded by adverts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MP challenges Circuit of Wales bosses to let him publish tape of meeting https://t.co/CYfnev71Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Circuit of Wales bosses accused of false major exhibition claims https://t.co/uy3Lk1fsop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop press? Last words on the future of newspapers https://t.co/zVsZWmLqoh via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16-year-olds could soon get the vote in Welsh council elections https://t.co/ZJSEUhW0sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top heart surgeon writes about the allegations that ended his career https://t.co/acrGbo3Fll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzfilms Yes of course. martin.shipton@mediawales.co.uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanPlaid Many congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowShouldWeVote Good. I support this. Who signs a contract without knowing the terms?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despicable racism. Is this the UK we want? May to discuss how to boost US-UK migration with Trump, say sources https://t.co/vDdGV2NRjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arriva Trains Wales' profits 'too high', says economy secretary https://t.co/VkFtkmwbhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welsh Government accused of 'buying' Cardiff Airport passengers https://t.co/we8u3ezo2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Row as AM reveals Wales' top housing bosses salaries on Twitter https://t.co/1fnrEWQ511]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey62093861 @WalesOnline All will be revealed at 11am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit plan aims to 'rescue Welsh economy from potential disaster' https://t.co/IWdoCcKBJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WelshFoodie62 Because they want a prosperous Wales where people spell their hashtags correctly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueWales Whatever your views on this initiative it's neither clever or acceptable to allude to Carwyn Jones and Leanne Wood as Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carwyn Jones and Leanne Wood to unveil alternative Brexit plan https://t.co/0qCsFkRL03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hard facts behind hard Brexit  | Jean Quatremer https://t.co/7futfUkWSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaranHill @NathanGillMEP These are home-grown dissenters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanGillMEP They don't like him, Nathan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstrations to be held held in Wales against Donald Trump https://t.co/dMT9ULyRHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChickyEFL @WalesOnline I share your doubts. Sturgeon clearly doesn't think separate deal is possible or she wouldn't be talking indyref2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Adam_Price @WalesOnline The Welsh Government has stalled for months on an FoI I submitted about the project, I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carwyn Jones insists AMs will vote on the final Brexit deal https://t.co/axNu0GJpDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Adam_Price @WalesOnline Before that let's make sure the business model stacks up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Adam_Price @WalesOnline Scrutiny isn't a bad thing when taxpayers are being  asked to underwrite a project with £200m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey62093861 Bullfighting could certainly be described as an extreme sport. And it would attract protesters who'd spend money locally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davegjames1 The clue to my view is in the word "trivia". Journalism has a higher mission, and that should never be forgotten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davegjames1 Of course! But unlike much social media engagement, my tweet is not making a trivial point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If ever there was a time for mainstream media to end its obsession with social media trivia, it is now: https://t.co/BYFZVWIfmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey62093861 @WalesOnline They don't have bullfighting in Catalonia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down @WalesOnline We agree at last, Graham!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage over how Spanish firm won Circuit of Wales building contract https://t.co/n9HfOqsgsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down @Mae_Carson2 Silver linings aren't what they used to be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down @Mae_Carson2 All one package: low tax, low wages, deregulated employment market. Bonanza for the rich. Misery for the poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down @Mae_Carson2  I think it likely your former party will be seeking to downgrade workers' rights with US-style hire and fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down @Mae_Carson2 Badly paid jobs with poor conditions and insecurity. Not the route to a prosperous society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen__Lloyd Mostly true. Some papers support such a vision. No pay rise for Richard Desmond's employees at the Express for about 8 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen__Lloyd Me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrgraham_down Because it indicates a wish to make Britain an off-shore tax haven with low pay, worse employment rights and deregulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frightening consequences for working people: Hammond suggests UK without single market could become tax haven https://t.co/LhFEIlBS3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapharri Not so sure about that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to @BBCRadioWales to talk about the relationship between politicians and journalists on Sunday Supplement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrBGentry @baynes_simon The main political point in the article  is not Brexit but the exclusion of chefs by tighter immigration rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxpayer paid millionaire's Hilton Hotel stays in Cardiff https://t.co/3AjiKuzYkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who killed the curry house? Excellent piece about the political threat to "Indian" restaurants. https://t.co/tXMPiqRQTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan You referred to your own experience, Janet. I naturally assumed you had some experience of libel law. But yes, let's leave it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the latest political polling shows in Wales as Labour slumps https://t.co/v0wkSJI4R5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan Perhaps you haven't personal experience of blatant libel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan I'm talking about 'no win, no fee'. As I've said, if the defamation is that blatant the publication will quickly settle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan A friend of mine got it to work just like that in a case of blatant defamation. So it is an appropriate parallel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan @gezkirby It's a realistic view. Lawyers do not pass up the opportunity to make a certain buck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan @gezkirby There will always be lawyers keen to pursue cases of  "blatant injustice". And papers will soon settle if blatant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan @gezkirby If it's so blatant, you'd get a 'no win, no fee' deal from a lawyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gezkirby It would be state-sanctioned regulation of a kind not imposed on lawyers and doctors. But whatever your view on that, S40's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southwelljan Bias is surely an inevitable consequence of a free Press. How could it be otherwise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gezkirby Whatever your views on that, nothing justifies the blatant injustice of Section 40.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public interest journalism is crucial to democracy and worth fighting for https://t.co/ed8bYYkxqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Hain criticises knighthood for man who 'scuppered' barrage plans https://t.co/Heyv8EFR5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why striking train drivers deserve our support: I work for Southern rail. This is why I am striking https://t.co/bmmxq3jzhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I share this Tory donor's concerns for the economy -  and wonder how many of his workers voted Leave: https://t.co/C8aybZSZLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New attempt launched by Welsh Labour to ban smacking children https://t.co/4MVyNSrbfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orbiscat Many of the Brits in Spain have done more to create ghettoised migrant colonies than anyone living in the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspended Lib Dem denies inappropriate sexual behaviour to teen https://t.co/WDoIhtBzdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@essexoldbird @anoracyracen Good for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 Now you're getting semantic on me! I answered with an assertion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 I refer you to my previous answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2  Sometimes people in politics say things off the record to avoid backlash from those who disagree or want facts suppressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 Because they'd have people like you on their back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 Nothing poisonous about a realistic assessment of Labour's chances in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 Prescott only spoke about it  after Blair had left the scene. I understand why you, as a PR guy, don't like off the record!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 Journalists only knew because they'd been briefed. If political journalists stuck to what's on the record, you'd get Pravda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 No it wasn't wrong. We wouldn't know otherwise. Do you also think whistle blowers should be forced to give up anonymity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 For the same reason as Blair and Brown never went on the record about their mutual loathing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 I suspect you didn't like the content of the story and would have preferred one predicting Labour will storm to victory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 I disagree. It gives readers an insight into how political leaders - and other significant players - are really thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidnicholson2 If we just relied on bland, cheerleading press releases, political journalism would be immensely dull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_Fabricant @TelegraphNews The people of this country have had enough of experts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the outrage in the Daily Mail etc if Spanish legislators said Brits should be forced to learn Spanish before moving to Spain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arthurroy So Labour will be sweeping to victory across Wales in May and Corbyn will be in Downing Street in 2020? Dream on, Roy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour fears losing Cardiff majority in 'tough' council elections https://t.co/AEyz6I9F1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a release from Ukip telling me Neil Hamilton is opening an office in "Whitlands, Camarthenshire". A part of Wales I don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales Office attacked for spending £330,000 on spin doctors https://t.co/7c1s8i1cbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Berger has died at 90: a great thinker and writer. I was bowled over by Ways of Seeing as a student. https://t.co/sTufwn2lkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tory donor who opposed  Severn Barrage gets knighthood https://t.co/a5mkQfwNcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Welsh employers prosecuted for paying less than minimum wage https://t.co/W7vpp7l3qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_B_Evans Take your point, Adam. Technically, of course, the coalition would have been between two parties rather than Plaid and Kirsty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plaid Cymru's plan for coalition with Lib Dems:the untold story of the Senedd's most dramatic moment in 2016.  https://t.co/iFpgkSs8fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crischarliepaul @DeansOfCardiff @_Adam_Price @NeilUKIP @LeanneWood It was the splash in the Western Mail. And this piece is hardly anti-PC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The untold story of the Senedd's most dramatic moment in 2016 https://t.co/iFpgkSs8fV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Council senior officers' pay scandal 'to rise beyond £2.5m' https://t.co/LS808VynJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe thinks the UK is living on 'fantasy island' over Brexit deal https://t.co/xWTaBkaAi6 via @MetroUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay row chief executive's suspension lifted secretly in March https://t.co/jbNtLGnqlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FromSteveHowell @WalesOnline It hasn't gone online, I'm afraid. I think she kept her head down while in Cardiff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S4C documentary showcases relationship between children and elderly https://t.co/Oy2TMF7qkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economist digital strategy chief: We expect display advertising to have disappeared by 2025: https://t.co/lsfmaprmje - via:@pressgazette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Plaid Cymru leader Lord Elis-Thomas to back Labour https://t.co/yRtWbv3bgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrey62093861 @WalesOnline Are you on the top rate, Jeff? If so, you should hope for a Tory coup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales takes on income tax powers for first time ever https://t.co/pvjJ46yyLZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>