<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr better be steak and cheese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MataiGG @FlyAirNZ @YouTube haha, that's a blast from the past!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @FlyAirNZ. Leanne on flight NZ5092 is awesome! I got on the plane and realised I still had the rental car keys. She sorted it all out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmoney_nz Knicks will lose by 14!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically we need to get a big digger to demolish all the hills and mountains and then we'll get some sweet weather. https://t.co/MPKHsQRUTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive breaking sports news here. https://t.co/TDIJfThjlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone wants a sneak peak of what Hell looks like, just have a look in the family room on any of the @BluebridgeFerry boats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nelson has a good sense of humour. https://t.co/0QG3R3xyNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance-enhancing drugs optional? https://t.co/dDmb2yJz67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great stuff from @MeadowsRichard. Almost keen to get a parking fine to see if it will work! https://t.co/SWPEMOTZTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz definitely team @amyadamsMP !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hours after @theHoltBolt says she plans to run for the Greens in Helensville, @johnkeypm resigns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ drops a catch and Taylor says it was a regulation chance.
Aus drops a catch and Taylor says it was a very difficult chance. #ausvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin @tmurphyNZ @NZNationalParty maybe shows Labour not as good as pushing the right message?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ @Tim_Watkin officially Nats were saying they had no chance, behind scenes I imagine they were telling media Little's in trouble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ @Tim_Watkin I think it's shows the impressive ability of @NZNationalParty to play the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's one thing to make high tackles but murdering people is next level. https://t.co/e4pgRhrhJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EQKaikoura Hi. This information is not correct. There is no loss of service - https://t.co/VJtYz7gvPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt @ryanfoxgolfer what time does he tee off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love your work @LloydBurr https://t.co/qnoU1Ed4Vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@royceyoung @BenJStrang the bloke can't win. The media talk him up and then when he doesn't meet your expectations you knock him down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, that one just kept rolling. Thankfully the kids are asleep #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an update from @ChorusNZ re the state of the telecommunications network following the earthquake #eqnz https://t.co/LavKCiERdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, that was a decent aftershock just then  #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NZGetThru @WREMOinfo fellas, you might want to have a chat and agree on what the actual story is https://t.co/0veoJwDG0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@demelzaleslie haha. My youngest didn't even wake up! Holy shit, that was horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was big enough for me to scoop up the kids and get under the doorway. Hold shit! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah that was massive! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Smalley it's now 77%!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmoney_nz We need to go one year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Richie McCaw was at today's @AllBlacks game. Looks like McCaw's @Olympics curse is contagious! https://t.co/dAY6dCeulL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianODriscoll brilliant win mate. Looking forward to the rematch in a couple of weeks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @IrishRugby. That was a brilliant performance from your lads. Can't wait for the rematch in a couple of weeks. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Marshall:"The crowd are on their feet and so are players." I'm no expert but I think the players were already on their feet #NZLvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's an impressive return of serve from @MPI_NZ boss Martyn Dunne regarding @RFStew column https://t.co/wrrzSXr92s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @hamishandandy, you up for this Kiwi eating challenge? @TimaruHerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daveburgess13 @GabitesJason be careful. He's a dodgy bugger! And even more dodgy on the footy field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daveburgess13 @GabitesJason how do you lads know each other? Dave, I played footy with Gabs in Timaru. Gabs, I worked with Dave at the Dom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraging first half from the All Whites. Just lacking a bit of composure on the ball at times but they're playing well #MEXvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is bloody horrendous. Great work @kirsty_johnston https://t.co/9a0pyv9hMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @GuyHeveldt  haha, I get the feeling you have had that photo stored and ready for use for a while!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt oh agree with you completely. The ex journo in me feels a bit embarrassed with some of the coverage today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt tough one for him. He was asked directly by media. If he refused comment he would've probably been labelled as backing Smith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good perspective here from @mattrichens https://t.co/eeoGCyeg6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuffSport and if you're going to name Smith's partner, why don't you name the witness?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @NZStuffSport is it really necessary to name Aaron Smith's partner in the story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshThomson @7DaysTv3 @JeremyCorbett or you could do a special version of Yes Minister - Yes Dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshThomson you've got to get your old man on @7DaysTv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshThomson @UrzilaCarlson brilliant! That toast combination sounds bloody horrendous, though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ @RadioLIVENZ he had to front. if he didn't, you probably would have written a column demanding he resign for not fronting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways my brother's teacher once put the class in a horse float to take them on camp. That was pretty normal on the West Coast though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fibre ignites White Island tour company" https://t.co/ZwxPq7G8rO by @NathanBeaumont on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one hell of a headline https://t.co/dfkmKCOcc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pass from Coles was a bit high. Come on, son. #NZLvRSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Ardie actually ground that? Looked like he grounded before line and then held up over the line. #NZLvRSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan @Primetv_NZ @CrowdGoesWildNZ easily my favourite show. It's been underrated for years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LloydBurr So she was actually sitting in the audience but was still too busy to speak?! Brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LloydBurr You should OIA her diary for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is ridiculously good.  https://t.co/syIP8BSuSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndiBeeeee @SHCSport that's an absolute screamer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LloydBurr @interislander Rather them than me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An @interislander ferry leaving the harbour. That's going to be a hell of a ride! https://t.co/GEDKOkcRS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have snow in Churton Park!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus media: Can you rule out Elvis planted the bug?
Cops: Not commenting till after investigation.
Aus media headline: Did Elvis plant bug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehancasinader @avancenz @SundayTVNZ that was a great story, Jehan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[September 4, 2016. The day @NZStuff jumped the shark. https://t.co/NDmm3LJ0hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former coach who couldn't improve the Warriors offers advice about how to improve the Warriors. https://t.co/TFUTyc4GY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the @NZWarriors win tomorrow they qualify for the @NRL playoffs. Oh yeah, that's right ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealEricYoung @guywilliamsguy @Andrew_Mulligan I don't have Sky but signed up to Fanpass but annoyingly that didn't include pop up channels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeborahMTNZ Hi Deborah. Happy to look into any issues if you want to send me some details - Nathan.beaumont@chorus.co.nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust Ireland to use a potato analogy to explain the Apple tax issue. https://t.co/iaAoDlo82h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Tim Southee can come in and smash a quick 300, we have a bloody good chance of winning this @BLACKCAPS #savnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKCAPS are 7/4. "New Zealand are in big trouble now," the commentator says. Yeah because at 7/3 we were looking good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't think there's much chance of any cricket today. https://t.co/LMMCdPNt8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way the @AllBlacks are dominating the @qantaswallabies line out, you'd think it was the Wallabies' room that was bugged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr that was bizarre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timaz Hard. You beauty @TomWalshSP #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt @AndrewGourdie reminds me of this one Shane Thompson had against South Africa https://t.co/82lcc6xB97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boxcarfred any idea how much funding the swimmers get? Feels like they've had a golden ride for a long time despite poor results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boxcarfred if rowing is under pressure, Swimming NZ must be shitting themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Y7News @DHughesy why did they put decorations on her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone please make sure Richie McCaw doesn't go to the rowing today. #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could watch this all day.  https://t.co/M5v5tSBbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan @cucomiris don't let them get to you Mulls. You're doing a cracking job over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That American goalkeeper could learn a thing or two about grace in defeat from @ValerieAdams84. You're a hell of an athlete, Valerie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody oath! https://t.co/yXaWkUWhS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How good would these Fiji boys be if played played in the NRL? Their offloads would create havoc.  #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie @prestonjscott the reaction to that if he got the job would be brilliant! Appears there has been no obvious succession plan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie @NewshubSport @nz7s @NewshubNZ he's been great but now's the time for a refresh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richirvine @Sportsfreakconz part of me has always quietly liked the thought of Fiji winning gold anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @richirvine I'm not sure why everyone's so upset. We've been average all year and this has just been a continuation of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been up watching the Olympics for an hour. Just enough time to see us choke in the equestrian and lose to Japan in the rugby. Back to bed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan thought you did a great job interviewing Lauren Boyle. Could have been one of the most awkward interviews ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That title is all thanks to Mark Hammett. #HURvLIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ @skysportnz thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ @skysportnz thanks Charlotte. Will channels 3 and 4 show live coverage of NZ's main medal hopes at the games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @skysportnz. Just wondering if the Olympics will be shown on Fan Pass (including pop up channels)? Keen to give you some money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How Ultra-Fast Broadband is helping boost the tourism experience in Queenstown" https://t.co/CmRN6bAaTB by @NathanBeaumont on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr we're worried we'll get caught having sex in the Warehouse carpark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr I'd be more embarrassed about wearing that tie.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>