<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubinReport RICHARD SPENCER. ON THE RUBIN REPORT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @glennbeck GET RICHARD SPENCER ON YOUR SHOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nontolerantman "the rational bit of my mind takes over" dear god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 Was definitely expecting either a huge dick or Bud Dwyer killing himself at the end of this video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 rofl drumpf will be impeached for sure after this ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone ends up getting killed by a Leftist protestor, the blood is on the media's hands for literally making people think he is Hitler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Left really shouldn't start advocating violence. They will be eternally blown the fuck out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because Steve Bannon and the Alt-right have been responsible for so many terrorist attacks. The left isn't sending… https://t.co/1kTgTPaMgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia literally has 3 million tents open to be used for refugees, but Trump is criticized for the #MuslimBan… https://t.co/SQNMMFb7j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not all Muslims are violent!" The fag shouted as he hurled to the ground after being thrown from a roof top in Iran.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 lol must be crazy buzzed brother haha (jelly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A society full of conflicting beliefs and motivations will never lead to growth and success. Multiculturalism is a lie. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do me a favor. Go ahead and just kys. https://t.co/FbgaLB5VdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump only uses his @POTUS account to retweet things he's said on the OG account. Hilarious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweets from the leader of the women's march. Great representative for a movement! https://t.co/GRRr73ehL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winning hurts so much. I can barely take it anymore! https://t.co/9FYAzeBOXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god. He didn't wave. This fazzshciszt dictator must be stopped! https://t.co/qPl3Ltidvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kantbot2000 is that your glorious mug in the video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PepeMindset The communist Chinese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@occdissent @MailOnline Imagine actually thinking Hillary will still be alive in 2020]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In terms of productivity, @realDonaldTrump is setting the bar VERY high for one of his children in 2024 when they take office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 Dear god using kettlebells is easily the most degenerate and faggy form of fitness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotJaredWyand Your power level definitely seems to be the same as the real Jared Wyand's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PizzaPartyBen @mexico not in the section you're being sent to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this rate, I'm fully expecting Trump to unlock the secrets of the universe through the harnessing of alien technology by April.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something something 1939 Jews holocaust 6 million Trump is Hitler https://t.co/lY3UOAE8Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never seen a president follow through on campaign promises like Trump has and he's only been in office for a few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump is signing executive orders to ban immigration from 7 Muslim countries. Libshits on suicide watch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT HE'S ACTUALLY DOING IT https://t.co/RAV8LFir4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneriderMA @hunterswogg Perfectly articulated my same thoughts over the past few days. I predict more violence ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTLDS By far, the best avi in the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewQuackson why is bugs bunny holding a flintlock pistol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;Being so mentally ill that you claim to be a feminist yet you are led by a women who represents true oppression of women.
 #IMarchWithLinda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias not at least for the next 8 years, thankfully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The patriarchy built western civilization. I kinda like western civilization. https://t.co/qdWsrYz6Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CantStumpTrump1 The responses lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I receive a compliment almost every time I wear my #MAGA hat around campus. University of Alabama is super #based]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical leftists (communists) are forcing any moderates that still exist to the right. They have no strategy. Very stupid people. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Or on the other side of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realBeckyBarnes @Vicky_Raughn Thank god they didn't though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CantStumpTrump1 When the choppers are ready.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagicRoyalty Most exercise he's had in centuries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Press Secretary @seanspicer absolutely tore into the #LyingPress today. A thing of beauty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicroAnimeGod @BreitbartNews If that's Similar Web, it usually over estimates significantly. Probably lower visits than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Some of your fans also like Richard Spencer. You're eating your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zanting @MicroAnimeGod I'm afraid if any of that pussy was grabbed your hand would immediately rot off from the highly acidic concentration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hyenas on the Left keep biting a lion that's about to wake up and tear the fucking shit out of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #WomensMarch was the single largest gathering of people with mental disorders in our world's history! Breaking glass ceilings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing the #WomensMarch actually accomplished was getting some land whales to burn a few calories for the f… https://t.co/iOmxiAOtiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Props to all the women too busy taking care of their families and providing for their children to participate in an idiotic #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leftists can't understand the world unless they look at it through the lens of Harry Potter, Game of Thrones, or St… https://t.co/uG75OigrDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauren_Southern 
&gt;balding
&gt;no jawline 
&gt;weak bone structure
&gt;probably a massive pussy

Definitely suffering from Low-T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanmcmurry Who said it couldn't be done? All they did was walk. A meaningless task was completed! Girl power!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$20 says 90% of the people at the #WomensMarch are lonely, self-loathing, blue haired, cat ladies that have no sense of belonging in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #Inauguration violence is this bad, I can't imagine what is going to go down when the wall construction begins. There will be blood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealHotCool will drumpf ever recover?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone shot outside of Milo event in Seattle. Leftists don't understand the "peaceful" transition of power. Completely anti-American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purplehullpea We have the power in this country, so it looks like you have to for the next 4 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Spencer is going to get even more PR from that punch and more people will learn about the alt-right. The left loses again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 you must be the guy always posting blacked shit on pol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being this big of a pussy. https://t.co/sBmqIm4tDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROUND UP THE CATTLE https://t.co/5Jumranz8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The violence we're seeing from the Left reminds me of an animal striking &amp; flailing around moments before it's death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicroAnimeGod If the Left continues this violence, they will awake an authoritarian sleeping giant. Plz let it happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I unironically support going authoritarian on the degenerates wreaking havoc on DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAHAHA dear god what is wrong with these creatures https://t.co/DQVlF3v0gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run them over. https://t.co/O9D1LSFE6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theneedledrop Very false. Good try though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The levels of Nationalism we're hitting with #Inauguration speech shouldn't even be possible. So beautiful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PRESIDENT DONALD JOHN TRUMP #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramzpaul A lot of American southerners are Irish, so that explains that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow how will Trump ever recover from a deranged hobo dancing in his underwear? https://t.co/BCTSjtNE4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 holy shit I'm in pain rn from cringe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump did get killed, the pendulum would swing even further right. A nationalist movement would rise that would really terrify the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen so many people calling for his assassination, but the shit fucks at Twitter won't do anything. They agree with the message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm confident if Donald Trump actually got assassinated many Leftists would celebrate. That's how mentally unstable they've become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit Donald Trump mouthed the words to All Star by Smash Mouth  hahaha he's unbelievable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He isn't wrong. https://t.co/xYTzFqmkAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump now inside the Lincoln Memorial staring at Honest Abe. Probably thinking back on the debate beat down he delivered to Hillary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battle Hymn is being sung while fireworks go off above Trump and his family at the Lincoln memorial. I can't handle the patriotism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It really doesn't get more patriotic than Toby Keith playing Courtesy of the Red, White, and Blue at the Inauguration concert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My President is Black but in less than 24 hours, he's going to be this white MAD MAN https://t.co/1555eDRYy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired: Low energy Joe Biden memes

Wired: High voltage Mike Pence memes https://t.co/w0CVyx8yxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IhaveAIDSIRL Wow you're a lot more crippled than I expected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewQuackson Make internment camps great again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 wow chill tune! Totally going to play this tomorrow right before I stick a fork in a power outlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It honestly doesn't get any more faggy than this. Get the jumper cables @mike_pence https://t.co/cAFLQXidU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine thinking Obama has actually been a successful president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiritBen @DawgsBiteMag "Misogynistic POS" God, how cringe. White knighting over women's basketball players lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhat concerned Trump will be assassinated, tbh fam. Hated by so many violent people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealHotCool Can confirm. We're the Nazis. Source: I'm a Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit. Apparently some black people expect whites to pay $$$reparations$$$ to them for slavery. Better start saving up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incelbonaparte All of these people in the class will be whining in a few years about being unable to find a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statue looks straight out of Stalin's Soviet Union. https://t.co/yATlun5O3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyAodh Thank you for saying invaders instead of "refugees".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CantStumpTrump1 Solution: Put them all in labor camps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTLDS Ask them why blacks are better than whites at sports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leftists are literally the most stupid people on the planet. "Accept everything CNN and the Young Turks tell you! Question NOTHING!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbanks420lol2 you should probably kys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SisypheanSperg HISPANICS ARE A RACE OF PEACE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>