<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@libertytarian What do you think about current situation with Iran? Isn't this counter-productive to peace?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being honest might not get you a lot of friends, but it will get you the right ones."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeAnnMcAdoo Someone told my husband in a Facebook group that he is going to work for you guys!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcGrawDC LOL how much time have you spent looking into it? There's some interesting stuff out there. That's all I am saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've really reached the point at which people are condoning a violent  riot because it stopped someone from saying things they don't like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcGrawDC @washingtonpost I don't think BO is who/what the public thinks he is. I have no idea if it's real or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcGrawDC @washingtonpost lol well recently there was an independent analysis that the bc was fake.. but who knows!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AGAIN The @washingtonpost had to "amend" their #FakeNews What is going to happen when stuff really hits the fan and… https://t.co/MFG7MuYo5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PressOn with even more #FakeNews https://t.co/kGrHJiC0WU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahouraxo @maria_engstrom Yea so many of these people need to take a seat! Pandering hypocrites!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump NO WAR! This has been going on since 1953, let's make PEACE with them! PEACE PEACE PEACE, thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't believe which president said this. Take a guess.
#ThursdayThought 
#Muslimban 
#nomuslimban 
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/8zhYNQdjwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMZ It was called African American History Month last year too. See this from 2016. Don't be #FakeNews :) https://t.co/77fZRPgR7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyMcFLY I meet friends in fb mom groups.. meet in person, its like dating, sometimes u hit it off, others not so much...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B_BNKS Me too! She did a very brave thing. I have been following the REAL Syria story. We have been completely lied to and it's sick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of these people in Congress or in the press have any desire to deal with the facts, so they attack her. Disgus… https://t.co/0YUCeyENrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Almijisti @ggreenwald @ericgeller Of course she is. Can't expose the war profiteers. The press is pathetic on this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @wjbk Girl this is #FakeNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeypurple yup. Both are propaganda. You have to sift thru the noise. Watch press conference yourself. Notice all the speculation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Maybe if they started asking more important questions. Front row "journalists" being petty for a sound bite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PressOn with your #FakeNews I mean come on people!!! https://t.co/91aMhLOJLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PressOn with your #FakeNews https://t.co/66YPES2qIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kppotatoes I think he knows, the question is will he be able to do anything about it. He's mentioned it a number of times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Flynn is putting Iran on notice: BEYONCE IS PREGNANT WITH TWINS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh these @WhiteHouse press conferences make me want to tear my hair out... I am going to come up with a list of questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmad75 @RealAlexJones @infowars I have no idea what you're talking about. I'm referring to Nobel Peace Prize winners earning their prize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmad75 @RealAlexJones @infowars I blocked that guy. 0 tolerance for that crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmchairBoxing @RealAlexJones @infowars LOL I'm a big fan I just don't want Trump to be another Obama.. He's up against a lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexJones @infowars Come on Alex, let's wait and see how he handles Saudi Arabia v. Yemen, Syria, etc before we give him a peace prize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyMetz Where were you guys last night? Rerun? Without warning? I was crushed!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanBiz42 @ggreenwald @ericgeller It's just a matter of putting it all together. I've seen DOD documents, pictures, news clips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanBiz42 @ggreenwald @ericgeller Well, now we're arming the Kurds against ISIS.. I just wish it would be exposed, the proof is there..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanBiz42 @ggreenwald @ericgeller Yup.. root of the problem that just isn't getting nearly enough coverage. I need to switch careers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@douglasj1894 @TulsiGabbard I do not do politics on my show, I just play music and talk about pop culture. I'm just passionate about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @ericgeller when will press start talking about who has been arming these terrorists? That is the root of the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zaroj6420 @Hill4America @HillaryClinton Yes we do.. then we send our military to die fighting them. It's so outrageous and sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @adamjohnsonNYC Which other views? Should she meet w ISIS? Al Nusra? Al Qaeda? Who else is there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin The FSA is aligned w ISIS and AQ among others.. do a hit piece on  that instead of @TulsiGabbard for telling the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NBCThisisUs WHERE ARE YOU??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timand2037 @amnestyusa @VanessaBeeley @sahouraxo I saw his video.. where is he now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kkcfly1 @HillaryClinton I couldn't resist.. these people have the audacity to act like they care. We know what's been going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blondenfun1 @fifi_j @VanessaBeeley Yes I follow her and many others trying to tell the truth. This has got to stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hill4America @HillaryClinton No, I don't. They wouldn't vote for wars in Libya or Syria so we armed terrorists instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanSMaxwell Sorry I don't understand what you are saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hill4America @HillaryClinton Yea people don't like the ones brave enough to tell the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hill4America @HillaryClinton They're all in it together baby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Your policy destroyed the countries on that travel ban list. Please, take a seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Shouldn't you be asking why the US/UK trained and armed the FSA which is now ISIS, Al Qaeda, and Al Nusra?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MIG29_ Please help me understand, is US now helping Syrian Arab Army or sending more help to "moderate rebels"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats helped to block Americans from getting cheaper drugs from Canada, so @potus is telling the drug companies… https://t.co/KGwbP7B4kR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when your owner pledges loyalty to one political party. What could possibly go wrong? https://t.co/23zGrlxqIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's because most of the media isn't honest. https://t.co/23zGrlxqIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII I haven't read them but I see it. It's dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @realDonaldTrump @POTUS for keeping your promise. https://t.co/NOtfAdyvhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kkingjr17 @almahobson @PressSec @POTUS LOL maybe 100. And they ask the same petty loaded questions 3 times  to get a sound bite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffMontes5 when was this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_seaman But what do you think he is going to do about the root of the problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL someone didn't think this through... https://t.co/3hSx5eBWT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mom2momswapmeet SNOW HERE! SNOW! Ugh... We need to move back!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Monday from the GW Parkway! 
#alternativefacts 😂 @KellyannePolls @PressSec https://t.co/HeExXBRJHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichS2012 I will listen to it today, haven't heard it yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will join the protests when we start directing them at our wars that have actually killed thousands of Muslims. #NoMoreWar #nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most powerful sign of the
#MuslimBanProtest #Peace
End regime change wars @realDonaldTrump @potus… https://t.co/LZ5keWxZdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefanMolyneux @Reuters Do you think this will work? What about sanctions on those countries ppl in Yemen are starving. SA is vicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSwann_ are you going to infowars??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems to be lost on a lot of people right now. It's really scary. https://t.co/RUQYlGvPsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmorGaia I've seen the pipeline come up a lot from various sources but that was a good article. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what desperation looks like when your lies fall apart. Smear the messenger, ignore the truth. Gotta run, Pu… https://t.co/SD9V18IkkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all of the people fighting this battle for truth to be told. #Truth#Syria #SyriaTruth https://t.co/sZGmopPBWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet I am not a "propaganda site" I am a wife, mother, professional, concerned citizen, and human. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet I don't know if they are fake, but I think they realized after they tweeted by truth that it doesn't fit THEIR propaganda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechcnd Yes when I started to wake up 5yrs ago it was very powerful.. but now all makes sense..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechcnd Thank you. The abuse is ridiculous but I am not going to stew in silence anymore. People need to know the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechcnd Thank you. He's on video speaking at Harvard about it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet Start there. It's a documentary that was also on PBS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet I focus on facts, not name calling. Enjoy your Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet @hrw @KenRoth HRW held a fundraising dinner in Saudi Arabia. Watch "Saudi Arabia Uncovered" on Netflix. It's very sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet @KenRoth From HRW war propaganda NGO? Really, I've done plenty of research from sources not funded by war profiteers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet @KenRoth Try harder. Peace to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not be a war propagandist, I reject your lies and wish you peace. #Syria #SyriaTruth #StopArmingTerrorists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet @KenRoth You mean the White Helmets who hang out with Al Qaeda? Pictures prove it, Google it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvonison I said nothing to justify the "ban", I shared an article about where the list came from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvonison He didn't pick the countries, DHS did before he was in office. Bloomberg and others made it about business ties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvonison Obviously not. The article is in response to the stories about how Trump chose the countries based on where he does business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvonison The list was determined by the Dept of Homeland in 2016. There was already a list. That's all I am saying, and that is a fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaTHuber I respect our military and their sacrifices, but I am anti-war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmorGaia @ReginaA1981 @MLKstudios @AllahamRima @TulsiGabbard Lots of ppl say that. https://t.co/gBI4GGGSEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amigorivas @GeorgeTakei @BBGVisualData Read this! https://t.co/bV2x8xaqmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting article about the #Muslimban and why @POTUS chose the countries on the list... or did he? https://t.co/bV2x8xaqmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichS2012 yes I am a dj.. tweeting politics bc I care abt the future for my kids. Want peaceful world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeypurple There is a massive propaganda war against him, like he doesn't do enough crazy on his own. I just don't trust it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowardsMidnight Lots of links on my timeline. US peace activists went to Syria. Ben Swann has done videos. Lots of info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeypurple @RoguePOTUSStaff What makes you think they're real? Anyone can make up a Twitter acct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowardsMidnight @RoguePOTUSStaff Lots of info out there. Just not publicized bc press protects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowardsMidnight @RoguePOTUSStaff admitted by Obama state dept many times that weapons end up in terrorist hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowardsMidnight @RoguePOTUSStaff many independent journalists have been there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowardsMidnight @RoguePOTUSStaff A US Congresswoman and a VA state senator both went to Syria and said same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @RoguePOTUSStaff retweeted my note about Tulsi and #Syria and then deleted it. #FakeWhistleblowers and no way to verify it's real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YnotKingme @almahobson @PressSec @POTUS have u seen this "rogue potus" account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasJefUnit99 @FashNova so there are US troops in Syria?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>