<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans face anger over Obamacare repeal during town halls https://t.co/Tm6iUl8pXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredibly insensitive and inhumane. An official calling for the killings of college students has no place in publi… https://t.co/20rTo88gC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOP will likely use distractions to hide their efforts to dismantle social and financial protection safety nets. https://t.co/nsmpo2QVBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters in Annapolis urge Hogan to denounce Trump’s travel ban, nominees https://t.co/kuaXTOykAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an important but underdiscussed subject. https://t.co/oACRwMQNeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NormOrnstein There's 1 more element 2 strategy: call on base 2 rise up if elite don't toe line. Base has private… https://t.co/aKdroPn1Tr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#flint Mi is a crime scene. Residents r victims of coverup &amp; discimination. Govt must compensate families 4 their p… https://t.co/IpembjzALB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neither does @gop at the moment. They have responsibility to step up on investigations of conflicts, Russians, etc. https://t.co/c4tbpfwifA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @Beyonce. We are all happy for your happiness. Many blessings. https://t.co/vhAbhleXhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given deep inadequacies of most Trump nominees, isn't it curious that the anti-Devos effort seems 2 b most successf… https://t.co/xd8gbCNSrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald the Menace https://t.co/ip1rLYkeZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GOP only believes in local control when it suits them: Texas Cuts Funding Over Austin ‘Sanctuary City’ Policy https://t.co/Pl7qvWFQdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our nation's leaders should understand that US military is most diverse org n r country. Soldiers of all races, faiths, genders, &amp; b-liefs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 Yet Trump already n campaign mode so @democrats have right 2 d-lay Neil Gorsuch 4 years @senschumer #SCOTUS https://t.co/CbIU77fV0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 @SenateMajLdr says he followed @joebiden idea of SCOTUS candidates not b-Ing considered during reelection. https://t.co/4JjzxjC6w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comstock a no-show at weekend town halls https://t.co/5hfu2OPbvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team building a wall inside National Security Council https://t.co/aY9mpvn0jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats 'deeply troubled' by 'racist, bigoted' views shared by Trump education appointees https://t.co/9NMucPLpGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Trump distracts, Russia carries out the next step in its strategic plan. https://t.co/h2cU5dCaJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dric_Hutcherson don't ask! They've got all kinds of stuff lined up for the lambs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Supreme Court pick founded club called 'Fascism Forever' https://t.co/VdrWxKNixz via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jury convicts man who wounded black Minnesota protesters | Daily Mail Online https://t.co/1si40BNCP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He thought it would be a good plot line in his drama. https://t.co/WOpSCsNPLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly right. https://t.co/oAwfwcyFks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil #GoredUs, the Nominee for a #Stolen Seat #StolenSCOTUS https://t.co/DsQus0fex3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#war must b outlawed. #mikhailgorbachev #poverty #military #armsrace #nuclear #environment… https://t.co/3WjRi2i3mZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is my #birthday! Happy to receive b-day love from my A1 team. @ Washington, District of… https://t.co/YX9VnkX1sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And descendants of natives and people held in bondage... https://t.co/WELiUi1KY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what racialized police repression looks like: https://t.co/iPOtd4oCWT You can b right but still b treated wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call @SenFeinstein 2day &amp; ask her 2 stop the Sessions confirmation. Dems who green light him will enable repression. https://t.co/kSxDkwGC1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like the  much ballyhooed separation of powers &amp; system of checks &amp; balances has been Trumped.… https://t.co/VZDJH9i7TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Boys Scouts announcement was pretext. FYI https://t.co/dF58ICwuBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the timing is suspicious; instead of being altruistic, it is meant to inflame passions &amp; set pretext 4 crac… https://t.co/ybccdfGi7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this not surprising? https://t.co/fL0Ja9GFq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was thought that Jared would b alpha male n admin &amp; that he would make everything ok, especially for those n his… https://t.co/dkEZLhcapd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Succeeding Against the Odds Can Make You Sick https://t.co/ZvMb9tAsgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCardin @ChrisVanHollen please vote against Price, Sessions, Devos and Mnuchin.  Need 2 b advocates for mainsteet, not Wall Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid 4 by Racists R Us! How can the same crowd claiming 2 care about  the life of a fetus, b in bed with the @NRA,… https://t.co/QPLmwRkeCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid 4 by Ed Privatizers R Us. Another Conservative bait &amp; switch. Devos not equipped 2 lead r nations schools. 1st… https://t.co/GyNgFuowf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenatorSchumer @senatorwarren Devos, Price, Sessions must all b defeated. We need 1st string, not backbenchers n… https://t.co/OdIEC71Swb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenatorSchumer .@SenatorWarren Please stand strong &amp; resist pick seeking 2 make discrimination legal again &amp; outl… https://t.co/cqmwVYgAfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This effort will result n hardship 4 low income, lack of access 2 care 4 those in need, less care 4 those n need, &amp;… https://t.co/U8ina1WRg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best political talk shows on television. #dontsleep https://t.co/KbHNGwoGf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's his nature. https://t.co/BgpJWWq2xc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True BUT his inane tweets r often cover 4 other actions of consequences. Media must avoid burying real stories by f… https://t.co/1HgDQZkE7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon is Trump's brain, just as Rove was Bush's. https://t.co/16w5Qk9u2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the point. It was strong but ppl couldn't process/hear it because of the aforementioned reasons. https://t.co/I1nhI4VLy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not N his nature 2. He will insist on his position despite evidence, truth or opposition. #alternativefacts… https://t.co/jpgx13Ntwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid for by Racists R Us. Every time u C this ad, call it out. @SenatorSessions must b defeated. https://t.co/fUIegQr0PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is only true if you redefine "disaster" 2 mean "success". The meaning of words mean nothing 2 this crowd. https://t.co/GUHVUKbdac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We r n the midst of at least 2 constitutional crises. We can't forget massive conflicts of interest. Role of Russia… https://t.co/7Bqr6o7LZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the start of a Cold War btween @realDonaldTrump and @GOP realists? Who else n GOP will stand up to the Titu… https://t.co/uYGJ3RiUc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true. My forebears were brought here by force. My claim on this nation has been bought &amp; paid 4 by their sacrifi… https://t.co/hGoYRSPjWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can America hear what @ladygaga has 2 say? They will try 2 muzzle her. Seems like @NFL crowd can dish it but can't… https://t.co/UcTp7y41oM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, @BarackObama was still in the #Caribbean when the EO was signed. No blame 2 b assigned. #pathetic https://t.co/WgF6Q3fEWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender bias, Clinton hatred, &amp; @realdonaldTrump media monopoly caused many ppl to tune @HillaryClinton out during c… https://t.co/ikymJCzp9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep or pulling an all nighter? https://t.co/spTVqcbPXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must show up 4 each other. https://t.co/w843V8YpGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would b called a social promotion n anyone's book. Who u know, not what u know helps many favored sons. @NFL… https://t.co/kT7ogJOaA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressional impeachment authority is only strategy to unseat an incompetent prez. Will @GOP lead if necessary? Serious doubts remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump will alienate so many Americans he will have to call on Russians to help him. Is it called a coup if they r invited n?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put that 2gether with empty diplomatic posts &amp; marginalization of joint chiefs &amp; you've got yourself a nice grand c… https://t.co/fF7cPlXBHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must remember the end goal is 2 make it nonprofitable to discriminate. Protests must continue. https://t.co/nXWgSqXBUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So they weren't the Greatest Generation after all? No sense in romanticizing bigotry and hate even by ppl who lived… https://t.co/FLKbeP0Ncj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want 2 destroy #NewDeal &amp; #greatsociety programs 2 benefit corporations, undermine economic security, &amp; promot… https://t.co/SpSt03aJOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what leadership looks like. https://t.co/PKIwhQcFNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These little cuties were giving lessons in #protest #democracy. Never 2 early 2 start training… https://t.co/Jp7zcoxcR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “Attack on ObamaCare is Blow to Civil Rights, Health Equity” https://t.co/phGthRXf42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “Attack on ObamaCare is Blow to Civil Rights, Health Equity” https://t.co/lnoQjtHFrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PaulRyan &amp; @SenMcconnell will have a special place in history 4 their role in this disaster. https://t.co/PMHHgN5flc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bloodless coup can happen if ppl responsible 4 military apparatus r kept n dark &amp; manipulated. https://t.co/r03FcHzqPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White nationalist added 2 NSC &amp; another set 4 @TheJusticeDept, doesn't take genius 2 figure out what comes next. https://t.co/wvWey93HOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughable conclusion since the ban excludes many countries that have exported terrorism. The country is less safe t… https://t.co/lzca0q4Iyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One has to wonder if that is by design. https://t.co/jrkZGIOfwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman Linked to 1955 Emmett Till Murder Tells Historian Her Claims Were False https://t.co/YcNxpIU27v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I said earlier. All law enforcement agencies have been infiltrated, including homeland security. https://t.co/4cV7BJdrvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was my friend Cassandra Butts. https://t.co/XS44lydKHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump is Bane from the Dark Knight? https://t.co/svrOFMqM8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought he meant us too. https://t.co/YfblY7b39r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately there are 2 many male white nationalists on top of her who are willing 2 overturn. https://t.co/yDnuhiK8CU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. https://t.co/3bx76ewqDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the point. #inclusionrevolution Time 2 stand. If u care about ur kids, this is an obligation u can't ignore. https://t.co/iD51sF3Q2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to launch #InclusionRevolution. R nation cannot b left at mercy of people who romanticize pre-Civil Rights America (aka the Stone Age)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieGripne #InclusionRevolution #Impact2020 https://t.co/qcNRB5T8Vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First they came 4 the immigrants, and I didn't speak out b/c I wasn't an immigrant, then they came 4 the Muslims... https://t.co/sxmUyU7Nue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Niemöller: "First they came for the Socialists..." https://t.co/sxmUyU7Nue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump knows something about defamation; chooses 2 pursue truth when it suits him; Melania wins suit: https://t.co/VBP5y2BfvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great 2 no some Republicans r operating n real world; Obamacare helps their constituents; Repeal has political risk: https://t.co/tNPFmWd8wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much appreciated! https://t.co/QHelT5YQtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when a global superpower places @realDonaldTrump at the helm of its ship? Support 4 multipolar world o… https://t.co/Ouh7AwqmfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx4 shout out Corey! https://t.co/MgkKmV1YIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Innovators Shaping Atlanta’s Black Startup Community https://t.co/Ogai9qTXKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom of press is under attack. Repression is part of Authoritarian playbook 4 consolidating power. So is voter s… https://t.co/iwmwMxm4hB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what excellence looks like. https://t.co/u68zs4tUa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@potus may b unfit to lead our military given his inability 2 see that Americans r of all races, ethnicity, genders, religions &amp; party ID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm worried about US military, our most diverse and integrated institution. Soldiers of different races &amp; faiths will bcome alienated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sends a horrible message to US allies and to American Muslims, many of whom serve in the military. Consequence… https://t.co/6pzkv3THH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paid for by Racists R Us. https://t.co/euolDGm008]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, in Post-Obama Era, Aggressively Woos Republicans https://t.co/gcbS4dif4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepMiaLove just gave a #BlackLivesMatter speech at an anti-abortion rally. Many #MAGAs in the crowd were not clapping.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>