<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkgolder @Newsflare I'll email now. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkgolder @Newsflare That's great too, what's the best way to explain to you what we do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sumayaali3 Hi, Did you film this video? I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voiceb0xx Hi, I'm with @newsflare. Can we have a quick chat in DM about your video? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkgolder @Newsflare Can you follow me back so I can send a direct message? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PumpsNKicks Hi Belle, I'm an editor at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about your #Bodegaprotest video. Can we talk in DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkgolder Hi Murray, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get int ouch about your video of waves on Cornwall, can we talk in DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chellcia5 Hi April, I'd like to have a quick chat about this video. Can you follow me so I can send you a DM? I'm with @newsflare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtrushkowsky Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Can we have a quick chat on DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ptbp_ Hi Ibrahim, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about this vid. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KunzeFilms Hi Kevin, I work at @newsflare and we're interested in working with you UC Berkeley video. Can we talk in DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hj94personal Hi, did you shoot this video? Can we talk about it in DM? I'm with @newsflare. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svbsvg hu Gus, did you shoot this video? Can we talk about it in DM? I'm with @newsflare. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_gregoryy Hi Ben, I'm with @newsflare can we have a quick chat about your video on DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenicoleraviv Hi Nicole, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about your Clinton video. Can you follow me so I can DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeygak Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a quick chat abut this video. Please can you follow me so I can DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentZwerneman Hi Brent, I'm with @newsflare, can we have a quick chat about this video please? My DMs are open. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyalto Hi Jimmy, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about the video you posted earlier. Can we talk on DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@satanseyebrows Hi Charlotte, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about your Trump video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Npflynn71 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about this video. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrewTae Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to get int ouch about your dancing video. Please can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDisneyChef Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordenTeo Hi Jorden, I work at @newsflare and we'd like to get in touch with Mark Annett-Stuart,can you possibly give me his contact in DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mimi1596 Hi Meaghan, I'm a journalist with @newsflare, could we have a quick chat about the video on DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xoshantsox Hi, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about this clip with you. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisBrogan Hi Chris, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this video. Pls can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staywithzoe Hi Zoe, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to get int ouch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Lewington Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Pls can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlantSci74 Hi Jess, I would like to contact you on behalf of @newsflare about this video. Can we have a chat on DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@telpierce Hi I work at @newsflare, do you have footage of the incident? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david_lospinoso Hi David, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat about this video.Can you follow me so I can send a DM? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadydeLuce Hi, I work at @newsflare video agency. Can we have a chat about your John Lewis video in DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahManley4 Hi Sarah, I'm wit @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about your video. Can u follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurie_pry Hi Laurie, can we have a quick chat on DM about this video? I'm with @Newsflare thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danmacl hi, I work at @Newsflare video agency and I'd like to have a quick about this clip. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanahrosenthal Hi Hanah, I work at @Newsflare video agency. Could we have a quick chat on DM about this clip? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikepicolson hi Eric, I'm with @Newsflare video agency. Can we talk about this video in DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murphycat2012 Hi Bridget, I'm with @Newsflare did you shoot this video? Can we talk about it on DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kadiasaraf Hi Kadia, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about your 'He will not divide us' video. Can we talk in DM?Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattyMalloy1995 Hi, I work at @Newsflare video agency and I'd like to have a chat about this clip. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyle_farmer15 Hi Kyle, I work at @newsflare. Can we have a chat about this video on DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirQuipsalot @Newsflare @SURJ_DC Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBarq15 hi Nick, I'm with @newsflare video agency. Can we have a quick chat about this video.Can you follow me back so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nibiaulloa75 Hi Nibia, I work at @newsflare video agency and I'd like to contact you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirQuipsalot Hi, I'm with @newsflare, can we have a quick chat about your video on DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDarkerBerry Hi Atima, I'm with @newsflare video agency. I'd like to have a quick chat about this video, can you follow me so I can DM?Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DominiqueMariex Hi Dominique, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commiecommando @Newsflare Can you follow me back so I can send you a direct message please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commiecommando Hi, I'm with @newsflare video agency. Can we talk about your inauguration videos in DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyBFrieder Hi Amy, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncqua Hi John, I work at @newsflare video agency and I'd like to get in touch with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BWAdamson Hi, I'm with @newsflare, could we have a chat about your video in DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronWEF Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdwardianPaul Hi there, I'm with @newsflare video agency and I'd like to have a chat about this video. Can we talk in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenna1025 Hi Kenna, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about this video. Can we talk in DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwhalen98 Hi Michael, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can you follow me back so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeandheather8 Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about this clip. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoxtecPT Hi, I'm with @newsflare. Can we talk about your Woodingdean fir video by DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dec_adams Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePieous Hi there, I'd like to contact you about one of your videos on behalf of @newsflare. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clnbrns Hi, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to have a quick chat about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacques_Fuller @Newsflare Can you follow me so I can send a direct message please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tobygilles Hi Toby, I work at @newsflare and I would like to contact you about your Scotland yard footage. Pls can we have a chat in DM?Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacques_Fuller Hi, I work at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch with you about this video. Can we talk in DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@comz90 Hi, I work at @newsflare video agency and I would like to get in touch about your Stansted video. Pls can you follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchieMaria Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare, can we have a chat about this video in DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheUKTrucker Hi, I'm with @newsflare and we'd like to work with your video, can you follow me back so I can send a DM please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredsharples Hi Fred, I work at @newsflare and I would like to have a chat with about this vid. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelMcArdle13 Hi Rachel, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this video. Can we talk by DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickdotSmith Hi Nick, I work at @newsflare and I'd like contact you about your 'Likes please' video. Can we have a quick chat in DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calebhailey Hi Caleb, I'm with @newsflare, could we have a quick chat in DM about this video? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhamil Hi Peter, I'm with @newsflare video agency. Could we have a chat about your video in DM please? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZiaWeise Hi Zia, I'm with @newsflare video agency and I would like to get in touch about this clip. Can we talk on DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmirick Hi Emma, I'm a journalist at @newsflare. Can we have a quick chat in DM about this video please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Connorr_15 Hi Connor, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsobelThatcher @Newsflare Can you follow me so I can send you a direct message please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@viktoriamadison Hi Viktoria, I work at @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaimie_tr Hi Jaimie, I work at @newsflare and I would like to have a chat with you about this video. Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsobelThatcher Hi Isobel, I'm with @newsflare video agency, can we have a quick chat about your video in dm please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fhoerhager Hi Felix, could we talk about your fireworks video by direct messages? I'm with @newsflare video agency. Danke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmoran513 Hi, I work at @newsflare video agency, can we have a quick chat about the video in DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@n_s_martin Hi Martin, I work at a video agency called @newsflare, can we talk about your video in direct message? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyMBell Hi Cathy, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@775sanreo We'd like to license the video to news organisations. You can upload the video on https://t.co/Yevoc9lLDJ or DM me for details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@775sanreo Hi, I work at @newsflare, video agency, and I'd like to contact you about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marutaro2000 Hi I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I'd like to contact you about this video. Please can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTweetsOfMP Hi Michelle, I'm a journalist at @newsflare, can we have a quick chat in DM about this video? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonytt25 Hi Tony, I'm with @newsflare and I'd like to have a chat about this clip. Can you follow me back so I can send a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThommySnow Hi Thommy, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to have a chat about this clip. Can you follow me so I can send a DM? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoramPohl Hi Yoram, I work at @newsflare, video agency. Can we have a quick chat about this video please? Can you send me a DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cielo_celest Hi, I'm with @newsflare, can we have a chat about your video of the Trump Tower evacuation? Can you follow me so I can DM? Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosefHanusCA Hi Joseph, I'm with @newsflare, can we have a chat about this video in DM please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavageEmily Hi Emily, I'm with @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about this clip. Can we talk in DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModernLifeDater Hi, I work at @newsflare video agency and I'd like to have a chat about this video. Can you follow me so I can send a DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auntywoo Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare, can we have a quick chat about this video please? Can you follow me so I can DM? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deeayygo Hi, I'm a journalist at @newsflare and I would like to get in touch about the train crash video. Can you follow back so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dukefrozen Hi Dario, I'm with @newsflare. Could you follow me back so I can send you a DM about this video please? Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GBabySanch Hi Giovanni, I'm a journalist at @newsflare, can we have a quick chat about this video in DM please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicoAmatullo Hi Nico, I'm with @newsflare video agency. Could we have a quick chat about your video of LAX in DM? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FroelichM Hi Martin, I'm a journalist with @newsflare video agency. Could we have a quick chat about your video by direct messages? Thank u]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>