<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do yourself a favour... GET THIS! https://t.co/6y5AaePGqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoHorvat way to go on that last play, bro. NHL 2018 stick handling: 62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate and Hal! And everyone who loves musical theatre and WANTS TO FEEL SOME LOVE IN THIS SHITTY TIME!!! You will... https://t.co/wyWxmwfVfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% on this guys side.

I HATE labels. I think they're stupid. However, some labels give certain privileges... https://t.co/Stq4gddt6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 months isn't nearly enough time for this psychopath. Disgusting. Don't read if you're sensitive to this sort... https://t.co/BjIO4VNBnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WIN your Vancouver Weddng! https://t.co/pWKDova6Oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole thing and then they do an amazing call back. https://t.co/Ng9V6Prfdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20thcenturyfox after Logan, give Wolverine back to Marvel. You guys have generally not done a good job and don't deserve him anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emperor Palpatine rarely cared about women. His government consisted mainly of men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: Emperor Palpatine also hated and mistreated "aliens"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government in Star Wars was called a Republic before Palpatine... just sayin']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This doesn't even read as funny to me. It's horrific because all those asshole men in suits signing pieces of... https://t.co/pU0A9BS668]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Okay, I have good news and bad news.. based on what you've told me, your coffee maker is broken. That's the bad... https://t.co/GV2HwVyT0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When was the last time a US President was this universally reviled?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't matter if you like kids or not... that was a wicked throw. https://t.co/C7qtLndXig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LangleyTownship who is responsible for the highway design here? This is insane. https://t.co/ZIrxotOREq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby sitting thoughts: make a show named Papa Troll to bank off success of Paw Patrol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecampaignbook LOVE THIS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistent chills through the entire trailer. This little girl!!!! She's epic! https://t.co/RMA0DaSEeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends Erin Elise Walker and Ross Foster are getting married! Please help them win their wedding! No... https://t.co/ofraom80bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh geez... please let them all be in a movie together. https://t.co/z3sOwaGyU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So little faith in law enforcement https://t.co/LZxQ2uuoWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msitweets after over a week of trying to get your shit GT62VR 6RE to work as well as my 3 year old laptop, it scre… https://t.co/VRqkdoJTfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to feel disappointed in humanity? Find a pro Trump post &amp; read the comments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww! Miss you, girl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit yes he was https://t.co/segbER0k3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An amazingly beautiful twitter rant in here. https://t.co/AtYMZLtfps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooooh! Will Ferrel! He should just give you a call, Stewart! https://t.co/Gu2g84y5VV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So weird and so good.

They get to certain points where you think they're about to start screaming at each other... https://t.co/JTuvvVYbAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, they got Trump. They need something to cuddle while their country implodes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good information! https://t.co/Ss7cLfO7qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canucks hockey! https://t.co/CqPBkbd4K7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That first question. https://t.co/wfzEI9a9de]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is a god... please help make this happen... https://t.co/oghkapVvDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No! The lyrics changed. I bet you wouldn't get it right."

My favourite correction of 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY NEW YEARS!!! Epic celebrations including celebrating the amazing Hussein and Brianna's engagement! Great... https://t.co/UFIzkQziYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The snow storm is 2016's last ditch effort to ruin as many people's years as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... wha!? https://t.co/6F2zJ2izMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, that's fast... https://t.co/QYi02iSFPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me want fake nails. https://t.co/Vtnu5X58Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart breaking. https://t.co/bf1ECG0cWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a pretty great Christmas with these (and more!) peeps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhhh!!! Exciting! https://t.co/Srx3rjUQuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow... duh. But never thought of it. https://t.co/lArXlSTr5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say for presents give experiences, not things.

Well, I like the experience of receiving things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shouldn't be unattended while shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My moods, generally:
😋😆🙃😈
And the comments below]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something I read last year and just was reminded of while watching a video: to all the parents out there with... https://t.co/l11IMkreHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Canadian Two-Face..? "You either die a hero or live long enough to see yourself become the villain." https://t.co/5zEOhLJ9T2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last girl must have been Canadian. https://t.co/RlGiTstpEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakeandamir totes was with you on titty fucking in ep248. You do the tits, they don't do you lol. Weirdest tweet I've ever written]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck?! If this stuff was regulated correctly then this wouldn't be happening. https://t.co/ljTVbqTCGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually stoked on this show... fingers crossed it's good. https://t.co/DbdNZWVEUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DA FAWK!!! THIS CAAAAST!!!! Amazing. https://t.co/n2bNwA8uUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting your laptop in to your backpack without realizing you didn't shut it off and then pulling it out dead on a plane with no outlets 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kid as Joker is up there on my list of fav Jokers! https://t.co/Z5sbU22T8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My internet is terrible but I'm sure we're cute!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing this for the contest but DAMN these are awesome. https://t.co/ncoYaCyZf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw! So cute! 2016 was a tough year for the world but still, it had its moments.

Lots of love to everyone!!!... https://t.co/Cq2Wusgw8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw! So cute! 2016 was a tough year for the world but still, it had its moments.

Lots of love to everyone!!!... https://t.co/K4B1WOx5Im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear the one true Marvel Cinematic Universe,

Thank you https://t.co/QytpPJblTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakeandamir I dunno. Trim the sides a bit, I think. Would look pretty good, imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moar Disney World!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time this guys been to ANY Disney parks! He has a good guide! https://t.co/YCLmD8eaJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good information a friend shared. Potential trigger warning. https://t.co/FHAXraiJge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This show!!!! https://t.co/73S9Yt0Ti8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing! The future is kinda awesome and kinda scary... https://t.co/Gv4vMZe6Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you send someone a snap and they still haven't looked at it but they've posted new ones to their story... 😒... https://t.co/m2wX9UfbzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as it's regulated safely, I think using things like this could be amazingly beneficial. https://t.co/WikxI1vqnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw what I think is my favourite show of this visit last night! So beautiful and emotional! The second act didn't... https://t.co/PujQRFSWGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yes!!! Fuck YOU, the cab companies! Your bullshit is done! https://t.co/xxnYtP5aDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking in on the computer I select "text me my boarding pass" so I don't need to carry around a piece of paper... https://t.co/EeOzZfBaf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady crossing street: start running in to street, look now to see if cars are coming.

Genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/5Uhqtd794p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who do I know that lives in Florida!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suing people for slander? Cuz they, you know, repeated what you said Ina public forum..? Okay... also, let's not... https://t.co/Lgnl2ANGUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mariah Ware... get ready https://t.co/cb6QnXvwPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This woman deserves a huge shit storm for this https://t.co/T8QuEgM8ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you get a free holiday drink today if you buy one between 2pm-5pm and I didn't want to so I offered it to... https://t.co/RslFw8rNgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now I am pretty much half my mom's age.. that's kinda neat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This = Dear America, fuck you. https://t.co/T0SZH11fiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These move a terrifyingly realistic way. https://t.co/kDdDOFRClv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to see right now but there's still beauty in this world. https://t.co/jjXgZegkbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH! Gentle reminder to everyone that Trump doesn't believe in global warming. And on that note of absolute terror... https://t.co/uFtRwfEbH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words... no more words... Terrified of the fall out but here to support anyone who needs it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada elected pretty boy, ineffective, social justice warrior Trudeau because we knew ya'll down south were going to royally fuck up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY, LUCAS!!! The world just started its descent in to hell :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished unfollowing all the uneducated idiots I had on Facebook who were pro Trump. Any others want to rear... https://t.co/Pzn0vQ7ZZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom: me and my brother had to have the safe sex talk with my mother after my dad passed away.

Grandma: well, of... https://t.co/MO2m9o4Crb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hal, Kate, and I did another thing! https://t.co/KhKGc3Qqqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy rocks https://t.co/UJnGqMjysZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing a smooth and sexy sign off to my lovely Magic peeps!

Congrats on a hella long contract! Wish I was finishing it with you guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 7 hours in the studio with the amazing Craig Zurba, Hal Wesley Rogers, Kate MacQueen, and a special... https://t.co/MqwklJi2Ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gentlemen, did you know there's a male birth control currently being used and tested in India and Europe that is... https://t.co/oM2KHEgIiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Infinity Doctor the Master of Death

Kate: Black Lord the Abolisher of Women and Stars
Hal: Flair Tiger the... https://t.co/DUdlugIwY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my scrolls! https://t.co/woVwEMxuF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/M5nQe0FOEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last task was an escape room! We stole the powerful artifact at the literal last second! Such a great birthday! https://t.co/7ax6aI8nvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final scroll.... https://t.co/FR9Zdlu09R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/pcEzgZwfQ7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>