<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[THE GREAT EIGHT! #Caps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsHernia Her and Barron were running errands in NYC with Secret Service, Maybe the evangelicals hero Trump will get a 3rd divorce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 3 months, haven't hired staff? She should have free time when Barron is at school, so strange https://t.co/THJKqyfaOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania pretending that she isn't First Lady is weird,Michelle woulda been ripped relentlessly for this behavior https://t.co/qQ54aLYbjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just threatening Mexico for the helluva of it https://t.co/AzHsZE5LcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Mark Warner isn't running for re-election in 2020 because this was some dumb politics in a blue state like VA https://t.co/YmUMLT7iJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aorf3 where is that at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freshxdesign people just want some local news that isn't Trump, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Press Conference from @NationalZoo on finding Ollie https://t.co/nJE9kyEGKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to update your handshake game https://t.co/SFyBPrEM8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updates on Ollie the missing Bobcat via @MeaganNBCDC  #DC https://t.co/UAROGWJJ5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On your next trip to #DC, Everyone should go visit the Frederick Douglas museum @FredDouglassNPS https://t.co/rX4kcSKszv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VTDuffman Even things they agreed upon &amp; past colleagues like Chuck Hagel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those worried how the white nationalism of Steve Bannon is getting normalized, all of this thread  https://t.co/9nvSNuNPds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No punishment for lying to Senators about screwing people out of their homes &amp; abusing office for personal gain w/… https://t.co/9hwN5OLo4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rules that makes Dems accept another Prez L while winning more vote is same logic why GOP should have allowed Obama get his SC pick a vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So let them put in a 49 year old judge to rule us for 4 decades by eliminating the filibuster but never forget they FD Obama &amp; it was wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama wins 2 elections convincingly, but wont give him 3rd SC pick cuz replacing Scalia meant court might not be conservative, power whores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court gave election to GWBush by stopping counting in Fl, Dem Sens still allowed votes/hearing on his SC picks, let that sink in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Senators would have allowed hearing/vote for Harriet Meyers, WAY more unqualified than Garland because had respect for losing/norms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power hungry GOP will get their SC way with Trump but that don't mean Dems gotta accept that is how system works, everyone knows it isn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media/GOP demands Dems continue to take Ls, when win more votes in Prez elections but wont give them SC seat that they know is theres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garland was respected by all GOP Senators, would have sailed through confirmations, zero respect of rules/norms, because it was OBAMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court been dysfunctional for almost a year because a bunch of white guys wouldnt let first black President do Constitutional duty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When was last time political media made GOP eat shit for blatant Dem hypocrisy like Merrick Garland not getting a hearing/vote, never]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse your political team didnt even allow a Garland a hearing, you know that was wrong &amp; would be outraged too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Iowa City, after Brent Musburger did a #Hawkeyes hoops game, rolled into Sports Column, purchased all of us broke college kids a beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first memory of the NBA was Brent Musburger doing the games on CBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malik Monk could play for any team in the NBA right now but is forced to make money for NCAA/Calipari instead of himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure Malik Monk never has to room with Nick Young on the road next season with the Lakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But F it #Wizards fans, we deserve to be excited, If Washington finishes out at 22-12, wins 50 games for first time in 38 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should go NO CLICK on this but #Wizards fans should see how awful Wall &amp; Beal were treated in August by media https://t.co/2VqkrTpHdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nohiddenfeas because Bradley makes more money so John never passes him the ball! haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH, this unnamed agent was allowed to be unnamed by this awful journalism to throw his slander around is an ahole… https://t.co/QNz7zZxABZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way too much hoops left for "I told ya sos" but this paragraph gave me a furious seizure in August, reads like disc… https://t.co/LcJSxeHSNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dclesboulez Wiz have a top 7 offense/defense in NBA for 2 straight months, Melo would be great for post season but hows it work until then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This headline was 2 months ago, LOL #Wizards https://t.co/47WrLHmtBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Havent seen many CLICK BAIT trade John Wall national media pieces lately, which even us cynical bloggers &amp; Wiz fans knew was so dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall just got busted doing bunny ears on Beal during Bradley's post game interview, SO MUCH TENSION #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dclesboulez only way the money works is to include Mahinmi, but then Knicks are on the hook for 32 more mil on Ian, that is dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VICTORY! #Wizards defeat #Knicks 117-101, now 28-20, Beal-28 pts, Kief-24 pts, Wall- 5 pts, 13asts, 15 in a row at home! Lakers, Thur in DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VICTORY! #Wizards defeat #Knicks 117-102, now 28-20, Beal-28 pts, Kief-24 pts, Wall- 5 pts, 13asts, 15 in a row at home! Lakers, Thur in DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dclesboulez I would trade Mahinmi, Oubre &amp; a future conditional pick for Melo, but still dont think Knicks should do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington outscores NY #Knicks 32-22 in 3rd Qtr, lead 91-76, headed into the 4th #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost feel sorry for the #Knicks but I don't, Washington is just toying around now, DUNK ON EM SPIDER KELLY, lead by 18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #KnickTape showing some signs of life by scrapping back so they won't get blown out in the 3rd qtr....yet #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those that killed Scalia with a pillow must feel like fools tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Im sure Gorsuch will just be calling "BALLS AND STRIKES" like Roberts claimed to do in his nomination hearings, such a front]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Wizards offense starts rolling, now lead the hapless #Knicks by 15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danecarbaugh you can go back to the BS spewed by Roberts &amp; Alito in their hearings to make them seem moderate, all a dodge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Supreme Court stops counting of votes in FL to install GW Bush,GOP wont allow Obama fill an open seat, now Dems should just roll over? BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Dems won't filibuster this stolen seat, then they are worthless as a national party https://t.co/CSOZLHz5CI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama nominates a 64 year old, respected moderate, GOP wont allow hearing/vote, Trump nominates a 49 yr old right wing ideologue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since 12/1/16, #Wizards are 21-9, why? NBA rankings - Off Rating: 7th, Def Rating: 6th, Net Rating: 5th, EFG%: 4th, TFG%: 5th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halftime, the #Wizards leads #Knicks 59-54, Wall- 15 pts, 9 assts, Beal- 14 pts, Gortat- 10 pts, 7 rbs, Kief- 13pts, 5rbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Wall SPLASHING, #Wizards now lead #Knicks 44-41, superb breakdown of his shooting this season… https://t.co/1pHVygTy1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Wall has 25 assists in his last 5 quarters of basketball #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satoranksy couldnt get those last two shots to fall but like his aggressive drives to the hoops #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Through one quarter, the #Wizards and #Knicks are tied at 28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAHA, John Wall better get that call against Ron Baker #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Wizards crowd was upset at the no call on the travel by #Nicks Kyle O'Quinn because it totally was, good to see the fans engaged early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Used to be frustrated at Beal when shot mid-range jumpers because he settled for so many long twos, that was an open one in rhythm #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennings just found out in person why Quick aint fair with John Wall, lets get Wizzy Wiz #Wizards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WizKnicks tip in 30 mins, Big Panda Ready https://t.co/xOn0NEZedu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before #WizKnicks go check out @Truth_About_It analyzing the recent success of the #Wizards https://t.co/cTNDGY64e3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exceptional piece on #Wizards by @ConorDDirks go read it https://t.co/v0CSUzJYd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration is considering a broad crackdown on legal foreign workers https://t.co/Im3eBxYe33 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is still day to day life in #DC https://t.co/GPd6mKrXlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RetrocedeUtah #DCstatehood https://t.co/2UCn3LJ2rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashback to simpler times last summer where I poked fun of people trying to find Pikachus https://t.co/uRzixKONHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On its 11th day in office, Trump WH found itself in a dispute with the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum" https://t.co/kRfaXN3Sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refusing the voting rights of DC residents is SOOO hilarious https://t.co/X1X7l2MTSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sReginald I'm already down to making Chaffetz's life miserable in DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If they tried this stuff out on the people of Utah they could get voted out of office” https://t.co/i5sIy313Hm #DCStatehood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey fellow DC citizens, ready to become Marylanders, so we can get our voting rights like other Americans? https://t.co/6Thd3NOkwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of people affected by Trump's travel ban: About 90,000 https://t.co/zZCT9JP6gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@famman93 Just cut Thornton, sign some guy in China or someone else who is on waivers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This old clip of Jeff Sessions and Sally Yates is surreal in light of Trump firing her https://t.co/gwvESN1GiB via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just raised profile Sally Yates, will be revered amongst all the protestors now https://t.co/n27xK8qilV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Americans have to be under thumb of government oppression like what my fellow DC citizens deal with https://t.co/5idYvCz9M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sucks for #Wizards that Boston won, but positive note, hair due of Marcus Smart has gotten worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley thank you for declaring opposition to Super Court nominee,this seat was stolen, you are correct, they didnt care about norms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@famman93 plus, why would Knicks want Mahinmi's salary for that long? I dont see it, especially when he is hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUH? Embarrassing to see in foreign media that our WH spokesperson is this obtuse about tragedy in Quebec City… https://t.co/EBIo7o3uat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooter in Quebec is a 27 year old white guy https://t.co/C2M0ltwlh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FunFactAttack I think Melo should back up Kief, which of course, never want to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is way too much for #Wizards to offer for Melo anyway https://t.co/8xn8ezGyMP https://t.co/4Fchy7JgYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lalamasala any word on the Landmark festival?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot on Assessment: "Red pandas are known for being adorable "https://t.co/O1L9LS1FwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephensDC The Panda might have took off because it was mating time, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephensDC lol, well I care &amp; hope the Panda is safe, some think that someone has Sunny at their place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunny the Red Panda is still missing in Norfolk https://t.co/vehJ2KYj7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ollie the Bobcat has escaped the National Zoo https://t.co/6d2W2d51zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is what governing looks like when adults are no longer in charge"  https://t.co/lNXA7L5aso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pro Bowl just went bananas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 minute warning at the Pro Bowl, Kirk Cousins is trying to lead his team to tying TD, there is NO one at this game, in Orlando?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["PROTEST IS THE NEW BRUNCH" https://t.co/O2gG2GliRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kentucky fans will fill conflicted on this Wall dunk on Davis #Wizards #BBN https://t.co/LC0cuxq37M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still shocked that Jason Smith did this today https://t.co/iEugmeTnJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In last 3 games combined vs Boston, Atlanta, &amp; New Orleans, the #Wizards have only trailed for 37 seconds, crazy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>