<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TAB_Sport @TAB_Racing does correct series score in odi's get refunded if a match is rained out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dev_enter son of a bitch I'm gonna spend one day in Melbourne and I'm gonna end up with a pile of useless Australian coins aren't I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSDeman I dont buy ice cream and I don't want more change lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These things are almost useless to me. #PhysicalCurrency #LowValue #LimitedUse https://t.co/gXgyEULdI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ sign out, close chrome, ctrl-alt-del, task manager , end task on every remaining chrome process, restart chrome, sign in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ if we had more children making the big decisions that actually matter the world would be a better place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane wow!! That sucks!! ðŸ˜¥ðŸ˜¥ðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsAM never win another grand slam huh? Mmmmkay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal will have to wait a little longer for the funds to buy a looser fitting pair of shorts #AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu oh come on Raj really? You've never given me a retweet and that wasn't good enough either?! You're a tough tough man! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Nadal wins perhaps he can afford to buy some shorts he doesn't have to pick out of his arse every 30 seconds? #AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow hey man new newsletter template is BOSS welcome back. This is the only newsletter I actually read it's the best. Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skysportnz What happens in Aus/NZ ODI series correct score if a match gets rained out? Every option loses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ open task manager go to processes and end all the chrome processes then relaunch chrome and sign in again. Fixed .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ I found another solution id like to share if you'd put on website?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great product @SKYNZ with SkyGo, Sevens aint working too many concurrent active streams. Seriously why do we pay for this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane #ThingsYouProbablyShouldntTweet lololol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The girl waiting for the train next to me is chewing gum and drinking coffee at the same time #MakesNoSense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMScuri OK that makes more sense thank god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMScuri what's harder to get though? Open carry or concealed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMScuri if you can't carry a concealed weapon can you carry it in plain view?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMScuri or is it permissible to carry it hidden from sight ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMScuri is a concealed weapon just 'legally carrying a gun'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there any Americans that can explain the concealed weapon law to me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot sit on a seat in a train that isn't facing the same direction the train is heading! #IllStandThanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane hahahaha! It's almost like you're not happy unless you're in a stable 24.5 degree temperature at all times? ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead is so dreadful but I can't stop watching this drivel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyrake Grand slams for men are best of 5 but 3 for women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is women's tennis best out of 3? #SeemsVerySexist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[male tennis players are the most colour coordinated men on earth #AusOpen #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bunghole has reached fizzing point #AustralianOpen #Federer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane People are that bigoted at your work? Thats pretty sad :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane that's brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane @KittyCatNZ I completely disagree with that, there are responsible men out there I'd take that pill in a heart beat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane the 90s were a magical time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ @itskaylenejane it's not so much about trust, most men ultimately think it's your problem not theirs, no responsibility ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ @itskaylenejane oh fair enough then more testing. No way men could handle that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane @KittyCatNZ usually by the time they ask that question that's a very convenient answer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ you've misunderstood. Im in the programme. How do I get a card?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane @KittyCatNZ where is this man's pill they've been promising for decades?! So annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu @mike_lowen how do you guys know each other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ How can I get an Air Points loyalty card for redemption at participating retailers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I avoid stupid people like the plague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane that's in the shade though, it feels a lot warmer than that to me, got a wooly sevens costume??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane are you just meaning temperature wise ? Weather here is amazing today! So warm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sat down at my desk after a weekend away and promptly locked myself out of workstation by typing password wrong 3 times #WelcomeBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doc Martens store has a massive poster with the words "NO HORSE SHIT". guess they're not trying to appeal to families with children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane or my favorite, 'did you get my email?' less than two mins after they sent it WTF , I don't live in my inbox!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane I literally get this every day, if you're gonna come over and talk to me anyway why send the email??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane I had a lil foam iPhone I left behind. I thought that was it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane not at all. It's not like it can exponentially increase forever there will be some great deals in a year or two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane is that the old foam iPhone in the picture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewtownMoon do you have epic hop shine yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EpicBeer where can I find hopshine in Wellington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wireless headsets are so handy until you forget to put them on the charger and come to work in the morning and they're flat! #EpicFail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It must be a little embarrassing for the girl in Fritz's Weiners to explain her job to #tinder dates #ItsJustTemporaryImAModel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[422 error returned, unprocessable entity - Hang on, you can't just MAKE up words Google! #Nerding #Geeking #WebLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dad said LOL in a text message #DontBelieveInAnythingAnymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I no longer have to fill out a timesheet !! #Bliss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu well your stuffed then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu loads of time for that it's called commiting to and from work and lunch breaks right ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu thats life eh? Things become more important and no regrets ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu I have too much great music to listen too life is hard haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu first world problems?!?! Hahaha!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you've just done 12000 steps and your fitbit tells you you should go for a walk when you're having some beers #fuckoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu @mike_lowen minimalism the documentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSDeman sounds unnecessarily complicated and it's stuck to the land you say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSDeman what is that exactly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't people change their wifi name and password from the defaults to something practical? Boggles my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane price doesn't seem that bad if you like the style go for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane tbh I don't think my charge 2 is great. I want music controls. I might sell it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are playing everyone's favorite summer road trip game, count the eviscerated possums! #roadtrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz what would she know?! Haha! 4,5,6,7,8,9,1,2,3 I reckon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz hmmm not sure starting at 1 is in order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow this beer is kick ass, real fruity like pineapple but hoppy and... (Beached As - Tropical IPA) https://t.co/1Cl6exTbJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane never say never Kaylene , come on. You gotta have faith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane naughty frodo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platypus237 exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platypus237 then self loathing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platypus237 Tinder is a great idea for meeting someone in a strange country might get a hook up might make a friend might meet other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane I got that from Alice. It was nice to feel valued ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darth Vader - The original intergalactic motherfuckin gangster #starwars #RogueOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one in that KFC ad has ever eaten real KFC before #ItsAllLies #WhereAreTheFatPeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Gus actual every day the last six months. Only got anything done from 7-8 and 5-630]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSDeman ohhhh nope. I havent worked at enlighten since may ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ @itskaylenejane it also has a likeness to poison like all 'energy' drinks ewh chemicals!! #HighHorse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when a staff member brings their new baby in and all the women circle and the men don't even blink in recognition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta @itskaylenejane Back to the future wins ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajrnaidu ear canals for life homie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can spot a tinder date from a mile away #awkward #eagertoimpress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to unplug more often #HeadphonesOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ yeah for sure! If it's for you I'm sure you can do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane yeah.... I agree. I didn't look at the Samsung gears in depth but aesthetically they look nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ As soon as you feel no one's reading you stop ðŸ˜‹ thsts my experience anyway hah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane mmm not great battery life eh. Fitbit surge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane I'm a huge fan of music controls on a wearable and I miss this the most after my msb2 broke. Battery won't last marathon hah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KittyCatNZ nope no one uses it because you can soap box to a larger audience on Facebook ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itskaylenejane naa its just not worth. Charging it every day, it's pretty ugly, very expensive. Unless it had an essential feature you need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platypus237 oh you mean a hard way of achieving a simple thing? It's apple so I'm sure there is an adapter of some kind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hate how delete on a Mac behaves like backspace on a PC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>