<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@swin24 I only read the kickers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your regular reminder that there are Republican governors in Maryland, Massachusetts, New Jersey, and Illinois.

https://t.co/xBclDUxkjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: The Democratic Base is Demanding Obstruction and Senators are Listening. 

https://t.co/JypZYIYhn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure he's just taking a walk on the Appalachian Trail https://t.co/Fesq84r7AO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notable that as Ellison keeps trying to put primary behind him and build bridges, Sanders keeps framing as estab/pr… https://t.co/7zSx8J6Rfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Fire emoji] for this bit of Bernie Sanders' statement on Joe Biden's endorsement of Tom Perez in DNC: "...failed s… https://t.co/nELPj5BJhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did they not make this model out of chocolate? https://t.co/KW11t2787c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hope this becomes a major Democratic talking point... https://t.co/4C4GuN4KCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec asks if Dems are "going to live up to the same standard that they set for Republicans" under Obama.

Answer: No, not even close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious Q: What does it mean for Flynn to be "officially putting Iran on notice”? 

https://t.co/qkGIvLjzXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and/but most DNC members are establishment themselves.

Biden always seen as more committed to partybuilding th… https://t.co/nsX3TAGr4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Legit BFD for Perez

2) Biden doesn't have a vote

3) Obamaland finally going public w/support for Perez. https://t.co/ExYXostWxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handy Democrat-to-English translator from @daveweigel on senators' Gorsuch voting plans. https://t.co/rxdaUH4Wue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why always refusing to apologize has consequences... https://t.co/2Nzj1NqaLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So does the press secretary speak for the principle? https://t.co/TpcpQyDCzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is such a poorly kept secret + so many anguished ppl, why isn't there single quote that supports thesis? https://t.co/TWSrvsnQCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign of polarized times? 

No Labels cancels "Congressional Welcome Party" night before with no explanation. Promises will be rescheduled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems right. https://t.co/b7G2GSX41X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold aside from all the Hill staffers! &lt;rim shot&gt;

Not meant to be a subtweet, just have seen several ppl and wanted to head off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Trump Hotels didn't photoshop the WH in this ad. That's EPA building across street. Note unique double columns… https://t.co/aqmHiLZV8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merrick Garland and Neil Gorsuch would probably both be easily confirmed in normal times, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neeratanden I guess we're disagreeing on "threshold." otherwise tautological. 66 is a bar that type of nominee you want could meet, better?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems plausible, but only of limited impact, no? 1.5 yrs from now amidst who knows how many other issues. https://t.co/jjf20idbMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neeratanden I don't see the difference between those two statements...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious Q: What's the evidence that Manchin or Heitkamp etc. will be seriously damaged by opposing Gorsuch? Did Garland move any votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren a no: "Based on the long and well-established record of Judge Gorsuch, I will oppose his nomination."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAP President @neeratanden calling for 66 (!) vote threshold on Trump nominee. 

From memo: https://t.co/TEMeno7o9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Chair candidate Tom Perez: "Gorsuch on the Supreme Court is intolerable and it’s up to Democrats to block his nomination."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile....

DNC boots candidate from chairman’s race for criticizing Ellison’s Islamic faith, via @JonEasley. https://t.co/KvYwlkJJem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filibuster it is... https://t.co/hm04JIqSq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toplines in Dem oppo book on Gorsuch: 
-"Radical right-wing"
-"Extreme on police brutality"
-"Bad for women".."workers"
-"Threat to privacy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young, cogent, serious. Favorable contrast to Trump's chaotic first two weeks. https://t.co/BXq46TFu7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's transparent nomination process also made it easy for Dem oppo researchers to prep. Statements already in from DNC, American Bridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fumbles on the announcement a bit: "Neil Gorsuch of the United States Supreme Court to be of the United States Supreme Court."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @VaughnHillyard read on view of immigration EO from Trumpland, USA. https://t.co/SNDcHaIbaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtweet (v.): What Merriam-Webster Dictionary Is Doing to the President. https://t.co/zqtJfqPjoe https://t.co/5XKl5ywVdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no, fashion brands are going to do protest-inspired lines now, aren't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChrisMurphyCT: "I'm prepared to shatter precedence" to oppose Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RNC just announced they raised $16m in Dec, month DNC was in hibernation awaiting new chairman.

Regrets on scheding vote for end of Feb?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of "it's about time" praise from progressives on Senate Dem boycott.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themadhatter355 I think you mean bi-partisan. bi-cameral refers to two legislative chambers, which was definitely intended :) but ur right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PastryPlate they will at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is a hypocrite on obstructionism and will be again when the tables turn. https://t.co/mPqIADFqG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 120 anti-Trump protests planned for today nationally, per @MoveOn @WorkingFamilies + @PplsAction. https://t.co/VXqRCiEu0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aim is to delay votes. Committee votes require quorum, which require Democratic presence. No Democrats, no votes. https://t.co/vAuLzjs80z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. @keithellison statement on Sally Yates: "By all accounts, this is looking like failed presidency. And it's only day 12.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't the plural of AG be AsG?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesting is the new brunch https://t.co/CQRdnEvMep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Chair races are not cheap: @TomPerez has raised $825,000 in six weeks since he entered race, inc commitments, per aide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Almost everything went wrong." https://t.co/1fjEUAMBKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough but fair https://t.co/vL99SaGcnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yates, right? Turning and turning in the widening gyre, the acting attorney general cannot hold..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest threat to re-election for most G.O.P. members of Congress is still a primary challenge." https://t.co/t6VxhX2TwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer says it's "pathetic" that people are "nit-picking" Holocaust statement for not mentioning Jews...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing one-president-at-a-time norm, Obama puts out pretty strong stmt on protests/Trump refugee EO. https://t.co/ySlWZpmZSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[86% of GOPers say most members of media not honest, per new Q poll.

But look at those numbers for 18-34 yos...… https://t.co/sBpAjXgdmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty stunning expl of new political calculus for Senate Ds. Hundreds confront @SenWhitehouse chanting "obstruct!" https://t.co/RpITXSMsdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of Omarsoa, little birdie sends this photo from a Dec. 2013 holiday party during 1st open enrollment perio… https://t.co/TiFio5Osao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't get over the fact that Omarosa is back in our lives, over the right shoulder of the president as he discusses policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality TV presidency: “You’re not here to be someone’s buddy." https://t.co/8xnmVt6mzT https://t.co/1hwe75IaYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kamala Harris (others?) heading to WH protest. https://t.co/KaXlbgmPSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @ACLU has been busy gearing up for battle since the election. More on their prep:  https://t.co/4LARD865uN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge grants stay of deportations, per @ACLU. https://t.co/I1NMJh1p55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC chair candidate Tom Perez at Houston airport protesting Trump exec order, per spox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is very Holden Caulfield this morning with the media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBaumann @MadeleineLEngle If I win, my acceptance speech would start: "When I was first asked to give this speech..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBaumann @MadeleineLEngle I've always meant to submit to this contest. https://t.co/R1fhjMXHEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBaumann I've already written my lead for when they do: "It was a dark and stormy night..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been one week since Trump's Inauguration, btw...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellison joining protest of Miami-Dade mayor who ystdy told police to comply with ICE after Trump EO on Sanctuary Ci… https://t.co/Pc1EIqoF7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That said, Gabbard beat Chan Hodges 85% - 15% in 2016... https://t.co/zPx5lo8s7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenFrumin Thanks! I was sure it or lead would get cut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shay Chan Hodges, who ran against Gabbard last year, told me she was seriously considering re-match.… https://t.co/TutHJC4Otq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've finally fulfilled my professional journalism goal to start a story with "Merriam-Webster defines..."  

https://t.co/zqtJfqPjoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Chair candidates run real campaigns have to pay for it -- starting at about $100,000, via @DanielStrauss4. https://t.co/Gq6ehBBavL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 clicks! https://t.co/VSDA0Yr36E https://t.co/Em8IwvIkeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the author of this bogus study: "Is it plausible that non-citizen votes account for...popular vote margin held… https://t.co/SdXiBhDutR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cool cool cool https://t.co/o7ezNNq01l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Democrats miss the boat on the women's march? https://t.co/csuxPFFlk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone feels like democracy is on the line." https://t.co/4LARD865uN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow up 160+ years of tradition over one week. Filibuster is arguably terrible, but this is McConnell's decision to… https://t.co/hNqx9pRnYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanie_ayse I've watched it too many times. It's like word-for-word from a Marvel supervillain sidekick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at GOP retreat: "This Congress is going to be the busiest congress we've had in decades, maybe ever."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump at GOP retreat: "Now is the dawn of a new era."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @imillhiser Apparently it's a legacy of Latin. https://t.co/1s5lfL6DCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias people as in marble lintels above the doors of a "mvsevm" or actual people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's border wall could be bad for one of his favorite things -- golf courses. https://t.co/MRRZJFzTIW https://t.co/UgcmILe0uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swin24 MrBigHands69@aol.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Woody Allen tried to Marshall McLuhan Doanld Trump, POTUS would say McLuhan was just groveling to Allen. https://t.co/eoqn6MKefL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjySarlin @Bencjacobs Also wanted to abolish the Electoral College, though I guess 2012 Trump would approve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to George W. Bush, civil libertarians are more prepared than ever to take Trump admin to court. 

https://t.co/4LARD865uN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He volunteered this me: "As for the Q of whether I might run for pres again in 2020, I just might."… https://t.co/64aTk0tahm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamDavidA Senior career officials are main check against political leadership. You can learn the machinery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this right strategy? Trump will just replace them all with his people. (waivers avail to hiring freeze) https://t.co/8HKdEQ81eU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Alex Jones learned to stop worrying and love Black Helicopters. https://t.co/YIttEBgvHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Shia [LaBeouf] took a hit for us. There were all these Nazis here." https://t.co/CP9C9OOBUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump readies EOs, opponents say: "See You in Court." https://t.co/4LARD865uN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool cool cool. https://t.co/tQ7A6jFvKY https://t.co/QfdqTRwM0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@splcenter pres: "Like the skyscrapers that bear his name, a wall at the s. border will be nothing more than a monument to Trump’s vanity."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are interesting to read together, from @brianbeutler and @mattklewis. https://t.co/9S7fn9GDdr https://t.co/SgtYKJvZkZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>