<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio You can stand up and be an American Hero. Save our Schools. Please Vote No on DeVos. In your gut, you know she's not right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redostoneage @nypost how does taking money from public schools and giving it to private, religious schools help poor kids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoFascistsPls @VictorYocco @SenBobCasey yeah, could someone at least pay for my sign supplies? Sharpies don't grow on trees, you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, #PresidentBannon has huge hands! They're like 2 catcher's mitts! #Truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump doesn't have the balls to get rid of him #PresidentBannon https://t.co/EhwjmmCtu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Shit. Bannon said he had a "small window" to push agenda b4 being found out https://t.co/hioPdQ9pZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gcbrown1956 FUCK THAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #so-called president is accidentally bringing out the best in most Americans. He can try, but he will never #MAHA! #NYC Subway #woke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The federalists crafted the system of checks and balances with you in mind, sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes. You DO realize that he won on a technicality, right? #gobrushyertooth https://t.co/rHlEZxXcwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angel4everyoung @matthaig1 yeah. What is that 10, 11 times you've posted that same graphic? It's pretty good, but not THAT good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angel4everyoung @matthaig1 until he is impeached and thrown out on his narcissistic ass. #goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes this tweet reminds me of when u were tweeting about NYT during the badly botched #YemenRaid #SoCalledPresident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He's a real judge, confirmed 99-0, and he's not afraid of you. That worries you, doesn't it? #socalledpresident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, it's getting sad now. Sounding desperate. Cringing for you. And us. #SoCalledPotus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @realDonaldTrump can we get this trending this morning?#socalledPOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poisoning streams, giving guns to lunatics, scrapping bank rules that protect consumers- great week #socalledPOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump he said the refugee deal still stands. So- u hung up on him for nothing? #artofthedeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what about #QuebecShooting??? Not even going to mention it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lucky5713 @realDonaldTrump most of those checks flow straight into red states- illiterate,Trump voting, inbred idiots #brushyertooth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump keep on stifling dissent and consolidating power, you know your deplorables are too stupid to recognize what you're doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. Trump, Frederick Douglass is actually..." click #ReasonsTrumpHangsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. Trump, the raid in Yemen didn't exaaaaactly go..." click #ReasonsTrumpHangsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. trump, the Quebec shooter was actually..." click #ReasonsTrumpHangsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump are you attending the 8-year old's funeral, too?  https://t.co/XBPa14wWiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump so, maybe you should have studied the deal… Before the phone call? Just a suggestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be subscribing to five separate news outlets today. Vanity Fair, Washington Post, New York Times, +2 more. A… https://t.co/Lzk485dHqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @dvrhztn nailed it. I wish I could retweet this 100 times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBobCasey please, please vote NO on DeVos. We would be OK with almost anyone else. Children everywhere are depending on you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenToomey Please, please vote NO on DeVos. We would be OK with almost anyone else! Children everywhere are depending on you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chapmanchapman so precious Baron staying in the same school is more imp than funding the entire arts  program. Sounds legit. #trumpregrets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorseyshaw to be fair, Rudy is usually behind him, with his lips firmly in the crack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT she plagiarized]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @xdelmar59 @staffernews i'm sure Mr. sessions wasn't referring to White presidents, silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the person now in charge of the free world. Thanks, Trumpers. You fell for the con. #RoastOfSteveBannon https://t.co/97Vzqv5G5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow @washingtonpost ambassadors kids can be pulled out of school mid year, but precious Barron must stay in NY. Sounds fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow @washingtonpost maybe she's working hard 2 stop cyber bullying. would be a shame if some1 got made fun of online for crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandBurns88 you are coming from a place of hysterical fear, rather than compassion. You're scared shitless of people different from u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandBurns88 @realDonaldTrump so now you trust polls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your #muslimban isn't playing very well with the people, sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Could you please read this article and comment on it, esp the 19% and Bannon role? It's gone viral… https://t.co/855c4TsPZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be drinking a flat white every morning from now on. #BoycottStarbucks #nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is in Pensacola, where @realDonaldTrump thinks everybody loves him. Getting more blue by the day. #laxprotest… https://t.co/bgwE47SFcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bocavista2016 please don't act like you give a shit about oppressed women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WaysToBeAHero #StopPresidentBannon #deleteuber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ban in effect for ppl from countries with Trump business interests - Muslim or not #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan OR from countries where he has business interests... go figure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicewonders101 what in the hell are you talking about? That's just a straight up lie. Also your avi is a stock photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @MrTommyCampbell @realDonaldTrump 132,001 after I read this mornings tweetstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future school children will read historical accounts of a president who sent out angry, misspelled tweets every morning. #ItWasSoAwesomeWhen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes @washingtonpost getting a little too excited this morning, Donnie. Try looking it over before pressing send]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you're making us all like these great publications even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman right! And if they do find voter fraud, it's more likely to be on the GOP side. They're the greedy, dishonest ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if all the marchers would adopt just 1 unwanted kid. We would save so much money by abolishing the foster care system! #MarchOfLies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Boots #ThingsYouShouldntLick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WajahatAli note that the ban doesn't include countries where he has business interests, Muslim or not. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @MrTommyCampbell if Walmart could throw up, it would look a lot like a Trump rally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You represent all of us, not just the boot-licking cretins who still support you  #PublicDemandsAVoice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roswell2001 ew, tears,urine-why are you Republicans so obsessed with drinking other peoples bodily fluids? Gross!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be donating extra to Planned Parenthood today in honor of your #MarchForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should call it the #March for Birth because none of you give a rats ass about the kid after it comes out #MarchForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, if all of you marchers would step up and adopt a kid, we could get rid of the foster care system! #MarchForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only dumb rednecks like Trump and that makes him sad #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If WalMart could throw up..." lol https://t.co/BzEtYUeT5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punishment for the march? #GlobalGagRule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio look out, I think @POTUS is about to grab you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madortiz1 sadly, that ship has sailed. But protest his vote on DeVos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBillNelson Please vote NO on DeVos. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio your vm is full, so let me ask here- PLEASE vote no on DeVos confirmation, she would be horrible. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because, overpopulation #7in10forRoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I've seen too many unwanted NICU babies with no shot at quality of life #7in10forRoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my place to start. Where's yours? https://t.co/6qBXriDul2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Party told you to reject all evidence of your eyes and ears. It was their final, most essential command -Orwell, 1984 #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why didn't you VOTE? #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an Inspiring Day #WomensMarch https://t.co/VpfHyOBRdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama #ThanksObama for your 8 years of service. #FarewellObama https://t.co/UCv3b9LOAe https://t.co/8pomzDpRd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will be missed #ThankYouObamas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cynderella63 @mcoop I think you missed the memo, the liberal tears thing died when the Russian P thing happened-get with the program]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Minutemaniac have you ever seen the eyes of a parent of a dying kid? I've seen hundreds. And I "recall" every pair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Minutemaniac what I "recall" is seeing kids turned down for exp treatmnts that could have saved them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Minutemaniac what I "recall" is the grief of a dad with great ins but not a cent for his sick son- because he turned 18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Minutemaniac What I "recall" is watching parents negotiate payments with greedy ins companies instead of being with their dying child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JaceX please tell me more about this "plan in place"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of their shit is made in China. But if the Trump -panzees don't care. https://t.co/cCYNyccsr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents of children with pre-existing conditions are terrified today. This is literally life or death for millions. #SaveACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, starting to kind of feel sorry for the guy. That's the problem with us liberals – too many human feelings #TrumpPressConference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! Don't get too distracted by #goldenshowergate -keep paying attention #sessionsconfirmation https://t.co/r2r5BtTsVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarmenG1983 @realDonaldTrump probably not a lot of ppl jealous of Donny today #goldenshowergate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump now would be a great time to release your tax returns- you know, to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump can you imagine Obama tweeting "so-and-so likes me!" Lol you're insecure #mondaymotivation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry, @realDonaldTrump - say the magic words "radical Islamic terrorism" to fix this!#FortLauderdale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what's the plan to stop the other 75% of illegal immigrants who come here by plane? A "great net"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ridiculous. US taxpayers will bear this burden. Mexico won't pay, either will you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospitals are so screwed #MakeAmericaSickAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump when exactly was it great? 1950's? 1800's? I'm seriously curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump he can raise all the money he wants, as long as it's not pay for play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKStahlUSA you didn't hear? We're no longer draining the swamp. We're frolicking in it! Yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[37 percent of repubs support the man responsible for this. #unpresidented https://t.co/KG0b2ULeKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish trump voters were smart enough to read and comprehend this article https://t.co/fqj4qGTsKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump when will you realize, it doesn't matter how many people show up to watch the circus. Circuses still suck.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>