<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Call for rethink on working week, study warns of health risks https://t.co/hwcxbdB7A3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a year old but still a very powerful read, Minimum Wage, Minimum Chance: On Being Nickel and Dimed in 2016 - https://t.co/N8WN4NxJRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACTU vice-president Sally McManus likely to be union body's first female secretary https://t.co/FfcO6y0hPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal Donor Insists He Has No Influence On Party Policy https://t.co/6nHaMRz8Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did any self-respecting journalist continued participating after this happened? https://t.co/cbgUKw5ej5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Democrats should hold the line and filibuster against Neil Gorsuch | Lucia Graves https://t.co/iEKXOdqGrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We wouldn’t want to be where you guys are, that’s for sure”, on Inside Story https://t.co/OMPuKHEpjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How The New York Times plans to get Australia “into the bloodstream” of its coverage of global events https://t.co/CFKycJ4Gz7 via @NiemanLab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we really call schools private when they get so much public money? | Chris Bonnor and Bernie Shepherd https://t.co/rJquifHRiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families hit with rising BYOD school technology costs https://t.co/yebnlApIiW via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and the Republicans Are on a Suicide Mission Together  https://t.co/1Etst6Fjbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Opposition to DeVos Swells, Hope for Her Rejection Builds - https://t.co/s25TuJ7ade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-truth politics: a short look at a long history, on Inside Story https://t.co/1DtnAaXBvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians All Let Us Rejoice... In Changing The Date https://t.co/KxTDcH1JvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull should put 'inclusive growth' at centre of budget, say unions https://t.co/3CJWnaxh1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas for a new electoral system in the US https://t.co/xXMGXfZfPP via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise... Trump Is Said to Keep James Comey as F.B.I. Director https://t.co/g5WXESjQyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought 'Organic Fairtrade Sneakers Lowcuts All Black' on Etiko Shop https://t.co/AslaF8mxjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia’s conservative government fiddles on climate policy while the country burns | Lenore Taylor https://t.co/hfHipcOwA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GetUp is fighting back against the Turnbull Government's automated debt letter fraud. Can you chip in? https://t.co/dxWFcE15bd via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathtaking how much today's Liberal party hates individual liberty https://t.co/uaE8hsHizU via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually @ColinBarnett it's not part of our culture for the state to tell people what to wear. If you don't like it, resign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Is Making Journalism Great Again https://t.co/1CZLjHIuCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to target the top end of town and the obscene profits of the super-rich | Helen Szoke https://t.co/3TwpjGqmvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shocking statistic https://t.co/w3YqqZdRRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calm down folks. How can Steve Ciobo govern on behalf of the ruling class if he can't hobnob with them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous owners hope ancient eel traps will be recognised as world heritage. I do too. https://t.co/muX4dvHaEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t forget that Megyn Kelly is a racial demagogue: https://t.co/LtDPT0n4kh via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Coalition flushed Labor's years of economic prosperity down the gurgler https://t.co/4dVIci47hI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Coalition flushed Labor's years of economic prosperity down the gurgler https://t.co/4dVIchMvT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if business lobbyists really just want to 'align' Saturday &amp; Sunday #penaltyrates, how about 200% on Saturday? https://t.co/5MdEVU7yl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaires get more leeway than vulnerable citizens. It’s obscene | Richard Denniss https://t.co/VvzUdKpzMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI @vanbadham.. Peter Martin: Labor ought to stop pandering to millionaires https://t.co/FlpzC4giC2 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kerry and Israel: Too Little and Too Late https://t.co/rnqSeARGSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That the Israeli ambassador to the UN thinks settlements are akin to the French building in Paris is truly alarming https://t.co/pB8dMmOO7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell to Brexit: some valedictory reminders https://t.co/MaQNnXABzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry Gerard... ABC most trusted news source, poll shows https://t.co/Oy1qr24F0J via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Windschuttle's fabrication of Aboriginal voting, on Inside Story https://t.co/TXu9DGYm76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to End the Electoral College https://t.co/rcZ70iNKix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Fraser Gov program helped Kuninjku people of Arnhem Land prosper and how Hockey and Abbott trashed it https://t.co/ECQ844AI49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buck Up, Democrats, and Fight Like Republicans https://t.co/M8cvEAeoD5@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Turns Out Spending More Probably Does Improve Education https://t.co/1ICIsQTYtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what's the difference between malcolm gladwell and a pseudo-intellectual sophist? https://t.co/pU07sJerhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers should be an example and that means speaking their minds on refugees https://t.co/uNTh4qCY8V via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the message from tame Dem response is you can f... us over &amp; get away with it https://t.co/zpDsrjZ4v8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The birth of modernity.. Bernard Keane goes off https://t.co/GzDYsqBImH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[greed n. excessive or rapacious desire especially for wealth or possessions https://t.co/QYwGS4RPXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Declining quality and equity in schooling part of John Howard's legacy https://t.co/PR3YwTo7Ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet parliaments continue to block the will of the people: why Australia should  have citizen-initiated statutes lik… https://t.co/wc8T0yetd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just donated to @Wikipedia. Support free knowledge! #iloveWikipedia https://t.co/Eovtr7S3Jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Queensland, Aborigines are still fighting for their unpaid wages https://t.co/S3rwEM5Ho8 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ABC staff say Michelle Guthrie ‘out of her depth’ https://t.co/UPQcYKP1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aroostook County, MA, voted 4 Trump &amp; to increase minimum wage. How important is economic populism to Dem comeback?  https://t.co/kLTdKNKWrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traders Bet on Big Stimulus Spending. Congress May Not Go Along. https://t.co/qi8ZpNhGKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My review of Bernie's new book... Against oligarchy: the book of #Bernie, on Inside Story https://t.co/o7H6FQNWip #BernieSanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Chris Bonnor writes, Grattan’s #Gonski circuit breaker is a timely one https://t.co/Diu0yPTvxa #edutweetoz #ozedchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US has been at war 93% of the time since 1776, maybe Australia should rethink strategic dependence https://t.co/Csufw9tQTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Electoral College wasn't meant to overturn elections... according to Garrett Epps in the Atlantic https://t.co/Rkf9bZKdQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economists are underestimating the costs of letting small Rust Belt cities shrink https://t.co/zB7XeiTuGP via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fossil fuel giants using questionable deductions to shrink tax bills, Auditor-General warns https://t.co/X9uukVO8z5 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Circuit breaker: a new compact on school funding | Grattan Institute https://t.co/ORFgma88nB via @grattaninst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For many, sexual harassment is a part of work. After all, the customer is always right. Well, no https://t.co/4OvpBPHLMw #ausunions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1966: One last election loss for “old Labor”, on Inside Story https://t.co/TbBxgKrIxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull government threatens to sue grandfather over 'save Medicare' website https://t.co/56N2uQpB3Z via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HISTORIC DECISION: Wisconsin Federal Court Strikes Down Partisan Gerrymander, Adopts Groundbreaking Legal Standard https://t.co/AKASBVxamv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indians, Slaves, and Mass Murder: The Hidden History https://t.co/ePSoXS7OT5 via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Reich's 8-Point Plan for a New Democratic Party https://t.co/oviuAJGYn7 via @RollingStone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Let’s Rebuild our Infrastructure, Not Provide Tax Breaks to Big Corporations and Wall Stre…” by @SenSanders https://t.co/tHtD99DPZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence that Jeff Sessions is complete scum: his fight against funding poor public schools in Alabama https://t.co/wKq3NZKKhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems need Comey https://t.co/JvGO00jEpH?? No they don't. They need to apply blowtorch to him, send msge that dirty GOP tricksters will pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI Brian Toohey on the official history of ASIO is very good https://t.co/OzniEWXvbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney General Jeff Sessions? A "Direct Attack" on Nation's Minorities - https://t.co/YTYWz1VRrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Bernie Sanders backed one of Wall Street’s favorite senators to lead Democrats https://t.co/W7jJ8XWKK3 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And when bill fails energy should be invested in getting enough states into the national popular vote interstate co… https://t.co/7BABQEhdNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will "fiscal conservatives" be half as concerned as they are by #Gonski? Or is their real problem that Gonski benef… https://t.co/IcDhwQNuJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real reason the US has an Electoral College: to protect slave states https://t.co/zAtnBMatA6 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ausunions this is how 2.1 million American workers won a pay raise last week @unionsaustralia @GedKACTU… https://t.co/ca4IFukWHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How American workers are winning the fight against starvation wages. And #paidsickdays as well. https://t.co/zBFWh44NIg #RaiseTheWage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amidst doom &amp; gloom, 2.1 million of America's poorest workers won a big pay increase last week https://t.co/zBFWh44NIg #inequality #poverty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @ProjectFairness and others. Inspiring wins in dark times. https://t.co/xjcGBFU2OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every school should do this. @ACTEducation? Sydney public school embraces fair trade uniforms https://t.co/TCHlWIuTIe #AussieEd #edutweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the #NPVIC will stop electoral college-popular vote splits and encourage voting in red and blue states… https://t.co/g086ngbDAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electoral college is large part of the problem &gt; outside a handful of swing states, there's little incentive to vot… https://t.co/mJvev7nUme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The battle for the future of Democratic party begins.. https://t.co/S3EH6pewpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus... the US now has a president who doesn't even bother to pretend he believes his own acceptance speech https://t.co/HWuEDWITLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marijuana is now legal in California https://t.co/HhZlT6Leia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second medicinal marijuana measure of the night gets up in North Dakota https://t.co/Aq1hjZL3t7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump with a Republican Congress. Fucking great. https://t.co/W9XGdUYmg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary is faced with the prospect of a concession speech having won the popular vote, one week after Comey. That's tough. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whichever way this goes, US needs reform so the winner of the national popular vote is the winner https://t.co/DKItFoSddP #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce that's not a lot to go on at this point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a high chance of another electoral college-popular vote split, attempted reforms are more urgent than ever https://t.co/bi2yKELuLI ($)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham plus Ohio and New Hampshire, must-wins for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While everyone's obsessing about Florida, North Carolina is looking good for #Hillary https://t.co/ieQZiIc2FD #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio wins in FA, Evan Bayh behind in IA... Not looking good as far as the senate goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicinal marijuana now legal in Florida. One pro-pot measure up, 8 more in play https://t.co/lCgakdz6iK #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump has to win FL, GA, NC &amp; OH where it's 50-50 + NH where he's well behind on early count #ElectionNight… https://t.co/2SWtyrmNzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FL, OH, NC, GA all looking 50-50 but even if Trump wins them all he might still not get to 270 https://t.co/PyHAuRc3cU #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All eyes are on presidential race but votes on pot, gun control, healthcare, death penalty will also change America https://t.co/fIMxHjogqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretOConno5 i can't stop watching this now https://t.co/WHAMoUIDpr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>