<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking confirmed list of Mt Albert candidates expected by 4pm tomorrow @publicaddress @JulieAnneGenter @jacindaardern @scoutriver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of doing geology around the Kaikoura #eqnz event. Discount, #ftw. https://t.co/ks84juARr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Claire_Phipps excruciating? maybe, but if it gets 1.6 mil to sign on, great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rnz_news @meganjwhelan (ahem) headline online says 'years', body of story says 'months'
https://t.co/MSES05jbmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nixon (effectively) fired the US Attorney-General on Oct 20, 1973. Didn't end well for him either.

via… https://t.co/aO7jy5XQQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiecampbell leave them, I'd say. No obvious danger - they'll head back home when they expect to be fed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pearce of the LA Times. Also @Fahrenthold of Washington Post.

Journalism done the right way. https://t.co/znKG03h0AO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways @HaydenDonnell "news is just saying what people don't want you to print", or something like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC wondering what you said to the Wellington lawyer who called you on for wrong process on asking for names? @lyallbaynz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdpearce "but you are better informed"

English jurist, FE Smith, later Lord Birkenhead. replying to a snarky judge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenceMillar "appose"

say it all, really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchieDaRival yes, thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH the tricoteuse wins again. Yuss. @edmuzik @jmodoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am also now following Sydney Ember of the NY Times. #prevRT

Partly for her job; party for her awesome Twitter handle - @melbournecoal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#prevRT Am now following @KLewis44, Obama's spokesperson

h/t  @andreas212nyc, a good tweep also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling goodness gracious. Trolls exist, don't they?

But (a) last 72 hours has shown there's a lot of good people
(b) you're one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico heading for 2mil, I'm thinking. Incredibly, at 2.30am (UK) it was still ticking over at 100s/minute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lobby_nz suspect that @pmbillenglish would be more likely to understand the original "mene mine tekel upharsin"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QueenofCobden points off, however, for the presentation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr you're finding out about buses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH @David_Cormack I now use the @NZParliament list of 108 (+1 post-Mt Albert) @matthewjpb 
https://t.co/Jdtim1lxnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomDavies be over in a jiffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomDavies mine's a Yorkshire Tea, thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[such a British exhortation.

this petition, at UK Parliament has gained over 100k signatures in under 2 hours… https://t.co/gCydKkQWmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hurrah for Lorde

five-tweet thread, speaking to millions of people, with specific calls to action https://t.co/4gutLEnuM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl Can POTUS turn off the internet? you asked.

Internet NZ honcho @jordantcarter will know the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @michaelwoodnz Westminster used to have a no hats/scarves rules. Stopped MPs sending their coachmen into voting lobbies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelcolhoun there's the 25th Amendment (although it won't be invoked this year)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwoodnz it would be a breach of SO409 to send @richardhills777 into the Chamber in your stead however]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one good thing about a shitty day in America - #understatement - is how many wonderful people there are in the USA &amp; worldwide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek @jgmccl neither please. They sound humorous, and it is anything but.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[looks like full-on fascism - "Trump Protects Nation" screams Breitbart, and then there's the awful TV ad

https://t.co/BLFoBtyiwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(minor in the scheme of things)

hahah, Newshub says Ohakea is an Akld army air base #AucklandSprawl https://t.co/IhPRzkrGNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico Am now hearing @WilliamShatner saying to @GeorgeTakei: 

"Warp factor nine for the RT engine please Mr Sulu"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KendraWrites @thatjohn yes, the original (re JFK) went way over my head @tlnicola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall stuff of nightmares. And yes, I remember Failsafe (1964)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia true @dimsie PS, best with the citizenship application. If there's any way I could help, do sing out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @JackieVimo is one of the most important tweeters in the world rn.

Policy Analyst, National Immigration Law Cen… https://t.co/dgdb0EEc62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This . He also said: "This is a dark hour for America."

Congressman for 30+ yrs.
Marched w/ Martin Luther King. https://t.co/NaExImZktC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @DubiousStephen you're a lot closer to that rohe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @DubiousStephen or, against the Nat party vote + the ACT or UF party vote. (Which is much the same thing as prev tweet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @DubiousStephen on that matter, any candidate there (as in my own Ohariu) is running against the MP + Nat candidate total.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji thanks. Yes, saw the Zahawi story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 9 days, Parlt starts with the Debate on the PM's Stmt, total of 13 hours.

Let's hope many MPs use it to denounce Trump's action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph from experience I find that, Oy, you, is also effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji do you have a source please? (had a quick search, incl her own bio, couldn't find out whether she has US citizenship or not)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams one does what one can to establish a brand. 

(also, scuffs foot, says, Aw shucks)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this, re earlier tweet. Also it's Cllr Peter Gilberd of Wgtn City Council. My bad re spelling. https://t.co/MiCdoYedJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great foray at farmers market, Johnsonville School. Mushrooms $3 for 500gm bag. Yes, $3.

Also, sighted Peter Gilbert of Wgtn Cith Council.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen "Oh yes he is"

Gonna be four long years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnat no.@MattNippert  Lots of journos tweeted (Fri) that DIA said now would be early next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia snorted at the tweep earlier who wanted to be in the room when Prince Philip meets the Tangerine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji can't wait for you to live tweet Flying High. Then, Casablanca. #PlayItAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yep, that's a genuine Trump tweet, 18 Sep 2012. h/t @latikambourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdpearce uber-trolling: "fewer than 300 protestors"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_ripple @jgmccl well, she could hardly lie back and think of the Queen, could she?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aethylred @jgmccl sorry, best was 4.07% 2008]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould ISP would give you the router, I'd have thought? Perhaps on 12 month contract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@real_Deity noted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[numerous journos tweeting that #ThielDump is not happening this arvo. Guess they're secretly happy as
(a) beer o'cl… https://t.co/88vPw0xfnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelcolhoun how? (I've forgotten)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH @Megan_Woods happens to the best of us, Madame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxpayers Onion has total equity of less than $2k - and $40k of accounts payable. That $40k is *five months* of their non-salary budget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megan_Woods um, Antarctica, with the first 'c'. Signed, Pedantic.

also, have a great trip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxpayers Onion wrote off a $33k donation. Seems they booked it when a pledge was made but someone reneged on the poor folks at the Onion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so the Taxpayers Onion have just filed their latest annual a/cs. $11k membership subs &amp; $185K donations - they don't say who donated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @jmodoh Speaker has approved designations that list MPs can use (in their paid material.) Pretty sure that's not one. @cjsbishop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@REasther ahem. #NotAllMiddleAgedBaldGuys, thank you very much @toby_etc @CherylBernstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankEndrullat @MrJonathanKing @garywhitta 
Also, @potus a/c is linked to easily-guessable Gmail account
https://t.co/HI8RWxNtbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safehavencafeUK thanks. I am aware of need to be security-conscious, but am not a tech expert @lyndonhood @WitchBrain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rtp NZ has a history of MPs' comms being attacked. I remember back to 1996. Yes, I've written to all Parlt parties this morning re 2FA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rtp If you don't, you are vulnerable to villains guessing and attacking your email. Especially if you are in public life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people, take 30 sec to check you have two-factor authentication ON for twitter password-reset-requests

Settings/Security/Password Reset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[speaking of opsec catastrophes, what's bet Trump's press sec hasn't changed this password?

https://t.co/JDZspPd7uW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus wept. What an utter opsec security fail by Trump. (Click to see)

Linking POTUS a/c to Gmail, easy broken by… https://t.co/cRlOzxcDj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beechworks 
Rule 1. The wife is always right
Rule 2. In case of doubt see rule 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oath. Yes, there should be #Accountability re Thiel. https://t.co/HmXZdP7GnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould hate to tell you, homeowners don't cute &amp; adorable. It's all serious business. Serious all the way down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth @torshin @norightturnnz @SamSachdevaNZ @nzhpolitics Would be (very) surprised if PPS got any Ministerial Services funding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torshin @norightturnnz @SamSachdevaNZ @nzhpolitics MP support budget (incl staffing) doesn't change for PPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sstewart_nz "they're just not that into you"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @Becs @KatydidNZ diagnosis for someone 11 days ago "it's terminal (pause) ileitis"

Not that meaning of terminal; another one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day Three. Damn near every journo has been (quite properly) keeping the pressure on Internal Affairs &amp; PM re Thiel. #Accountability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin also RMA. Palmer had a bit to do with that. @robhosking @BenThomasNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia Bannon first. Currently chortling over @WhiteHouseLeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndonhood in Philadelphia, circa 1789: "What do we have Dr Johnson, a republic or a monarchy?"

"A republic, if you can keep it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth @Katieshould as you were. 10 weeks for original contract?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould woo-hoo! Also, that seems like a long settlement on the original contract - six weeks or so?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin Gerry Wall was the last Speaker who never held Ministerial warrant at some stage. For obvious reasons. @BenThomasNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin Ministerial-level package, without the pressure? Can't see that she'd turn it down, if it came her way. @BenThomasNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[events in Washington over the past five days make me realise that Spitting Image made a documentary

https://t.co/w8KBJWhJAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming @simonpnz also (while filming in Prohibition days) he roared:

"Who the heck put pineapple juice in my pineapple juice?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz "Whenever I feel the urge to exercise, I lie down until it passes" - Oscar Wilde, or WC Field, I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Herald has text of Clark's (classy) letter to UNDP staff announcing decision to leave at the end of her term.
https://t.co/YURXsAgsFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk (2/2) Also fm memory, lobbyists for a dam putting a report in front of DoI eyes. Seems viable to target ads to White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk had seen reports (2015?) of Facebook ads being targeted to a single DC block. Fm memory, Dept of Interior. (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nikki_Macdonald @GlennMcCNZ ahem. Headline at variance w/ body of story. I know, "leaves at end of 2nd 4-year term" isn't as shocking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for the record: deleted first incorrect version of this tweet, and re-posted. I had Brown 4 yrs &amp; Derviş 6 yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, much different story. Clark leaving after 2x four-year terms.

No UNDP honcho has ever served 12 yrs (i.e. 3x4) https://t.co/pacsHEQFSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(2/2) UNDP established 1966, had 5x US honchos till 1999, only one served &gt;6 yrs. Then:
Brown (UK) 6 yrs
Derviş (Turkey) 4 yrs
Clark 8 yrs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>