<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@technerdian @NoelRock I get your point. I don't feel privilege is adequately policed or violations punished. Absolutes tend to be dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock @thejournal_ie article doesn't make mention of the fine and reparations to the individuals damaged. What did it cost Mary Lou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock seriously? When? 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock I just struggle with the idea that unanswerable TDs with malice aforethought bring the weight of the state to bear on individuals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock and of course the Dail does a fabulous job of regulating itself and no one libels citizens with impunity #alternatefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HiberniaForum Let @Buseireann become insolvent. Put in receivership. Sell off assets. Have private bus operators bid for routes. Simples!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinCityUni @clgNaFianna @NoelRock Let's get the word out and support a Glasnevin institution: @stvincentsbball https://t.co/8vqH87g2nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note this is the big boys playing Super League Basketball!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free entry at DCU Sports complex Sunday 3:15pm @stvincentsbball v. @warriors_bc. ALL WELCOME. Fantastic intro to BASKETBALL @offtheball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/u04w9CIoEA the ultimate political whore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep in mind graphic depicts expensive bureaucracy created to give out funds taken from taxpayers who can't be trus… https://t.co/CA8XHEq7NR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishexaminer the sooner the better. Replace with private sector services not hampered by NTA being downtown office of Bus Eireann.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad I've spent all that time at DUB airport queuing at passport control. Especially from LHR #CommonTravelArea  https://t.co/TSJZGAQzre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. What an arse! https://t.co/q7i7uMcQKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa Hillary Clinton realised the popular vote is irrelevant and used strategic campaign to win the electoral college #alternativefact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conormeany all a bit chicken and egg. Hard to get sponsorship w/o turnout. Hard to compete w/o sponsor. Hard to get turnout w/o competition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conormeany a little marketing by @BballIrl might help more than 12 people show up too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrapCrokePark1 what's with Irish people thinking their opinion and outrage about US President matters to anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we all know they don't call travelling in the NBA, but seriously, that was a full-on stroll! https://t.co/DoGPRN3lWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrapCrokePark1 although with #GE17 coming up the gobshites will likely step in and rescue it w taxpayer money "in the national interest"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrapCrokePark1 probably better a fresh start when it collapses. Opportunity for private buses on level playing field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreasLeKirk Dude. Put it back. That whole thread was frigging fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrKRedmond seems Progressivism becomes steadily more recognizable as secular orthodox religion. No counter-Reformation can be tolerated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LavinnaW @atheistie they'll go at Easter too. 100% increase!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanganley Agreed. Was wondering at @harr57's too low comment like there is some amount that's not too low. Wonder how much is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harr57 why? Tax by definition is due if the law requires it. Is there is some moral amount that should be due?
@declanganley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newshub_Ireland @davidmcw assuming most of those companies goods are UK originated exports. Interesting to know percentages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newshub_Ireland @davidmcw how'd you figure that? They'll all shut their subsidiaries? Huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector GE votes go on sale for €1000 a piece. #GE17
https://t.co/13FsFzJgej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beyonce4pres better on govt handouts than employed. That way they're dependant. The Progressive way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesleyDolan @StewartLewis2 @Dalek_fan so more of an EU IMF bailout of banks laundered through Ireland and billed to the Irish taxpayer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesleyDolan @StewartLewis2 @Dalek_fan the so called bailout money was in Ireland for mere days before heading to German (and other) banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gutenmorgan what are European Values?
Who decided that a pan-European value system be created and when did this happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanhealy do what about what?

You have a choice:
a. Buy them
b. Don't buy them

What's confusing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubFireBrigade on the plus side, 10 days ago that would've been a house fire!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McAslanClan likewise up etc. But junior basketball is indoors! Off to the peoples Republic of Cork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swissport sitting on BA flight for 10 mins while your staff can't move a stairs 6m. Pitiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charmagh @DrJimGray @Lapps100 how so? You lost me. I was commenting on excess of unproductive admins in HSE and DoH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhistleIRL well because @kpgumbo is the arbiter of importance. No one shall frivolously discuss what he has not approved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJimGray @Lapps100 and yet health gets the biggest budget. Should the focus perhaps be on cleaning out surplus admin and waste?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRutherford one they grew in a vat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremyrhammond @FriedrichHayek @BobMurphyEcon oh come on! Consistency is so like, boring ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loc8code @MrsWookie1 @EndaKennyTD thanks for the link to @PA_Consulting. That is some of the best BS I have ever read! @Dept_CCAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatKennyNT WRONG. HSE needs to get away from crises mode and do some strategic and then tactical WORK to organise into a SYSTEM that works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanhealy @inmo I'm sure the HSE will lead the charge villifying them. Always the front line that takes the pain while bureaucrats hide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinPoil yup. Used to bring minor complaints to triage wait room. But was on me and against policy. Bureaucrats' asses covered as always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@re_keogh @ProfJohnCrown repeatedly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YxKwXdPAOl This is fundamentally a failure of HSE &amp; Health Dept MANAGEMENT. More money to same incompetents is NOT the answer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinPoil used to piss me off no end standing round with pt on stretcher while urgent calls dropped in my territory. And that was in Houston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinPoil most medics I know want back in field to make real runs. Pt must be accepted by qualified staff. Legal requirement!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinPoil No. Once EMS takes on patient they must handover care to receiving facility. If hosp can't/won't accept pt EMS can't dump them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GroganRichard @ghook @HighNoonNT right because efficiency is the first thing to mind when considering public sector admin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobbyFM104 off to Holyhead with you mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrapCrokePark1 no shit! Anyone not left of Trotsky is labelled "right wing" these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrapCrokePark1 as opposed to the regular left which had been doing a fabulous job, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrKRedmond @TransformDrugs how many times do you have to be told about the application of logic to government?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micrabam what did it say? She's run scared and deleted it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GgJm3gnGFg Regression to the mean? Do they cover statistics at all in Journo school?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrKRedmond how does it define "offence"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa not a penny. There's no such thing as public funds, just tax taken from taxpayers who earn3d it and spent by bureaucrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PyFdF4YtqB Is there a point where private sector workers will refuse to pay for voracious incompetent pub sec bureaucrats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejournal_ie or you could prepare properly, know where you're going and dress properly especially boots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond @HunkyGayJesus do you think they might hold civil servants responsible for their job performance? That would be outrageous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HiberniaForum @Independent_ie the price is paid by private sector and our children to pub sector. 'We' has been split into us and them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimwaterson @mon242 or was Private Eye the only one he couldn't shift as the others sold out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meathcoco what are the hours for the Ashbourne recycling centre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastNT @Paschald ran for cover with labour court to blame. Was pension value considered by labour court? Your call in the end #manUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WBVT_98FM what did it say? They bailed ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubFireBrigade nice job. I always found a real result makes up for about 15 BS 'taxi to hospital' calls!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertaSaidThat @DetroitQSpider @Independent most efficient campaign ever then, right? Max Elec College w min wasted effort on pop vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ocdr2z3Fqo Strategy villifying drug co. developing small population drug may work this time. What effect on future development?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HunkyGayJesus the true skill is in getting it between syllables! Absa-fuckin-loutely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skippergimp @daraobriain ridiculous! Trains would get flat spots due to leaves and cause chaos ... Right @piccadillyline?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnellyStephen Have you mistakenly engaged them in robust political discourse, or perhaps disagreed in some way? Problematic + offensive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaturaleBeeReed so a white woman can't wear hair clips like this because Solange did it and she's black? or did I miss something? @deray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gemmaod1 When TDs use parliamentary privelege for an ideology-driven attack on a citizen, they invite such "legal threat"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealEddieHobbs reading that I thought he makes a great case for electing O'Leary. #PravdaAxis @IrishTimesOpEd @rte leftists not happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEVECONTRATI @SkepticNikki @michaelshermer @l1ght3n @charli_says please ... Troll!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deray can someone decode this? Apparently this is outrageous ... Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC what about tourists? Does the constitution or bill of rights apply? Or should they stay home ... not safe from USA govt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC so legal immigrants have no constitutional protection until they become citizens after min 5 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? Chose to service all the trains at the same time? #logistics https://t.co/qYMYk31L8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marmian: scrum half; in case of emergency deploy as centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard today about a second year student on his 8th concussion. Off for 6 months this time. My thought was How is a… https://t.co/8dH5H7bFo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa 😀I know a few builders wouldn't piss on him if he was on fire!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa you saw where I mentioned responsibility, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa clear line of responsibility no one to pass the buck to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa single small task force in central govt directly contracting with contractors. Splitting out into incompetent cocos not feasible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa instead of sovereign bonds to pay voracious pub sector use them for cap ex housing schools + transport projects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HangBlaa councils couldn't organise the proverbial piss up in a brewery so how can they build houses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrKRedmond so neutralish on the right side, with a side order of smug holier that thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrKRedmond @Independent_ie does being neutral mean there is no principle on which we will stand? We're equivocal about everything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the date. https://t.co/Eop2j03Jaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickyRR @jlocke13 @VABVOX @francescrook @HillaryClinton why not? Do you not understand how your presidential election works?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillStewNeuro @BBCNews "Norfolk Police does not plan to investigate." Cause beating someone to death is OK if sport! Outside pub, different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomClonan No doubt. Depends whether trying to manipulate people via fear or discuss if 3D-printed firearm is real @NickOBrien999 @guardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paschald @P_Bulletin you could also address the use of sovereign bonds to finance PS payroll while failing to build infrastructure.

No?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paschald @P_Bulletin make sure you explain kicking the commuter rail infrastructure can down the road again while you're at it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickOBrien999 @TomClonan @guardian "have not been tested, but" ... scary facts about weapons "like" these. Shit journalism #StudySTEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonOCon @CllrKRedmond @KarlBrophy less the 23% VAT of course oh and the import duties.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>