<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@beebee880 What ever happened to Mary on the bus? She was in everyone's business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DweezilZappa Please try for Ireland. Would love to see you again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy how can you make a techno chocolate bar? Doesn't make sense man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy I felt like that once, but it turned out to be a dodgy chicken jalfrezi. Was up all night shitting liquid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beebee880 Have you ever smoked a cigarette Beebee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulClement1972 for better or worse we're in this together now. Best of luck #SwanseaCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beebee880 I'm from Ireland. You should come over here some time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valkilmer happy new year Val]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RetoKromer @kieranjol @ecodonohoe both are great, but the Teeling would be my preference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maffewgregg as him to reupload that video and see what he says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@historyinmoment the French...Always ahead of their time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MJMcKean why is Justin Beiber using the Spinal Tap font? https://t.co/T0EGNLvejX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble better than his taste in defenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worsteditorever I'm having the same problems looking for hd vhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE is there an outage in the sandymount area at the moment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOddsBible go on then you twisted my arm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy surgeon simulator is brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruceprichard @HeyHeyItsConrad Any chance you guys can livestream the live show for those of us who aren't going to 'Mania?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy we all have our weird obsessions Limmy. Leave her to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DweezilZappa Any chance of your tour coming to Ireland? I'd love to see you play again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones Why don't you go up to HW then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnysBet welcome back* and lets hope it goes better than yesterdays one ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnysBet well that was nerve-racking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani why was Mickey Rourke translating for him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy he was recycled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worsteditorever idiot assistant looking for locked cut.If i told him once I've told him 1000 times its Untitled Sequence.01.copy.01.copy.01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrichardShow not worthy of its own episode but can you tell us the plan for GDTV and why it was forgotten about after a while #LoveToKnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandonfrmNJ jesus Christ Gabi looks like the Joker without makeup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kieranjol simultaneous does HD and SD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Szzandman hope you enjoy watching America lose!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@80sWrestlingPic @TheRock wow, does anyone know if video exists of this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Monsoon_Classic @TheFranchiseSD how many years had you been wrestling at this point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cobyhectic @TWooodley I think you mean @demianmaia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worsteditorever Superimpose old lady at computer over it and have it spin 360 degrees and you'll win a daytime Emmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWENetwork @REALSteamboat @steveaustinBSR wasn't that back bump from the rope what pretty much ended Steamboats career?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cobyhectic @ih8lukebarry damn right I'm bitter. We could have had a win over inaugural WWE Universal champ @FinnBalor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cobyhectic @ih8lukebarry not if you kept leaving teammates high and dry #hitandrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@beebee880 great picture. Lovely looking bus beebee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Saymun @OldWrestlingPic but Hogan was the champ in Feb 99?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@80sWrestlingPic Naitch looks a lot like Terra Rizin in this  @TripleH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKingRegal should have been the Nature Lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishNerds crowd let her down. Not one of these   https://t.co/XIOYh7OclX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealBobbyHeenan who was better, Stevens or Bockwinkel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is Asexual Pride day?  #HeterosexualPrideDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker don't worry, you'll be in your underpants in front of millions of people soon and everything will be better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDMitchell Dublin is lovely these days fyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougStanhope white label of black bush?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougStanhope Cool, i'll buy your book then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieDMJ @NoelEdmonds it tackles cancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringfox1 try some Teelings if you can find it. Lovely stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthePhoenix OMG I bet your tweeting from an iPhone 5s grandma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy can you tell yer da to cover up when he goes ootside https://t.co/mWtsznGtoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GerryAdamsSF I'm sorry to hear of your erectile disfunction problems. Maybe @Pele can help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSBible  Calamity @jamosfoundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKingRegal @80sWrestlingPic a bit generous with the ol body there!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's such a gorgeous days outside. I wish I had thicker curtains...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter this is a Photoshop. No such thing exists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy 20 mins in, what do they look like now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryAdamsSF yeah it's cotton picking weather out there alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice beer and @TheRealDisco on TV https://t.co/NuKosv1qGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maffewgregg they need to bring back little Naitch for all Charlottes matches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryAdamsSF shouldn't have packed all those dildos in your bag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RicFlairNatrBoy I love you Naitch, never change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrchrisaddison I'm thinking about you thinking about it. That's as good as exercising, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cobyhectic maybe if you draw the mcgregor tattoos on her it might make it easier?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dirtydutchman1 no love for KC? I bet you and Rufus had great matches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secrettourpro but won't you get more spin (slice/hook) from more loft?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy @WeegieJambo to be fair, that's more of an indifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aiannucci this is possibly the least inspiring picture I've ever seen. I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanJamesPoulter nice Star Trek jumper though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's no Mean Street Posse run in then #Wrestlemania is a failure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoringMilner post the text convo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganamram very Captain Beefheart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy nah, just a muffet of tea for mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKingRegal @WWEShop You don't look a day over 46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy very snazzy. I bet your friends will be so jealous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy that's not the Internet,  that's a mirror mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker Its not, you've been in a crisp induced coma for 6 months. Please wake up Gary, we all love you and hope you pull through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy How about cups of tea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanceStorm you don't want that dirty white boy in your house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosieLong start taking PCP to balance things out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidHerro that's why you leave they boys to come up with their own shit too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lexusireland Hi guys, can I get clarification on something please. What is the plural of Lexus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKevinNash Really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@testicleas it's also Pancake Tuesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloodyElbow @mookiealexander let's hope it doesn't go like the Irish boxing weigh in earlier today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worsteditorever tell me about it. 30:09 is still 30 secs!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @GerryAdamsSF what are you doing in Ireland @DaftLimmy ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lexusireland the Japanese Mercedes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cobyhectic if that happens I'll have to go get back in the ring for another run. Statistically I'd have a great chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKingRegal I really hope that's a shadow on your trunks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMartinToGo I'm extremely allergic to qualification and have left my epi-pen at home. For the love of God disqualify me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConanOBrien I hate it because I cannot afford anything as I am so worthless 😧]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carrie_Rachel @portlandia @IFC there's nothing sexier than mortality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealAlSnow @AlSnowAcademy gotta work on that promo timing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeSnakeDDT Just watched the film. Cried like a sumbitch! I'm so glad you now have the life you've always wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maffewgregg @MAGFest @Codstermania Either way can you film it and put it on the next Botchamania?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charltonbrooker Good show. No Stanhope though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy what is the name of the song on Adventure Call? I heard it playing in a charity shop once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beebee880 I are on a tran]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>