<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mellopuffy One of my locals used to do them. Sadly, they're long gone... =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annaturley @WomenDefyUKIP This from the man who insisted that he would not accept a 52-48 vote for Remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is promising 'war in the South China sea' and another war in Middle East.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whilst at prep-school, Neil Gorsuch founded a club called 'Fascism Forever'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph 'I Know What You Did Last Concert'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some footage of antifascists beating a Yiannopulos supporter unconscious with metal bars shows utter thuggery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpeacekeeper @simonbwilson Says the Government that gutted the Training Incentive Allowance and personally attacked those who objected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairfax printed a piece written by the PM on Stuff, a news website. That's not news, it's pure spin, and they know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Trump's green light to anti-gay discrimination is very bad. If he is impeached, much, much worse will follow at the hands of Mr Pence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick It is an excuse for a two year old, not a grown man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aravosis @LostArcNZ Precisely what Mr Trump repeatedly and falsely claimed about Ms Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlyfrozen @LostArcNZ @NewshubNZ It's an 'alternative infographic'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @bootstheory I remember when they "backed" beneficiaries by making Training Incentive Allowance a practical irrelevance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessalaprofessa @GlobalRevLive The GOP loves streams. Of toxic waste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The words 'candidly' and 'frankly' are diplomatic dynamite. https://t.co/iDFAfrAn7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hcirePT I agree with you about the change in tone, and I think it's more than slight. I do wonder whether it will be temporary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly one-third of the refugees in Australia's offshore camps have been in detention for more than two years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Turnbull learns that political cowardice is inevitably treated as a sign ow weakness by Mr Trump. https://t.co/uWzFkloIG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Spencer is celebrating what he calls Mr Trump's "deJudafication" of Holocaust Remembrance Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneTHoye You're absolutely right. I'll never forget just how popular Dr Brash's Orewa rant was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFluker That's exactly the gist of what I was just about to tweet. =)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFluker Or eavesdrop on the bus...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned French at school. I've rarely used it. But learning a second language taught me an extraordinary amount about English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many on social media who don't want children to speak Te Reo seem to have great difficulty even speaking English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery Overheard on the bus: 'They was sayin' on talkback that the Greenies want to only let us speak Maori'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatchSilentHill @1428_Elm Damn that makes me feel old! Silent Hill was the first game I ever fell in love with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasRimmerNZ The Little piece of wood reminds me of Eric Cartman; the English piece reminds me of Munch's 'The Scream'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sallies store around the corner from me has so much unsaleable junk dumped outside. https://t.co/SEjAxvEWX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Albert has Labour, Green, TOP, Communist, Socialist, and at least one left-wing Independent candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek @NZGreens 'Vote Labour and get the Greens' will be the gist of his election campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa @reckonsemoji I'm not sure when the requirement began for local body elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa @reckonsemoji He polled third-last in Albany Ward in 2010. (In a field of 19 candidates, for two positions).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa @reckonsemoji Hold the phone! Does that mean he isn't a scrap metal dealer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa @reckonsemoji I don't think it was at a General Election. I'll do a little research. It would have been an Auckland seat, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care about Mr Trump's appearance and I don't care whether or not he is scared of stairs. I care a lot about his horrible policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik A fantastic score. I really like how CM Sydenham has a low price, high turnover sales strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've "got to the bottom of it" for the Minister. The oil companies decided they wanted even higher profits. https://t.co/cH0dEfishu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik I love it so much! Where from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transparency_a1 The country already has a (bipartisan) refugee policy even worse than his.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that I've had a chance to listen to Mr English's comments, I agree that his criticism of Mr Trump's ban was both indirect and weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks as though Sean Spicer's retweeting of @TheOnion actually happened, and is not just 'fake news'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec City police have announced that they consider the atrocity there to be a terrorist attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Sean Spicer really retweet @TheOnion? It just seems to good to be true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reject any politics in which human beings stop being regarded as individuals and are viewed only as a member of a category.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CearaProut I am sending all my best wishes and my kindest and warmest thoughts to you. I'm sorry that I can't do more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delete Uber? My Uber is the bus. And sometimes I can't even afford that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. 1 problem with impeaching Mr Trump: Mr Pence. No. 2 problem: the politics of which Mr Trump is only one representative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 It stands for Hero Of the Masses Of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have witnessed three motor vehicle accidents today. All relatively minor, luckily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Trump's decision to simply ignore the court ruling on his immigration ban is exceptionally disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo I've already ignored three calls to the dinner table, so I'll be off Twitter for an hour or so, but thanks for the discussion. =)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo who are calling this measure a cop-out (and far worse). (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo That's a valid point, but now he is also required to govern. And on right-wing social media, there are more than a few (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesDKArt @SGardinier It's certainly become common to forget, for eg, that an impeachment of Trump would result in a President Pence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notchyo1 @serenity22 @JoshuaGreen It's the logical extension of what every 'America Firster' is referring to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo and not his left one. The more demagogic the campaign rhetoric, the wider the gap between the hustings and actually governing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo We have different views on that point. I think Trump, because of the nature of his campaign, is vulnerable on his right flank (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo That was my question. Do you think some of his 'base' will realise the contradiction? (2/2).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo Now that he has specifically excluded from his ban the nationality of nearly all 9/11 attackers, will they still be fooled? (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Trump's ban targeting many, but not all, Muslim nations, shows that this a measure against Muslim refugees specifically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo Why won't you just answer the question? Why these diversions? Do you think Mr Trump's fans will accept his "safety" argument?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo It doesn't change my question - are Mr Trump's supporters stupid enough to swallow this oh-so-obvious lie? I fear they are. =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northshoreguynz Sadly, you're almost certainly right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo In my view, because Obama did it too is an extremely poor defense of anything. I'm not one of his fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Trump's supporters stupid enough to swallow an anti-terrorist "safety" ban on immigration that excludes Saudi Arabia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not a Muslim ban" says Mr Trump, insisting that his ban is honouring his pledge to ban Muslim immigration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So few people seem to be aware that there is already a barrier along huge sections of the US - Mexico border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CherylBernstein Ah, my alma mater! The 13yo is not a seeker of higher things, then? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt was my favourite actor. His portrayal of Winston Smith was simply extraordinary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN @miriampierard @CNN What is she, a dystopian version of Santa Claus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howlieT @DebsHancock I have it on good authority that Stephen King knows where we could get a dome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogueNASA @melulater A 21st Century version of Soviet political commisars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melulater Yes, I think that is what worries me most. His ego is so gravid and so brittle that he could commit atrocities out of sheer spite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melulater It's the same dynamic, to be sure, but I think Trump is so much more dangerous and hateful than Reagan. =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May's unbelievably craven speech to GOP lawmakers makes it very clear that she regards Trumpism as her politics, as much as theirs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ptoothfish Every time I leave my front door I am pounced on by two cuddly neighbour cats. Very good for the soul!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjarichardson Never mind, there'll still be free speech for a 21st Century 'Der Sturmer'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon (who holds the imaginary post of Mr Trump's 'chief strategist') demands that the media "keep its mouth shut".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway admits that "we" (the US) will pay "to protect our own" (ie build the racist wall).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admits that US consumers, and not Mexico, will pay for his racist wall. https://t.co/bbkd5EmVm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kebabette That looks like Edgeware Supervalue! It was my local for 30+ years and I worked there for four and a half years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had my first ever property inspection and the tenancy manager was very pleased indeed. =)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews The men who built the Berlin Wall also insisted it was constructed for their people's "safety".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Times are "tense" for team Trump because they have a reverse Midas touch where everything they touch turns to sh*t. https://t.co/ubuvqXfRbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a Grampa Simpson level of crazy old man. https://t.co/eLpwSbrfJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to stop thinking of US intelligence agencies as 'on our side' against Trump. They remain our deadly enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Mr Trump's claims of massive electoral fraud were true, the election he won would be completely invalid, and a new election inevitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we learnt that there are alternative studies and alternative evidence of massive US electoral fraud. Alternative fraud, of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenanmalik My concern, for example, about hate speech and hate crime legislation is that it can be a double-edged sword.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenanmalik I was thinking earlier today about when George H W Bush belligerently barked: "I don't care what the facts are."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji I'm not sure what is more bizarre - Mr Spencer thinking he is Nelson Mandela, or Mr Spencer thinking he is Carl Jung.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph @Dovil @bootstheory You can still make it. I'll laugh, I promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcDFace And if it was true, it would completely invalidate the election he won, requiring him to immediately call another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Trump has invented another imaginary position on his "team" for another jeering Breitbart hatemonger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony of Trump trolls screeching when you say their idol is authoritarian, and then telling you he'll put you in a concentration camp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DingPong01 @guardian I am not even vaguely interested in what you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian It also has echoes of Nazi Germany, with the day of Hitler coming to power being the "Day of National Salvation."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery Don't you find the cans a bit crunchy? You know there's LP in there, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If America's exit from the TPP "kills" the deal, then it wasn't a truly multinational agreement in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expecting a meaningful "free trade" deal from an extreme economic nationalist? Don't hold your breath.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>