<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira I'm guessing I'll get very angry if I read it, no? Thanks for the warning. 😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well worth a read. https://t.co/XgE2QTqlWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamesler @Rooiphine depends on the porn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread. https://t.co/gsTaHnWrfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lanalopesi those things are ludicrously expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pomegranate_NZ I'd been meaning to order, but this week spurred me on to do so. Yes, please let staff know how much we appreciate them!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch. But unfortunately true... https://t.co/VJWGHvuNwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange I know. So sad. A shell of my former self. Don't tell Pete I got a lyric wrong. He thinks I'm some sort of song goddess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley ugh. Sorry to hear that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hillside_nz so bummed I can't come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz @jwaaaap I have nightmares about that movie and I only saw glimpses from the seat in front of me on a plane. *Shudder*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wellingtonista I was only there for 20 minutes (ah, children), but I felt better than I had all day. I met @GrumpyYetAmusin, yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrlcurry whoops - that was from 90 minutes ago! Protest still on until 5...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the US embassy right now to protest the travel ban (really Muslim ban, of course). Come join us! 3pm, 29 Fitzherbert Terrace, Thrndn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NazrMohammed @lilyallen It may not be much of a consolation, but many, many of us think otherwise!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[read this whole thread. (please) https://t.co/JTEJm28P5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This made me cry. https://t.co/0WHp7d1Jf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just checked what fox news has to say - not ONE WORD about the ban or "restrictions," just that Trump signed order to defeat ISIS. Jesus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shiprib I know. Horrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ I did, but with my family; we had one bedroom, another guest had the other, we saw him once. It was a group of us, though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awesome. Thank you, @johubris https://t.co/GdElb1V2NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell? The ENTIRE FESTIVAL should be safe for EVERYONE. I see what they are trying to do, but...no.
https://t.co/GOn33ALC66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@innesmck I love the reflection. 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ I needed that. :) Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrlcurry @DearMama_ but yeah, it sucks that there are horrid people out there who hide behind their keyboards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ hugs. I actually find it better than Facebook, but that might just be my social circles...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaohmee yep, it didn't seem weird when I was growing up there, but it's abhorrent to me now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira can't find it. Something about park rangers being librarians of the outdoors (in that they don't take shit and protect truth).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira whoops! Original tweet forthcoming...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira - I thought you'd like this. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I AM DOING ALL THE THINGS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley I love that you "feel quite comfortable with doing 3D ones" - :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ I did a google search and didn't find any different answers, but there are some hysterical stories out there...good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend @NicNicNZ that, too, obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadlandsNPS @BadIandsNPS yep, found screenshots with real acct. As you were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadlandsNPS @BadIandsNPS or are there screenshots of official acct tweeting about climate change?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, two accounts, one with the blue tick...Is the whole thing a sham? @BadlandsNPS @BadIandsNPS (note the capital "I" instead of L in 2nd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ let me know when you find the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamesler yup. I've given Facebook a wide berth...Hugs from a not-that-kind-of-crazy yank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debperelman @nytimes please say it's a joke, please say it's a joke...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#makethepridelandsgreatagain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck, Be Prepared from the Lion King is basically what just happened in Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephapple @wellingtonista with the hat and cards?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @pantographpunch wow. Eye-opening. Guilty, but now aware. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["urn containing the ashes of America's future." Best line...so far... https://t.co/KjBXmGjxow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz @dinopoloclub Was going to give you grief about the "upcoming" part on the website, but I see it's just a cache thingy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asher_boote The @hillside_nz new tables are awesome! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@innesmck I'm opening and closing my mouth like a guppy. I just... Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley that is AWESOME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asher_boote good question! This guy did rye... https://t.co/naOXRmROZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ I could see it coming and had the biggest grin on my face. She's even more concerned about my mental stability than before. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ my MIL told me to be grateful about 6 hours after I read your 'I am grateful, now fuck off' post. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris @TheBillfold I'd never heard of this! Dark side =data mining, I guess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeybycrikey what an absolute fucktard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuOld @MoataTamaira I use specsavers. Easy to change things if needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira @peterc_nz finished it last night. Loved it. I'd wager on crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz @liamesler https://t.co/zboQ9SIezk
Please watch this. It's the BEST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant worth reading...Thanks, @farmgeek. https://t.co/b4tlUEOqpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ thank you for writing this. We really really love you. Thank you for being you. Ugly crying now. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ actually crying now. You are brave; I don't always say what I think b/c I'm scared of the reaction; with good reason. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ whoa; you really took down the post! I'm so angry - and frustrated and sad - that you were driven to that. Huge hugs/coffees/etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X oi! You're in our 'hood and didn't stop by?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HatePash1 @DearMama_ I know. This is my new favourite ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X in wlg? There are quiet rooms upstairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz Shout out for the @GoodBitchesBake pinny in the background!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter is kind, loving, joyful, and pretty awesome to be around. I love you, Elizabeth. Happy birthday, Grumbl… https://t.co/evXgvlnm52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X that was meant to be in reply to the lockout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X could you make another acct; one for Lucy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I snorted in public reading this. https://t.co/Crpx08ZPQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris @wellingtonista douchecanoe is my new favourite word. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrlcurry actually, Pete texted that to me, but it was too good...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! If I see one more like or RT come through I'll be down there with a hammer. 😘 https://t.co/7WpQHiuXzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yes. Halloumi and creamed spinach on sourdough @hillside_nz. I almost want to be hungover so I can enjoy it even more. Almost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirRice I have actual family members who support Trump. They're in the 'well-off white" category. I am horrified by their choices. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now something a bit more cheery: https://t.co/BnT4seCyCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirRice I'll see if this works... https://t.co/gb0P9gxgae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekitchenmaid I also love the @smittenkitchen blog - great recipes and detailed how-tos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekitchenmaid I have (and still use) cooking for dummies. Also read this post and comments: https://t.co/44xAhsmcN2 (US-based, though)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fUy49PatDM
Would love any insight from twitter crew (as my twitter followers and facebook friends are *very* different).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X I'm cheering for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzfi I know where that is! Ta! (lst yr it took AGES to find her.) If you need hints for Spikes, Tuitara, or Zuzu, let me know. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira @NZBlood really? that's fabulous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ ouch. Well-played.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, spotting a stylish woman: "I bet she got her glasses at Geraldine Booth."
@itgirlnz : "Mary, that _is_ Geraldine Booth."
Oh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilynFussell so you knew, but she didn't? 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HungryandFrozen enjoy it! I went on Thursday and had a great time. Had to read up on wtf was happening at first intermission, though. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hillside_nz welcome back, guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hillside_nz and then you realise it's opening for dinner, not day service. 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you remember @hillside_nz reopens today - 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris (I know you're renting, not buying, but the idea holds). Our last flat was 65sqm or so; small, but perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange @lucyamorris also, not sure what size you're looking at - we bought our house as a "starter" - but now I love the size. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange @lucyamorris yep, start of the year can be brutal due to students looking for flats as well. What suburbs are you looking at? 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ MY LIFE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HungryandFrozen @Medium huge, enormous, not at all awkward or threatening hugs. This post meant a lot to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @mic @peterc_nz told me about this article and I interrupted him, saying... "Where he was a genie? I remember that movie." 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilynFussell this is horrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ the main troll, honestguy or whatever, seems to be an MRA gamergate evangelist. Into the rubbish bin immediately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andierosenberg I just saw that. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShoeClinicNZ @HarcourtAnna good work. Thank you for acting quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarcourtAnna @ShoeClinicNZ https://t.co/9sBDoxcC7G. up your game, Shoe Clinic.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>