<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@FantasyGolfMan @Kenny_Still All over Cauley and Castro this week. Castro FRL too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Bjorn and Shinkwin decent FRL pops at 150/1 and 125/1. Both out early and looks like massive draw bias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. What a back nine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 4ft putt missed by Ollie. Painful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorenzo Vera my favourite golfer to lose money on last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New greens firming up on the North has messed the theory up a bit. North looks like its playing as hard as South today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it Lucas keep missing those putts. Don't want to hit the front too soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the SC is going to be fun when the wind blows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyfatbastard Try being a night person with Kids. Then come back to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deurtee @jaebberwock @NYCPunter @RBaroff427 Cheers for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deurtee Lowry would interest me but got a bum draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deurtee Couldn't argue with DJ. Was great T2G last week. I backed Glover at 150/1 early in the week. Look at the g… https://t.co/1C23owAKm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also heard from a caddy that Torrey is unplayable. Rough is worse than US open and greens not holding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like 20mph+ winds on the Friday at Torrey. Much calmer Thurs. looks like SC day 1 big advantage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HV3_Golf @futureoffantasy @SonyOpen @OxfordGolfUSA Hope you are going to wash it after the round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Still I heard he is fully fit again and flushing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter Doesn't Noren fade the ball. Also a bit of a negative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@15thClub @EuropeanTour Any chance you lads could do a shot tracker for the ET similar to what they have on the PGA tour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicsPicks yeah I was waiting for course draw. Missed the boat. I got 100/1 on Mullinax with betstars so happy enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicsPicks betstars have a combined one which is nice par 72 v's par 70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuntaThePunter World Chess is on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lofty3662 @MattWalluk You better hurry up. That price will be gone within an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetonRyaner @racingblogger @aftertimeansell their description of who aftertimeansell is. You fit it nicely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pgatour No shotracker this week or did they just oversleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes hitting refresh every 10 seconds on the web leaderboard. At least I can watch this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRankings @daraokearney Please feed me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grahulvity @FantasyFootyFix Rashford to Bony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kateharro1989 That was in the Charity Race In Punchestown. Probably the furthest he ever won by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes I found €10 in one today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new sky remote for the TV on the bus #WhatsinSimonspackage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes only started doing them last year. Soomin and Barnes both leading after round 3 was the closest I came. Got part ew double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicsPicks Ilonen won at the London Club. Don't remember the grove at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicsPicks was that not the course Ilonen won the matchplay on a few years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@14northside make sure you film it or no one will believe you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoLayingUp with no partner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveThePunter @MikkyMo73 why didn't he putt before Willet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Melinhogolf @bpkelly78 it's weird that you picked probably the only other guy on Twitter who still wears visors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The European Anthem is from Die Hard. Maybe It's the Hans Gruber Overture #RyderCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfBetting12 that's gas. My brother is Alan O'Sullivan. @sulky20 he is a very good coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfBetting12 in Ballyneety in Limerick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfBetting12 @ETPI_Physiounit Nice one. My brother is giving him lessons and wanted to see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfBetting12 @SteveThePunter @FinnMcK95 I am trying to find a video of Paul O'Connell hitting off the first in Hazeltine. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bpkelly78 @Melinhogolf thanks Kelly and Ricardo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Everton_Damon by calling him a drug cheat every second sentence. Think they were pretty clear on his expertise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Everton_Damon @graeme_0 @BBCMarkDaly @danroan Ok so what about all the other athletes. all really sick too but winning. What am I missing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Everton_Damon @graeme_0 @BBCMarkDaly @danroan are you saying BW needed that amount of the drug because he was sick and that's ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sam_golf cheers. Had a nibble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those trousers on Ben Evans are giving me a migraine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yadavharish05 @FPLFantasyTalk 11 from 7 with captain used]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilOBriain Well done today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickDougherty5 @chambleebrandel @DiDougherty1 @jacknicklaus do you like ice cream. If you do then that's 3 things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickDougherty5 @chambleebrandel @DiDougherty1 @jacknicklaus Did you not lead a US Open for 1 round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilOBriain Good luck this week. You seem to be tearing it up at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoLayingUp The no flinching with a huge puff of sand in the face and mic drop when he holes it. Ultimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter Saturday very windy ATM but again looks like all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter Looks like some rain on Thursday and dry Friday. So early Friday starters may get some advantage. Same wind pretty much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critchley at it again. The 11th is nowhere near 500 yards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowdo83 My brother will give you one for free. Involves a flight to Ireland though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Pat Hickey need 3 rooms in Rio?

Well there was 1 for the master, 1 for the Dame and 1 for the little boy who lived down the lane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucas Glover maybe 10th time lucky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eireannkelly @15thClub @WyndhamChamp All points towards Lucas Glover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheChristinaKim @shanebacon Had a burner 15 degree with a driver length flex twist shaft. Ping eye 2 wooden 5 wood was also great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfBetting12 wait till Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HitTheHighDraw @NYCPunter don't worry he won't be leading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes thought they might have been just really slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes was there a delay in NI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter great start by Holmes🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter both. Kokrak is interesting. Might join you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter More of a firm and fast golf course guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zakcus also Beef at 250/1 for a guy in form who plays tough courses well looked a little big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zakcus I am mainly Holmes. Rose can't putt. Thought about Garcia but couldn't pull the trigger. I fancy Rory but too short for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Still Thanks. Will have a nibble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter also super sick. Both Barnes and Cejka didn't birdie 16 or 18. Only need one for a decent week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnes misses from 5ft for birdie at 10. Pity. Still only 1 back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cejka, Barnes and Campbell running tonight. No exactly confident but you never know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FGMetrics doubled driveable par 4. Bogey at 17 and a 9 at the last🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FGMetrics 8 over for last 3 to shoot 81.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice triple from Ames at 17. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter Did Chad 150, Cejka 200 and Barnes 150. The wind looks like getting even more up this afternoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter Started backing a few from this morning who were hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter followed you in. Doing Castro and Blixt too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuntaThePunter I am one of those Morons. Based more on suitability of the course for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter t5 and t9 in full open. Always had him down as a good tough course player. 100/1 seems ok to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeefGolf what's the largest animal you think you could throw over a crossbar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter @MikkyMo73 more rain less wind. Afternoon gusting to 30mph only around 20 max in the morning but things can change quickly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveThePunter @DaveTindallgolf Do either of you know which wind direction is straight downwind on the front nine in Troon. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter have you seen the expected weather. I know he is good in the wind but anything could happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicsPicks Much easier than yesterday. Good few tees up. Wind easing a bit now too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweeterAlliss the music is quite soothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Lee now gone. Grace a danger though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully no one gets to 4. Blow wind blow. Hend FRL watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oddschecker Bale, Penalty, 23rd minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrington 200/1 for next week. That's so wrong I almost feel guilty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conanm123 Wales and BTTS 9/1 is better I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to win the €500 Voucher for Restaurant Patrick Guilbaud @RPGuilbaud @thetaste_ie #WinRPGVoucher #TheTaste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bettingbias what about Wales and BTTS slightly better odds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenColeyGolf didn't Faldo bring DJ Spoony or did I imagine that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCPunter took him at 40/1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thirtysixholes @SteveThePunter seems like a good enough reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveThePunter do you know why James Morrison WD last week]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>