<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso  that comment was no intended towards you honey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @pmbillenglish excuse me but tax paying and acc paying citizens have friggen accidents through no fault of their own! Arrogant dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls, 9 and 10, die of self-inflicted injuries https://t.co/BgBHZCGz9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr he probably observerd Southlands also recently, waste of space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drink driver most concerned with sushi after crashing into Port Chalmers shop  https://t.co/kvYktEYDhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One dead after fatal crash near Gore https://t.co/rV0OpouErp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child seriously injured after fall near Te Anau https://t.co/fwuvj1QsrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cellphone reception deficient in crisis | Otago Daily Times Online News https://t.co/zScqYCOW7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four injured in crash near Gore https://t.co/25a75PtcPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interim name suppression continues for family member of prominent Dunedin family https://t.co/DT30v5Z0KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5000 dairy cows China-bound on Saudi businessman's ship https://t.co/15tPFbrgA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two arrested after police car taken then torched https://t.co/sWt8IEcaOG via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 killed in fiery bus crash on Italian highway https://t.co/Cc6GNNCjSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Islanders cause boilover in Telegraph as Signify and apprentice jockey Racha Cuneen claim Group I https://t.co/uR4NAYkK0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: 'Hardening up' is never the answer when times get tough https://t.co/xA7tYcxm2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan I was wondering yesterday how your travels were going!! Happy family moments??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreneLow lets just say it's not raining in Southland today, yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police concerned about 12-year-old boy missing since Christmas Day https://t.co/elcX3PdT4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 we had hail and thunderstorms in Southland all day and night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious crash near Heriot https://t.co/vljBb9usaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year that might be: Our political predictions for 2017 https://t.co/7mp7PQ7MuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm just worried that I won't see' - Dunedin man's eye hit by debris at public fireworks display https://t.co/PMFC5Af7Zl via @1NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a Teen Stops Treating His Type 1 https://t.co/yCGXB7LEeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters battle large blaze in Dunedin https://t.co/8TJETGbc4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man dead after motorcycle crash in Southland https://t.co/7ccLV3c2oK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gore student wins Prime Minister's scholarship, for the second time https://t.co/OQCVd5YqlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forty tonnes of dirt dumped outside central Auckland restaurant  https://t.co/izw1oqmEFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zara and Mike Tindall suffer miscarriage on eve of Christmas https://t.co/96wpfz7Otm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gisborne bus crash https://t.co/gNyDYOZh1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasp Wipeout: The human cost of 'one of NZ's most dangerous insects' https://t.co/VCo0el9p3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Waihi mother has no idea why her toddler died https://t.co/du6DtELz7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invercargill mother forges ahead with DNA test to confirm Prince is her son's father https://t.co/evCfQNbgAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southland mystery beach object identified https://t.co/FSXcj0yIk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth front powerful video hoping to reverse NZ's horrifying trend of suicides https://t.co/DFqf97IJnE via @1NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riverton jockey Rebecca Black dies in race fall at Gore https://t.co/Tk3paXdHKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents discover their son was alive in a mortuary freezer for two days before dying https://t.co/frhPXp66Pk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call for clarity after $700k school trip to Hawaii https://t.co/kUkNcJ4Vvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parole decision slammed | Otago Daily Times Online News https://t.co/kxPxjfcRuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would you pick for New Zealander of the Year? Helen Kelly. What do you think? https://t.co/Zm6ZyZ7Z8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innapropriate conduct sees Auckland teacher deregistered https://t.co/3VJT6uJYep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PETITION: Stop withholding HIV medicines https://t.co/sW3axxXPFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this petition: https://t.co/yOlmV680kn via @actionstation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CallActive directors declared bankrupt, company owes more than $2.6 million https://t.co/rHs51uBQ0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The application form to get on First Dates asks for every skeleton in your closet https://t.co/WcSzbmlvqK via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio theft cripples rural South Island fire brigade's emergency response ability https://t.co/fgKWfpqsCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong 5.1 earthquake rattles Wairoa  - Yahoo New Zealand https://t.co/IUygbFGNiX via @YahooNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driver smoked weed before causing fatal five-car crash | Otago Daily Times Online News https://t.co/taVvpWaaqL via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys approached near scene of Ranui abduction incident https://t.co/EsoFuUbJ89 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child abuse report 'shut down' https://t.co/5Xm5pwjZlj']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casper the acc cat! https://t.co/0oK6DjgmUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Key: Strip Destiny Church from TAX free status - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/QYEmwlHHKm via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Let's make GeoNet 24/7 https://t.co/pT7EjQvAyV via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed offenders squad callout to coastal Otago town https://t.co/PEzJGGTVsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan @Zagzigger2 @TomSaterCNN Everyone in New Zealand admires the hard work you do here to assist us with accurate weather forecats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquake: A guide to getting through the aftershocks  https://t.co/HZO54ObYIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney woman tossed 80 metres after being hit by NZ driver, court learns https://t.co/rgPNGPHhvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postponed scholarship exam to be changed https://t.co/m3PgwCN8YL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquake: More cows stranded on an outcrop of land after three saved https://t.co/ozQNAY9oaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divers and volunteers band together to save stranded shellfish and sea life  https://t.co/w3I6jzmCEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: Large quake strikes New Zealand https://t.co/pRwuAevLUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsunami confirmed: Civil Defence gives urgent warning after magnitude-7.5 quake in South Island - evacuation advised https://t.co/Vpz2oubgeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An emotional hunger is feeding our anxiety, says the Dalai Lama https://t.co/2wb6LSTc9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan excellent idea to have a drink! If you were not so far away I would of joined you! Xx  politics ehðŸ±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US election: Hillary Clinton will not address own rally https://t.co/tjajRCrVdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've signed to tell the govt to back decent jobs not dodgy employers like Manpower. Will you? https://t.co/e9RX1PF6DK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighter airlifted to hospital after dramatic cat rescue near Wellington https://t.co/hMzREbhQoz via @OneNewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CureT1Diabetes Its Kiwi slang for totally agree with you and your thoughts and comments    xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuff Idiot and Idiots clearing him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CureT1Diabetes @SenSanders @novonordiskus @Diabetes_Sanofi @LillyDiabetes Bloody Oath from New Zealand also!!!   xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mojomathers @CheckpointRNZ We are sheep farmers and it appalls us also. Go for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caffeine_addict Really?? Bugger she is a type 1 diabetic like my daughter that follows me, must look into that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan I could do with a rainbow in my life at the moment so thank you!!!   Lovely photo.   Trust and hope all is well with you also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did police use booze checkpoint to target elderly women at euthanasia meeting? https://t.co/eE2n7XmXSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ewen Macdonald, man acquitted of Scott Guy murder, finds love https://t.co/IYQmbMG4M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum staged bomb hoax as revenge for her daughter not being invited to a party https://t.co/d0BNy74vur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sand and milk: Dairy farming in the desert https://t.co/2pStPChj0M via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pregnant woman seriously hurt https://t.co/vBWF21J06L via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effluent discharged into Southland stream https://t.co/81tLfatFbc via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once flea-covered student flat one of the first inspected in Government crackdown https://t.co/GC5NLpOHSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southland meatworker charged with nearly $55,000 fraud https://t.co/cAqh6GsbqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[94-year-old Wellington woman waits three months for caregiver after displacing hip https://t.co/UsIwfLr4d8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otago man offers 'bloody job' to non-whingers in employment ad https://t.co/3UI0o94jsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just signed a petition calling on the Govt to fix the health system. Will you sign too? https://t.co/6zQoQBHcYU via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double shooting in Cook Islands https://t.co/h6cEPuMI1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan that is so funny ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live blog: Local body elections https://t.co/4JR4ly6SHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MediaWorks sees other possibilities if Fairfax-NZME merger rejected https://t.co/qYU50ebRto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed police respond to incident Brockville, Dunedin https://t.co/tSPqBKNbwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contractor plows Fortrose Beach, stalling whitebaiters  https://t.co/8JU24ihbyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karin Ann Ross found with 'halo of blood'  https://t.co/d8k2uoYUqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Illnesses - How Do We 'Visibilise' them? https://t.co/y8kTfimaww via @HuffPoLifestyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child rushed to hospital after fall from rope swing https://t.co/KDW8EvxWnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire service rescues child stuck in car https://t.co/NV7wZw1EMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father shocked at $1700 bill for teenage daughter's paintball birthday  https://t.co/BUpf4GDCMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thunderstorms hit Otago, reports highway underwater https://t.co/HxxhfO5QOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government employee on serious charges suspended on full pay https://t.co/P4pmp9G3pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jay-Jay Harvey reveals marriage separation with Dom https://t.co/N6YVRUVihS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taika Waititi, Karen Walker nominated for New Zealander of the Year https://t.co/MnUBjj1iI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucas Cochrane search: Body found in waterway https://t.co/n7ZIPK6spo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Australia without power as 'worst storm in decades' hits https://t.co/1Br86CNGhK via @nzherald]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>