<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterHoskinsTV @guardian I loved that line too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This reminds me of my time in Rome... https://t.co/KvDx7wsyz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Itwitius Good point, well made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM Mine was missed 3 weeks in a row! Do the bin collectors even know they're supposed to take it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important story that should be more widely reported... https://t.co/XgRNtx5i3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AFP is reporting that Madonna is in Malawi seeking to adopt two more children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@figarolloyd I liked it, just didn't love it. I'm seeing Jackie on Thursday so I'll report back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tancredipalmeri You'll enjoy it but you may also wonder what all the fuss is about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I alone in thinking that La La Land is massively overrated? It was a good film but not a great film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Livingetc Can't we have them all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM I've tried this two weeks in a row &amp; both times the bag has been ignored. No point introducing policies without informing the bin men!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tsojcanth @RealBenCarson Interesting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really enjoying watching Designated Survivor on Netflix but I've not read anything about it. It's really good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM Two weeks in a row textiles were not collected from outside my house. Why not? And my food bin was not emptied today. Why not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suellewellyn @guardiang2 Spinach shortage too due to wet weather in Spain!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighwaysEngland Large pothole just past J5 of M4 going west, middle lane. Just struck it at 70mph causing damage to my car! Who can fix it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woo hoo! I have tickets to see @HamiltonMusical in London! I hope it's as good as I hear it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM I left a bag of textiles out with my recycling as per instructions on your website but it wasn't collected with the recycling. Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBWM Can you tell me please why you have closed St Leonard's Road in Windsor with no warning? I am unable to access my road (Albany Road).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story moved me... https://t.co/mdtDiXMM5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contender for strangest story of the day... 
https://t.co/tTCcHJeEp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loo with a view @citysocial_t42 https://t.co/Wni37VAhOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling Christmassy #mulledcider #publunch #fridayoffwork queencharlottepub https://t.co/sIHMFMxa4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixUK I'd love to continue watching this but my Netflix keeps crashing! Why??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$849 pp to see @HamiltonMusical in New York!! And people think the theatre in London is expensive! That's just shocking. And sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First News Today - Kids online &amp; Fantastic Beasts https://t.co/vL8O0jnzFE via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Sky News bulletin for Twitter https://t.co/krPmZKbiwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted along the Southbank last night. Does anyone know what it is? Or why it's there? https://t.co/rnWu9CItqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would make an amazing reality TV show! https://t.co/CUD0M0jWLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted on the Southbank #bignose #christmascomeearly https://t.co/nhfw000Uxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great burger tonight @byronhamburgers in Windsor. It tasted even better knowing it only cost 25p!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the Copper Horse on a beautiful autumn day #windsorgreatpark #windsorcastle #deer #nature https://t.co/LoRJuGXKct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matilda at London's Cambridge Theatre is totally brilliant! Go see it! https://t.co/x33qkJWMC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marksandspencer Will any of it be available in your Windsor branch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lifeafterlondon I think the answer in the blog says it all. Windsor is a great place to live. We don't miss London at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ongoing joke between Heathrow and Schiphol airports... https://t.co/UVDBh8etA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrSimonDudley It was good to hear your views tonight. I think RBWM council is in good hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamAfriyie Good to meet you tonight. I was very impressed with what I heard. Keep up the good work for RBWM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HairyBikers I can't wait to get stuck into this! https://t.co/gTwlT4Pysh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuswareing I'm looking forward to learning some new recipes! https://t.co/uHVaZIa8Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved @deborahross's column in @thetimes today on middle-class emergencies! So funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real issue - is Brexit masculine or feminine? https://t.co/IzxrKaa3q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to read about a boom in Italian language learning. Che bella lingua! https://t.co/RpIfi0wudC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings of Leon are playing a 'secret' gig in London tonight. Band members are handing out tickets NOW in Covent Garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard times... https://t.co/eU7PnTsQ9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's longest-reigning monarch King Bhumibol of Thailand has died aged 88.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobel prize-winning Italian author Dario Fo has died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this had me jumping out of my skin this evening... https://t.co/W3QzjE57Hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefanohat @Tesco I noticed that it was missing! Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very interesting read..
BBC Radio Director Helen Boaden resigns, criticising state of journalism | The Independent https://t.co/1sLg6zgIJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Wenger for England?? https://t.co/CnpqYlsEfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenpollard So right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think England should withdraw from international competitions for a few years. Players don't want to play, managers all about the money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigella_Lawson What is your ultimate 3-course dinner party menu please? I'm cooking for friends and not sure what to make. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deanpiper Yes, she looks amazing. But Kate Moss looked awful in the pic you posted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGooders @RobBrydon brilliant news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddiel Great show last night. Really touching and poignant yet at the same time hilariously funny. Good luck with the West End run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGooders Wanna go for a drink tonight or tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another summer holiday book done. I was sorry to finish this one. A great read. https://t.co/peQkopR3jK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EyeSoHungry Last night's dinner... Seafood rice! https://t.co/MUB8t7U6kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night's amazing dinner at O Pescador #seafood #rice #prawn #clam #lobster #pinecliffsresort… https://t.co/okgYqwrl5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent book! Thanks for the recommendation @indiaknight @thesundaytimes https://t.co/Nqwwr9GS8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for @EyeSoHungry... https://t.co/GDq2D5YCg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champagne grows on trees in Portugal... https://t.co/cfpumUj6Zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champagne grows on trees! #champagne #holiday #Portugal #holidayspam https://t.co/MW6z3uk0lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French fashion designer Sonia Rykiel has died at the age of 86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited! https://t.co/HKOEQmGNjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first Deliveroo now they've launched in Windsor. I think I could become addicted. So much choice &amp; great service! https://t.co/llMeOT31gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pommieknight Well said. It allows you to better understand people and places, the culture and the history. It's sad that so many miss out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to read about the decline of language learning in the UK. Learning French &amp; Italian taught me so much more than just the language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyKatieSpencer @RidgeviewWineUK Lucky you on a day like today! Make sure you bring a bottle back - it's delicious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GBR is 2nd in the medals table! https://t.co/aGMGGVQPZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sad article about the sorry state of Hollywood... https://t.co/dU0sXDTnOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other Olympic news, this has been making me laugh a lot today... https://t.co/6JPqjQCgHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzanne_moore Hilarious! Good on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played @GaryLineker #MOTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alextomo I remember waiting for a train in Sicily only to be told "quando arriva, arriva" (it'll get here when it gets here)! #loveItaly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third now! Wow #TeamGB! https://t.co/5RdXvJ0J8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're 4th in the medals table! #Rio2016 #GBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh! Just in time for Season Two! https://t.co/THRhaptIgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The REAL story of the Olympics... https://t.co/6CiTLz8mPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShellStationsUK The people who work at the Shell garage in Windsor are so lovely. They always make me smile. Please reward them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful weekend in Paris but the city is eerily quiet. Lots of police and soldiers around though. https://t.co/DebGPAb4j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bevnolz @pzf @PzDeals Strange business model! Might have to unfollow. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pzf @PzDeals Are you a serious news organisation or not? I don't get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What every Olympic team needs - their own plumber! https://t.co/FLydBmvqaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorfollowill Do you have any plans to tour the UK soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenpollard Agreed. Excellent documentary. I never realised that they raced each other a second time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart-warming... https://t.co/xsYNckKa1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm ignoring all the negative media surrounding #Rio2016. It was the same before London2012 &amp; the Games were a success. Rio will be too. 🇧🇷]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bread, cheese and meat @Jack_and_Alice in Gerrards Cross. Great wine bar! https://t.co/d3YquGCOTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groundhog Day at The Old Vic. Brilliant, brilliant show! Laugh-out-loud funny. Go see it! https://t.co/C6vMHqeiZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomesProperty I don't know where you got your info but Windsor to Paddington can take as little as 29 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of deliveries...straight to your car! https://t.co/J8Gqx5isbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very much looking forward to seeing @Baddiel when he brings his show to Windsor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Spoils starring Jesse Eisenberg is brilliant! The whole cast were outstanding. I highly recommend it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just filled out an interesting survey from Amazon asking if I'd allow deliveries to be left inside my house or car when I'm not there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendopolis do you always tweet the jc? First time I've seen it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can people stop retweeting the fake Donald Trump tweet?!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>