<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TennantNicolas Enjoyed your brief appearance in Denial! Hope all well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The launch of Breitbart in France has been delayed https://t.co/9ysjPPQQnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The search for a "providential man" - excellent @FT Big Read by @ChassNews on the French election https://t.co/Ut36J8OUPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quite the letter from Congressman Patrick T McHenry to Janet Yellen  https://t.co/4nJPIG5xwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This came out at the height of the last, Bush-inspired, wave of French (and European) anti-Americanism. Trump has m… https://t.co/ZaKU6vGQvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChrisGiles_ on Theresa Tsipras https://t.co/NPoC2ZpsR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guillermo Ortiz, former governor of the Bank of Mexico, on Trump and the future of Nafta https://t.co/wNh29ERQLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philipstephens on how France could resist the populist tide https://t.co/pqNgSXHhjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelfAdam @b_judah He might do, but it's too late. Macron has the wind in his sails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per @franceinfo, Penelope Fillon said in 2007: "I've never been my husband's assistant."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecMacGillis I hear Ralph Ellison and James Baldwin are doin' great work, too. Beautiful work. The best work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JamilAnderlini on the chilling case of Xiao Jianhua https://t.co/jljSpG4PR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's looking dicey for Fillon https://t.co/6cV85eu2iS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duncanrobinson Don't forget the Russian loans https://t.co/I6Kj97AiMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good profile of Philippot, but longer story to tell about dédiabolisation that goes back to Bruno Mégret in the 90s. https://t.co/PtYczN7uyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the grand scheme of things, this is not the most pressing issue, but @mePadraigReidy is right nonetheless https://t.co/ip5rinaQLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very useful summary of what we know so far about "l'affaire Fillon" https://t.co/BYvoanD5YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice piece by @austeni on what the Pope's battle with the Knights of Malta really means https://t.co/Yc9v5lURtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMarkHerman I read and enjoyed it last night, David.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In memoriam - this morning's book post https://t.co/KEp55wEIp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@benoithamon is struggling to rally his party behind him after beating Valls https://t.co/uepMRo6StY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A case study in over-promotion" - @JananGanesh on Theresa May https://t.co/ILYgY2Ivhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to see Denial tomorrow. Reacquainting myself with this by @RichardEvans36 in preparation https://t.co/5yVep6hknF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartMaconie Oh man, that was an extraordinary combination of analysis and eulogy. Biit about having the snare off was particularly good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jah Wobble fascinating on the genius of Jaki Liebezeit on @StuartMaconie's show right now. "A tremendous humility in the playing."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgnesCPoirier @PedderSophie Which way do you think he'll jump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_nuttall Some in the party have started jumping ship already. Royal might be the first "elephante" to show her hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PedderSophie When is Bayrou going to show his hand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartMaconie Wonderful and fitting tribute to Jaki. He's up there with Tony Williams and Tony Allen in my drumming canon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can and Thundercat so far - @StuartMaconie's Freak Zone on @BBC6Music is essential listening this evening. Sustenance in dark times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, time to settle down with this https://t.co/YZUlLNoV5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to #PrimairesGauche coverage on @franceinfo. Result still not in, but everything points to a victory for @benoithamon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jacobwe on the horrible historical echoes of Trump's executive order https://t.co/1e9HfqgRXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Results expected between 7.15 and 7.45 #primairePS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, turnout in the second round of the French centre-left primary is up https://t.co/6ISSVzORGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This account of the maevolence and incompetence of Trump's executive order is devastating https://t.co/zPy5irEYtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @GeorgeProchnik as he tweets Stefan Zweig's account of an earlier headlong descent into the abyss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving a last bump to Stephen Sedley's elegant analysis of the role of the UK Supreme Court in today's @ftweekend https://t.co/O4qQ4zKZpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great job for someone at my alma mater https://t.co/F6Noxp2B5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djmgaffneyw4 gorgeous aren't they? Acquired over the past year at various locations, including @BooknRecordBar and @RecklessRecords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bluenoterecords' mid-70s re-issue series was a triumph. Current status: Art Pepper - Early Art https://t.co/IZkkQOFTsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Using a long spoon, I confirm the absence of bacon" - @henrymance has lunch with Daniel Hannan https://t.co/p6auXsxVna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oenological discovery of the week: South Australian (not Austrian) Gruner Veltliner https://t.co/YotaBOW7ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really good piece by @JKynge on China's illiberal globalism https://t.co/rXR3atEAdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice profile of Damien Chazelle, the FT's Person in the News this week, by @MattGarrahan https://t.co/pFpfFYvSFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duncanrobinson Some photos here of @manuelvalls not looking angry https://t.co/hoV2nAMTmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Alignment With Trump Threatens European Order https://t.co/1mRtEfiGdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanWeldon @IPR_NickP If not, this might do as a placeholder https://t.co/54Obolm40m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Le Monde front page: "Trump and May shake up world trade" https://t.co/Xxcndr22ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the pieces I'm most proud of having commissioned: the late David Cesarani on Shoah in 2010 https://t.co/PDYGFJhLB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once interviewed CL: "You asked me where is my homeland ... it is there, in the constant struggle against death" https://t.co/UDtG2wcbzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've never seen Lanzmann's Shoah, go tomorrow. One of the greatest works of art of the 20th century https://t.co/bG0JqZVBDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May will not find it easy to broker a US-UK trade deal, says @alanbeattie https://t.co/EzKkP9JPXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Sedley defends the independence of the UK Supreme Court https://t.co/WaQNdSnlgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valls adviser @ZakiLaidi writes for @ftcomment on French lessons for the European left https://t.co/RVcAoMRNqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philipstephens on Theresa May's "hug-em-close" approach to Trump https://t.co/bA4JmxjB84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's assault on America's senses - the brilliant @mashagessen on the new dispensation in Washington https://t.co/wvzJRvsoat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kerr, author of Article 50, on just how tortuous the Brexit negotiations are likely to be https://t.co/54Obolm40m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's a teenager in your house, chances are they're trafficking in clothes - excellent column by @johngapper https://t.co/8yn0CuGFkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LesEchos picks up on @EmmanuelMacron's@FT op-ed (vi @ChassNews) https://t.co/PGqDdQ1T8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure if Kellyanne Conway or Sean Spicer read *him* at college, but there it is ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have heard that thinking hard about truth, facts etc is a peculiarly French affair - well, this is JL Austin https://t.co/6c7ooz1rkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With May in Number 10, the joke is no longer on geographers - very nice piece by geography graduate @GeorgeWParker https://t.co/3u13k9pS8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Macron urges reboot for Franco-German engine, Russophile Fillon tells Merkel to soften her stance on Putin https://t.co/7koCzYYu2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US is leaving Europe to make its own choices - @EmmanuelMacron writes for @ftcomment https://t.co/ijugljbft2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jim Gallagher wrote about Nicola Sturgeon's vacillations on Brexit last week. Where does she go next? https://t.co/ufPmpTszKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would be useful now is one of JL Austin's "Saturday mornings" devoted to differences between a "lie", an "untruth" and a "falsehood".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece on John Cale. I'd forgotten that he played on Nick Drake's Bryter Later https://t.co/RPbtDLwHaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Separation of oil and state? @Ed_Crooks on Rex Tillerson https://t.co/Wpo82htneH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fog-bound Burgess Park https://t.co/ZaIa9F54Cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In memoriam https://t.co/ZvPqZ68Wsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible news about Jaki Liebezeit, up there with Tony Allen as one of the finest drummers of all time https://t.co/OOflkvEGoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benoît Hamon, candidate of the universal basic income https://t.co/9fHTr4Y7cQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnout in the first round of the French centre-left primary down on 2011  https://t.co/vPXtD2qGHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Thames at Hammersmith https://t.co/iY8rv9LaZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyless fantasies abound in Trump’s inauguration speech https://t.co/uA8UzMwqHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent piece on Brexit and the future of the UK by @IPR_NickP and @michaelkenny_ in @NewStatesman https://t.co/Qrk2ngMS2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LHSummers offers Trump-leaning business a lesson from Burke https://t.co/3wPK6Xq3UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another bump for Linda Colley's piece in today's paper - Theresa May’s global ambitions disguise diminished status https://t.co/39TFAwiuz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KesewaFH I always find that Jean Knight on Soul Train is a restorative https://t.co/6isnccSgDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow's @FT front page https://t.co/hgN7zBZRbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb by @EdwardGLuce on Trump's "harsh, metallic warning to the rest of the world" https://t.co/HnesqopZDl v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the populist "there is only one true, homogeneous people which can be represented by only one party" https://t.co/mN5afI2uMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's confusing this with a stump speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JananGanesh Definitely France. If anything, they're even more hopped up on 'grandeur' than we or the Americans are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linda Colley on Britain's endless search for a global role https://t.co/ZIkTeSUHgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRentoul @alanbeattie Alan is right that it's not a recent confection. Cf this by Milton Friedman from 1951 https://t.co/bdH71O6DGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olivialanguage Arthur love. I'm spending my day off profitably https://t.co/QYLlcvrgJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit, Donald Trump and the threat to Europe https://t.co/4oCBK1Kd37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_tooze We must get you on the op-ed page some time soon ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a treasure trove https://t.co/kap0IOYrSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How our neighbours see us: "Boris Johnson gaffes again comparing Francois Hollande to a Nazi" https://t.co/8YDa29Bs29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshspero Ernst Cassirer (l) and Martin Heidegger (r - extreme right, ho, ho!), before their "Davoser Disputation" in 1929.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will always be my favourite Davos image https://t.co/IPCvcRRgT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As per @ChassNews, "la bulle Macron" shows no sign of bursting https://t.co/VdYKQq8CZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lemondefr: "May chooses an iron Brexit" https://t.co/5XLku5WDMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atomic Bomb https://t.co/4jkGDlconn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great William Onyeabor has died https://t.co/g5rsnUb82M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crisp and sun-dappled Burgess Park this morning https://t.co/NtbnQOtdbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nebulous rhetoric about global competition" - Alan Milward on British attitudes in early 60s, cited by @IPR_NickP https://t.co/TJzFSdLnXW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>