<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Maybe Cheetoh Jesus meant he'd bring him back to life so his accomplishments would be better known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, And did you know, children, that Cheetoh Jesus was betrayed by his own acting employee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFP @juliedavisart  So, the Monday Night Massacre continues. What Congress member will have the courage to bring bill of impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wigleaf So when is the impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we not expect a Monday Night Massacre, pace Nixon? https://t.co/EhgwEItxGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, CHEETOH JESUS, what was that? Oh--a staircase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Cheetoh Jesus ain't afraid of anything. Except refugees. And stairs. And ramps. And horses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pennybrownpeny @RoguePOTUSStaff  I think, sadly, you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff @pennybrownpeny Is it Nixon already?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now we are as cruel, as viscious, as uncaring, and as stupid as our worst enemies claimed we were. It's a proud day in America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, I just wish the media would do more pices asking Trump supporters how they think he's doing. So bigly illuminating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's How Republicans Plan to Kill Net Neutrality, Climate, and Labor Rules: https://t.co/KMcljv2rAI - via @VICE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“America’s New President Is Not a Rational Actor” (@foreignpolicy) https://t.co/RPwPR5kWWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hands are tiny, but grasping. https://t.co/lMeg9E3kN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Look, I faced the bigliest illegal vote and got the bigliest crowd. Understand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Well, we tried the Village Idiot, but he was just too stable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Batshit crazy, fantastically ignorant, or moronically stupid. Why not all three?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, I wasn't a candidate, but I'd be president if not for fraudulent votes. And constant danger of grizzly attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is gagging public servants and violating the emoluments clause. Who in Congress has the courage to attempt impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Tiny Hands want a pipeline!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, What was that song? Patriotically devoted to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at this lying weasel. https://t.co/unpFnGttYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Then I got in trouble, cause they caught me, you know, telling a Spicer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, You know, tiny hands, tiny crowds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, You know, praying to Cheetoh Jesus to save me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/O5IaRIoSqX

Watch the 1st 4 minutes. Trump has a Minister of Propaganda. This is Stalinesque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, God stopped the rain for his only son, Cheetoh Jesus or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed this. Retweeted too. https://t.co/oFl6Hu4ewW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['He has already let America down': the reaction to Trump's first speech as president
Expect any different? https://t.co/8WlkUjWrjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, But I don't like Cheetohs--maybe if I soak them in vodka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aristotle: The telos of an acorn is an oak.
Me: The telos of Reagan is a Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Lots of people have insulted me, but nobody ever called me Jon Voight crazy before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forced choice:
A. Trump cuts all federal arts funding.
B. Trump doubles funding, but personally picks the artists who get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, I didn't say I want a grizzly bear. I said I wanted access to a grizzly bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whew, got through another day of teaching without a grizzly bear attack. This only happens, like, every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to teach today. Hope I don't face one these dreaded grizzly bear attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump's appointees are so bad, people like Lamar Alexander have to try to railroad them through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had this weird feeling like I was a really rich president who had a cheesy, awful, low rent inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mulcahygreg I really meant vote. Not the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just called my Senators to urge them to vite no on Devos. You should do that too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gearing up for my new third world lifestyle. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1blesedlife @erictheteamster @RickSmithShow @Teamsters728 @Teamsters @thinkprogress 
How about we bring back dark, satanic mills?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Jeb! Is that you, Jeb! Where are you Jeb!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will a failed governor of Indiana be our president in six months?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan's empty moral core: Fight against Obamacare shows a man on a mission to win at  https://t.co/yJ2BSQ9kG0 https://t.co/gggitMSPqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nina Turner should be president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Sure there are ethics laws and practice and the Constitution, but if anyone applies them to me, he's politicizing his office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, I don't know, something about a Manchurian president elect or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sitting around waiting for that better replacement for Obamacare. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Coups are hard. You know who's pretty good at coups? The CIA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine what it'd be like to live in a country where you didn't have to worry about health care, university tuition, or retirement security]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyrantbooks @blakebutler  The one that destroys is the one you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump told us he will maintain an unethical, illegal nest of conflicts. Will any Congressperson call for impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restaurants run by labor secretary nominee report 'disturbing' rates of sexual harassment
Sec. of Scumbag https://t.co/chF8QX1mRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics. Politics. Politics. Hey, it's not like I'm a celebrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doleful, faux serious, self aggrandizing statement about being an artist or creativity or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a Hack wins because of a hack, are he and his unethical appointees a pack of hacks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, I'm afraid some women with reproductive rights might bring me a petition. Don't we have some security around here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, If only someone could free me from the onerous threats of health insurance and social security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Kleptocracy is a pretty word, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's -6, the perfect weather to read WINTERHATE at https://t.co/U3aoN3IFIr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreamed I lived in this weird country where the government was trying to take health care and pensions away from its citizens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: A leader leads so he can't be unethical.
Q: How do you say that in German?
Me: Un, fu--fuh--fuh--]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying about how I brought 5'000 jobs to the country. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voted for lying, greedy, tax evading, reality denying, right wing crook. Cause you know, he'll shake things up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Foreign policy is hard. Can't we just get some leaders from other countries to tell us what to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, It's not like I'm President Elect Crybaby or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about joining a club, you know, for people to have a good time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a lot of this lately. https://t.co/MCgpeC0PgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigitteLOignon @ArcadiaBooks @guardian Isn't that the highest tribute for a writer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a president elect who's comments about nuclear weapons have to be staffsplained. Worried yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More nukes. Law and order. Is it 1969 again? Don't tell me we have to reinvade Viet Nam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to climate show. Thinking about WINTERHATE @BlackSunLit .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dzancbooks You can get Out of Work as an ebook here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so, in pathetic reluctance, we pinned our hopes on the deep state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackSunLit Have a look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woodardwriter It is no different than Walmart. In both cases, the answer is unions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Looks like the future. https://t.co/cn2CxU843H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, First you drain the swamp, then you fill it with oil. From Russia. Via Bermuda. Sanction free. See?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! https://t.co/kQg5JI0OC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Why not take the country as though it were a vehicle and drive it straight into the ditch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rusdaboss Thanks for the WINTERHATE tweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackSunLit WINTERHATE. Just in time for a Trumpy kind of Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy my long story WINTERHATE is up at https://t.co/QWM7Dnjv72.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter Sunday--another lazy day to reflect on our debased and debasing politics. At least we haven't hit bottom; just keeps getting lower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, No winter storm is going to unpresident me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VehiculePress @AodhBC @guardian Boycott these anti union bastards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Maybe Cheeto Santa will help me write the restaurant review.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pennybrownpeny Pitch it to Hollywood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smith: It's Bill of Rights day!
Me:The last one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barely passing "Meats." You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, You know what we need, more political leaders from big oil. Look how great Cheney did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Destroy middle class 
2 Start stupid war
3 Make politics clown show 
4 Elect psycho clown
5 Kaboom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up for the Professor Watchlist though I hope the professors there don't mock me because I'm technically an instructor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, waiting on the new fascist regime. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of the herbarium. https://t.co/8Ya7kN4FAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, What's good for Exxon is good for America. That's it, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you hack an election that's rigged by decades of gerrymandering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I go, Replace the President with a robot? Sure, why not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True that. https://t.co/Sr9Xe9s8HJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>