<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaiBrodtmannMP this is why #Canberra is the most beautiful place to live on earth! #NoFilter https://t.co/XddNbgVVGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great meeting with our @UN social  team 4 youth @UN_CSW. Not going to lie, pretty happy to go to bed before 12am ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/jR8drMWFLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Tasmania!! https://t.co/uZi6pMRg3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really needed this program in school! If your child is affected by #bullying go to @alannahmadeline https://t.co/AqcplrUBFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump thank you for taking international diplomacy seriously ðŸ˜’ Also asylum seekers are not illegal. https://t.co/VZUKrlVCC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tara_Moss that would be the 'smart thing', but then again, look at who we're dealing with... https://t.co/b57JkAeWGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look out @UN_CSW the #Australians are coming for you! @hannahwandel &amp; I are confirmed to run a session at Youth CSW! https://t.co/bhFcZYRPpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute #girlpower! So proud of my amazing friends and colleagues @MKisOK @A_girlempowered HUGE INSPIRATIONS #SDG5 https://t.co/dTa9aYYUCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConstanceWu #GirlPower! Thank you for being a champion for girls. If we don't speak up, inequality will prevail https://t.co/NyWQsfZJbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go @tajpmahal! #ausoftheyear watch our Australia, this kid is going to change the game! https://t.co/eWswbyDNoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching from home, good luck @tajpmahal! #ausoftheyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_C_PR1 @ravikarkara boys and men for gender equality! #WomensMarch #EqualityWillPrevail https://t.co/UxpbL4AzbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS are you scared yet? This is what standing up to inequality looks like. The world unites. #WomensMarch #SDG5 https://t.co/Z1V00O9Wcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not have said it better myself! #WomensMarchOnWashington #Planet5050 #NoRoomForInequality https://t.co/bKLQA4zdSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! https://t.co/DrvXXCUnVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahwandel love her!! https://t.co/Q4voqcsnpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love you @EmmaWatson! This is what a feminist looks like! @UNWOMEN4Youth #WomensMarch #Sdg5 https://t.co/Q4voqcsnpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhyIMarch for every girl who has been bullied, abused, oppressed or killed because of her gender #EqualMeansEqual https://t.co/UQtg1Lheco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This little girl is waking around the mall with a sign saying "Keep your tiny hands off women's rights" #womensmarch https://t.co/BpY6X0CVUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to meeting you in NYC! #Youth4GenderEquality https://t.co/tAviFTLQOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always the best way to start the day! Thanks girl, can't wait for our #genderequality plans! @ravikarkara #SDG5 https://t.co/81FAPC1t0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduDiversa @Richard_C_PR1 @A_girlempowered excellent! I'll task to the task force this week. Let's talk Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduDiversa can you come to NYC in March? It would be great for you guys @Richard_C_PR1 @A_girlempowered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant work @ravikarkara @RosaLizarde! In order to achieve #Planet5050 we need to bolster momentum for the SDGs https://t.co/NlSrmGC3gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at the 1am meetings! Preparing for #YouthCSW with the @UN_Women @UNWOMEN4Youth task force #CSW61 #EmpowerGirls https://t.co/UcGxrtAJxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my sunburnt country. I'm finally home and ready to get back into service and hit change head on! https://t.co/fUx3XXSh3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduDiversa DFAT has a grant we can look at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely working on it! @LBeachleyAFTS https://t.co/E7GDQQeGgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Addy_Ade merry Christmas Adeline! I look forward to seeing your influence for change grow in the new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks 4 the XMas message Ravi. To all the team I send my thanks &amp; blessings. Let's make 2017 even better for #SDG5 https://t.co/ok5kOTy0oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wrote a book? Wow girl!! Amazing! https://t.co/e6z5T31zmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning from @LewisHowes through his podcast and my mind is expanding through every word. 2017 is going to be a powerful year for change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_C_PR1 going to be tough but I'm going to try! We need to get @hannahwandel to speak on rural engagement. @ravikarkara let's do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to it!! https://t.co/6u61sWJ2Qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @MennaRawlings I'm so grateful to be safe, but I'm completely shaken from last nights events.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sakyanaa that's going to be a bit hard to do. I actually spent tonight at two Christmas markets...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sakyanaa thank god we went yesterday instead of today! I cannot believe this. Stay safe xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was meant to go tonight but instead went yesterday. My thoughts and prayers are with the victims #Breitscheidplatz https://t.co/pEOz3qeqNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sakyanaa I'm in a state of shock! Are you guys okay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to #genderequality we must include men equally. Which is why @UNWOMEN4Youth work is vital @ravikarkara https://t.co/hQW4e3mAId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday dear friend @Richard_C_PR1! Thank you for making the world a better place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WGEA boss wants to challenge Australia's highly gender-segregated workforce https://t.co/Jgt1O7Hond via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FairfaxMedia For a top 20 nation, 60% is horrifying. We need to work to increase gender equity across all industry by 2030 #Auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @TurnbullMalcolm for supporting strong gun laws that keep Australia's children safe @alannahmadeline https://t.co/YD4CtwRUWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the team @meglanning7 ðŸ’œ https://t.co/Q112JcArqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was scary sharing my story, but knowing it may help others gives me strength. Thank you @rubyconnection #WOI100 https://t.co/PDkkoBtGXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next stop #Hogwarts. Christmas at @wbtourlondon #HogwartsInTheShow childhood dream come true @jk_rowling https://t.co/rbFdEsaEz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sam_rowley96 I would love too! I adore Christmas time and lights like yours makes me really happy! But sadly I'm in Europe. Next year??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!!! Thanks @Tara_Moss, you're amazing ðŸ’œKeep signing everyone!! https://t.co/M9K2qnOdpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this so much!! Sam_rowley96 definition of the Christmas spirit! #alannahmadeline #christmas https://t.co/t7VB2SLVtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign to help keep all Australians safe from gun violence. - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/YTDsVLYdn2 via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was almost like Tyrone -we must work together to end the bullying epidemic! It literally destroys lives #RIPTyrone https://t.co/tJWDjVEp6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed! Australia's #gun laws are admired around the world. We cannot weaken them, lives are at stake if we do! https://t.co/tHi0J5VtQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rsencourage @ausoftheyear @ABarrMLA and 2017 will be even better!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to joining a call with Valerie Jarrett, Senior Advisor to the President and Chair of @WhiteHouse Council on Women and Girls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just applied 4 @LBeachleyAFTS I think it shows internal growth. Last year I was to scared to apply &amp; now I have the confidence within myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterDutton_MP Australians don't need political correctness --- we need human decency #auspol #spreadhummasnothate https://t.co/dTIxGQkZ10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @tajpmahal just heard the news! Knew you would get it - next stop, Young Australian!! #YouthPower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud! My girl @hannahwandel and her absolutely inspiring, courageous #powertrip winners. Great start to the day https://t.co/EP7noMYnED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @Mattel for donating $50k to keep children safe from violence - true hero's #starry16 â­ï¸ðŸ‘ðŸ½ https://t.co/hWtA888GKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mattel you're incredible xxx https://t.co/JKcwE1weWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sally_nicholes such a pleasure meeting you last night Sally. You're absolutely amazing, wish there was more people like your self xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW. Wow. WOW. Wow. WOW! Thank you everyone for supporting @alannahmadeline and Australia's children â¤ï¸ï¸â­ï¸ #Starry16 https://t.co/XvtOvevY1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STARRY STARRY NIGHT with the Australian Hero's â­ï¸â­ï¸is it okay to be in love? #starry16 @alannahmadeline @_mackhorton https://t.co/mSgak51jTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @melissadoyle and @RobMillsyMills up close and personal. Growing up I watched them on TV..Is this real #Starry16 https://t.co/usBvb0WTUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the drawings is a child's story. Cannot wait to join 1000ppl support @alannahmadeline at #Stary16 tonight https://t.co/KvdWFWibzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blown away by @alannahmadeline #CubbyHouse, #BuddyBag &amp; #eSmart programs-Such an honour to be an Ambassador #Stary16 https://t.co/exbEcSSEYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Macker62 you're incredible!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Macker62 pleasure to meet you too Tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too â­ï¸â­ï¸â­ï¸â­ï¸ https://t.co/2vO9IJuslT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@podesta_lesley welcome to Twitter Lesley x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for @TEDxYouthCBR!Spreading innovation and leadership through our capitals youth - what can be better? #Youth4GenderEquality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to joining the incredible @hannahwandel at @YWCACanberra as a board trainee #SDG5 #WomenWhoLead https://t.co/fRU7RIgryq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @2XXFM studio for interviewing @CBRWiseWomen   &amp; myself to discuss the topic-Women Who Lead  #SDG5 #GreatFun https://t.co/Jr95Kaasqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravikarkara @jk_rowling @GIRLBOSS @smrtgrls @BBCNewsbeat I love this!! Just the #hope I needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone needs some inspiration after the #election I want to send you one of my favourite books. DM me #ShareLove https://t.co/R55RglpJ3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@community_hope it's wrong to attack a person on their choice of career or shame them for what they decide to do with their body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@community_hope exactly, so let's work towards ensuring Trump doesn't enforce his oppressive views and try reunifying society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@community_hope this truly horrifies me. But we cannot give in to hatred and bullying. Two wrongs don't make a right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@community_hope I don't support Trump in anyway. But I'm primarily taking about the bullying she is receiving over her supermodel career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see criticism of @MELANIATRUMP career. If we want to support women we need to support their freedom to CHOOSE without judgment. #SDG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpreadGirlLove little girls need to hear this today. Help remind girls of their worth #GirlPower https://t.co/p3tPuisfzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm feeling incredibly sad today, but @ALeighMP your Parliament speech just gave me the hope. Thank you for standing for unity and decency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed! We can not give up on freedom and human rights! https://t.co/Nuwf5fnUuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HorrifyingTruth-Exactly why we need to address structural inequalities &amp; advance SDG5 for all girls @officeforwomen https://t.co/l61UFLXzM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree @MingYLong! But I have full faith that we will get there just as long as we work together https://t.co/lZues5m9WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#America has voted. Despite the outcome, as Australians we need to work with the USA to uphold human rights and development. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnowwyWolfHowl @kartik48 they definitely are, just look at a number of economic policies for one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnowwyWolfHowl @kartik48 I agree I want @BernieSanders for President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_EmmaCrane it's about gender equality, human rights, global stability....now all of that is in jeopardy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_C_PR1 working visa? Check out Australia's immigration website]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_C_PR1 don't worry, we've got rooms to spare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashstreeterrrrr @realDonaldTrump @PressClubAust @YoungAustIntAff what were you doing at the press club?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldsonAbbey they said that about Brexit as well...but whatever the decision, we have to stick together and support defenders of equality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldsonAbbey I'm actually crying. I cannot believe this. How is this reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free licence to oppress women.Women of the world-We must stick together-We will not let this break us #ElectionNight https://t.co/dQusXQi4jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling #DumbledoresArmy Unite! Together we will protect the values we hold so dear - love, respect, peace. Stay strong #potter heads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnowwyWolfHowl I have, and she has always supported the advancement of women's rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrified. Shocked. Scared &amp; on the verge of tears. #GenderEquality is about to be set back by 50yrs #ElectionNight https://t.co/6G7ATgdLt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahwandel @HillaryClinton @Tara_Moss me too girl! I think drinks are on the cards tonight.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>