<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/x1Yw1qTzU1 Dog with stretchy cheeks CUTE VIDEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/5KJT3MCcuN Touch My Body (Tuts My Barreh) / Karaoke Fail (English subtitles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Tyler's tribute to Graham Taylor | Football | Soccer | Sports https://t.co/53OeuoSQWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are we wasting time on this when the real crims are out there beating up their wives, stealing money from the... https://t.co/G63py7Wbw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/BHwkFi0wVG Princess Leia Space Buns for Extremely Long Hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Malaysian's physics-defying, long-range free kick crowned FIFA's goal of the year https://t.co/3DQIKEukjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/Az7Bu7gaFb Debbie Reynolds Carrie Fisher Tribute The Golden Globes 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/cvjuHIuWWT The True Cost of Hair Extensions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warriors Mom Dances with Cheerleaders | 12.20.16 https://t.co/zzEuYhwmIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/IeGcmOEkWd Warriors Mom Dances with Cheerleaders | 12.20.16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Richardson say's sorry for running out Brendon McCullum on Debut https://t.co/rPpkx3PtUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brendon McCullum ODI debut ruined by Mark Richardson - Funny https://t.co/H8jla2WEd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CGW | Mark cramps up on air https://t.co/NwmvqSM1ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you may have heard Mark Richardson is leaving CGW for the greener pastures of 3am wake up calls and breakfast... https://t.co/cVJShI5lTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live coverage of Berlin attacks courtesy of German state broadcaster, Das Erste. https://t.co/C5Ay0gymDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live coverage of Berlin attacks from Deutsche Welle. https://t.co/8JzVY20HBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/UqBlq3FIiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can terminally ill Bradley Lowery win goal of the month after Sunderland strike? https://t.co/KAdvYDm1n2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/2gG0m9H0W9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is ridiculous. https://t.co/IlJhgorGuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports suggest Ernie Merrick has resigned as Wellington Phoenix https://t.co/PUI0DiQUFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa! https://t.co/dPLZjRV4P9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapecoense goalkeeper Nivaldo confirms retirement after plane crash https://t.co/qOxbMsAk4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool FC v Manchester United final? https://t.co/ebTkZd4471]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapecoense plane crash: The victims, the survivors and those left behind - BBC News https://t.co/mG2f2ckscc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not just the players who have been lost. https://t.co/8Xn05RAmQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cartoon is the most touching tribute to the soccer players killed in plane crash https://t.co/3gYGeQvsxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with most but I'd have - 

5. Devin Toner for Maro Itoje

6. CJ Stander for Chris Robshaw

7. Sam Cane... https://t.co/YXdgVxLtAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapecoense's last game before the tragedy yesterday. https://t.co/fdGl0LmfFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More grim news. https://t.co/9I81fnD2lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trendsetting F1 star https://t.co/WZS7HoBC3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, football witnessed a tragedy of the type that we haven't seen since 1993 and hoped never to see again.... https://t.co/1B9XrorASy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F1 | Jenson Button Farawell Tribute | Thank You Jenson! https://t.co/EuUVuQ6hM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @f1prezes367 https://t.co/ybTkjpIuM4 F1 | Jenson Button Farewell Tribute | Thank You Jenson!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I save the best for last :-) https://t.co/3Rw3hpOt6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Button And Massa On Saying Goodbye To F1 | Abu Dhabi Grand Prix 2016 https://t.co/MQfmrFTFtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie G's greatest goal for Liverpool IMO. https://t.co/eVOZVPijYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay away from pub quizzes, Jenson. https://t.co/P1FMXgYmyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it me or am I getting old? In the last couple of hours, Liverpool and England great Steven Gerrard (who is... https://t.co/vjgsmPk6EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, Jenson Button &amp; Steven Gerrard announcing their retirement all in the last 24 hours. I feel old now! https://t.co/RcnW1wqmXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump very close to naming who he will appoint as President https://t.co/teVokGn0IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jenson's first ever qualifying (in full) - fast forward to 20:48 for his first lap - and to hear Martin Brundle... https://t.co/KZ1zsDXShC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new beginning awaits - Jenson Button Q&amp;A https://t.co/GmZkXh5KcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray Walker &amp; Jenson Button - Full Interview https://t.co/ab9w9IhRRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jenson Button's Career Highlights https://t.co/4QlF9PoPds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 27 November 2016, one of the most venerable F1 careers will draw to a close (for now). 

Abu Dhabi will... https://t.co/Lwko73ZLJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This and Jenson Button and Felipe Massa retiring from F1 will really feel like the end of my childhood now. 

Is... https://t.co/DZxl17FYLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/qxHr672xQe New Sunday Night Football intro - featuring Carrie Underwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayhem in Wellington. Buses held up on Willis Street and Johnsonville trains suspended at the moment! @NZTAWgtn https://t.co/69BxYsW4hN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayhem in Wellington. Buses and trains all down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline. The All Blacks need discipline. — watching Ireland v New Zealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Colin de Grandhomme the new Scott Styris? — watching New Zealand vs Pakistan 1st Test Live Stream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a 48 hours this has been. It's as if God decided to remind New Zealand about the forces of nature. We've had... https://t.co/onWRr4Dfqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government pushes urgent legislation to end 2016, have New Year’s right now https://t.co/bc1xUiHlNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another big one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did anyone feel that aftershock? I thought that was Ezekiel Elliott running into the room from Pittsburgh. #eqnz... https://t.co/rCtpsgM4NU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellingtonians advised to stay out of CBD unless essential https://t.co/1eoKlG1Fqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington workers urged to stay at home following 7.5 quake https://t.co/OAlgg9F8G2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know https://t.co/0U1KRrKLeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did anyone else feel that earthquake? That woke me up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's official - New Zealand has forgotten how to beat an Irish team. — watching Munster V Maori All Blacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad we can watch sport rather than more Trump this morning. What should I watch -

a) Munster v NZ Maori
B)... https://t.co/ojs6vU6b9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RIPLeonardCohen 

This has really been a sad week for America/Canada. https://t.co/l6Y0VzkzjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn where are your ETAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see that generation of ultra strong super criminals and midnight basketball. https://t.co/g3I9qHrypj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladygaga Come to New Zealand!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelissaStokes Well you made it to the @DailyMailUK! https://t.co/zek8N7iz99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I should put my two cents on President Trump after the most extraordinary 24 hours I’ve ever witnessed... https://t.co/AROCdDOd1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump (it is).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, America flips a coin. Literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Christian Americans, I quote 2 Timothy 1:7 - "For God gave us a spirit not of fear but of power and love and... https://t.co/JtFQzGPULP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok here's a question that really baffles me - what do American Christians like about Trump over Clinton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fail! Steelers Kicker, Chris Boswell. Attempts Worst Onside Kick Ever! | NFL https://t.co/PPRKsn3Vpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL. Scotty, Shaun. https://t.co/rn2tDua2u4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well they did make history at last. Well done Ireland. https://t.co/GfHANRZ5Xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. https://t.co/VLHFvpNlpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing's for certain - it'll be Back to the Future 2 or How I Met Your Mother tonight depending on who wins... https://t.co/0U0du2Ls5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Highlanders squad for 2017. This cracks me up. https://t.co/ed5VuithJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will watch nothing but How I Met Your Mother and talk like Ted Mosby if Cleveland wins the NBA and World Series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph Parker is set to head to the home of Jerry Jones. Dallas here we come. #BREAKING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic 'Afghan Girl' arrested https://t.co/SjoqbRaH29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passion of the Mitre 10 Cup https://t.co/eAdXxrOaj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you SKY Sport NZ. This brings back memories of my early days in NZ watching Josh Blackie, Brendan Laney,... https://t.co/Hivdr8rci6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iceland braces for pirates https://t.co/PT52SDgkCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most boring #SNF ever? #SEAvsAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Izzy and Maria!! Imagine their kids...... https://t.co/oaohLM8GBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyprus here we come. Only 6 more wins.. — watching All Blacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/LnJnSTzgGh The Simpsons - The Bus That Couldn't Slow Down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #GableTostee trial is turning out to be a very B-grade version of the #OJSimpson trial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be huge. https://t.co/m91V3VMtwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikedurack Hey buddy, you may remember me from Rugby Rebels - wanted to say shocked to hear about Anthony Foley's death. #RIPAnthonyFoley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatPokemonGo piss off we live in a democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear New Zealander of the Year Awards, please please give the late Helen Kelly what she deserves and the ultimate... https://t.co/o4ocKsc9xU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what's outside our house. https://t.co/hmOcYXpI2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know @RuthWW was engaged to @will_davison. No wonder she took the @1NewsSportNZ job at #Bathurst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/czWiPzvXss Wayne Barnes gets hit in the head by the ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @thehaarminnaar https://t.co/X3APcDGkoy Long hair to please men? I'm past that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/JNGA9YdtMQ Donna Lewis - I Love You Always Forever (Official Video)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/ykHQunJYic 11 YEAR OLD PICKING UP GIRLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/waZmngzImY Bass Blows Model Girl's Hair Wild &amp; Crazy https://t.co/K6QaN4tCJz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>