<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Of the Supreme Court, to the Supreme Court" was worth staying up for alone. And the odd lesson on #SCOTUS history.
Sorry, alternative fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could do with the Fellowship reuniting at the moment! #LOTR https://t.co/WzBYnkVKSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkandelic That's my position too, but I want a strong answer for a seminar debate. Up against C20th folk it's already complicated enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slightly cheating before the roundtable discussion tonight, but out of curiosity...Is the American Civil War a modern conflict or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoiler: American Civil War is a modern conflict, but my research contradicts this, leading to an existential crisi… https://t.co/d66CJvVcpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn Is this for later this afternoon? I'm at 10 mins 22 seconds - so shave a few seconds off, that less last minute work for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally getting around to listen to @WhiskeyRebelPod. I'm a biased listener, but @davidsilkenat &amp; @FrankCogliano are highly entertaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should academics boycott Donald Trump's America? https://t.co/rln9xr2N3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preach. After an evening protesting, this is the best interview to watch. @CarolineLucas giving an honest answer… https://t.co/9PeUtE36qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely peaceful, unifying, proud and loud #MuslimBanProtest in #Edinburgh tonight. This is what democracy looks… https://t.co/qBVh9NT4yN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down @RoyalMileEdin to @ScotParl #MuslimBanProtest #Edinburgh https://t.co/vyQAtlpwtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edinburgh right now - peaceful protest #MuslimBanprotest #Edinburgh https://t.co/uDdAGKoPUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A statement which hovers between paradox and meaninglessness" - a comment about Progressive historiography or current UK gov't attitudes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Scottish cities to hold Donald Trump travel ban protests https://t.co/yoL8LRI78b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time last year, teaching this 1922 US women in politics cartoon meant something very different. Tutorials tomo… https://t.co/4wY4fqzMUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order: Million sign petition to stop UK visit - If you haven't already, sign this! https://t.co/T6i42lOdrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling so outnumbered for my ACW/C19th part of tomorrow's Mod Con seminar, I'm relying on Robert E. Lee quotes to… https://t.co/e0GO7wSroo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if it couldn't get more grim, he goes and mentions world war himself. It's been 9 days. Mother. Of. God. https://t.co/G3BQ0jBJ03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Nero played the fiddle while Rome burnt... https://t.co/A57BsyQG6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Trump petition. His coming will cause riots. Don't be a coward @theresa_may, you should sign too #TrumpBan https://t.co/ZWT11cb1jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @BuzzFeed is pointing out GOP hypocrisy, you know you're in a brave new world of political commentary… https://t.co/HB7tbOso9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted to retweet this at the end of every week of this administration https://t.co/IlOya7Mz0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon Sopel's gloves: How they appeared as if by magic - A more lighthearted note from America via @BBCJonSopel  https://t.co/9GQ8R4EFz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May fails to condemn Donald Trump on refugees - This is despicable &amp; cowardly #NotMyPrimeMinister  https://t.co/yBg0OjziH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally put up my new map of the USA, mapping authors, poets and writers of importance to the history of the States https://t.co/x4DxKeNIqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on the America presidency and the state of the American nation in 1865... https://t.co/vOQNpkt8XO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The times seem to me so out of joint that I can scarcely bear to write. It seems to me that the country is mad" - 1864 or 2017 America/UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George III's draft abdication letter released https://t.co/5sMbX9LXGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir John Hurt: Bafta-winning actor dies  - Sad news about John Hurt, a brilliant actor with such a distinctive voice https://t.co/dTYUTrnxsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's trustworthy. He's the Doctor @TheLastLeg @bbcdoctorwho #isitok #thelastleg https://t.co/st9ShmFKGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Republican press say there were 25,000 persons present. The Democratic press say 100,000' -  so much/so little alters over 150+ years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time last week: alternative crowd sizes. The Sept 1864 Democrat ratification meeting in Union Square also questioned attendance...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@contestedground @bbc5live @realDonaldTrump They did! I cheered when you came back, much easier on radio ears than Trump. Well done Malcolm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@film_und_foto I'm surprised managed to survive this entire week - I came close to destroying it with May's speech yesterday to be honest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When it irons out, you're going to have your identity" - WHAT? We've got lots of multicultural identities. Brexit won't change that Donald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the fact the British reporters are subtly getting under Trump's skin. He really doesn't like any hint of criticism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's. Saying. Nothing. Just words. Pointless yet harmful words. Come on May, do a 'Love Actually' moment. Trump is awful. This is all awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew my years of listening to @bbc5live would pay off. Great interview @contestedground! Only to be cut off by Tr… https://t.co/3c1wXdXCJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s a German word that perfectly encapsulates the start of Trump’s presidency https://t.co/mUTI74Smle via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really cool Scottish American item in the Museum of Edinburgh - an American Bicentennial Goblet @ScotAmStudies… https://t.co/7v8032kUvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not on the @stuffofwar treasure hunt, but interesting history items regardless - pottery relating to Ireland, Corn… https://t.co/fPezrt8FjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a @stuffofwar treasure hunt/planning meeting in the Museum of Edinburgh. Baby Haig &amp; uniform will appear at our… https://t.co/TyA53wNK1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen May's speech to Republicans. The rhetoric is deeply unnerving. Not a good special relationship development #NotMyPrimeMinister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Chocolate, a glass of sherry, and a sandwich was the only entertainment" - New York house partying c.May 1864. Sounds like a riot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing I could go to this - already midway through it @irishacw, the stories are so compelling! Can't wait to chat… https://t.co/6dgFbgoeoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting the final plans in place for this next weekend - looking forward to it! @ScotAmStudies https://t.co/AqP68MYWxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) "A nation without borders is not a nation" makes no sense &amp; 2) how can you make Mexico pay for the wall? https://t.co/lEnedUNjqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to make a Welsh person happy - give them a very funny Welsh language pun #StDwynwensDay ❤️ https://t.co/TplUF9AJe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Lucy Worsley just imply William of Orange is disliked by the Welsh because of the Battle of the Boyne on @BBCBreakfast? Um.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching C20th US history this year will be different, but the students are already so on the ball it's lifting my 'oh woah America' spirits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to hear this paper later - kinship and giants oh my! https://t.co/F0Bm3wenNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some serious alternative facts about Americans and WW1 &amp; 'Gone With the Wind' screenings in tonight's #Halcyon episode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final bits of tutorial prep for tomorrow. As 'alternative facts' seem to be the new order I'll just throw out the importance of context part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are ruled by an aristocracy of public cheats and swindlers and have no right of choice" - Again, 2017 or 1863?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Unnatural, and dreadful war. When deserted by those we suppose friends...it is the more gratefully recognised' 2/2 - Trump &amp; Putin c. 1863]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One diarist: 'I am glad to see us show such recognition of this national courtesy which Russia has shown us during this tedious...' 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about the Russian Ball held in NYC in November 1863 and all the festivities American/Irish American dignitaries put on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest number "a slap in the face to a man who cares about size". Yes! Applauding @KattyKayBBC's #MarchOnWashington report #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Precisely #WomensMarch https://t.co/RHiSyasVzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world definitely needs an enormous cwtch today - and everyday #cwtch https://t.co/LXZetfWYCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseannaJane And modern history - yet another reason why the C19th is problematic, no space travel...haaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseannaJane That's brilliant!! Wish I could make a reference to that - or anything space related #C19thhistorycontextproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['One lady...wears a bird's nest with eggs...I doubt if there is enough brain there to hatch anything'. Times change thankfully #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...Such vapid, inconsistent, violent expressions!" - that's 1863 American speak for #nastywomen #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It says this about women in #CivilWar America... "It was amusing to hear the political views of the ladies..." 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing some 1863 diary reading that makes me so glad times &amp; opinions changes, and voices get louder #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum. Most of this sounds delicious #Lincoln #Inauguration https://t.co/EVnffm33Ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Here We Are: Donald Trump Is Officially The President  https://t.co/rrhtXhYRrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've moved my nodding Obama to my desk, so he can hang out with Lincoln. If life is like Toy Story, these two will… https://t.co/2YBKvn1XEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god, I thought it sounded familiar... #Inaugurationspeech https://t.co/jiXqBlwEnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KEBlackstone From here on in, make it up history!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we just take a moment to mourn the #Inauguration speech we won't hear from @HillaryClinton, and how much of a queen she is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophcoCooper @contestedground Harrison was probably sick before his inauguration...was this one sniffing??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KEBlackstone Given how much of it really makes no sense, none of it can be taken seriously. The course will be cal… https://t.co/gIYhbBZg1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@contestedground Is it wrong to hope the same Harrison fate might befall Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wrote this? Is this serious or satire? This is terrifying, hilarious &amp; sad all at once. God I can't wait to teach students this speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All talk, no action...Empty talk...The hour of action" - ladies and gentlemen, behold the hypocrisy #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This speech is saying nothing. It's just words for supporters. #Inauguration isn't the campaign. Has 4 years passed yet? This is unbearable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Issuing decrees? Jesus it's the Hunger Games. He's saying nothing, yet it's terrifying. Imagine this in 1930s black &amp; white. Reminds me of..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It belongs to you...everyone gathered today" - yes, including Hillary who is behind you. It belongs to Hillary #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Determine the course of the world" - no thanks Donald, you've got enough to do with those small hands #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this speech is missing is Ken Burns music.... #Inauguration Let's just be clear he's referring to a CIVIL WAR. Welcome to 2017...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm also watching because I really want to see if time travel is a future possibility. Today's the day we find out #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so tough to see though. Still can't believe it's happening, but history, including the bad parts, has to be witnessed #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because observing history matters, American historian me won the internal debate over watching #Inauguration. Not going to enjoy it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The replies to these @ScotAmStudies are also cheering me up enormously. Americanists are lovely folk. Roll on #SASA17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hoping all the @ScotAmStudies emails I'm sending out provide a bit of happiness on this dreary day for America...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I feel about today....#Inauguration https://t.co/3SMxNH6Ga3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have given offices to the highest bidder and...placed authority in the hands of brigands" - more blurring between 2017 &amp; 1862 America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to @stuffofwar and enjoy three great days of papers, talks, debate &amp; events - registration now open! https://t.co/9pf8KJzUqP  #WTOS17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be such a great end to the first day of #WTOS17 - Pan's Labyrinth &amp; Spanish Civil War @Filmhouse -… https://t.co/vca531kopV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voting restrictions 'trace back to Jim Crow and slavery'. @BarackObama I'm going to miss you as president so much. History &amp; present combine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton And this is why I view you with such suspicion...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton Also not so sure he threw an tantrum as more just doesn't get the Welsh, Welsh history &amp; it's peculiar politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton Waving that Welsh nationalist dragon flag through history forever :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton It's definitely a quite hostile opinion though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton Well the Welsh result does an upset. But the Celtic fringe argument doesn't work - England's the fringe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton In short, not a fun read there Fraser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton 'Peculiar treatment' is mild. It forgets Welsh nationalism's long history. And conflates Wales into England.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserRaeburn @JonSingerton 'Wales.. the role of the afterthought that follows the conjunction in ‘England-and-Wales’. Er....no...sigh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>