<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the @NancyPelosi #PelosiTownHall tonight on @CNN @CNNPolitics whilst here in the US https://t.co/V3HElzqXcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is getting a lot of kudos for his stand today and the points were well made, but we're too far down the #Brexit path now @andriumacl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am indeed @MMaryMcKenna and met @Entirl in the same building as @IrelandCGAustin Wonderful city. Full of character. Incredible food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely, that's key for focusing the mind on positive priorities and actions that matter  @DBpsychology @hiberniaroots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one of my favourites @AoifeMollin @LEODublinCity My New Years Resolution in 2013 that yielded dividend after dividend. Best wishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's wall-to-wall coverage of the latest thing, whatever that might be at the time! @byard_inspired @PaulineLogan @LEODublinCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am indeed! The fastest growing city in the US that can preserve its character very well. @byard_inspired @PaulineLogan @LEODublinCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're welcome and I send you my very best wishes @VasilenkoTania]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are more than welcome @VasilenkoTania and thank you to @PaulineLogan for giving me the opportunity to speak to you @LEODublinCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This can keep you on track towards your direction and help influence daily actions @VasilenkoTania @LEODublinCity Go for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheel of Strategy can focus the mind alright. @VasilenkoTania @LEODublinCity Keep a list of daily meaningful activities done towards goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Strategy? Four key questions to ask when establishing or getting #strategy back on track  https://t.co/p5JHZ0Dk4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you there! @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess @LoveCork @CorkHour @SBSTodayfm @GriffinsGardenC @Corkinnovates @MyraHayes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just about to go there now @pam_rave What do you suggest? #RaineySt #Austin #Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very glad to hear that as it adds even more authenticity to what you do. @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will be the day you set the record straight with yourself. Enjoy it! @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you and let's collectively #DreamBigFor2017 @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess #GoForIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's wonderful to hear and your enthusiasm will be felt by your members @URInspiring @NetDublin @IrishFairyDoor @CIT_Careers @LEOSouthCork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like your staff, your events and your holistic offering! @legalisland @robcullen79 @DubCham @JayneGall2014 https://t.co/tS1aZhlwMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, in a most endearing way! @ItsSocialBee @unahealydesign @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need to apologise at all! It caught my eye as I'm in #Austin TX currently and met your @Entirl @EI_theUSA  colleagues. @sxsw looks great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace your nerves. They create empathy and are the antithesis of complacency. @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic! You have a great story with a great header underpinning your sparkle. @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots @Tweetinggoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very happy to hear that! @letusrevolt @SBSTodayfm You're  working with the momentum of a very significant trend #WellnessintheWorkplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you're doing the same Marie with @NetDublin! @URInspiring @IrishFairyDoor @CIT_Careers @LEOSouthCork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a memorable talking point, photo op and Modt tweetable! @robcullen79 @DubCham @JayneGall2014 @legalisland #Goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope your first month has been the foundation of a superb year @IsleenDesign @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan and #February is even better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This question really cuts from the brain to the heart @TheTaxStudioIE @SocialZavvy @SavvyWomenBrand @NetDublin @LEOFingal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @hiberniaroots and I hope that spreadsheet is filling up with actions bringing you closer to your personal and professional goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! @unahealydesign @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan Interested to hear what you take from the book &amp; put into your own business #Goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @AoifeMollin @LEODublinCity Any particular insights that have worked out for you? Hope life is treating you very well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to hear that @TrishFoxDesign @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan Interested to hear what has worked for you since?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @maker_dublin @LEODublinCity Networking within my network has been immensely useful in organic growth https://t.co/ixoU0YLETh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #BlarneyStone is helpful too!! @ItsSocialBee @unahealydesign @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan #DreamBig #CorkChatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much! #DreamBig @wegiveitawhirl @LEODublinCity @PaulineLogan How are you getting on since?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the truth @JuliaEazyCity @SavvyWomenBrand @letusrevolt @EazyCity @Aircoach @DublinAirport Didn't know @Twitter was blocked in China!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a fantastic business idea and I can imagine that life is going to get very busy now! @stpatdaydublin @PaulineLogan @LEODublinCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great! @marygwebdesign @LEODublinCity How had your homework materialised? What's been particularly effective? Any unanticipated blockages?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to hear that @bayinfoods @oishii_foods @LEODublinCity and I would love to hear your story along the way. Keep me posted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet you and thank you for your suggested newsletter @byard_inspired @PaulineLogan @LEODublinCity It's on my reading list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you continue to do that @hiberniaroots as you strike me as a woman that has grasped opportunity on many occasions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a tough mantra to live by... and most effective for those who choose to. @DBpsychology @hiberniaroots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's such a lovely thing to say! @busybeaders2013 @hiberniaroots Are you going to @Tweetinggoddess #WomenInspire in #Cork?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet you again Camilla and to follow up on our conversation at @DigitalDNAHQ @bespoke_comms @salesireland @LeanInBelfast @BespokeNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True to her fabulous personality,  @nualafmurphy says "I have time for everybody, just like my Dad" @LeanInBelfast @salesireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a continuously dynamic relationship between sales and world affairs.Crucial for business people to keep at… https://t.co/CGuJGUTu6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Issues to discuss; #Brexit #Trump #border #sterling #importsubstitution #immigration #GDPgrowth #NorthernIreland @ConsultNb1 @salesireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A most sincere, mutual respect for you both @JoWatson42 @ConsultNb1 https://t.co/j49SPtZRp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a delight @ConsultNb1 @salesireland @JoWatson42 You've got a great group. Wholeheartedly encourage #Belfast #businesses to join you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has that #Wowfactor @robcullen79 on arrival! @JayneGall2014 @legalisland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to hear this @VasilenkoTania @LEODublinCity Have you put some of the ideas into action? Would love to hear your #progress!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharing this innovative entrance with offices here in #Austin @JayneGall2014 @legalisland #BelfastLeadingTheWorld https://t.co/jSZ1VidSRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great that you could join us! In the US currently.  So much change since I spoke to you all...@Watsonmydear @ConsultNb1 @salesireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fashion and colour-co-ordination is nowehere near the level of Noel's @mavishanlon @JoWatson42 @ConsultNb1 A great guy in a great city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing @foothillexpwy @PaulineLogan @LEODublinCity Hope you've implemented some ideas from the evening. May 2017 be amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always @AerLingus It was top class, full of wonderful, attentive staff, Irish food and great entertainment #SmartFliesAerLingus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely @reworkpip @teamrework There are several events and dinners that you hold of interest #fintech #VA #IOT #disruption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will remember that @letusrevolt How are you getting on? Last time we met was @SBSTodayfm #teamsbs in Cork!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for sharing @Entirl @EI_theUSA Can I ask to clarify who this @SXSW2017 is as the account has been suspended? Interested to attend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eurozone’s economic recovery picks up speed https://t.co/rlkhvLVadR via @FT A broad overview, but youth unemployment is stickily high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE 7 HABITS OF HIGHLY EFFECTIVE PEOPLE BY STEPHEN COVEY - ANIMATED BOOK... A great summary of a phenomenal book https://t.co/ixlvVtrKeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a @TEDTalks that brings everything to a presentation; trchnicsl@insight, vulnerable emotion, a story, an ou… https://t.co/U5Dm2kNrUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My stroke of insight | Jill Bolte Taylor  https://t.co/nEc070pPv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #quote in the #Wanderlust cafe Austin, Texas https://t.co/SPZ7fYQCFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A throwback to growing up in rural Ireland! This is the front of an Irish bar in Austin, Texas! https://t.co/8VtoguPI1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I highly recommend attending this wonderful university! @nuigalway https://t.co/EOAOyV8Ua7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["1.5 days worth of tasks in your working week  could be automated according to @McKinsey. That's $2 trillion saving… https://t.co/Wi7BKEsoT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know how many of my fellow delegates here in #SanFrancisco would know of that type of #AI at all Ken!!!! @KillorglinKen @reworkVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what's missing from #AI? "Deeper semantics of natural language" @reworkVA #reworkVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure! I will update you right along the way @tallainc @ArdleCulleton @SlackHQ @reworkVA #reworkVA #SanFrancisco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Self driving cars have the possibility of making far better decisions and being better drivers than humans ever co… https://t.co/fCxcl49SYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Machines are now able to see and hear us. What's the next frontier of perception?" @reworkVA #reworkVA @teamrework #SanFrancisco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You should be afraid if you enter a space without understanding the laws" says @MedWhatYou @reworkVA #reworkVA… https://t.co/Ctwmjc8SuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to meet you @algorithmia we will continue the conversation after @reworkVA From #Dublin to #Seattle @DublinCityUni @LEODublinCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello @stevenogara Check out @Hal24k @JennifervdBerg_ regarding managing the Dublin City data for planning. Interes… https://t.co/PUyEhifePf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to test @tallainc in our company @ArdleCulleton @SlackHQ will post thoughts and feedback  here soon… https://t.co/e4jndCHwwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where those streets have no name! I'm trotting after admiringly you! @MMaryMcKenna @nualafmurphy @DubaiIBN @IIBN @eithnetreanor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I met her there last September. You're a #NetworkingQueen &amp; #NetworkingRoleModel @MMaryMcKenna @nualafmurphy @DubaiIBN @IIBN @eithnetreanor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BuddyGuard @george_platon is launching in the US in July @BuddyGuard_io @reworkVA @teamrework #reworkVA #AI https://t.co/aga7NtCvWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like you're connecting with nature there! @MMaryMcKenna @nualafmurphy Re Dubai if you've time check out @DubaiIBN like minds @IIBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At #reworkVA @george_platon talks is through service-based assistants vs interaction @reworkVA @teamrework https://t.co/WAR2R4D66W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one smart robot!! #BigI @tinlunlam @reworkVA #reworkVA @teamrework https://t.co/bFahgmrkO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to be of service! Best wishes to you all @DouglasLawsols @findingjimoh @ROSSIntel @reworkVA #Future #BestPractise #SanFrancisco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A home robot needs to be calm and peaceful, safe and warm, (huggable) and alive to communication" says @tinlunlam… https://t.co/QZk4d17qxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could #robots become part of the family? @reworkVA #reworkVA @teamrework @tinlunlam https://t.co/lgAOC9X15l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch that space. It's very forward looking and would be a service disruptor in many ways @DouglasLawsols @findingjimoh @ROSSIntel @reworkVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a big dream! @ekuyda wants us to use machine #bots to help us become more human. @reworkVA @teamrework… https://t.co/xLFxzkfhUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There isn't any space on the internet right now for #vulnerability" says @ekuyda @facebook is too public and irony is used on @Snapchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The moment that we become vulnerable; that's when we connect" says @ekuyda @reworkVA @teamrework #reworkVA Watch this space. She is great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very smart observation on the part of @ekuyda at @reworkVA @teamrework #reworkVA https://t.co/3aUqb4yTyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure! Let's do that @abethebot @ArdleCulleton If you follow me here on Twitter, I will DM my details.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are here to enable everybody to be be able to afford justice" says @findingjimoh @ROSSIntel #reworkVA #AI #bots https://t.co/uvuIlm6b5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AI is set to revolutionise legal services says @findingjimoh with greater efficiency, comprehensiveness and profitability @ROSSIntel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright #California sun high in the sky this morning before a run around #UnionSquare #SanFrancisco Aerate the brain… https://t.co/dJDyK2UoHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the author of "The Savvy Wonan's Guide to Financial Freedom" with @PenguinBooks so there may be some way to col… https://t.co/52KKKIsCLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to Orlando shortly @abethebot and it would be great to meet while there. Are you going to the @MoneyShows in#Orlando next month?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Treasa @letusrevolt So far @teamrework has been massively thought provoking and lots more to come!… https://t.co/9a8ac3Jter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I followed this exactly @MichelleGielan https://t.co/ucAH8hmKpL when flying from @DublinAirport to @flySFO Mych easier to beat #jetlag!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["47% of Americans would struggle to come up with $400 in the event of an emergency" @abethebot tells us at… https://t.co/SLzZC54AKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm now a real supporter of the work you do at @teamrework Great forward looking, well-organised  conferences with diverse speakers]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>