<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Its advertising a Danish tv station ( I think?)  but it conveys a fantastic message. https://t.co/cBPL6gNppH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enough! https://t.co/ZTY8zpymWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I acknowledge the Wurundjeri people, the traditional custodians of the land where I use to live and where... https://t.co/EWLCbJOp3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many pictures from around the world of yesterdays hustorical marches. These ones are from Edinburgh, Scotland by... https://t.co/tGWPFbyCri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pictures From Women’s Marches Around the World https://t.co/50vgryehuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#chicago has always been my favourite city! https://t.co/9sXLOQllVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the Full Transcript Of Angela Davis's Women's March Speech https://t.co/CP5SPgJwXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apply for Designers in Residence 2017 https://t.co/eGtM00LHGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Street https://t.co/bDBqFjMNMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bang goes my healthy eating! Apprently theres no courgettes, spinach or aubergines in #tescos due to spanish... https://t.co/4SiCPFkhMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now accepting applications: Craft &amp; Design Artist-in-Residence Program | Harbourfront Centre Blog https://t.co/5qSqF8iOnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great project which I was involved in. Watch out for their auction https://t.co/gHa8yYIXr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the textile printers in my life Lorna Brown Jenni Douglas Gill Norval. Enjoy! https://t.co/ZYiWiV3DIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schmuck 2017 here I come with Lieta Marziali. Canny wait!... https://t.co/Hjeeln9yuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im booking up for schmuck 2017 but I have no idea which part of Munich to stay in. Id like to be pretty central, any suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[open call for artists: Art+Text @ 44AD artspace https://t.co/w1UtEznzfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A warning to children': Police release powerful film about... https://t.co/EkkLrXWmhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 tickets to Trainspotting 2 Premiere in Edinburgh &amp; after party access! https://t.co/9cZhRNwcdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please copy and repost (not share)? Someone is always there to help !!!
#SuicideAwareness xx♥ 0808 808 8000 LIFELINE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this would be great! https://t.co/MCRUz59dkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Princess Leia!. I have now had enough of the year!!! https://t.co/F8hZEzgOXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all a very happy Festive time. I hope you are surrounded by friends, family and love. Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rather lovely reflection of jewellery of past, croissants (aka train journeys to sheffield), fireworks (aka... https://t.co/PBo5UTJBbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter Solstice – History and Tradition https://t.co/s16FdYb834]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are your most beautiful photos from 2013-2016? https://t.co/9NUbbOcTkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Open! https://t.co/tGMKb0Re9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want personal EU citizenship?  Send a message to the European Parliament - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/4g3JPktq1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016 https://t.co/SR7iLMJxm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016 https://t.co/WvkuMMO4yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be a great prize https://t.co/FDjQa34ic7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacular bronze age gold torc unearthed in Cambridgeshire field https://t.co/wgRKO4yFnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very special place is under threat from wildfires https://t.co/sGJW75KGF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 Doors of Advent - What's on - Edinburgh's Christmas - Underbelly https://t.co/WzFO2GI7hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I still lived  id go and see with my Melbourne friends https://t.co/dk22LjT9br]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds about right... https://t.co/Hvek4mVgmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram photo by Ali Wolfe • Jul 20, 2016 at 3:12am UTC https://t.co/atIwVoB4Og]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aberfeldy has it all. Fantastic music, walks, cakes, waterfalls, art deco architecture, Rabbie and independant... https://t.co/UJ2yGu0EmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great night with great tunes at the #aberfeldyfestival  #derosa #ianrankin – attending Aberfeldy Festival No:7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Just Announced He’s Going to Save Standing Rock By Rerouting Pipeline https://t.co/f6zMGqThpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Largest Native American Protest In HISTORY Is Happening Right Now And YOU Need To Know About It! – Indigenous... https://t.co/Umkbhgagrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revival of the little mesters: a Sheffield pocket knife maker – in pictures https://t.co/2JEOrkUBuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10,000 Books Create a Literary River on the Streets of Toronto https://t.co/8Kj055rpPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dyslexia Awareness Week | Dyslexia Scotland https://t.co/IwDQUBVGId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the iPad is a bigger threat to our children than anyone realises https://t.co/3XjgDzt4Ds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand with Fatima and Gary https://t.co/fKz7fIMEGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every bit can help. https://t.co/eedaqStJnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grime news for art in Edinburgh https://t.co/VhIAN9OWBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankfully we have Radio 6  #dancinginyourkitchenonasunday https://t.co/x4Wkbo5x62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldnt agree more! https://t.co/DIgnz0oIks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which one word describes you? https://t.co/vSvIkK7W0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Breast Cancer Awareness Month...There's a personal reason for asking everyone to put this message in... https://t.co/3oDNOFtraA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK GOVT: Reject Amber Rudd's proposal to force companies to reveal foreign staff numbers - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/xopygeV7i6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wrong! https://t.co/0L6mc8N5Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The current perspective being put forward by the British goverment is wrong, so wrong. 
A very talented friend... https://t.co/nTkuKPHvUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would we give to have a leader with soul! https://t.co/QfYjKxSjvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram photo by Women's Rights News • Oct 4, 2016 at 10:47am UTC https://t.co/GfRWkRBRU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial abuse of women a hidden form of family violence, inquiry hears https://t.co/X8gVzzxtW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iceland Writers Retreat Alumni Award: Applications now accepted! - Iceland Writers Retreat https://t.co/VM6gSQZ8rV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear friends. I worked for this great charity for five years and even absailed down the forth rail bridge for... https://t.co/9TuLhqgnse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10,000 Hours: The Silversmith https://t.co/9sqZbF1QXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Keep Your Daughter Away From Toxic Friends https://t.co/hXgeKOkLVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you cant see the STFU go and see these guys they are FANTASTIC! https://t.co/We9U6eyK4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go see...they are great! https://t.co/k404w65SED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a total plonk. Left my red note book on the train. I am hoping good karma and the spirts of the humankind... https://t.co/B5JcvXAGBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Dialect Quiz Will Determine Where You're From In Scotland https://t.co/xqQS3IJ4DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article in the hearald #craftscotland promoting scottish contemporary craft https://t.co/Mm78ZJmr7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity! https://t.co/bCJGULI6yG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be amazing! https://t.co/mtWJahWlyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female Artists Give Advice to Women in Art World https://t.co/jEngvpR5gW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good night will be had with great music! https://t.co/SRa7KS6th5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering, where is Steven Hood?..... well he is teaching painting in France. Which is a fantastic course!... https://t.co/aSEMJtQfqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very exciting opportunity! https://t.co/oJTKgWXWFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me want to head north.what abt you https://t.co/au18cx5T0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great film supporting Leiths creativity@LottoGoodCauses @ootbdrillhall #CreativityMatters https://t.co/e1bhnI06RQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great projects supporting creative change @LottoGoodCauses @TNLUK @CreativeScots  @HLFScotland  @_hinterland_ @ootbdrillhall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Years of my life stolen because of abuse” Woman speaks of abuse hell https://t.co/V56txTOlWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its good to listen and important to share your thoughts... https://t.co/tBsZiTJdnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New and exciting comtemporay design business supporting the leading designers. Goodluck #craftdesignhouse https://t.co/JRiuSLfCx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoHoltan @CreativeEdin @Edinburgh_CM @TribePorty try the local high schools art department. I've used them and they helped out with easels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung literally put profit over workers' lives https://t.co/eSWcigAuAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save lothian buses https://t.co/ZXfaXKdhUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What It Really Takes to Be an Artist: MacArthur Genius Teresita Fernández’s Magnificent Commencement Address https://t.co/nrgoX0Wf2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want To Remember Something? Easy, Just Draw It https://t.co/yHNmpAJ2KX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long now till Tales from the Hanging Captain opens...have you got your tickets? https://t.co/RvhFxMK5Ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheffield Hallum University  made it into the top ten design degree show to go and see. Its well worth the visit.... https://t.co/kMigcTLyYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear! https://t.co/tvIBBIOLtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Twenty Years of Kath Libbert Jewellery Gallery at Salts Mill https://t.co/X7bWARWvVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in a million years did I ever think I would make it to 5!!!! Its been an amazing journey. So come and join... https://t.co/vnBVGfQQUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people meditate I love just sitting in my garden watching the bees and all the colours grow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU vote registration deadline extended - BBC News https://t.co/Qph6oXIF1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very exciting new multiarts project about people of leith docks opens 16th June tixs from #outoftheblue... https://t.co/5B5AHckANu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The National Gallery is erasing women from the history of art https://t.co/pNeYsOazh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RSA BARNS-GRAHAM TRAVEL AWARD | The Royal Scottish Academy, Edinburgh, Scotland https://t.co/dPzAilxpgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lecturer in Contemporary Art and Curation at University of Glasgow https://t.co/qDiYz1p54o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the SilverHub Studios Summer school. You can do stonesetting, fold forming enamelling and beginer... https://t.co/5Q0AdnVHqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama on the arts - 25 May 2016 https://t.co/otiaXnuZol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely article from #makeworks about the studios in Leith and my 2nd home #SilverHubStudios #Iloveleith... https://t.co/tlxtZijUtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't believe what the remains of Glasgow School of Art fire look like now https://t.co/ZatKQ5GhZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local Jewellery needs your support https://t.co/2qFMi1LTP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming soon: Tales From The Hanging Captain https://t.co/qeGKwODCF3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>