<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassos I think I'll just try ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ no harm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day I go through Finglas and at the exact same spot my phone wifi goes ðŸ‘ŽðŸ»ðŸ‘ŽðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJOE_GAA @SportsJOEdotie ok, how much of the attendance's in this article are down to the Dubs following. Take them out and see diff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeneNaoupu any time, just glad you're with us not against us :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly ha ha we'll just get another sugar daddy like AIG ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ he's scored goals against us but never robbed our Leinster title]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly he'll always haunt you Louth men ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ at least your football team can give you some success ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ŠðŸ™ŠðŸŽ£ðŸŽ£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly can you remind me what the qualifiers are ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ 30 competitive wins in a row ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‰ #March2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly they get out in huge numbers remember last time we played up there when in division 2 wasn't a 10th of the crowd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly never managed to get up today unfortunately so I'll have to ask about that ðŸ¤” The dubs love to travel and when it's so close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreddiemurphy his craftsmanship is on a complete other level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda on #roomtoimprove is a serious craftsman. His wooden stairs wow. The finished house is just mesmerising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly it's absolute madness, Gilroys vision was for all and as Brolly players are no longer club players which is suffering major]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaoimhinReilly as much as Brolly has me blocked here this is a serious article, can never understand how a teacher got the job over Gilroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheriff_YC @THEJSP_INFO @VillaFC1953 excellent, great teams know how to overcome adversity and today you showed why your a great team ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEJSP_INFO @Sheriff_YC @VillaFC1953 how many did mr Murphy save]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheriff_YC has Murphy come on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEJSP_INFO lee Murphy on the bench??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @SophPerry on the scoresheet on her Brighton return]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheriff_YC interesting, pity tv ain't there today as we'd see why. Huge 30 minutes ahead:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to start fining players every time they are sent off!! https://t.co/Kum6O0YhCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialBHAFC may as well start planning there summer holidays because there season will be dead and buried in next few weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mike Dean show again!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j3cK_b Andre Ward would eat him for breakfast ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@africanlion76 @Laceupboxing @davidcoldwell I 200% agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke11campbell it far to say that after your loss to Mende you rectified your errors and worked harder. He seems to not have learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModerndayLister @Laceupboxing @davidcoldwell you would have for sure. 19 st9 is way to heavy he should be no more than 17st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModerndayLister @Laceupboxing @davidcoldwell the same place it was when he first lost to Thompson,  nonexistent.. way to heavy for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laceupboxing @davidcoldwell for me Dave given him the right advice but he never listened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to feel for @davidcoldwell he's given Price some great advice and he just ignored every bit of it. Why take breather on the ropes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Price is a poor mans Audley Harrison, at least @audleyharrison made some decent money from boxing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irishkieran Kelly is very very impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irishkieran I seen that, sometimes it's annoying how much they look down on league here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irishkieran yeah, it reminds you so much about trap were it was all about not losing. Some talents baller players at underage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irishkieran no idea, think they need a change of direction as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to John Delaney the new @FAIreland WNT manager should be announced in the next week, he says it's a "big and exciting appointment"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanKelly_ ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I thought so..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanKelly_ is this you with the orders ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/qGt3R9mbby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a line from @paddyjackson10, @ConorMurray_9 put the ball on a plate and be picked some line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henderson off and O'brien into second row would be a good move, game made for van der fler an out and out 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intensity of the Scottish team is unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the F is there such a huge gap between Best and Furlong, to make things worse furlong didn't even know what was happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonanTheGreek be interesting to hear the clubs side of the story, all can say is it's great that Wexford hasn't lost LOI football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonanTheGreek by the sounds of it it's been a manic past while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smallie_13 it's shocking, they are normally available on world rugby site. Don't see why can't now. Good to see rte showing women earlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smallie_13  one the annoying things is sky are shown the men's tournament right now :( oh btw good luck against UCD tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRugby @WomRugbyComp any streams?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland really got out of jail there without Larissa Muldoon, Niamh Briggs and Sophie spence they are a shadow of themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wondering how we managed to get @SeneNaoupu, talk about a gifted ball player one of the best 12s in world rugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen @WaterfordFCie's Director of Football Pat Fenton heading into Dublin Airport in his Waterford gear, new arrival??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is going to be scary as a pro https://t.co/PhmihxBZcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaAWheatley @NathanKelly_ ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ of course he would he'd have the vines and all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know who's worse for the #FirstDatesIRL running commentary @EmmaAWheatley or @NathanKelly_ ðŸ˜‚.. biggest question is Nathan when you up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this tweet got me blocked by @spenceeoliver ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ what an absolute premadonna ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ https://t.co/csIrB0l1zV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@league_ireland we can only hope they get back on there feet if they ain't because can't afford to lose a club like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJWOODFORD1988 I've blocked so many of them. You can never trust them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@league_ireland @AthloneTownAFC that's it, was getting worried but if stories of new investment are true be brilliant. Such an iconic club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@league_ireland @AthloneTownAFC great to see them signing players, we haven't heard much from them at all lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can people follow somebody with a fake name and no profile picture??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how to be a fan orientated club ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/26dZxx3qFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KPD_1895 it's not good to be honest something needs to be done and soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an interview, Andre is very honest such an intelligent guy. https://t.co/MUk5HPg5gQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irishkieran absolutely not, Friday be back to the way they used to be :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry up 24th, League of Ireland is only a number of weeks away now it's been way to long a break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryONeill_4 it will all peter out very soon lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very good interview with @klbardsley, it was a huge risk moving to City but she's Noe getting her just rewards  https://t.co/Yfn3XAeKuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blink and you'll miss it lovely free-kick from Luiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerardGrimes11 @Ballinamallard @DroghedaUnited ten euro into that friendly ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBoxinNews @Irishboxingcom let's be honest that's an easy night for Warrington and a step back from pajo fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted for @stfintansrugby and @akaforbsey such a cruel way to lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 300 people have watched the video of @UCDLadiesHockey -v- @MonkstownHockey Strokes https://t.co/yUJMBbPXzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirSport people chose wisely now let's hope Fintan's can get over the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirSport sounds like you made the right choice of games to show :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMacByrne They can be a gift sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirSport @clongowes @bankofireland what's left ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boscoisalive ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ enjoy the game, hope your well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the big premier league clubs given an away draw in fifth round. Plum tie for Sutton United https://t.co/IFWT1EZIl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinSmith3 bohs play in malahide united tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duntz_3 ah that makes it so much easier, the very best of luck with them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duntz_3 that helps a huge amount some colleges ain't as fortunate as youse. Mustn't be long till inter varsities? Where are they this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duntz_3 but by march college should be just over the fact they'd gotten rid of midweek games should help colleges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duntz_3 be very interesting alright, hoping the new summer season works would have liked an extra round of games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryomahony4 he's been boasting about it on instagram]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit surprised to see Noel Kealy leaving @KilkennyWFC  for @ucdwaves but it's to big an opportunity to turn down was building nicely with KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoftballIreland @IrishTimesSport he cannot get the top job otherwise we may as well bring Hickey back because things won't improve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The42_ie nothing less than a stoppage good enough for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen a tweet saying it was level after 10 holy shit am I missing something ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame mcguigan's lack of experience in huge fights tonight is showing, he should have read him the riot act. He needs a ko to keep belt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dubsoulrebel Haye is a gym mate so his opinion is always going to be biased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton ain't winning this fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpencerOliver talking some absolute pony on sky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skyedrobinson any idea times for main/co main event tonight??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgusting @EndaKennyTD should be ashamed if he lets this slide https://t.co/rPjTTkITLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciara_hanson ah me not to bad :) Hope you're well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciara_hanson ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ hope you're enjoying Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciara_hanson because you're turning into an alco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vinnyc86 can't wait serious night ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full @UCDLadiesHockey v @MonkstownHockey Strokes from today's @irishhockey Senior Cup QF @sportswomenIRL @hookhockey https://t.co/VKdn8JV27g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game of hockey @deirdre_duke marks her @UCDLadiesHockey return with a superb finish 3-3 now what a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-2 Katie Mullen with her second of the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game on UCD pull one back after 25 minutes from Katie Mullen with UCD goal after goals from oflanagan and Evans had given a Hermes 2-0 lead]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>