<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllenFrancesMD @scATX This seems appropriate 
https://t.co/Hf7N40Meht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio turnabout is fair play is it not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo If one of my tweets gets picked do I get to add that to my resume?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClickHole @onlxn @SpeakerRyan Can't sell what you never possessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The OTC doesn't always work https://t.co/L1SPZcJ4t3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @danmoran3 @redletterdave So you're the next Chamberlain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mohobishopi @iskandrah @charltonbrooker @realDonaldTrump Not every one https://t.co/JPvZAPeQDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tried to renew my membership, it can wait https://t.co/znGCgvfyu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanSarandon So tell us again how @realDonaldTrump was gonna be better than @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Lewis_ @jbouie @politicususa Wow, never thought I'd say this, #GoBlue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaraJeffery @CNNMoney Don't patronize companies looking to screw you, your friends, country - that really cuts down on my spending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trump_democrat @BCAppelbaum @mims Trump should try that himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin Words mean nothing unless backed up with actions. What are you &amp; @tammyduckworth going to do? You're my Sens. Do something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC @BoingBoing You're surprised? This is this the same @GOP that takes food from the mouths of poor school children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradheath holy cow there are 6 more Orlandoes in Fl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill first time, sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill You forget, he can't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tammyduckworth good practice for dealing with @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill It was illegal when Bush authorized it. @realDonaldTrump doesn't give a damn what a nobody like @SenJohnThune says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaraJeffery how much of that will end up in Trump's pocket?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@consumerist So this is the GOP plan to replace ACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of pseudo profound bullshit
https://t.co/StWQA91c0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Price went to bat last summer for the makers of a commercially unsuccessful heart failure drug
https://t.co/78o0PIUjkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Do Political Figures Lie So Blatantly?
https://t.co/H8Rh7a3ZLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump a bullshit philosophers gold mine
https://t.co/qgqWoh0iOa https://t.co/SJxCkzhFDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling Bullshit
https://t.co/pvZyTMcUcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMegerian Here's an idea, take away the remote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd Spicer: he's so popular he surpassed 100 and came back around to 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd They say there's no where to go but up, but with @realDonaldTrump all bets are off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SchoolChoiceNow Am Fed for Children - does that mean you aim to turn them into food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pookleblinky The person who drafted this has no heart, but I'm sure he proudly calls himself a Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drzax @Asher_Wolf Shouldn't they should call it the facial?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodStinks @ElMonte08 Everyone in administration is forced to buy Trump off the rack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtrench @joanwalsh Shouldn't the be PeeStreet Band?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill His or ours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veronicamarche @HiddenFigures Wow, beautiful - painting &amp; movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaulfieldTim @wordbirdbinder @AlanLevinovitz @YoniFreedhoff You can have carb free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecularStudents &amp; we get to tax churches &amp; all their property]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoniBloomfield @adamfeuerstein Every other pharma CEO - noob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessetarbert @Lollardfish @pashulman He lost money while working for Fed Gov. Clearly not doing it right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Hard working doesn't include you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalstonReports One thing we know for sure - @SenDeanHeller won't be losing his insurance, ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Maybe this would help https://t.co/FhNEkmU0XL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonMaloy They take food out of the mouths of children. They don't give a damn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanMcElwee @AdamWeinstein Natural disaster. Euphemism for governance by GOP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtaibbi Haven't been blessed with many @ChicagoBears games, huh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xpostfactoid @DanaHoule When @SpeakerRyan &amp; the GOP are done, that monopoly will be eliminated. No choices, no monopoly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Sat morning ads from lawyers urging toddlers to sue parents far off?
https://t.co/I4Fz5KBrpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which one of my garish charts is transformed into a cool-looking NY Times graphic
https://t.co/OprVSHUCij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crazyyhorse69 @thehill Sucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@democracynow They're not entitlements.  They've been earned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Jeff Sessions! https://t.co/nND1XHsk0t #StopSessions @moveon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You and OJ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paleofuture @ClaraJeffery So basically this https://t.co/Cum4p6VMLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT What year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head leech in the swamp https://t.co/KP5EcKIHof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTtheIslander @PenofUmar Look at the picture. It's pretty obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ass_deans @HarvardBiz Unless they suffer from the Dunning-Kruger effect, like mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the o/u on minutes after the game for Fox being fired? @ChicagoBears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakedansavage @MSignorile Yeah, book deals, USAG, POTUS. Being a white supremacist's a bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual, "reform" means fewer benefits
https://t.co/y787wXf0ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalstonReports Of course they have to start the @realDonaldTrump administration sooner too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Says the privileged whited guy who eats for a living. Nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill For withholding info? How about for being a neo-confederate, flaming, racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twenty Percent of New Cancer Treatments Do Not Offer a Clinical Benefit
https://t.co/dy76NBuiDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfruh Plus, Holsteins are dairy cows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LOLGOP Orange, fat, and stupid is no way to go through life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehil Wasn't this basically the allied response after WWI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ragingpencils His first trip to Dallas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb And people said watching pro wrestling was a waste of time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias WMD was pretty bald faced and he sent Colin Powell to lie to the world. So far, no one's died bc Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @realDonaldTrump Lying sack of shit https://t.co/yfpGT5MkpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. spends more on health care than any other country. Here’s what we’re buying.
https://t.co/o3Rr9ktvBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenTDennis @LOLGOP you mean it hasn't already? Shit, now I gotta drag my sorry ass outta bed and into work. #ThanksTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper 8-Track that split the best song on the album in half, cars without FM radios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill There isn't a Republican in this country that's got the brains or guts. Please, teabaggers make 'em poop their pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT: Proposed law would charge protesters with terrorism. Sign our petition to stop it: https://t.co/FuaET0uTWQ https://t.co/SjTPVWOLwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott Health camps and surveys: marketing an unproved, unapproved drug in India

https://t.co/rRPueCVE0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @MHSMiriam She'll be getting lot's of brains &amp; teeth too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfruh in Trumpland, she's the black sheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubenBolling So not only does "It's A Wonderful Life" star a RWNJ, it's directed by a fascist sympathizer. Gotta p… https://t.co/wKgiPGEdFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee Isn't your god in charge of the weather, you know Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIG story about why customers and workers both need #JusticeAtTMobile - pls RT + read: https://t.co/0uC9zKqBtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs How many days into the Trump admin will the Russians be able to disable all US military hardware?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb Understanding doesn't matter. Tweeting for effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @EJDionne So who do you think discovered it? The Keebler elf? Carson? The Amway queen, or one of the kids? Barron, that's it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what you can expect when you @visitidaho 
https://t.co/Z2sZ6xxSSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @qz That's how you deal with fake news. Of course, they've been through this before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this survey, pharmacists, physicians, nurses, voted 2:1 for Clinton https://t.co/PybTG9Lo7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham neither is a good choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Another tone deaf white guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSNBigTen Did he steal those glasses from an old lady or Woody Hayes? https://t.co/I7KiSc3Owo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @nytimes He violated common sense and the people of Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lmoliva_ Wonder what the response would be for other POC &amp; how it breaks down on soc econ status]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter homeopathy, fish oil/flax seed oil/krill oil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judahariel @NoahShachtman @ArmsControlWonk As I remember, even Bobby Hill aced that class https://t.co/8eqXaKjYWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alabamafication @mmfa Press secretary. Is that what we're calling fluffers now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kesayers @mmfa Tubes, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmfa Good luck Alex, you'll have to scrub this too https://t.co/jt92J0k2fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willmenaker I wonder what the waitress did with the bread sticks before serving that made them so tasty]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>