<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJoshuaTepper thank you for another inspiring talk @ideasontario #IDEASCohort10 the best leaders are generous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations IDEAS grads @ESCLHIN #IDEASCohort10 https://t.co/sVymuJxO35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations IDEAS grads!@WW_LHIN https://t.co/M7cScwp5Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasontario @NorthEastLHIN  great work and congratulations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasontario @AcclaimHealth great impactful project. Congratulations team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improving palliative care in Sault Ste Marie. Wonderful work not a surprise! @SAH_iCcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasontario @HealthLink_SGB congrats on great work team :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasontario @LauGuerreroGTA @Syan_ide great job team! Congratulations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian war: Red Cross doctor's heart-breaking letter from Aleppo https://t.co/uu9ts0dI2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Michelle Obama 'ape in heels' post causes outrage https://t.co/VYOETmCEXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outcry Over Oregon Standoff Verdict: White Militants Acquitted While Native Protestors Maced, Beaten https://t.co/AMmNgop6xx via @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hounded for giving birth outside the system https://t.co/kcyuTJNKyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inhuman and inhumane BBC News - Syria conflict: Aleppo a slaughterhouse, UN rights chief says https://t.co/8OK9T2lNsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cathedral or bazaar model of Improvement? Or like garage sale - reusing other people's work? #HQT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The hyper connected make change happen' but need to bring everyone on the journey #HQT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Votes on who will make change happen?? Positive deviants!! #HQT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to t/ maker movement- Global Renaissance in people doing it for themselves -engaging everyone on frontline #HQT2016 #WeAreNotWaiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paradigm and culture shift required to harness diversity in thinking #HQT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenbevan getting the conversation started at#HQT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends reunited! IDEAS alumni thankful to see their HQO advisor again #ideasontario #ideascohort8 #QIPSF2016… https://t.co/XeqQIjqNsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving people more data/info doesn't make people smarter #humanfactors @ideasontario]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's groping boasts inspire millions of women to share sexual assault stories on Twitter https://t.co/wvw5mb7BrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Meet the seven-year-old girl tweeting from Aleppo https://t.co/fB2CJjGeww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Ten times Trump shamed others on tax https://t.co/KnDUjakxGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free exchange: Down to earth https://t.co/q1VBTNlMsC via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linda turned up at A&amp;E twice a day. A dedicated team now stops that https://t.co/LfdnkCod6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting to be at the birth of a movement in improvement - thoughts into actions, from statements to strategy thx#Bridge2QI @RC_ICRE_CIFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PtSafetyExpert take a look at resilient systems and the notion that systems can absorb change  go beyond reliability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change the system, care then education to truly effect improvement in healthcare #Bridge2QI @RC_ICRE_CIFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QI and patient safety remain an 'orphan topic' in physician training. Well said @Brian_M_Wong @RC_ICRE_CIFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s gaffe that no one will forget: Boasting he pays no income tax /via @globeandmail https://t.co/2IcXDP63gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Colin Powell calls Trump 'national disgrace' in email leak https://t.co/3Z5uJ3OoxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMF chief launches thinly veiled attack on Donald Trump https://t.co/AmC6xgmMUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit camp abandons £350m-a-week NHS funding pledge https://t.co/7Xeamm2xj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which 3 Canadian cities were named amongst the 5 most liveable in the world? Spoiler -Vancouver, Toronto, Calgary https://t.co/5O1VjTVwai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imam protests burqini ban by posting image of nuns at the beach in full habits https://t.co/9KZ9yR5Xm0 via @WomenintheWorld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must do better! I Felt Alone But I Wasn't: Depression Is Rampant Among Doctors In Training https://t.co/lTE8d0dfyT via @commonhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Canada's Mounties allow women in uniform to wear hijabs https://t.co/17Y8bvWEFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Syria conflict: Image of injured boy in Aleppo draws outrage https://t.co/euQpj99qIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Rio 2016: Bolt and De Grasse grins spark bromance delight https://t.co/GlJLkmRDDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOlympics  please #SynchronisedSwimming less commentary!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOlympics  less is more in synchro commentary!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump insists 'Obama is founder of IS' https://t.co/CYnFXXqkUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can mental health services learn from the automotive industry? https://t.co/2RjU2c9eKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three-Term GOP Rep.: I Will Vote Hillary https://t.co/KVvDv6Hdjt via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world saw a grieving mother. Donald Trump saw a Muslim | Amana Fontanella-Khan https://t.co/wf3bNrcTla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Online 'university of anywhere' opens to refugees https://t.co/XcSwUWeEVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - David Brown: Dallas police chief with past marked by tragedy https://t.co/Uysu5CfKPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Einstein, "You can't solve the problems created by current pattern of thought using current pattern of thought." Just think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words. Barbaric and inhuman. Women held captive by ISIS used as 'human shields' and sold on apps https://t.co/rwpJOU09wA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Top 37 Things You Will Regret When You Are Old https://t.co/p7n5VU7yUl via @TruthofToday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Queens of Syria gives modern twist to ancient tale https://t.co/Kbj4Neqbto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important factual assessment of consequences of Brexit  https://t.co/jr4Wfsm4aT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day Compulsory viewing if you haven't seen My Cousin from Andrew Soar https://t.co/e3Bxdl4XwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful ignorance of Farage in EU parliament speech  - EU health commissioner explains his 'Farage facepalm' https://t.co/XyZnqJulPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What It Means When You Spot Someone Wearing A Safety Pin In The UK  https://t.co/ku3JMErHV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Martin curates Lawren Harris exhibit at the AGO https://t.co/YjcYoFEOVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bristol resident challenges racism by offering roses to immigrants after EU referendum https://t.co/DJdflmlRxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aziz Ansari Pens Scathing Op-Ed Denouncing Trump’s Anti-Muslim Hate Speech https://t.co/sEGgMPQMke via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality improvement much more than LEAN/6 Sigma!!! See https://t.co/AzBCVDEPBC &amp; https://t.co/jDmogIKO9h #ILI16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to disagree agreeably https://t.co/hYEsrGPXsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask stakeholders 4 input 2 understand their perspective = engagement, implementation success @DrPeterSelby #ILI16 https://t.co/xli66pFEUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deal w/ resistance in implementation-use adaptive leadership see it here - https://t.co/W3HMfZTrt5? v=QfLLDvn0pI8&amp;sns=tw via @youtube #ili16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is this possible? https://t.co/ejkZuOSsZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skate smoothly to successful implementation step 1: learn about implementation thx @melaniebarwick #ili16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reduce resistance to change with a robust needs assessment @allisonjmetz #ili16 https://t.co/eZDdB25NgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let the learning begin Implementation Learning Institute CAMHPSSP #ILI16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u have more than u need build a longer table not a higher fence https://t.co/QT6FiWVaUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 MP Jo Cox -  Pianist plays Imagine by John Lennon in Birstall https://t.co/IEI0lFnC8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdered MP Jo Cox' message to those fearful of refugees https://t.co/teXH9flDip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The migrant policy helps no one! Europe migrant crisis: Charity rejects EU funds over migration policy https://t.co/HoRVLV3ZdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The best inheritance a parent can give to his children is a few minutes of their time each day” – Orlando Aloysius Battist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched driver from Fresh jump out to give homeless guy fresh fruit salad!#kindness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tear-jerking open letter Joe Biden wrote to the Stanford rape survivor. https://t.co/DolbTYYM1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the world freaked out over a gorilla this week, 1,000 people drowned in the Med https://t.co/kmV6WdQPwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 'total lie': Trump University ex-staffers condemn school as 'fraudulent scheme' https://t.co/oLywc9IyQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump University a 'fraud from top to bottom': N.Y. top prosecutor https://t.co/SocG4kLUxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump said these Syrian refugees might be ISIS members. Here's the real story. https://t.co/lYefOIh8xk via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks@SteiniBrown healthcare in Ontario relentlessly pursuing improvement at natl forum on simulation#SIMone https://t.co/CLRDCf7Kum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5:2 author Michael Mosley: 'I'm proof low-fat diets don't work' | via @telegraph https://t.co/vEZbASozbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic mushrooms lift severe depression in clinical trial https://t.co/i05GyNl5Qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Award winners! Lovely to be recognized in this way. https://t.co/xyvMDBiwqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudis use armoured vehicles to suppress internal dissent, videos show https://t.co/JCBw94z1l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GPs are leading the way on NHS transformation https://t.co/oXZAM2ZQS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving and insightful - Providing Better Care for First Nations in BC - Evan Adams at Health Talks https://t.co/gQUmtMQstj via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimprovision closing reflections once the training is over @ideasontario mindful improvements and keeping us zen https://t.co/APzsDHNnwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day here at @ideasontario 9th Graduation day. Congrats to our new graduates #ideascohort9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utah will require use of anesthesia for abortions after 20 weeks https://t.co/bimBWyb18F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Fisk: Why is David Cameron silent on the recapture of Palmyra? https://t.co/3zyf25tejQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Kindness Became Our Forbidden Pleasure https://t.co/8gGxbXFAtX via @brainpicker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How People Learn to Become Resilient https://t.co/89ubekDhxB via @mkonnikova]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidnapped by Isis at 15: 'I never thought I'd see the day when I was free' https://t.co/HkW9F30KwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humans of New York’s Open Letter to Donald Trump Is Going Viral https://t.co/hL2sTYJfLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great summary re coping with anxiety when public speaking. https://t.co/fR2JadbJ5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ugly truth about body dysmorphia https://t.co/MWGBLhZipV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring thoughtful closing remarks #ideascohort8 graduation @ideasontario from @DrJoshuaTepper thank you! https://t.co/uSsVgkK2Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful- Why this man walked 1,000 kilometres of icy roads, dragging an oxygen tank /via @globeandmail https://t.co/vdRlbVLYSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great simplification of transformation concept by @tnvora thx @helenbevan  https://t.co/WcummfbrpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great tips on managing self doubt. https://t.co/c5Ohu7jq0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @Microsoft is betting on a radical new type of design thinking: https://t.co/fNGpd4XG2R by @CliffKuang via @FastCoDesign /]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>