<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ballysbest if there's one man who could rock a bra on his hips, it's you Paudo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people use the term 'straw man' in a discussion, this is your cue to pop them into a canon and fire them off into oblivion forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneWoodfull I can never keep it up. Had all nighter last night. Came home at 3pm, napped until 6, and a 12 hour day tomorrow. *Stress*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindyMean they may well have no other choice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvilPhil certainly some sort of mythical creature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women, Teresa? Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanreidsays you'd be surprised how often this has happened. I love the idea of you sitting in stunned silence for the rest of the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want a women who's pregnant but also a size 6.
Say it with me: GET FUUUUUUUCKKKKKED https://t.co/XfyDtNfUeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpoolandThimble this has winded me from laughing, and I don't know why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me as I celebrate escaping a group project - a fate worse than death. Sure it means a presentation and 5k essay, BUT ON MY OWN 🎉🎉🎉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan pretty pleased with myself. Even he'd have to give that kudos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan aka the Neil Prendeville story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan not my sharpest moment. But still, you *could* make this happen, right? https://t.co/xsWzoblbTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan no no, back to the dolphins. How what when why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan sorry what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I rule the world, I'm going to put bras in place of pockets on men's clothes, and see how they like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhySharksMatter I might need to petition to get these to Ireland. So wrong, yet so right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee Hmm. That might have swung it for me, I admire your willpower. TEACH ME YOUR WAYS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan I swore off it forever once a guy recognised me in work, because the crippling disappointment wasn't reason enough apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee ...did he think you were five years old? So bad!

 (how much did you consider it, because I would, like A LOT)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee See, really, I am holding out for my own show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan yes! This tweet sums up my feeling on it exactly. https://t.co/dLOtvDWSwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan what, my poster? I imagine that will bring you much success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan I'm using this as a quote on my poster for future gigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan as should you :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan I only realised today I accidentally had a dry January, and I intend on making up for this ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm hungry, what can I eat?"
*sees unopened bag of apples*
"Nah, I'm grand actually."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan I think I meant 'drunk'... it's not always a negative though, in fairness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI @Rob0Sullivan I just rely on my teenage sister to educate me through a series of eye rolls and laughs. Harsh training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan so we both make bad choices? Excellent :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan @CiaraMPSI I Urban Dictionary-ed it, but I wasn't gonna admit to that because I just want you guys to think I'm cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrStackpoole she was actually deadly and had great taste in dresses and deserves someone ridey. Maybe I am projecting, I dunno.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrStackpoole not so much for her, but more for the inevitable barrage of questions about being a comedian, especially as a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrStackpoole now you mention it, both. But there was a UK comic on First Dates Hotel and it terrifies me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI @Rob0Sullivan I have never heard this phrase before, and now I have, will attempt to use it as much as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan Ha! Who's been spreading rumours? The cool kids all have longboards now, FYI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee that night ended on a HANDSHAKE. 4) Got stranded at Bull Island at 3am. Thought he could 'fool' me into going dogging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee 3) asked what gays bars are like, and said because I am bi, I could take him to one. I did, because I am a fool for pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee online dating?" I tell him to keep quiet. At the interval, he screams at me. "is it you're ashamed of me? YOU SLAG." etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee I waited until he finished his chicken roll that it was Good Friday. 2) Met online, went to a comedy show. MC asks "anyone try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee then strap in because I have many, many stories for you. 1) He took me to Centra for coffee. We then sat in the rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan We are massive rides, in fairness. And really, who are we to question the wisdom of a random Twitter app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname @SpellenBee okay, I'm about 85% convinced now 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI absolutely. I've started compiling a mood board for our debut video https://t.co/6n5xEvfss4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI the music will never die, let's bring this show on the road 🎶🎶 https://t.co/0kxvWs3KnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah not enough credit is given to how shitty this feels, I think. You do whatever you've gotta do to get it out of your system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessiblah ah, that's such a lousy feeling, sorry to hear that! Hope you feel much better very soon, the heart-hurts are the worst!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee I'm 60% tempted then remember it's me, it will be a disaster, it will be televised, then I come to my senses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@griffski maybe it's me, it maybe it's the tache. Either way, I'm trying to fix my bad choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI my heart dances for joy. But honestly, you do whatever you have to do to mind yourself, though keep in contact if you'd like to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm not telling you a joke. Yes, I have met X. Heckling is not an interesting subject. Yes, I have a day job. No, don't start comedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching comedians on First Dates gives me heart palpitations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJ5000 @CiaraMPSI cc me in on these plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@griffski I... Not sure how to tell you, but... My vagine feels nothing for him. I AM SORRY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@griffski babes, you know how bad I am at choices. This is like catnip for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI how many tweets of praise and cute dogs do I need to send you daily to keep you here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob0Sullivan sorry about the bad news, rob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Valentine] @sorobotic's Valentine should be @Rob0Sullivan! Who should be yours?
via https://t.co/pIrftBNEtx https://t.co/7H5IQAZmrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today has been a great day, which I partially attribute to the fact I'm wearing shark print socks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegarydoyle excuse me, I've some emails to write and a bakery to call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegarydoyle hypothetically, how much would it cost to hire this guy to egg a house in say... Palmerstown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegarydoyle I want a celebration cake that looks like this man, then share the cake with him. Glorious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname Yes and no. It would be more a Like Letter than love letter, which is an impressive admission for me. Still counts, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname I gasped and said "nonononono" out loud, and yet you're so right. One day, I'll have the guts to do like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aideenblackwood teeth are actually the most inconsiderate pricks. My dental dramas have always been *just* before pay day 😤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname bring back the love letter, I say! You did the right thing. Just hope the wait isn't too painful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still better than the one Valentine's I was in a relationship, where I went to the cinema to cry in the dark at Shaun the Sheep. Good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I signed myself for a 10 hour tourism course on valentine's day, because I'm nothing if not a realist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee 10/10 would subscribe. I will buy all your books. https://t.co/sqfuYFu9zA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname effort - you have tried. More than a lot of people could say. That's proper ballsy, so no matter what the outcome, well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname Once something like this is finally set in motion, it kinda steamrolls. The anxiety is understandable. At least you made an]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee you are the hero we need, but don't deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname I'm rooting for you. I totally get what you mean though, as scary as it is, not knowing can be the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname I'm so invested in this. Fingers crossed for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How badly could you want a free holiday? Fucking hell. https://t.co/KD82nTIRF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee that's life the way it should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealP55 in some ways, a pasta dinner is my porn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've set up a splash zone. Stand back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is craving some intense, harrowing Sunday night entertainment, I'm about to eat an obscene amount of pasta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bernasher @NursepollyRgn you're absolutely right. saw screenshots of it, and it's her usual poison. She causes genuine harm to people imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stayed in work an extra hour off the clock to avoid work at home. Smart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mgtscott oh, stop. I'm roaring at the telly when she's on. How can someone be so woefully devoid of empathy or understanding?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm asking this as a personal favour. If you give a shit about the women in your life, DO NOT CLICK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1980worldchamp yup. I think it's genuinely harmful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAPE IS NEVER THE FAULT OF THE VICTIM. YOU DID NOTHING WRONG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[knowing it's even been published has me on edge and feeling sick. Sexual assault survivors - please know she is wrong and poisonous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please please don't go sharing or clicking on the N*amh H*ran piece. Her trash opinion is so fucking damaging to women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen @ciaragemmam you too, it's good to have a space to say "fuck that shit" and be heard x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaragemmam @darthellen took me 3 years. Even now, if I read her guff on a bad day, it's enough to set me off for weeks of self loathing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen we're our own worst enemies at times of trauma like sexual assault, and she is salt in the fucking wound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen because if I had heard some of this shit in my early 20s I'd have used it as a stick to beat myself with even more than I did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen she's fucking poison. I'm so terrified of young women assimilating her victim blaming trash and severely damaging their MH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoChaela she's fucking poisonous that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incogellen I think I would too tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I Cranky Or Do I Just Need A Cup Of Tea?: An Autobiography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee when Emer called him out on cheating, he was the one that went on a sulky killing spree. Get a fat grip, mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpellenBee hahah! I think I'm doing my next Headstuff lecture on this. So much compelling evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annapickard and I know he's surrounded by sycophants, but how is nobody around him saying "is this a bit much, no?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annapickard just been having this chat. How can he have such absolute power - and so immediate? Esp compared to here and UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI I do feel there's an obligation to keep myself educated and informed, and maybe figure out ways I can actively help]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>