<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can argue with that? https://t.co/mgpf8z9VKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on a funky book trailer for the new novel. Don't know if I can pull it off. Wish me luck in my efforts/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so funny. https://t.co/JTOaD1oZuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoonful Chronicles Book cover art reveal-----&gt; https://t.co/RzHmDJAaWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[book reveal will happen tomorrow at @_diversebooks .... watch for it there. https://t.co/JzVveWXxdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoonful Chronicles Striptease Day 4: Book cover art reveal. https://t.co/oVcKytu5El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoonful Chronicles Striptease Day 3: Book cover art reveal. https://t.co/LmjZnr5KYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperSaetta Dubai is not in Africa  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoonful Chronicles Striptease Day 2: Book cover art reveal. https://t.co/KdKTYLjkED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoonful Chronicles Striptease Day 1: Book cover art reveal. https://t.co/0nY0poVtHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 70+ ebooks 100% Free!
Download ALL of them now! https://t.co/vxZ3dnJlXq

#freebooks #booksgiveaways #amreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reminds me of The Harlem Shake .... just a little https://t.co/ZBWrGlbUWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NJoseph4 It was filmed in a church under construction. The total effect is stunning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[breath taking https://t.co/lg16v5EuEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How awesome is that? https://t.co/tUoUllOqMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[started watching Juana Ines on Netflix, enjoying it so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyHumorIn4Words
Highbrow unibrow
Damsely fierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Fridge! https://t.co/SkZFsYnu4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FoodVillains  Tomato Menace https://t.co/xHxno8Nbyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warriorofstorm yay! You got it. So happy. nice carpet by the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nancyfreund Yay! that is cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nancyfreund really enjoying it so far. Where would I find your youTube book review video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reading Today Will Be Different by @_MariaSemple https://t.co/uMUZFUWqiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisachristCBC I am curios how they developed the alien language for the movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to see Lion last night. Make sure to stock up on kleenex if you are planning to see that movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyFirstWordsAsPresident  Free dolma for everybody. https://t.co/2wag4VlH6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 2 minute video worth watching https://t.co/qxq7a8MSrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol It feels better than getting a new dress 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol exactly! You probably know what that feels like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElenGhulam Hoping book is better than movie. Continuing with the literary foodie adventure with The Hundred-Foot J… https://t.co/YLwfADiQrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current Status: Pregnant with a novel. https://t.co/9yKNWESAMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Receiving a book cover design is a like an ultrasound when pregnant. "Wow! there really is a baby" "Wow! there really is going to be a novel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperSaetta That is terrible. Please be careful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_CVB Will do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a break from my literary foodie adventure to read this. https://t.co/9N8ET4jcgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NGSPITZNAGLE thank you for the RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This icified snow must go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if The OA staring @britmarling was a prequel to The Walking Dead 
https://t.co/uclTOiEsAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildkatCook  thank you for the RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Video: if The OA was a prequel to The Walking Dead https://t.co/uclTOiEsAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New video coming out tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HolidayGoer @LisachristCBC I would still eat that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing writer enters kitchen to inspire
#DescribeYourselfin5words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[been watching Oliver Stone's Untold History of the United States on netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[160+ free ebooks. Discover a new favorite author. https://t.co/HnwKRiXY9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all prolific readers. 160+ ebooks on offer https://t.co/Y70E3nYW5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyGeller @Elif_Safak @VikingBooksUK looking forwards to reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 135 #free #SciFi and #Fantasy #books from #Instafreebie authors: https://t.co/d1VHNVY1nL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on a new video. Starting 2017 with a bit of silliness. going to be a Story Mashup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomzillaNC Each time somebody gets my book, I feel: Yay! somebody will read what I have written. At the same time: Oh No! What have I done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret life of trees. https://t.co/Arn7ctmQyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElenGhulam Next stop on my literary foodie adventure is The Restuarant Critic's Wife by Elizebeth LaBan https://t.co/qabVto7WqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another zinger. Wow! https://t.co/dtBYMi7obn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Yes! Yes! 
Raise you hand and yell Ay! if you can relate to this page from the novel as much as I do. https://t.co/V44SAnD4yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trippmadam That is so cool. Thank you for telling me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next on my reading menu is The Dinner by Herman Koch https://t.co/SVLO4OK49o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol Thank you! Wishing you a beautiful and fantastic 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year. https://t.co/dDR31JL8dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau Happy new year to you and all of Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jojozawawi That would be so fantastic, to share a meal with you. BTW, thank you for the lovely Christmas card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing New Year's dinner. Hummus is the first thing that gets made. https://t.co/k4ijtOZyRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartbache I really liked it as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win – Turn Your Book into an Audiobook (we’ll cover the costs) https://t.co/ZXglF1R7n0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Books make the best gifts. Thank you @SuperSaetta for this surprise. The Return by @hishamjmatar https://t.co/DfF0A7aKbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelaceylondon Citizenfour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Leia gets to battle the dark side in heaven now. RIP Carrie Fisher.
https://t.co/HhReQgjYwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretEastonEllis next comes POW! by Mo Yan. The story of a boy obsessed with eating meat. https://t.co/m3XIRVU3yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperSaetta I did enjoy it. It is visually stunning. Although I didn't feel attached to the characters. Worth seeing anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KasandraLaChina tell us what you find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darth Vader in the #RogueOne is so awesome. I wish there was more than just 30 seconds of him in the movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KasandraLaChina gonna see it tomorrow. Looking forwards to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever the flamenca, my gift wrapping has polka dots. Happy holidays. May your passions bring you many gifts. https://t.co/fMKTuqbfFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretEastonEllis eerie how many times Donald Trump is mentioned in this novel given the disturbing subject matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElenGhulam not very christmasy of me but I am reading American Psycho by @BretEastonEllis next https://t.co/wLdUGD7C3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know what you want for Christmas! Grab 60 + novels for ONLY $.99 or FREE! This HUGE event ends on Dec 26.  https://t.co/YDmExg3P4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElenGhulam Heartburn by Nora Ephron is in because it is soooooo hilariouse. My review of it here.… https://t.co/cTXH6sXys0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElenGhulam My Year in Meats by Ruth Ozeki is a "maybe" https://t.co/8rY6CQgTFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning a giveaway of novels about food. A literary foodie lover's feast. Reading up on candidates now. Suggestions welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol This is something I hesitated about for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol In my experience people are usually very happy when I give them a copy of my book as a gift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody else watching The OA on Netflix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reading My Year in Meats by @ozekiland https://t.co/o4bIH1uqcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol I know what you mean. I am writing the blurb for a novel I am planning to release next year. Feels like torture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzicarol this is the hardest part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieIngold Whenever the fancy takes me. I don't have a schedule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Christmas burger in red and green. Recipe: https://t.co/4GP1PkfiCK https://t.co/l2NPyR3MYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So here it is. A dinner for 50. https://t.co/MXH4ZBoCDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roasted chicken marinated in pomegranate molasses. https://t.co/F1aoaEgBMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole roasted cauliflower with a side of mushroom gravy https://t.co/kONFVUwjz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roasted eggplant in tomato sauce. https://t.co/VOPmdSF7sW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saffron rice https://t.co/PaqF15EtD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole roasted cauliflower served with mushroom gravy https://t.co/fnKHig1FOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are definitely beginning to sizzle in my kitchen now. https://t.co/YRaLAxshhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I peel boiled eggs, I think about Vin Diesel's head. Eeeew! not an appetizing thought. https://t.co/9xcAu6F6Cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be sad darling eggplant. Your story will have a happy ending eventually. I promise. https://t.co/mbcJ4GgGSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not going to cry.
I am not going to cry.
Ok! I am crying. https://t.co/TBzYD1cKyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trippmadam Thank you! I always feel better once one thing is ready. At least there is one thing to eat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These naked beauties have no idea what to wear tonight. Just wait until they find out what I planned for them. https://t.co/EblLT19GBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The star of tonight has arrived. Hummus is wearing a haute couture dress jeweled with olive oil, parsley and pickle… https://t.co/fge9bUSHCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KasandraLaChina thank you!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>