<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Second straight year that an ITF Cup has potential for #1-vs-#2 battle…and neither plays. In 2016 Djokovic-Murray, in 2017 Serena-Kerber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESPN gets record numbers (since it's been at 3 a.m. EST timeslots) for blockbuster #AusOpen finals: 1,133,000 for men, 953,000 for women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAFez66 @FlyGoalScoredBy that's a *POPULAR* opinion Chem, jeez. Trying to shake shit up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyGoalScoredBy Matt Carle was the best d-man of this decade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know the drill, folks. Your votes shape my next 12+ hours. Get 'em in quick! https://t.co/z3iwnermkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun while it lasted. https://t.co/BQVwE47GUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomVanArsdel it's sure to be a highlight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaMarseille @Renestance @carole_bouchard I can reassure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thengp12 @footfaulttennis @birdy87 yaaaassssss. This deserved much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rungineered it's a hole worth living in for a while!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaMarseille @Renestance @carole_bouchard time for a relisten, clearly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdy87 @footfaulttennis I think this is more in JJ's vocal range... https://t.co/l7BiGJCESg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaMarseille Also did we or did we predict this Federer win? #successcomesback cc @Renestance @carole_bouchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaMarseille ooh! Should I work on it on the plane maybe? Also, will you be watching melfest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@footfaulttennis I CAN PLAY THIS GAME ALLLLLLL DAYYYY https://t.co/eDdzFxYjc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh I'm so ready for Melodifestivalen. Can't think of anything this bleary world needs more. https://t.co/Du1ObTmffj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeevankakasht You clearly like this Federer guy quite a bit, I can tell :) your passion for the topic comes through, which is great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only fitting to leave Melbourne as I so often experience it: sometime between 5-6 a.m.

My sixth #AusOpen was the best yet. To many more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMcCarvel @michaeljbeattie @LeighWalsh87 this is the album cover to the soundtrack of my soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisSBN You watch how you talk about Jeffie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This woman is my everything (via @justinkirkland4) 

See you soon, America. We've got some work to do. https://t.co/fSeCfQwhjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who thinks Rafa looks like Tommy Haas here? Had to double take. https://t.co/hv4pIsgEl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How popular is Federer / tennis here? He filled a whole second stadium! Second victory lap on Margaret Court Arena https://t.co/GPUgwq2VC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reaction from WTA St. Petersburg https://t.co/zfEMIyQy9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We made it, and we're going to be partying like rock stars tonight, I can tell you that." -Roger Federer, ready to get lit af. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A first in my career: main press room at a Slam beyond capacity. Journalists turned away from Federer's post-win press conference. #ausopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From December. Federer knew his stuff. #AusOpen https://t.co/3mrLxnZ0Uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday's ATP top 10:

1. Murray
2. Djokovic
3. Wawrinka
4. Raonic
5. Nishikori
6. Nadal
7. Cilic
8. Thiem
9. Monfils
10. Federer

#ausopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With 18th Slam, Federer into a tie for fifth overall:

Court - 24
Serena - 23
Graf - 22
Wills - 19
Evert - 18
Federer - 18
Navratilova -18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdlamb9 Great to meet you too! Australia is always amazing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match conclusion: #GOAT gets knocked down, #GOAT lands on his feet, #GOAT kicks some ass. Federer wins his 18th Sla… https://t.co/oJ8Nxit9x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Channel 7, Roger Federer says he would have been happy with quarterfinals here. Would've been a "great" result given his absence.#AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first Federer-Nadal Slam final in person. Couldn't have asked for much more. #AusOpen https://t.co/3y9oSu3lO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A COMEBACK FOR THE AGES:

Roger Federer climbs back from down 1-3 in fifth, wins #AusOpen 6-4, 3-6, 6-1, 3-6, 6-3 over Rafael Nadal.

#18.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes a second championship point for Federer, after an ace. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer, eventually, loses his first championship point. Deuce. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer saves two Nadal break points at 5-3 in the fifth. Deuce. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer, from 1-3 down, is serving for the #AusOpen at 5-3 in the fifth. But down 0-30. Deep breaths, all of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT POINT AT 3-4 IN THE FIFTH?!?!?!! holy wow. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #GOAT machine overheated with excitement, sorry. Federer breaks Nadal, holds for 4-3* in the fifth set. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: #GOAT mounting a comeback. #AusOpen https://t.co/GomqzTB61z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4TheTennis the bull GIF scene is just so underserved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: after a stiff start to fifth set, #GOAT is locked into a tight, tight battle. Nadal still ahead *3-2,… https://t.co/x2LrAHZIKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal is being made to work for these holds but he's meeting the challenge. Up 3-1* in the fifth, time running out for Federer. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how quickly Nadal turned defense to offense on that break point. Federer hit great shots; immediately negated by Rafa. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainer back out for Federer on this first changeover of the fifth set after he held for 1-2*, massaging his right thigh. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal challenges Shino, Nadal loses. Not sure I've ever seen her get one wrong. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MASSIVE hold for Nadal there for 2-0* in fifth, fending off a great return game by Federer. Took a bit of air out of crowd, too. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Nadal breaks to open the fifth set. #GOAT in some big trouble now. #AusOpen https://t.co/WamfKlemGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer is struggling with an adductor issue in Melbourne; any treatment off that would have to be pantsless, hence the off-court. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainer comes out for Federer after the fourth set and Roger follows him off the court. Nadal had already left. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see a Nadal match played at a Federer pace. We're going to a fifth set after just 2h37m. Yes, it is possible. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loose, loose errors from Federer in this fourth set. Will need to clean it up considerably in the presumed fifth set. Nadal *5-3. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Nadal up 4-1* in the fourth, looks like we're going the distance. Hope you're hydrated! #AusOpen https://t.co/tkMeC7MqS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Nadal breaks for *3-1 in the fourth set. #GOAT staggered. #AusOpen https://t.co/dvnFXxafwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpt_3 There just aren't that many good bull gifs out there, tbh :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaximHammel I'm really not sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Federer takes the third set, 6-1 over Nadal. Looks like the #GOAT is on his way. #ausopen https://t.co/jA31JYv131]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If good ol' blind man Federer is making those kind of challenges, Rafa, it may just not be your night. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: #GOAT breaks again, for *5-1 in third set. Federer a game from being one set away, having an absolute… https://t.co/Y0i6qDiDbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a proposal in upper deck of Rod Laver Arena, which I've rarely seen in tennis. But if Federer-Nadal isn't romantic, what is? #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: #GOAT off to the races, up 4-1* in third. Still, Federer's record vs Nadal could prove to be a...monk… https://t.co/sJzDuV8ymI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal digs out a long hold for 1-3* in third set. Survived quite a strong patch from Federer there--double break looked imminent. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: #GOAT gaining the upper hand, breaking and holding for 3-0* in the third set (thanks, @gironimo707!) https://t.co/bTCphayaC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: #GOAT survives a wild ride in the opening game of the third set. #ausopen https://t.co/zQoyUwTcij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer making an absolute mess of this first game in the third set. Up 40-0, then spates of bad errors. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NNemeroff Yes! Gosh, imagine the excitement and tension if this third set were do-or-die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second set to Nadal, 6-3. Momentum, though, probably neutral with how well Federer fought back in the second half of it. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer holds for 3-5* and now Nadal will serve to level this #AusOpen final at one set apiece. (After lots of ball bouncing).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FortyDeuceTwits where's britney i miss britney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer holds for 2-4* in the second. Still in quite a hole on the scoreboard in this set, but at least he's regained some momentum.#AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Federer stops his skid, gets one break back for *1-4 in the second set. #AusOpen https://t.co/LzQbEGqltJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal off and running in the second set, up a double break at *4-0. Federer may well be wise to let this set go. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal fends off several break points, holds for 3-0* in the second, with some thanks to a couple mishit forehands by Federer. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match update: Nadal gets his first scare of Federer and his first break, up *2-0 in the second. #AusOpen https://t.co/Uh9ekJM5tG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer saves a first break point; Nadal returning from somewhere near Cairns. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal holds to open the second, 1-0*. #ausopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match summary so far: #GOAT strikes first. #AusOpen https://t.co/ZVImZLkvz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First set to Roger Federer, 6-4 over Nadal. He's never won a Slam final vs Rafa after losing first set, so that was *quite* large. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal gets a hold, and Federer will serve for first set up *5-4 after 31 minutes. Fastest player cancels out slowest player, so far.#AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if you can hear on TV, but there's a heavy techno bass beat pulsing into RLA from somewhere nearby and it is not pleasant. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another love hold for Federer and he's officially feeling it. Up 5-3. Couldn't have asked for a much better stretch here. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal misses a backhand on break point and challenges but goes to his chair before seeing result. Federer up a break, *4-3. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal running around so many backhands that he's getting caught flat footed and Federer pounces. 15-40, two break points. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convincing love hold by Federer for 3-3, then walks slowly to his chair for new racket. If he's feeling that adductor, not showing much yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger Federer hits a backhand approach shot into Rafael Nadal's forehand. I believe the Swiss call that a "death wish." #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer holds at 30 to get on the board, 1-1. Nadal able to show he can make a dent early, and he remembers the patterns that work. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal finding success attacking Federer's backhand. #ausopen https://t.co/1imO0wmVmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal opens with a hold at love. Federer *might* be moving a bit hamperedly? Tough to tell early, but he wasn't super explosive. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal won the toss, elected to serve. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis fans are amazing. These knockoff Mirka sweaters restore some faith in humanity. #AusOpen https://t.co/UUl3SWz9Df]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans! Are you coming to #AusOpen today but didn't plan to/didn't have tickets before Federer and/or Nadal made it? Message me! Let's chat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By definition, an immigrant/refugee coming to the United States seeking safety, freedom and opportunity is the most American person of all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ask myself this question quite a bit, too... #sleepisfortheweak #sleepisfornextweek https://t.co/awn8jmtQdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2h44m after her match ended: "Serena Williams is on her way to the main interview room." Applause rings out in the press room. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportypitkis meant within men's doubles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peers/Kontinen are 10th champs in the last 13 Slams where both guys are first-time Slam winners.

Even WTA is like, whoa, slow down, guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Peers clinches the #AusOpen men's doubles title with a beautiful lob on championship point to win with Kontinen 7-5, 7-5 over Bryans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, should be 0-3 for Kerber vs top-20 outside Singapore, not 0-4 (Kasatkina was #26, misread as #20). Battle for #1 in 2017 will be fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svenja_mastro Sure, but looking at her results it stood out as being an outlier week (granted, very tough) compared to everywhere else.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>