<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Melon very impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah boys, Olivander is dead. Don't do that to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBoyne cheers to Robbie Savage for seconding my notion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stone Waller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Butterfield at there? Standing in the goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know when they announce the telly games for premier league in March please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeopardstownRC @JohnFitzart @WillieMullinsNH hurricane fly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBoyne please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Randall Cobb any time https://t.co/G6OGuhB838]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anto_hayes29 cant even retweet. Poor form young Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevByrneBox @IrishSunSport @TheNotoriousMMA @IrishSunOnline  washed up and looking for a reason to be talked about. Pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to Merrills... This is not a drill!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're are some severely idiotic people in the world, human race what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedangerfield ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­poor rudyðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ and then you tooðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson @myracingtips serious isn't it what, imagine seeing that at Dundalk. NeverðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myracingtips @PhilfiSigurdson makes the Hereford thing look like an accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upset to see the cowboys didn't pull off the comeback. But rooting for steelers in AFC championship by far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys won't make it playing like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karma for that awful hair cut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah wait, I forgot to make him captain(in lieue of costa)! Ah well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twigged that costa was out late last night, switched him with Kane. Despite the 4 point deduction I'll take it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnEnright1995 @MapMyRun that all John? Disappointed ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson @_PennyLane__ @DanieOBrien ahhhh... lovely cans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PennyLane__ @PhilfiSigurdson @DanieOBrien all I read was will we do some dramatic Guinness and head to Guinness for some lovely Guinness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paddy Holohan wearing a Kieran Marty Waters Jersey, made my day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OE310816 exactly! There has to be at some point though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OE310816 "we'd live on the street, only for her" that was my favourite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean McDermott leaving makes me want to cryðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was pony keeping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OCowzer shame that, they've been good opportunity for players over the years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OCowzer does he have a twitter? I'll take a free holiday to Norway ðŸ‡³ðŸ‡´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After one of the most difficult days ever, the 77a is now delayed. Such poetic injusticeðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson thought it would!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanyeCorr good value alright mate, I just mean I usually buy for the promotional extra, but was a raincoat this yearðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanyeCorr nah mate there almost every week but not a season ticket! Not this year anyway, not looking good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanyeCorr haha yeah getting fed up with it. Becoming more of a bruiser with time tooðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanyeCorr bits and bobs pal, with Tallaght city at the minute what about you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanyeCorr if that ever happens I'll never get a game palðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have got to be f'in kidding me https://t.co/e0vIWLAP4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do players leave their cup for African cup of nations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing willing me through Jane was @Brettdier , first his return from Mehigo, and then his return from the hospital. Love that man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PennyLane__ ha ha funny, Betty shouldn't throw stones in the glass house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspecting I have a BO problem, packed bus nobody wants to sit with me.... I'm kind of hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogersdave123 worth the red I'd imagine ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson I did last year bud. 9/1 to beat roversðŸ˜…ðŸ˜… ah no but seriously he's decent always was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson already confirmed pal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogersdave123 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ plead the 5th if that's alright with you mate. Think there was a time fans confused the backside with the frontðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honorary mention to big @rogersdave123 , the maddest man in football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day that was, absolute heroes the lot of them! Even Glen Fitz https://t.co/SpiRtpWCot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina? Gewan the Liam https://t.co/mBoJwCBGP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteRudds that's the attitude man! Forward is forwardðŸ˜‚ no matter how slow we take it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteRudds ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜… some serious scratching done today so! All that overtimeðŸ˜œðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteRudds well for some bud, don't all have a handy number like yourselfðŸ˜œðŸ˜œðŸ˜œðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing worse than not being able to stick a mates missus, holy Jesus of Nazareth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas hi, is the green line running towards town through Balally? There's no real time info on the boards? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson Kempton today mate not sure time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toxic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneOReilly93 ah no, I reckon Keith Andrews taking an underage coaching role makes it all okðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stpatsfc any real signings to go with thisðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson @RacingPost did you see the full race? New one, my tent, yanworth, vvm, hunreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BackPostHeader love a bit of paddy Eccles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching seamus block that broke my heart, Liverpool -1, so close ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's this tripe on @spin1038]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Virtualnsainity sorry to hear bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will I learn to stop backing Portsmouth....top of the see you next Tuesday list anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyOReilly4 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚will have to rethink my strategy after that one! No reforming for us jaquines, the big smoke and all that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyOReilly4 same boss, up the walls trying to get sorted! Bit of a Scrooge me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyOReilly4 that tweet alone has sent your respect sky high mate! All well with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downloaded the @OfficialAslan collection from iTunes! So what if I have every hard copy, Christmas is Aslan seasonðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder not to take things for granted. Luckier than most, not just at Christmas, but at all times https://t.co/2VsiuDZG6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PennyLane__ haha it's a new weight class, they've literally just invented a world title for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone gonna sign for us? Anyone at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day https://t.co/2R9TYeUWPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimplyFinch "Brian, get out there and just make yourself big"... I can see it now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paul_mujayob try watching pats budðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does nobody remember Zenit being 3-0 down to Maccabi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dundalk fans giving up? Give over will ye, footballs a long aul game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBoyne looks like I've done the whole "curse of the commentator" thingy there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stream won't load on phone, praying this bus moves quick enough so I can at least see the second half. Mon Dundalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Syrian forces retake Aleppo, I'm waiting on a tweet from @AlabedBana for confirmation of safety.... really is an awful story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 still hitting them free kicks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 ah yeah that will suit Leon. Be laughing so, graham the 3rd yeah?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 ah sure you'd forgive graham, too much of a baller to hold a grudge! Who'll replace Darren and Conor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 yeah I get you, that's probably all the @anto_hayes29 fellas red cards mind you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 the Kyle of September is no more! How are you's getting on anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 ah stop, all I remember is being petrified that I'd miss! I'd love to go back but would rather play haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 3 at the back, I'd be sure to flourish. If only franner saw my true potential as a marauding wing backðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 ah no motivation across the board. The lads are sound, just keep losing. Back with the saints? Ah no the bench here is warmer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleCounihan9 for now pal, not enjoying it though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wanna get to a Peterborough game, so much on at the minute though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PennyLane__ ah balls. Thanks Peter's not coming home to that muck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Tara's delighted I'm stuck here, all I wanted was to see @declanorourke ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ agh traffic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dying for them to get back to me, be like floyd #prodigalson https://t.co/jxNsFnw8ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many last fence fallers does geraghty need in 2 days? I backed both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the point of having mates not that you can give them a shout when you need them? Hopeless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PlymouthðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Barry Geraghty at there man? Sitting up off the horse jumping the last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pphorseracing @Racing_UK @GetYourTipsOut @PhilfiSigurdson my 3 bankers, now destined to fail!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson the heart of this city they are, and of course, Celtic]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>