<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so excited #BeautyAndTheBeast https://t.co/hFhDrsWbC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just calms me down ðŸ˜Œ https://t.co/sW4afSFTGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taron Egerton seriously needs to bring out an album or something his voice is just too amazing ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horses are such beautiful creatures ðŸ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so excited to see @DannyBMiller on the NTAs ðŸ˜#NTAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Wolf is slowly but surely killing meðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cutest human being ever ðŸ˜ https://t.co/nkem0KpAoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way some people carry on aggravates me ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes Chicago PD so great ðŸ˜» https://t.co/qwC4S09YN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love for Scooby Doo will never go ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can people be so cruel to kill elephants just to make furniture or accessories out of them ðŸ˜¢ what is happening to the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can people be so cruel to kill a beautiful animal like elephants it's so sad ðŸ˜¢ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalyBurke omg a new invention ms.flynn be so proud of you ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalyBurke yeah especially in book shops ðŸ˜ people do be looking at me like I'm a psychoðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will ever beat the smell of a new book ðŸ“–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you should be studying but rather watch Chicago PD instead ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithAoife2 done nothing ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually have no motivation to study anything but I know I should]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Ed's new song ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He makes Chicago P.D ðŸ˜ https://t.co/oGxn0mbTEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ready for this film ðŸ˜ðŸŒ¹ https://t.co/wNhRMTX4tH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moulin Rogue has to be one of the best films I've ever seen ðŸ˜ the music is just so good in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sherlock is too good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sherlock is making me feel all the feelings tonight ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad ðŸ˜¿ rest in peace Princess Leia. https://t.co/a14oDXtxjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The original Spider-Man will always be the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unbelievable how many people are dying this year ðŸ˜¿ #RIPGeorgeMichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you start sobbing because your brother got you tickets for Adele in London ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't be more happier with my pressies ðŸ˜» @laurenscullyy https://t.co/lmZJrbfKkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithAoife2 definitely ms.hannon would be so proud of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to run away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buying presents is so stressful but it will be so worth it when you see their faces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me after next week ðŸ˜… https://t.co/oHXKfQmDdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Hanks will forever be my favourite actor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the new Spider-Man but trailer ðŸ˜ðŸ•·ðŸ•¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you got so much work to do but all you want to do is nap ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everyone around you talks about missing their boyfriends and you are still single afðŸ‘Œ https://t.co/aW9ia2cByr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only two episodes into Teen Wolf and it already has me an emotional wreck ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your family is the best family ever and get you Bruno Mars tickets ðŸ˜Œ I love my fam â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic Beast and Where to Find Them is so magical I wish magic was real âœ¨âœ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see Johnny Cooper in the flesh it's a good day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything Stiles does in this season is going to make me cry ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No please ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/wUqzlsIlm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiles will forever be my fave ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally favourite princess and film ever ðŸ˜âœ¨ðŸŒ¹ https://t.co/tTNofOBmOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg my excited it's going to be so magical ðŸ˜âœ¨ https://t.co/zfEv9xqvqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is wrong with me lately ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen Wolf starts back in two days and I'm not one bit emotionally ready for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Theory of Everything is such a beautiful film ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you start crying because it just hit you that your not going to see Coldplay ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everglow is such a beautiful song ðŸ˜» new fave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm making it my mission in life to see Coldplay live!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The John Lewis ad is so adorable #bustertheboxer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Bernie not the president of America ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business makes me want to strangle myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Republics new album is just too good ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally me this year ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/zKcc2N67GY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so excited for Christmas ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I will never not cry at Me Before You ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to learn how to drive ðŸš—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing Shawn Mendes preform makes so excited to see him live ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Tedders voice soothes me ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find out One Republic is going on tour next year ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One republic on X Factor tonight yayy ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shower, bed and greys anatomy ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Bridget Jones Baby makes you laugh and cry at the same timeðŸ˜… too good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenscullyy I know makes me laugh all the time hahaha same â¤ï¸ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are a emotional wreck over our win and Johnny being sent off ðŸ˜­ #COYBIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotham is just too good ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce has grown up so much since the first season of Gotham ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally spent the whole day doing nothing and just now realising I have English homework ðŸ˜Š FMLðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow Patrol 'Run' will forever be my fave ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This better be my husband! https://t.co/wGjUdHPDC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the new episode of Grey's Anatomy already got you an emotional wreck ðŸ˜¢ good start ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do is get into bed and watch Grey's Anatomy ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't be dealing with all these new emojis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know a talk is shite when you fall asleep through it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What even is the new iPhone update I hate it! What even are those emojis ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a job to pay for shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I got Shawn Mendes tickets ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love hearing the sound of rain hitting the window at night in bed â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait for it to be winter so I can start wearing cosy jumpers again ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I regret not getting tickets to see the 1975 ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Republic never have one bad song ðŸ‘ŒðŸŽ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your man in the background ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/blRqVx8juh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughed way too much at this ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/IGQyFl7Jmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your Lumee case finally comes ðŸ˜ my selfies are going to be ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalyBurke 30th of May next year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes is coming to Ireland I am so excited ðŸ˜ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see the new The Fall trailer so excited ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to watch Peaky Blinders or Sherlock decisions decisions ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I. AM. SO. READY ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #Sherlock https://t.co/T5Fdv8vAW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that over under cooked chicken like come on get over yourselves ðŸ˜  #xfactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so excited to see Beauty and the Beast but it's so far away ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie Dornan and Cillian Murphy on the late late like yes please ðŸ˜ðŸ‘Œ #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The O'Donovan brothers are literally my favourite people ever they are so funny ðŸ˜‚ #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce has grown up so much since the first season of Gotham like what the hell ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalyBurke no they can't kill either off spoby was only starting to begin again kill Yvonne off no one likes her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalyBurke OMG what about Toby though he can't die ðŸ˜°]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>