<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT Technical Case Study: Implementing strong user authentication with Windows Hello for Business. https://t.co/Xq3EM0M42v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT Showcase Business Case Study: Optimizing resource efficiency in Microsoft Azure - https://t.co/bL33nwThN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've updated the Microsoft Trust Center - offering detailed security, privacy, and compliance information for all M…https://t.co/2h2zl8SjUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT Showcase Case Study: Skype for Business accelerates modern collaboration at Microsoft (check the metrics!) https://t.co/klu83OFpga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT Showcase Business Case Study: Microsoft Power BI and MyAnalytics drive executive effectiveness - https://t.co/inGkRv5Af4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OneDrive brings new file collaboration and management features to the enterprise. https://t.co/zBYsChBxqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey podcast and article: Staying ahead on cyber security. https://t.co/FLHstQqSxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - Discussions on digital: How strategy is evolving—and staying the same—in the hypergrowth digital age. https://t.co/LUclSQ28uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing Microsoft StaffHub, a new app to help frontline staff workers manage their work day - https://t.co/6N3XqFbEx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NIST FIPS 140-2 certification for Windows 10, Windows 10 Mobile and Windows Server 2016! https://t.co/FUqd03EPIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 0.11 release of Microsoft Team Data Science Platform (TDSP) - 
https://t.co/z40BpUoXuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modern Windows 10 management strategies, using Configuration Manager and Microsoft Intune [video 15min] https://t.co/B2YO1I4zOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An overview of modern management for Windows 10. [video 6min] https://t.co/2B6RTuLeAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure Information Protection December 2016 preview now available. Note also RTM of HYOK. https://t.co/wEsWydAzUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how Microsoft has approached the adoption of cloud? Check out this MSIT Showcase SME roundtable https://t.co/08G0PLWlAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT Showcase Technical Case Study - Reducing IT costs with Azure and Windows 10. https://t.co/pjivLEtZUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An in-depth look at the Cerber ransomware.
https://t.co/ddaGO5ZGhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power BI Desktop – 2016 Year in Review - 11 releases and &gt;190 features &amp; enhancements! https://t.co/jsEG2MWH33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ArcGIS Maps for Power BI now available in Preview in the Power BI service - https://t.co/fHrVXcuQzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth noting if you missed it last year - signifcant tightening of the Microsoft partnership with Adobe! https://t.co/ixiL5NcxsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Microsoft partners with mapping companies to build next world graph' - Microsoft + TomTom + HERE + ESRI. https://t.co/DRsux6Ci3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering what Microsoft is doing in the age of connected cars? Meet the Microsoft Connected Vehicle Platform! https://t.co/oJnxEdPVV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - The next acronym you need to know about: RPA (robotic process automation) https://t.co/O4tIqrjeeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - Using agile to accelerate your data transformation. https://t.co/UbhUnRnIcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - The age of analytics: Competing in a data-driven world. https://t.co/VCU7xMr8K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Update for January 2017 - https://t.co/VWt29inb39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An overview of modern management for Windows 10 [Video 6min] - https://t.co/2B6RTuLeAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server next version Community Technology Preview 1.1 now available. https://t.co/DLvvY60UxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - Transformation with a capital T. https://t.co/A8VGR23mdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - Making data analytics work for you—instead of the other way around. https://t.co/oF5wF6BZi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krag Yes life is looking simpler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big news - Azure AD Pass-Through Authentication and Desktop SSO are now in public preview. https://t.co/0NmeA2X8R6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An insightful piece from Brad Smith on responsible tech - including relevant education and access to broadband. https://t.co/eTWTUWdRv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The AAD Playbook™" - Explore and quickly implement Identity and Access Management scenarios.
https://t.co/wnlXQXc7X2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imorrish They just called me this evening - can't we trust the Aussies any more? +61 always seemed like a responsible prefix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anniversary Update (Build 1607) has moved into Current Branch for Business!
https://t.co/tiQvPsbn8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[X3 is an awesome device! Hats off to HP ... https://t.co/bjzNxCLYoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting visualization of the big bata &amp; analytics marketspace https://t.co/yYEPl5go4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have Satya here in NZ! https://t.co/6EPTL9IBk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks great! Even better with a Muppet on stage for impact. https://t.co/eagbEPZpKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering what you can do with Sway in Office 365? Check out this beautiful web presentation for Surface Pro 4! https://t.co/dM4JmWfSHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great advice from Dr @DrHaroldHillman on managing career development in a flexi working context. https://t.co/HRXq1VpFqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawgeeknz That is a bit wack! Privacy matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Azure support in BackupExec! https://t.co/C81qF1b1x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see this partnership! https://t.co/qbJ3XPGA4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft &amp; Poptech present SuperCreativity Salon - a 7-part video series focused on creativity! https://t.co/qTBiIJ8kae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft &amp; Poptech present 'The Changing World of Work' - a fascinating 8 Part video series. https://t.co/eLiA7mfLp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT SHOWCASE - Creating a personalized experience in the modern workplace with Windows 10 - https://t.co/Nbch7jTPhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Teams: Step-by-step intro for using, enabling and managing the experience [video 13min] - https://t.co/1DTW4V22EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on the US election and moving forward together  - from the leadership at Microsoft https://t.co/rUCv9r0fEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krag did you see the announcement last night re Microsoft Teams? That's our entry in this category 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reinventing productivity looks like this.... ! https://t.co/NXDYuBeZD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ Euro often = 'relationship' :) Can be a good idea to have Mechanical Breakdown Insurance. Vero/Autosure = good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing the launch of Microsoft BizTalk Server 2016 - bridge traditional and cloud apps. https://t.co/R3oR7U1wNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CASE STUDY: Poole Hospital uses machine learning &amp; wearable tech to create new healthcare reality for people with ep…https://t.co/V6mGnOO7IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great detailed example of how to make bots do useful things - using the Microsoft Bot Framework. https://t.co/ifwTmKJVT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat 2min video on Modern Workplace themes - 'Journey of an Idea' https://t.co/p8jHL7PdC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see the modern Skype for Business experience arrive for Mac! https://t.co/pWcGRhijO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey: Making data analytics work for you—instead of the other way around. https://t.co/oF5wF6BZi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see these 2 powerful toolsets (Flow and PowerApps) hit GA!!! https://t.co/ZGTI5ItKE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New kiwi mobile app for healthcare professionals to offer safe and secure information sharing to improve patient car…https://t.co/inIoE9YDse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breach Resistance in Windows Server 2016 [video 7min]. https://t.co/uLqTuwZkwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great track from the Surface Studio launch! https://t.co/JGCOxa0X3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSIT SHOWCASE - Microsoft Azure Key Vault helps protect keys, secrets, and certificates. https://t.co/zDx6KwM0LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science with Microsoft SQL Server 2016 – Free eBook. https://t.co/CwjX7rFhid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Preview of Azure Analysis Services - https://t.co/FJU3wt8Eef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting piece from the White House on Smart Cities initiatives
https://t.co/0Z9alJKqQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Case Study - Cambridgeshire Constabulary on how mobilisation as changed how they work. [video 5m] https://t.co/78cdBh7EWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't make it to Ignite NZ this year? We record pretty much everything so check out the excellent keynote for sta…https://t.co/rhpkv9JQjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to watch this -  90s summary of the Windows Event - stunning OS &amp; device goodness! https://t.co/WG6PjTUV2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cauld @TeamIntergen @MicrosoftNZ Welcome Chris - awesome to have you onboard!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrieSheers HoloLens is awesome - an experience not to be missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukaszfromwelly @krag I'm seeing if I can pull in a favour Lukasz!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukaszfromwelly I haven't seen them yet - I'm not attending this year so I'll have to check with my colleagues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad Smith: A Cloud for Global Good. Navigating a responsible path through the 4th Industrial Revolution. https://t.co/PwhTpxcl1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing the Team Data Science Process from Microsoft! https://t.co/wxeuZ3kIuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 2007 family of products approaching end of extended support https://t.co/sgqnb2ceC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 CIO Mag NZ Global State of Information Security Survey 
https://t.co/WvTaNmOxjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great sales leadership role at Microsoft NZ! https://t.co/E4OwPthuBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gartner names Microsoft a leader in 2016 ODBMS MQ, second year in a row!
https://t.co/OFkJazp8YY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft announces SAP’s choice of Azure to help enterprises transform HR - https://t.co/9NUKjKrVXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz OneNote is the Modern App optimised for small/touchscreen devices ; OneNote 2016 is the regular desktop version :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrTweetTastic Well deserved bud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligent identity protection with Azure AD [video 15min] https://t.co/riPsfUASeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! Office Lens comes to Windows 10 and adds Office 365 support! https://t.co/dvIs36QbCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey - Is cybersecurity incompatible with digital convenience? https://t.co/DyPVUtHKNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIOs, CTOs playing greater role in technology decisions.
https://t.co/RL4uY4jDRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing guest access for Office 365 Groups. https://t.co/Q0PbJH0MvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure AD with PingAccess: Secure Remote Access to even more on-premises Web Apps [video 3min] https://t.co/uhg6Oiulky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Defined Storage with Storage Spaces Direct in Windows Server 2016. [video 13min] https://t.co/Pvgg4myiE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Trusted Data Platforms' - storage, protection &amp; access providing 'compliance as a service' via 'Data Kitchens' - wi…https://t.co/LMHBWnpO0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinsey: IT as a service: From build to consume. https://t.co/dR0c18J4W9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm Looks very nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Total Economic Impact™ Of Microsoft Azure Platform-As-A-Service" Some stunning numbers! 
https://t.co/fg4zQILKxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's new in Intune - August https://t.co/UgQYK4o8if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Present your data in style with the Power BI app for Surface Hub - check out the new full screen presentation mode -…https://t.co/sPBh857h17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book from Microsoft Press: Microsoft Azure Security Infrastructure. https://t.co/NnwFKnl1x3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuous Delivery of iOS Applications with Visual Studio Team Services. https://t.co/oT6aNmSXtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on APIs and looking for some useful guidance? Check this out ...
https://t.co/Kt7YRd1Onc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest MSIT Executive report - beautiful presentation of a strategic discussion - https://t.co/7ozDo47eJC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>