<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kathleea Hope she feels better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final course.  Later there shall be a nap. #bitteredsling @ Four Seasons Hotel Vancouver https://t.co/8S0gGzwxry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second course The Tipping Point Best Sunday ever #bitteredsling @ Four Seasons Hotel Vancouver https://t.co/mO59te1uHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For science. More cocktails. This is a Pajara. #bitteredsling @ Four Seasons Hotel Vancouver https://t.co/E0dVXAb02l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending Sunday in a cocktail course. @ Four Seasons Hotel Vancouver https://t.co/KSpWceLF0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White knuckle drive to Rogers center to see Henrik 1k celebration #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously Mother Nature. I got it. It's winter. You can stop snowing now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you aren't reading Hallie- you're missing out.  Trust me on this. https://t.co/6FT8zczPzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maureenjohnson I wonder if he saw his press secretary telling people we shouldn't call it a ban... because irony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling Reading your tweets make my entire day. I want to make you a G&amp;T and just watch you work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to everyone who came out to hear me talk on character and conflict on a day with too much snow and slush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching! https://t.co/KdyyVMg1m7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleASigne it was a slip slide ride in. Class on character and motivation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't make a point without using all caps and five exclamation points might I suggest you seek anger management?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tough_Talker_Ty slamming women for how they look? Classy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tough_Talker_Ty one who doesn't respect the law and acts like a four year old. That's not leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tough_Talker_Ty @chrislhayes the point is that he didn't say anything. He only ramps up when it is muslims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am supposed to teach tomorrow. It keeps snowing. One of these these things cannot continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinawilkie @SamSykesSwears Want to bet that he points out he's #1 in low rankings? Winner by a yuge amount.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a ninja in the snow #dogsofinstgram #westiesofinstagram https://t.co/qWzyDwBrka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the horror https://t.co/AWrVDTvpHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Occasionally I say smart things. https://t.co/CGOnkdQfoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh https://t.co/eBPdN0RA4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need this adorable middle grade @JoanneLevy Crushing It https://t.co/YzZPYpvM7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler Tomorrow evening and Friday out. Next Monday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I picture you enjoying this @CollisMeansHill https://t.co/Ux8f4x2BuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler @goodreads Oooh we should set up a phone call. I'm too chatty for 140 characters.  : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcharbonneau no pressure I'm not going anywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler @goodreads I can tell you some places to go....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler @goodreads Could you pack any more into the month? :  )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@readwritetell You may be my new officially favourite person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOwleryBooks It was like going to the oscars only I wore yoga pants and ate chips while I watched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you added my new book to your want to read list on Goodreads? The Hanging Girl will be out in October. https://t.co/McmQxyItgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved the live show and huge congrats to THE CALL! https://t.co/ilHtjFdkEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hogwarts underoos for grown ups.  Well, life is now complete. https://t.co/shfx5EtA4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in creativity? Be sure to check out the Creative Women's Summit. Free and VIP options available.… https://t.co/GeQROIKM2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AHHHH!  So excited. It's an honor to be nominated with such amazing books. https://t.co/MeK9roghEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School visit today (call out to Richmond's Palmer Secondary) and was reminded that things may seem bleak in the news, but teens are awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_hill Done. I am hopeless in the face of a good book recommendation. Keep em coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all need this video   https://t.co/keWR4yzsRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I say smart things. https://t.co/bICaZVvHjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Author visit with Darren Groth at RC Palmer in Richmond. #schooltalk @ R.C. Palmer Secondary School https://t.co/1V7GwQ3DZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I rather love this. https://t.co/bdsn0aH8Uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the mood to read about revenge? https://t.co/19FUpjrJja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CollisMeansHill Cinder is clearly smarter than many elected officials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling As a writer I always admired your writing skill. However, as a human- you impress the hell out of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lazy Sunday afternoons are made for naps. #dogsofinstgram https://t.co/POFSc6ZgSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight there will be cocktails and board games because while I am a grown up I am not mature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/ruwR6xdevR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't be who I am without having had weekly library trips with my parents. Yay for #familyliteracyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahWLaurence @NicolaYoon @CLLFirestone @JenLiaLongo @mpadian @BethKephart @RConstantine14 @nina_lacour @davidlevithan Wow! Thanks you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in/near Vancouver? Then you need to be following @Roundhouse983]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tagatelle pasta with truffles at Wildebeest #dineoutvancouver @ Wildebeest https://t.co/wl6Y5jlCxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the warm fuzzies https://t.co/XIHt83b9NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to celebrate #SFUgrad. Look out there are some new writers in town https://t.co/uuV7huqxvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've made and frozen three batches of potatoe soup and it isn't even noon. Call me a rockstar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katyperry PLEASE remake Helen Reddy's I AM WOMAN. We need that song again. "Hear me roar, in numbers too big to ignore."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmfaris No one's ever going to keep me down again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want @katyperry to do a cover of I AM WOMAN. That would be awesome   @GabrielleSaraP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking we all need a listen again to Helen Reddy's song I AM WOMAN. "Hear me roar, in numbers too big to ignore."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flowers in my office because why wait for someone to bring you flowers when you can buy your own? https://t.co/H5eaDvfJAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you voted? Lots of great books including With Malice! https://t.co/LBBIbfs5B5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CollisMeansHill You need your own home fur device. I can highly recommend it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decided to follow this Twitter feed because I think we all need a bit more dog in our lives.  Especially these da… https://t.co/RgJ4uelPqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super excited to give a Deb callout for a new book! https://t.co/GStIary1zB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking we need Besties before Testies t-shirts. https://t.co/Fw5nKRWi0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@junniekahying Ooooh happy reading!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CollisMeansHill This seems very reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to jumpstart your creative goals in 2017? Check out the Creative Women's Summit https://t.co/05mTuICyRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The depth of my love for the sounds of puppy snores is hard to full describe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcdyer I imagine you've bribed a dog or two in your life.  :  )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will they be quiet for conference call? Peanut butter kong as a bribe coming up #dogsofinstgram https://t.co/6IderFORPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you signed up for the Creative Women's Summit yet? https://t.co/0NUCI8o05b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HotComesToDie And so articulate. He's a word master indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessskoog Aw thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never believe the way to make America (or anyplace) great is by demeaning and mocking others and spewing hate. Never.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisadaily Sigh.  That might be where I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyKenzie_ Completely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLT16 I now have PTSD when I hear Sarah McLachlan's voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching SPCA ads makes me cry.  There should be a warming before they come on the air. #bigsoftie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@so_chez @AmyRComms So much nicer than saying "my you are a bit obsessive, huh?"  : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are days when being cleaned and wearing clothes feels like an accomplishment. This is one of those days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRComms also a bit crazy pants- but it works for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRComms  for a book by that count (80k) would be 16 weeks. Then I add a month for unexpected things and that should get me to first draft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRComms I have a good sense of how many words I can write in a week. Say for you it is 5k words. Then I divide the typical word count 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh an excuse to buy more books. (Not that I needed one, but the rest of you might need some encouragement) https://t.co/wi7TvrZDmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I create a project plan with target goals broken down week by week.  #TWSOchat #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HilltopDiner Rubs hands together and laughs with an evil tone mwah-ha-ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you signed up for the Creative Women's Summit? You should. https://t.co/nALlXcDyjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plotting world domination with a chai latte @ Caffe Divano https://t.co/e1pKy2CCgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJBanner1 @danyelledrexler @KimberlySBelle @chaptersindigo  I had no idea you were so close! Some day there must be a meet up and wine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@authorwendy I laughed at this tweet in the morning. Now I'm wondering if you have room for a few more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler @AJBanner1 @KimberlySBelle @chaptersindigo BOOM Just bought Twilight Wife- looks like just my cup of tea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcmystery I love this tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danyelledrexler @AJBanner1 @KimberlySBelle @chaptersindigo Loved The Marriage Lie- now will have to check out the other book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahEHealy The Sisters Chase is AMAZING.  Can't wait until I can get a copy for all my friends so we can discuss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to do a deep cleanse facial mask while watching the hockey game because I like to be wild and crazy like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember how I said it was so weird that it wasn't raining in Vancouver? Yeah. Well that's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roserambles1 Thanks so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I read tweets like this I let out a tiny squeal of joy. https://t.co/moW32ZFeJE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>