<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@arsenalfcspares looking for 2 tickets for the Arsenal V hull game if you know of any...Tia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shevchenko will give Nunes huge problems if they rematch and feel she will win this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!!! Never expected Shevchenko to sub Pena]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect timing on those sweeps by Shevchenko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboy caught with that counter from the kick in the exact same way as the first round,great stoppage by Herb dean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for 2 tickets for Arsenal v hull February 11th if theres any going?@tiktscambuster @Tickets4arsenal @GunnersTickets @arsenal_tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiktscambuster yes please,if there's any info on tickets that would be great I'm looking to book flights to London to get over for a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiktscambuster I was wondering about tickets for the home game if you would have any info on them please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have tickets for Arsenal v Bayern been released yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiktscambuster I'm looking for 2 tickets for Arsenal v Bayern Munich in two weeks time is there anyone reputable to buy tickets from ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In need of 5 tickets for Arsenal v burnley tomorrow ? If anyone has got spares please get back to me they can be picked up at the stadium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for 2 tickets for Arsenal v burnley in a few weeks if there's any going @GunnersTickets @arsenal_tickets @tickets2arsenal ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneMcCullough @bryancallen @FighterNtheKid @joerogan @BrendanSchaub brilliant hopefully that happens soon but glad @WTSPod had you on ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneMcCullough @bryancallen has mentioned you train him on @JREpodcast I'm surprised he hasn't had you on @FighterNtheKid or @joerogan yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing podcast lads wish it could have went on for a few more hours @WTSPod @WayneMcCullough hopefully Wayne comes back on soon,what a man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray Borg by sub here I feel #UFC207]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicious knockout,that's curtains for Mike Pyles UFC career,always enjoyed watching him fight #UFC207]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanSheehanBA @DamonMartin Thatch V northcutt ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Kavanagh he will be cut after that,think he will find it even harder at 185 too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArsenesArmy shes world champ!Taite was an amazing fighter who beat Holly Holm..Nunes is really good and hits super hard,could go either way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArsenesArmy do dong yung Kim and Cruz,rousey fight could go either way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arsenal_tickets looking for two tickets to Arsenal V burnley in january]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PetesyCarroll he will be calling out Royce Gracie next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Skip Baylis fella is insufferable wish he would piss off away from MMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Gall for real? dan hardy? Is he not out with heart trouble? He certainly knows how to pick fights,a healthy Dan Hardy would ko him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really feel Sage needs to go to a top gym and get some better coaching,phenomenal athlete and all the potential in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These adverts in between fights are getting beyond ridiculous #UFCSacramento]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @UrijahFaber great performance,it's the best Uriah has looked in a few years i wonder if this retirement will stick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge heart there from Brad Pickett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jouban by decision 9/2 ðŸ’ªðŸ» faber by submission,sage by decision,Paige by decision are my next 3 picks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great performance @AlanJouban clinical striking and fought really smart throughout, #UFCSacramento]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't remember a time that I've seen a fighter totally uninterested,Cole Miller looks a shell of himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickygervais Please bring back Rockbusters, Buy em ferry,Phil colons,this man likes his wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shaun_Smith_84 @marcgoddard_uk sorry I missed what happened,in which fight was there a mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going with davie grant in the next #UFC204]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There goes all my betsðŸ™ˆhad Tumenov to win in all of them ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to watching Tumenov in the next fight,not many better strikers than him in his division,think he will win by 2nd round ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really happy for @Marc_Diakiese  some lovely shots there for the finish,world class potential #UFC204]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O https://t.co/xiVOf4x8C3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FIFA17 is so realistic,I started out with #AlexHunter,I picked Chelsea and they sent me on loan to Vittese Arnhem for the rest of my career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChuckMindenhall Yoel seemed the happiest fighter there he was really enjoying what Conor had to say,he just looked so happy ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimSeery20 sold out now I'm afraid,more tickets go on sale tomorrow,sign up for the UFC newsletter and you will get a presale code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimSeery20 go to the UFC fightclub site and the pre sale tickets are for sale there now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets sorted for #UFC205 can't wait to go to NYC for it ðŸ’ªðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take nothing away from spicely very good performance he dominated Thiago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely horrendous by Thiago Santos,great win for Spicely easily the biggest in his career,can't emphasis how awful that is by Thiago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pacing of these fights is horrendous I can't take another ad break #UFCBrasilia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chagas saved by the bell in both rounds,both fighters look really tired hopefully Silva can catch him in the third]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very poor fight IQ by silva and it looks like his chin is gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DominickCruz knows what's going to happen and what strike's fighters are going to throw every time it's amazing,best fight IQ in the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going with silva again here he has let me down more than any mma fighter ever so why change now #UFCBrasilia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great performance by Gillespie,amazing wrestling,had him at 12/5 by decision #UFCBrasilia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFCs Joe silva seems like an asshole listening to @ALIAQUINTA is saying and other managers have said seems like a dictator #SmallManSyndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just listening to @ALIAQUINTA on@arielhelwani Mma hour and it's disgraceful that the UFC can treat a fighter so bad,no show money,no bonuses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punches thrown to landed percentage in this fight with Eye v Corriera must be about 5% #UFC203]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful by @ymedeiros excellent performance #UFC203]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latifi just fell into the darkness #UFCHamburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shitðŸ™ˆ what a knee by Bader,Latifi looked good up until then,what a finish #UFCHamburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Rocky theme song for the walkout from Latifi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something all week has said to me that Latifi by ko at 4/1 is far too big a price,I think it's a bad matchup for Bader #UFCHamburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick hein and Rustalam Khabilov on points double upðŸ’ªðŸ»ðŸ’ªðŸ»ðŸ’ªðŸ»#UFCHamburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven madness! Same old story,at least when Moyes was there and Kenwright as owner yas didn't have any money what's the excuse now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The money paid for some of these average players is ridiculous,we signed Sanchez for 32m and Sissoko is sold for 30m football has gone mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't see why Spurs would but sissoko and wanyama in the same window!
They have Delli Ali and Dier in there too,30m for Sissoko is madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven how much did you's net spend in this window? Sell stones for 50m buy Williams 11m and bolasie for 25m #SameOldEverton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven why would you want to spend 30m on sissoko anyway? Could have got Wilshere on loan til you found somebody this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven I'm honestly in tears here ðŸ˜‚ enner Valencia hahahaha,after all the players you mention you end up with him on loan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven Everton doing some great business ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful finish from Pettis there didn't expect him to sub oliveria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FunkMaster_UFC very close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit what a kick,amazing knockout #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steverhoeven twice for 120 and 170]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These ridiculous decisions are costing me serious money what a fucking joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck sake! How can they see Miller winning that fight Jesus Christ #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's a fucking joke of a decision fucking hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wish any bad on a fighter but it has to be Kevin cadets last UFC fight,same old story gasses after 3 minutes and looks for a way out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casey doesn't look interested,looks like he wants a way out #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countdown has begun until Kevin Casey gasses out #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an awful decision #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bbutcherr it's a mark of respect to the victims of the earthquake in Italy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've given up on Shane Campbell that fight was tailor made for him and still manages to get ko'ed #UFCVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garbrandt V Cruz next hopefully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markos looks very nervous,hopefully she gets the decision here I've really rated her since seeing her on the ultimate fighter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing performance from Lorenz Larkin,travis browne style elbows while Magny was looking or the takedown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnys leg is bleeding from leg kicks,Larkins kicks have been lethal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet on Larkin to win by decision but now feel he will ko Magny #UFC202]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rioferdy5 signing Mustafi tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every post fight interview Conor has been mentioned #RunsTheGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would the crowd boo that fight? 2 heavyweights throwing down at really high altitude for 3 rounds what do they think will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The booing by some fans in a fight like this seriously irritate me #UFC201]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was crazy #UFC201]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmcgahon_ great !thanks for the updates,I couldn't believe there was no live stream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellatorMMA @TheO2 @StrabanimalMMA where can I watch this in Ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrabakaHitman do you think he will look as good as usual while training and fighting throughout Ramadan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mynextmatch @andremgeorgiou @IMMAFed thank you so much il keep up with the updates I'm surprised there's no live stream or not on fightpass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andremgeorgiou @IMMAFed @mynextmatch is there a link where I can watch the fights live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UFCFightPass is @UFCFightPass showing the World Amateur mma championships I can't seem to find it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love  @rory_macdonald I hope he signs a new contract and makes a run at the title,I feel he beats everyone other than Wonderboy at 170]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[48-47 scorecard from the judge??? Somebody was pulling for the Canadian,where u get 2 rounds from I have no clue]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>