<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright, I'll continue this tomorrow. Thank you to all those who have liked and hope the essays/responses have come across as genuine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny Just the truth, good buddy :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny You see! That kindness and generosity, you were right and you are the fucking best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny P.S Thank you for sending that film info over. Next week, I'm watching em, I promise. I trust your opinion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny film reviews. You're greater than awesome and I'm so grateful that you follow me and put up with my bullshit tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny and support and you've never stopped with every response you've ever sent to me. I also love your grounded yet genuine film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny You. You were the first one to offer a place to stay/take me in and encourage my insanity. That is such a great act of kindness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny I don't know if you remember this but almost 2 years ago, I declared that I was considering visiting NZ for NZ Film Fest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyleKurner came to be. In other words, I've always read your work and your thoughts on film and it's always spoken to me so thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyleKurner Scorsese boring whilst most found that to be blasphemy) &amp; how it was impossible to objectify the male body until Magic Mike XXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyleKurner out bullshit on sensationalized straight male masculinity  in film (re you being the only one I saw who admitted to finding some]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyleKurner Oh Kyle, why have I not spoken to you in ages? To start, you were one of the first people I saw on here that challenged &amp; called]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smolexH Just the truth :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_beeee catch up and talk movies and your greatness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_beeee I thank you so damn much for following me, being so supportive and so goddamn lovely! And on my next Canberra trip, we gonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_beeee Gave some wonderfulish advice about AFTRS, and always favourite my rambling movie bullshit &amp; bad jokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_beeee Speaking of supportive, You! Wonderful kind person you. Only following me for a month or so you got my producer call out asap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd Thank you and I hope the positivity sticks and gets you to create great art!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smolexH Always friendly and having now met you in person, it's all there and more in person. Alex, you are so damn cool, never forget this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smolexH ...&amp; then I read them. You're a meticulous, concise, considerate &amp; most of all great writer who is ALWAYS honest, always supportive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smolexH post your reviews and how often you'd share em (There were so many) I found it refreshing to see a writer share their work so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smolexH When you first followed me and I followed back  (Or it could've been the other way around) I remember how excitable you were to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd But please let me be the one to say, for the future of my film viewing and making, please make another film asap!....please :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd display and any grand comments or thoughts can be channeled in a piece of your own work. It's still hard concentrating though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd Aahh I am semi in the same boat but more in the edit room. It's a good thing in some ways, re it keeps energy up, emotions on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd It really did. It was really great work and I'm so damn excited to see your next film!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd you have on here multiple times and just overall being inspiring and amazing. Please make more movies. Forever, if possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd But on top of that, I have to thank you for your amaxing festival and for ALWAYS supporting filmmakers including myself (Which]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd taught me something. It taught me to be patient with every scene and reminded me to embrace silence. I love that movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd That movie was The Room At The Top Of The Stairs. I was a month away from shooting my first proper short with a budget and it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrionyKidd So, I don't know if I ever told you this but I owe you a huge thank you. You once sent me one of your short films without q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love this Cannes poster for PATERSON https://t.co/qttDiR4N8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adlow76 Where???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator You need to please please send me that one day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcinefileguy film insights!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcinefileguy engaged and appreciated differing film opinions. Bravo good buddy, it'll be a pleasure to continue excitedly awaiting your]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcinefileguy word on great cinema and above all, always being supportive. Film Twitter can be mean and bullshit sometimes, you've always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcinefileguy while I have yet to apologize, I have to say thank you for your wonderful movie insights, your dedication to spreading the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcinefileguy We have been followin' each other for a lllooonnngggg damn time, I mean you've had to read my shit since the beginning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram Haha just the truth/thank you for reading!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram And sorry for the 800 tweet long essay and for my overuse of the word Incredible but you are...fucking awesome. (Honestly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram when it seems like no one can or does and thank you for following me and putting up with my bullshit tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram PLEASE keep offering every idea, thought and response you have. It has helped me through bullshit days and provides reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram effortlessly is incredible &amp; your bravery &amp; dedication to what you preach is beyond incredible. Please PLEASE keep tweeting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram insights, wisdom, perception, consideration and knowledge. I mean it, the way you respond to people and support them almost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram and followed your tweets, let me say with all great honesty, I am so fortunate and not grateful enough to have your incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram and loved all the things I've said about his work from 16 onwards was amazing to see/Respond to. So now having read your work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram in some way or another sung your praises. (Your fanbase is incredible, goddamn). And seeing that you also dug Chuck Palahniuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram So, I followed you because I had seen your writings shared around by many friends and half of the people I follow on here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I do promise to respond to every. Single. Damn. One. No matter how long it takes (18 weeks later: "U R Tops")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, yay more favouriters! Keep em comin']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re these responses. If you've followed me longer than a week, you know I can't summarize anything in a single tweet. Excuse the essays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator bullshit I write so Thank you for still following and favouriting this, good buddy!
Also, have you seen Southland Tales?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator film recommendations and quiet yet appreciated little favourites and responses of support in the endless amount of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator So over what's been a good 6 years of Twitter followin', I've seen similarities in our film tastes, your amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator Following and had this moment of "Oh goddamn, I'm one of the chosen ones! Be cool, Christoph. @ So u like Southland Tales?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEBermanator You know, you were one of my very first followers on here. No shit. I remember seeing how many followers you had compared to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow Oh and P.S, come say hi to us all at SFF!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow keep talking movies. Keep comin' with the funny Twitter replies. They are VERY much appreciated. 
..Sorry for the essay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow were no fluke. You have incredible skills despite keeping them hidden from time to time. Please don't. Keep writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow Are in fact, one HELL of a writer and your modest yet incredibly insightful, perceptive and well thought out mini tweet reviews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow "Rebecca - Not a writer" - Only from one fucking article which I have shared around and read more tjan twice do I know that you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow "fashion over &amp; over". You wrote that. A small snippet from what was one of the best articles I've read. And it's signed off by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow "We see all kinds of stories on screen, all different kinds of sex, yet birth is portrayed in this one-dimensional" (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youwontknow Oooo well then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright, sorry for the delay. This day has been 46 different kids of bullshit. Here we go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beer_movie @erin_beeee @debbie_zhou Also, that was the compliment you fav'd for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beer_movie @erin_beeee @debbie_zhou (Cont'd) Please do not release Knight Of Flops despite my colleague TimBeer4U2c2001's letters of demand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aWomanUnderThe Holy shit, Preach!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_beeee @debbie_zhou @beer_movie Thanks for ganging up on me, VULTURES. *Continues writing letter to Criterion demanding SFITY release*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that people are slowly favouriting this throughout the day. 

Shall be sending these through tonight! I promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bump de bump. I'm feeling complimentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny Aayyeee ok stay tuned! Also, please remind me of that rare movie you love/recommended me a while back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you don't interact with my tweets a huge lot, doesn't matter. I'm sure I'll have something to say. 

Favourite away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My responses, if anyone can be bothered to fav this may take some time, but it just means I'm thinking of the best compliment imaginable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you favourite this, I will send you an honest compliment

You all have improved many of my days somehow or way, let me return the favour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck it, why not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateJFitz01 Rectify both!! (The movie is decent! Even if it may evoke some annoying/not great memories) You should definitely hit up Bath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be a good time to do this again (Can't find the original tweet) https://t.co/acVSH8q8nS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateJFitz01 The film and Bath, I mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateJFitz01 Oh wowww that sucks! And to add to it, of all movies, one as depressing and low key as the one he chose. Did you ever revisit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@episode2480 I can imagine! My flashback memories of that film are all intense, awkward scenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamalouf Malcom's a great movie as well! (Definitely not suited)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamalouf A few of these answers have popped up re dates who declared disinterest in cinema after seeing a movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamalouf The one HUGE drawback of Govindas and that sounds like the most unfortunate date of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LA_Fairweather I was in the minority at the time. Everyone loved it. I loved Goodman's monents. Denzel was great. Not a Zemeckis fan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddieWhiteJr As far as movies go, you got lucky at least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexxkittle It really was! (Made my Jan list also)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@episode2480 Nope. This wins. Bravo! I love how it's that scene that tops what was probably already an uncomfortable 2 hour film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd Thank you for informing me, good buddy. I could do with a 57th rewatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd @FilmMomatic As was AMERICAN SNIPER the very next day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best answers:
- Hannah Montana The Major Motion    
  Picture
- The Inbetweeners 2
- Come &amp; See
- Punch Drunk Love
- Anything with subtitles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Coronel @registradus Woah! How'd they find it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LA_Fairweather Oooo we finally disagree on a film. I hated Flight! (&amp; that was a film me &amp; my still girlfriend saw and both did not dig)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karenyhan Bit of both and thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 January First Viewings:
1. MOONLIGHT
2. JACKIE
3. LAW OF DESIRE
4. FARGO S2
5. XXX: RETURN OF XANADU CAGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jocelynseip It was a beautiful thing to hear, we still friends, thankfully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jocelynseip He stood in the foyer on the cinema and said "Nup. Sorry. What if someone see's me?" 
- She called him an impotent weenie aloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jocelynseip Re it being the other way around. A friend of mine dumped her boyfriend because he refused to see Elizabeth: The Golden Age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jocelynseip Yes!! Same here, they should just never commit the cardinal sin of being both cheap and boring!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>