<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see so many people out discussing the future of Chinatown with @cityofvancouver today!… https://t.co/kTf3ionYRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My next article is live! Inge Roecker's studio imagines vibrant and empowering futures for the DTES! https://t.co/DzmlKSGsTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering last week. There is one bus in the photograph. This is what happens when Vancouver… https://t.co/yIiuQ1Hzyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eye of Sauron peeks around the Fairmont last week. Photo taken last week from the Shaw Tower… https://t.co/sbGVEb69t2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly a white Christmas but I'll take it :) my wife and I agree the red cranes are to be… https://t.co/1OkLbFR4Oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What constitutes a good view? This certainly is an unorthodox one in Vancouver, where the cult… https://t.co/BdhjO0cCuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ghost crane. Appeared at main and 7th Ave early morning this week! @ Mt. Pleasant, Vancouver,… https://t.co/X8c9KuphaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from work today. Facing north, looking down Ontario Street from Mount Pleasant towards… https://t.co/57D3ewuvVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic jam on the water yesterday morning. They were either Buffleheads or Barrow's Goldeneyes;… https://t.co/oCPLAIMFZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn it looks like it might be summer outside from down here; site inspection at Van Lawn on… https://t.co/xvZeelfjSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome site visit intempo_interiors with Robin Woronko, who has been so generous with his time… https://t.co/QEU6Gquu77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention to detail: cutting a 1/2" reveal around an exit sign rather than surface mounting it… https://t.co/DFk5Bzlxbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lighting installation underway in stairs of the Vancouver Lawn Tennis &amp; Badminton Club today.… https://t.co/2cbzSYPFYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might not always love the rain in Vancouver but it always loves you! Errin's toes are… https://t.co/Tg33t8KfgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my architecture friends: were these lines put in by mistake by the contractor or… https://t.co/6qDSBMR7Oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday to my thesis dissertation "Vancouverism Revisited: a Late Entry for the… https://t.co/8FCEksU82n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a lot of scaffolding to preserve one lonely little Art Deco detail. You're looking at the… https://t.co/qjWsVdtemq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great architecture: https://t.co/cfHt2hOilR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy spooky scary Halloween; ooOOoOoOoooo so scaryyy is that a ghost? @ Woodward's Building https://t.co/BdAC45PEIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the view up Burrard Inlet (at the speed of a vehicle, in this case the 211) now that the… https://t.co/fWgbyyBlw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing tapestries on display at Inform Interiors. Ruth Jones spoke about her work last week,… https://t.co/AkHIhpvuzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wanted a live symphony orchestra at your next beer pong tournament? https://t.co/KN1F7Vskh0 via @pricetags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folly at the Columbia Street Pipe Station, no clue as to why it was made. No history of the… https://t.co/CvWo1O8WIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't see this everyday; legendary Grammy award winning sound engineer Don Harder built a LEGO… https://t.co/lkvGHeUXPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lobby of 53 W Hastings by Gair Williamson Architect &amp; Ankenman Marchand Architects. From the… https://t.co/UBu6fQTVq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game 3! @ Marine Building https://t.co/I2oXhDXP7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your 7 day forecast: over 200 mm of rain and wind strong enough to blow the nuts off a steel… https://t.co/f9aMhMZUx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Errin and I are working on our next design excersize that we think will sweep the globe - googly… https://t.co/iM0t40UEBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two of my top favourite buildings in Vancouver. The Marine Building by McCarter and Nairne and… https://t.co/2WLzHFfozW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A doctor can bury his mistakes, but an architect can only advise his clients to plant vines." -… https://t.co/yQHJEssMup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stone on facade of Dunlevy Food Equipment at 80 West 7th Ave. I've seen this stone from time to… https://t.co/EeekfeTXq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback to IDS west - amazing candle by Ontwerpduo called Tallow: "A candle needs the… https://t.co/cMWbIk7GBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Board formed concrete in the Crane building on Beatty Street. Does the name sound familiar? This… https://t.co/K2T2c96ZV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep Cove Road. The serenity of the trees and mountain backdrop was congested with endless car… https://t.co/aYGofPdU3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver take a look at this bad boy: https://t.co/eq01ZOcZcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What looks like the remnants of a splash pad has been drained and is now perfect bum height for… https://t.co/yj823gmfCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North side of Museum of Vancouver and HR MacMillan Space Centre. You might recognize the name… https://t.co/2QcpmkUPHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My camera can't begin to capture the outrageous sunset we had last night. Shots like this are… https://t.co/hnpqBcizRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Maritime Museum by CBK Van Norman. "Six foot four, three hundred pounds, and he played a… https://t.co/P2YVHMNa1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Friedman Residence, 4916 Chancellor Boulevard. One of five stops on the Midcentury Modern… https://t.co/k79RfwumzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice day. Steamworks, a Vancouver staple, featured on right inside The Landing. Built in 1905 by… https://t.co/xoEJyLbdjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like all the designers in the city came out to party on opening night of IDS West. This is… https://t.co/aPLsDkE4Mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The underbelly of the Cambie Bridge, built 1985. Such a large and surprisingly graffiti-free… https://t.co/Ij2yoIVxPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site visit with Kori and Sara at Pipe Shop! We're looking to add some rad washrooms and a posh… https://t.co/16zxBm067G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Concourse Gallery at what for now remains as the Emily Carr University North Building.… https://t.co/fPSZm7S5bg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Red sky at night--sailor's delight. Red sky in the morning--sailors take warning!" Photo taken… https://t.co/fmgl1dl3FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the spirit of @cityofvancouver and @milkovicharch public engagement for Robson Square, this… https://t.co/zIDdmeyDOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empire Landmark Hotel, previously the Sheraton Landmark, built in 1971 by Lort and Lort. This… https://t.co/2CtrVhoSlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thea Koerner House (Graduate Student Centre) built in 1961 by C.E. Pratt and P. Kattfa;… https://t.co/YjRGCcSSjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2EGF8C72Sv

Go take the questionnaire before it closes tomorrow so we can have this in our city!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this gem in the lobby of the Hotel Georgia. "In the late 1980s Hughes revisited exploiting… https://t.co/YhlLbhPXPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern Archect mrallard and I are playing Cattlestar Galactica tonight. #bsg… https://t.co/fpsb5xKuRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Down in front Henriquez!" Lots of great ideas brewing today for Granville Island 2040… https://t.co/68dij1FYIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killer Whale Has a Vision and Comes to Talk to Me about Proximological Encroachments of… https://t.co/sMuvY8EYKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vanlawn getting closer to occupancy! Inside this reverse Tudor pattern are five squash courts.… https://t.co/zbg8tvNAry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an interesting detail. What do you do when your building has a wall where you expect… https://t.co/UeLbzVGSAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneak peek schematic rendering of upcoming renovation in the Shaw Tower. When built this will be… https://t.co/UAIIvdBQ5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BC Hydro Centre, designed by MCM and completed in 1992. Rumour suggests the glass top… https://t.co/P1IitEdylJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMO Theatre Centre by my awesome friends prosceniumarchid. The folded glass provides lateral… https://t.co/qnUztivuXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Le Corbusier was a frequent steamship passenger, traveling aboard the Lutétia, the Patris II,… https://t.co/gUyMpUHGDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know that Science World has had four different names? Or that the center of the sphere… https://t.co/559jRiIjPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver: "I want to be the greenest city by 2020." #vancouverarchitecture #vancouver… https://t.co/7ahhywxBs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This piece of property is at least as big as the Olympic Village itself and was largely used an… https://t.co/8t9P36K3UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an effort to save money, it was decided to repurpose the existing rail corridor into… https://t.co/vY3rKh3uQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#graffiti meets #dadjokes. This is what happens when a generation of angsty teenagers grows up… https://t.co/7QALJto48W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concrete column with rounded edges in Olympic Villlage station. The column was either formed in… https://t.co/IO73ZbnHWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This building is the oldest of the four and is described as having an Edwardian Baroque style,… https://t.co/W1fuFkmHCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site visit at #vanlawn with Greg and Kori prosceniumarchid :) the patterning you see on the wall… https://t.co/YOm7s1M8Zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These tours are not to be missed architecture lovers! https://t.co/EDkf9JOKmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiny boxes on the hillside. This is a real photo of what development looks like in… https://t.co/wEozU3upum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Royal Bank’s art deco skyscraper – or more accurately, half a skyscraper, was built to the… https://t.co/DjfcCH70O2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either this is art or that bird had too many tacos @gringoyvr last night #vancouver #gastown… https://t.co/HJeBj2OUMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found at 225 W 8th Ave #exposedaggregate #concrete #vancouver #vancouverarchitecture… https://t.co/ydpDGAXxjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luminous article surfaces in Toronto. Does this sound familiar Vancouverites? https://t.co/TxQ47e3ULH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This project is not "like" Digital Orca nor do colour combinations create a visually engaging community. Is it 1990? https://t.co/l3HMtJ6TRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Incensed at the prospect of a 65% rent increase in 1980, the residents of the 32-suite Quebec… https://t.co/cQHsRtEPLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a previous lifetime I was the president of the anime club at UW; maybe I was in love with the architecture? https://t.co/sDM6dkmu9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to "SMART CITY TALKS: Meet Vancouver's New Chief Planner".  See you there? https://t.co/ElyjOvqvoG via @Eventbrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic #dazzle mural by @scottsueme Previously occupied by the #vpd and now leased by… https://t.co/pyLtzim6B5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever added that light deserves to be shot. This, the second #hootsuite office, was originally… https://t.co/InatDgMaXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough day at work prosceniumarchid ;) #vanlawn cladding wrapping up at the moment. The reno… https://t.co/liOGoAXzv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey I can see my house from here! W32 is a market condo tower in the Woodward's development in… https://t.co/JW2hSeReht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landing at #yvr :) we're back baby!

#terminus #poopipe #breakwater #ionaisland @ Iona Island… https://t.co/0UMXcQPBCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#raildeckpark announced in Toronto will bridge over the tracks in the attached photo.

One has… https://t.co/IcoNBNpisM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This pedestrian overpass between Raymur Avenue and Glen Drive is the product of direct… https://t.co/An1xMhcOoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the early 20th century a roof shingle company created this pattern for wall shingles to break… https://t.co/yTQsaQvz37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From dad: most Vancouver nightmare ever? "We tried to move the Marine Building over to improve our view and accidentally knocked it over!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Traffic @ Shaw Tower https://t.co/EjiMRXckAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cranium-vibrating good time at THE IMPERIAL. @ Imperial Vancouver https://t.co/rYjqntbVvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockbuster Video: Coming Soon to Cambie Street! https://t.co/k7TCcUr6zD

Likely contractor having too much obscuring the windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Dr. Sun Yat-Sen Classical Chinese Garden https://t.co/eP2yHUeyUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beaver Lake at sunset; the aquamarine glass of Vancouver's towers were meant for these fifteen minutes each day. https://t.co/XxHh4WlAGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Goldiein604 I liked "Condo boom comes to the industrial sector" piece; a friend wrote a thesis on this topic if you'd like to seeing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gray_Magazine I recently did a series of blogs on this topic for @pricetags if you are interested I can connect you with them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver: the greenest city by 2020?

https://t.co/YBZVyDtLYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Candid interview with @LanceBerelowitz @pricetags https://t.co/5qhYCCqsLq https://t.co/w1S9xPI5Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Vancouver's buildings unnameable? https://t.co/PWQuEaNjQf https://t.co/5dbr9KNvNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing really mattress. Found in mount pleasant on my walk to work this morning: https://t.co/pYlzslWH3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urbanarium They're already sold out! Will there be a line at the door for empty seats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for the opening of @Museumofvan "Your Future Home" today! Very happy to contribute my model of Vancouver. https://t.co/JIcjAh81tG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>