<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bizendal really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl psh why when I already know the answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelittlepakeha suck it tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole idk where I'm going here either but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole and like
Not looking and Not interested are probably more accurate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole but those things have more to do with the autism than the aroace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole like Ive some srs nopes around some things pretty central to romance and sex stuff and I'm ok w that and not looking 4 anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole being aro ace myself I feel u deeply. So much of that ident is wrapped up in not doing anything that doing anything throws shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole I really like the idea of relationship anarchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelleHopeBlog its awful, really very awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelleHopeBlog im in the same boat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelleHopeBlog there were some floating around before the election and the electoral college vote but I haven't seen anything more recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coldconstruct they're good chemical, brent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metropIex it's all just. Interesting. Hmmmm interesting, not ooooh interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metropIex I'm of the opinion the roguePotUSstaff is fake, because of a number of weird inconsistencies. That's not to say this one is true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting https://t.co/tXv1Qj7Ikx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@serenaswolfe it's so good I cried the whole last episode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heuristic7 @cannibality I've studied a LOT of stuff &amp; you can get a warp engine to do just about anything by spilling the right drink on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverCarle @Ali_GSDP part of me can't wait for 2017 to get wild
but then I remember who's the US president and I just get sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverCarle @Ali_GSDP what a world we live in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP @OliverCarle  none of it made any sense, but like
none of it was surprising, either, relatively speaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP like, the magic shit was like "hahah thats gotta be a joke" and then it wasn't and yet at no point did I think it was unbelievable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ali_GSDP nothing she does makes sense at this point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I wanted to watch a version of Journey Into The West, would Dragon Ball be a good or a bad option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@precariatqueer he thought "If it worked for Mia, maybe it'll work for me-ah"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amisamileandme sounds about right from what I've heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee :O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_queenoftonga @bekathrills well, thanks. I'm dead now, and it's your fault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cannibality like, if you turn up the Red Lights too high, without compensating with the Blue Lights, you'll accidentally wormhole to 1920s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntoniusMajor @amisamileandme aggressive expansionism which necessitated war to conquer needed resources, plus wiping out underdesirables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntoniusMajor @amisamileandme Nazi Germany would have collapsed without the war, but that's more because it was built on a foundation of &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amisamileandme the USSR but like
There are extraneous factors there as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cannibality my interpretation is that warp engines are basically most of the way to a time machine anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee S T A B H I M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 @creatrixtiara Russia? Is that like, part of Ukraine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 @creatrixtiara the only think Risk has ever done for me geographically is that I can still spell Kamchatka by memory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 @creatrixtiara I have difficulty remembering most of them. But somehow I can still remember where Gran Columbia was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 @creatrixtiara yeah and then theres Guyana, I think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 @creatrixtiara French Guiana?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliereed84 this is EXACTLY what's confusing me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee we call those rocky roads here, which is an enormous missed opportunity imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee among other things, they are the ultimate source of all queerness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee exCUSE we have them here too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jondauthor I tried throwing a $20 at the screen, but apparently amazon doesnt accept that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jondauthor I'm hoping to buy it on thursday, when I have internet money again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where
where do even i start here https://t.co/0NYr9reeBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nasa_dog im dying ace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writingforart @AURORAmusic I seethe with envy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwasnamedchris happy to help friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwasnamedchris nah bro, ur at least slightly above average]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl too early, for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwasnamedchris i havent nut ive seen a lot of pictures from it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwasnamedchris he IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chateura @trojieface oh dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kahlanamneII there is no chill here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole youre welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole Pharisees as proletariat vanguard? Levite as bourgeois academics? Samaritan as nonacademic following human dignity over praxis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micheinnz she is a good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastelprole interesting interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope had to fav from both accounts because seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon stepping on them is also organic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon gurl I'm like a replica of hadhafang from fellowship of the ring: pretty cool but not accurate to the source material]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ate too much at the wedding and basically now I'm dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kahlanamneII what a good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kahlanamneII he's so good I love him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin I intend on living long enough to guarantee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin it's not gonna look good for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin No One Could Believe It Would Happen Again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bootstheory Luther was awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee well, we can't take all of australia, but we can probably take a few]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee we should just
take all the people
and put them somewhere else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee that cant be good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee australia isn't a good place for as many people as live there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee so you had it whilst living in australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee well, mine was new at the end of 2011, and currently it can't be moved too much or it won't charge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee yeah, that seems pretty reasonable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee my uncle illegally installed it on my laptop when he bought it for me and I've never looked back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hasenschmerz @LeVostreGC i do nayt speake Waelsh, byt that sound ryte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_loulee ...oh, of COURSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeVostreGC should not hufelpuffe be moer waelsh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metropIex but it means "the time of celebration for those who love the banjo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl *eats popcorn communistically*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metropIex okay so the festival is "Hambindalismia" and the audience is dudes with beards that listen to banjo music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl @fancylettuce im chaotic boring, and ineffective good, respectively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce STOP CALLIN ME OUT LIKE THIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swarthy_swabs it's from my list of "Days the World Almost Ended"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swarthy_swabs the main consideration is deliberate intent to cause a nuclear event, with the knowledge this will likely cause an exchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swarthy_swabs unlikely. I'd love to do some traveling, especially for gaming, but money is. An issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swarthy_swabs yes. I'm definitely excluding mistakes like that. And Nagasaki and Hiroshima.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swarthy_swabs I wish my local GW was still open. I got a Hankering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS LEAVE HIM, HELEN I'll do for free, mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS I should hire myself out to just yell things at people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writingforart punch him and steal his pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS no, definitely not.  Mostly I just like yelling ITS A BAD IDEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS its a BAD IDEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS which is 100% a bad idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bekathrills im crying im so happy for you and hae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transboyvitya he has emails to check]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scarfacelaws @gurrlwithacurl ah, the boots with leggings combo. classic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merteuiI the prequels and the other sequels might be ok, but they were all written like 30 years after the original trilogy so ymmv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>