<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Think self-awareness is same as self-indulgence? Am sure you don't want to be like #Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonnyBenjamin If schools still produced citizens, #MentalHealthMatters would be significant, they produce workers now so diff priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarercgp Kindness left the platform a longtime ago. We are a competitive society, who has time for kinship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He just wants the White House. She is the one who wanted to give the present so she carries it? https://t.co/lWIby96uYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is all you need. https://t.co/4dY6p5ReW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the liberal left going to wake up or continue in its delusion, berating others? #Trump #Politics #Psychotherapy https://t.co/Kbo7sY9Y66 …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the past year teaches us anything, it is not to take our freedoms for granted. Don't be a bystander, be active in changing your world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonnyBenjamin Painful, isn't it? Recognising &amp; accepting that reality will help you to change it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our mind isn't a thing but a process. When you affect someone deeply, a piece of your mind stays with them &amp; you. https://t.co/n4zLbdkq7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We use substances to escape suffering. Suffering is a part of life &amp; needs to be endured. If you're escaping life, what are you living for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess the Qatari Investment Authority need that money more than the workers? https://t.co/jpp0yfebnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the House for? https://t.co/7mhu7vjetU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reach out. Gain help. Continue to bring yourself together. Don't give up on yourself &amp; return to ways that you know are unhelpful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Not sure I follow your argument. Imagine the study is signif. 'cos antidepressants sometimes promoted as reducing risk of suicide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdithSurrey Perhaps results of first are in one's face, provoke fear, deemed legit but the 2nd are more abstract so easier to disregard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is all we need. There isn't enough love in the world. What are you doing to ameliorate the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder why India's Minister for women @Manekagandhibjp links publicity about rapes to the impact upon tourism? Which is more important?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychotherapy is about learning to know &amp; understand life, especially its dark corners.  https://t.co/kektB8ZXkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do some deny other people's reality? https://t.co/RM9VvUbu0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all that has been on display the past few months, can we still claim to live in a kind &amp; gentle society? https://t.co/pHoB2eh9ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Prince Harry's statement condemning racial undertones of intrusion into his rlsp, do we still think we live in a post-racial society?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Bingham's son writes to @TrussLiz. #wheresliztruss https://t.co/MhQicrWddH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear Hear https://t.co/kGtyBko8Bh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Observe what is happening &amp; let it sink in. https://t.co/zcTpBo4xyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MazzucatoM Must feel good to have their country back so they can abuse strangers in response to a request for common courtesy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero for modern times https://t.co/Gof9s5GvRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We really need to learn more about life... https://t.co/1BkDP5rB06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What voices do you hear? https://t.co/VhUZqI9ad4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes people claim the depiction in I, Daniel Blake is not real? https://t.co/xksL047NB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who were doctors &amp; teachers in Syria &amp; Libya y'day are homeless refugees today. Is that message of precarious lives what frightens us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessBerryHart @vicderbyshire Good luck. I hope you are treated better than some others recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all are responsible for the energy we create in the world. https://t.co/tse7FmmSXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaiWaddingham I would say in a sick society, we are all sick. First step to the cure must be to realise our common sickness w/o projecting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering about the pardon for gay men who stood up for themselves. Isn't it a bit like forgiving freedom fighters or suffragettes? Apology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you speak of your soul or just do small talk? Why do we hide so?https://t.co/SK1exJNvDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we all focussed on changing ourselves, the world would surely change. Difficult though, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it true that we "should always just be ourselves"? Surely self examination is necessary 'cos Trump is being himself &amp; it's not ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ukschizophrenic congratulations and Very good luck to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some important questions for all here. I don't agree that others are always the same &amp; constant but mostly I concur. https://t.co/R57D4MZYx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religion, myth, magic, nature, feelings and relationships together with rationality make life worth living https://t.co/7sWEBN2tYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgbrownlow I imagine we try to maintain positive affect mainly in order to avoid troubling emotions. Does that sound true to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big thank you to @TessBerryHart for Cargo, thoughtful play about how close the world is to losing all that is good. Bravo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this an example of symbiosis? IS kill, Sky hammer home the message of terror &amp; hate? https://t.co/0jcdSR4J6V …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More proof of #EUref being anti-establishment from all these champions of workers' rights. https://t.co/CbwbbybjK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EUref was anti-establishment. Need proof, just look at the total lack of reference to it in all the paper headlines https://t.co/FgxtuSK1AY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ian_Fraser @pollytoynbee So Leadsom saying Brexiter needs to be next leader 'cos the 48% don't count &amp; deserve to be abandoned? Good pitch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we a banana monarchy now? https://t.co/GocS8a2DIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's 1 psychological lesson from the #EURef for our pol. class, it is to take care with unleashing misunderstood unconscious forces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what #DavidCameron has to say about this? https://t.co/FgNFvFnCeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that London is under Islamic law, anyone know if it's ok to get married more than once? I'm bored of old #zacgoldsmith London?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone doing research into how much damage his campaign @ZacGoldsmith did to #racerelations and the #prevent strategy in UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is this ethically or legally acceptable?#BHS https://t.co/dkQgXi5pOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #parkrun are charged for using parks, I imagine industry will be charged for recycling their products soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone would think there was an agenda here rather than honest reporting... https://t.co/4UF85HZfkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychoanalysis is sexy! Let's shout it from the rooftops...https://t.co/oHOuMlFV2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASUWT Does this blog reveal the real reason for all schools becoming Academies? To ban strikes? Really? https://t.co/W99mm7fOUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tories bullying &amp; manipulating the whole country, all for narrow political reasons? https://t.co/W99mm7fOUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we live in a sane society? This film raises a few questions for workfare.. https://t.co/24ubkiWnRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a brilliant piece of writing. Hell is other people....https://t.co/cfcM8WzQAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to respond to one-sided programmes such as one from Stephen Fry on his manic depression so here we are: https://t.co/MKToYB9vsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@askdheeraj @SameiHuda To me, pts understanding narrative of their own lives is worth all cost. What else do we have in life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Sure. Nothing works all the time. Sometimes it is not meant to make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda If pts say that after a lot of digging sometimes years on, it makes sense then I go with that. Meantime they feel heard. Win win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda If we are patient, in time I believe it does make sense. That's what a lot of the patient movement &amp; psychotherapy lit says..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good attempt at starting a conversation between 'pure scientists' and psychotherapists.  https://t.co/Ho4iL27H9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is psychotherapy and do I need it? A brief animation.... https://t.co/eZBQ2MeA5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SageSilk RD Laing said 'treatment is the way we treat each other'. Perhaps they need to be asked why the treatment is so harsh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Of course I believe in recovery &amp; that hard work is needed on all sides. Wondering about the lessons for the NHS in this, if any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda What do you think of his recovery? What helped? Do we know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grounding and focussing training in Manchester with someone who knows... https://t.co/Qa6o5Bvr6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddoggie2 An eye for an eye makes the whole world blind, comes to mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frozenwarning @SameiHuda @OCDTrudy LOL. I'm against harm to patients but also fundamentalism &amp; scientism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frozenwarning @SameiHuda @OCDTrudy has repeatedly said she's been helped by the holistic approach taken. Listening to patients is useful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frozenwarning @SameiHuda @OCDTrudy It would seem to me some of us r more open to acknowledging expertise in others. How about respect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A well written piece on the co-existence of the devil &amp; the angel inside us. https://t.co/7x6nyctEum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only we could actually learn to think &amp; manage complexity rather than rushing into aggression through action. https://t.co/1QKQBmdEbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think your relationship is uniquely problematic &amp; you should move on? https://t.co/LIa37Sln8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Medicine is a social science. Wonder how many doctors would agree to that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not prepared to work for satisfaction or examine yourself, what will you do? There's no App for happiness. https://t.co/k5UN7G59T0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SageSilk take care and good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we still in it together? https://t.co/3pnyXRUX53 #wheresJeremy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They know when to turn up to work!! https://t.co/zA4e4ztS8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An informative film questioning what is mental health &amp; how much we know ourselves. Worth the 8 minutes it needs. https://t.co/FmvX87buug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But do you know? https://t.co/TNlx252doW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandycann2 @SameiHuda @profjamiehh How about you tell us what you feel is the correct noun, after the supper?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they're unconscious, they don't want tea poured down their throat. Brilliant video on consensual sex https://t.co/sY5xe3bfNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PsychiatrySHO @lacanlune @vaughanbell We're being told current treatment not comprehensive or effective. Be good to move in that direction?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps it's all part of a grand strategy?  https://t.co/LubFUmdOJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda I just came out of my cave....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinnofTheShire @OwenJones84 @SuperVallo she trusted Cam. &amp; feels lied to. Sympathy for any1 in that sit. due to Tory lack of integrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Maybe that's a hashtag worth promoting? Perhaps start a mass movement asking him &amp; his team to join us at work to find out more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no 'App' to help you find out who you are or what you need in life. Great article.  https://t.co/k2shhHKJj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We really don't like listening to the message, do we? The fluff is oh so important. Poverty vs. the throne?? http://t.co/qUnedr1Yo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psycholdham @SameiHuda @d_galasinski @HviteOern As ever, issue abt working together to understand. 'Together' bit is what we're rubbish at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's to be a new Minister for Mental Health. Perhaps we'll have some equity now with other health concerns. Brilliant idea #Corbyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle, powerful and very real. Please watch. https://t.co/y4hpcPfxDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning or purpose in life, what are we living for? In fact, is it a life if there is no meaning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonnyBenjamin You might want to get in touch with Rachel here if you don't know about her already. http://t.co/DtlmBkRnhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think along these lines, perhaps psychotherapy is not the profession for you? http://t.co/MjcbEfSItu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameiHuda Isn't it? I would say all psy- professionals need to be philosophers &amp; work with patients to understand their lives &amp; distress.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>