<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trillything Give him enough rope...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New US Secretary of State gave touchingly respectful, humble Day 1 speech to the 75k members of dept. And with some humour. Smart guy. 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trillything Can't see him there in two years. He will go, one way or another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trillything We shall see. I cannot believe this madness can continue for long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am heartened to think that every day that passes brings us closer to the next US president. There is no way Trump will be re-elected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We agreed on 1250 asylum seekers - not thousands of illegal immigrants. Getting facts right is essential, Mr Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers -3, Unfollowers - 0. I didn't know I was this awesome. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump set to ‘eliminate arts funding programs’, cutting off NPR and PBS https://t.co/Otc3cPn7rJ An appalling prospect for the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 2 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone needs to tell new US president Trump that President Obama already brought back American jobs. New president uninformed!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The women’s march in Washington was roughly three times the size of the audience at President Trump’s inauguration, experts say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust me, I'm intelligent" sounds as trustworthy as "Trust me, I'm a real estate (or car) salesman".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he might have lost his memory, or still be in denial. https://t.co/gDws5YSUlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 tweeps followed me in the past week. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 weekly followers. 3 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump’s First Term https://t.co/TzGSpuldqF via @eosnos This is worth another read 10 days before it all begins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the latest episode of @April_Pressler on @ https://t.co/EiSY7XDzRk #AusAirplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @April_Pressler (Saturday 7/1/17) on @ https://t.co/EiSY7XDzRk #AusAirplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 3 more followers in the past week. Get your stats right here https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NYE coverage of Sydney on ABC is embarrassingly bad, the worst in history. 
Dreadful cringeworthy television. What on earth's going on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 5 followers in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the latest episode of The Pressler Project on @ https://t.co/Xx2DVcGeC0 #AusAirplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Progressive_Con A new Conservative party may have to compete for their 5 per cent with the PHON too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely Cory Bernardi's Australian Majority is a joke? He'd be lucky to get 5 percent of voters. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@AFP: After eight years, Barack Obama finally gave vent to his frustration with Israel https://t.co/bLT0r6mevm"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oqpbhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gained 4 followers in the last week. You? Know your stats and grow with https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 6 new followers in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@AFP: Ukraine offers Trump own jet after Air Force One flap https://t.co/8mZfJo6yTT"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 4, Unfollowers - 3. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickessler Great to find you by chance today! Hope all going well with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 1 new follower in the past week. I know them via https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past week - 5 new followers and 9 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Nakkiah Lui and Terri Butler are terrific - and spot on regarding 18c #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Turnbull Govt is responsible for funding cuts to resources to counter DV #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 3 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past week. Thank you https://t.co/7yyn8FukEX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oqpbhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two metre high tsunami hits NZ South Island following 7.9 quake 80km from Christchurch. No casualties reported so far. Fingers crossed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oqpbhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my playlist for the latest episode of The Pressler Project today from 4-6pm on FM99.3 @ https://t.co/gQuuNWqeFw #AusAirplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Putin must be very happy about the US election result.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@michaelh992: #Breaking: Podesta: Clinton will not speak tonight."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@JaneCaro: Well, women, POC, LGBTQI people, atheists, immigrants, climate activists - at least we know where we stand now."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@DrRimmer: Top Trump-Backing Senator Declares the Trans Pacific Partnership ‘Dead’ #TPP https://t.co/5zHMbTmqpy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Colvinius: you know who else came to power without winning the popular vote"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@wendy_harmer: Swannie was on the money here... https://t.co/CTpSgOjhP4"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@BrightLikeA442: No. She had the policies and the experience. They wanted ratings and a reality show. https://t.co/P1o3AEQyT5"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Mareeoh: @Mareeoh are we seeing the beginning of the fall of US?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@AP: BREAKING: Trump wins Pennsylvania. @AP race call at 1:36 a.m. EST. #Election2016 #APracecall https://t.co/Sqkx3T2F67"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@davrosz: Today's been a bit rough, so I'm just going to cheer myself up by watching The Day After Tomorrow."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@GeorgeMonbiot: Trump in the White House, Republican control of both houses: the implications are off the scale."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 9 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@barriecassidy: Fascinating to see how we deal with American refugees arriving by boat."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@bpolitics: BREAKING: Hillary Clinton projected to win California https://t.co/twHWnEWTJ7 #ElectionNight https://t.co/Qiscsark7n"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@workmanalice: Everyone needs to calm down. @AntonyGreenABC hasn't called it yet. https://t.co/ba9sMWZye7"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@MikeCarlton01: This election is looking very dark. If Clinton scrapes in, Trump is perfectly capable of wrecking the joint."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the latest episode of The Pressler Project coming up today 4-6pm on @ https://t.co/Wa5tp0eR3y #AusAirplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 3 new followers in the past week. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda John Howard started this appalling treatment of asylum seekers 20 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda The purpose of this proposed legislation is to wedge Labor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition unhappy at new ABC pay deal: not tough enough https://t.co/o2NAyFOofb Nasty Govt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 2 more followers in the past week. Get your stats right here https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is showing his lack of knowledge and weaknesses in the third #PresidentialDebate. He is a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 2 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/7yyn8FLW3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/YlZ1oq7Aqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Turnbull Govt is scared to have a vote in Parlt on same sex marriage #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Watts, Ged Kearney and Richard Di Natalie have been a breath of fresh air on #qanda tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Role models and language from leaders play a big part in ensuring respect for women. #qanda]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>