<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews We need a leader like Mr Trump in the UK to clean this country up street by street, house by house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph There is no confusion. Another lie from the Lying Press. The new rule is very straightforward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews 1.5 million signed the petition - how many of them are postal voters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Mr Trump should visit Rotherham to see what might happen to the US if he doesn't ban them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphTech Breed as fast as possible, take the country over innit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@royalsociety Many people don't seem to understand the importance of Mr Heaviside and Mr Faraday. We must resurrect them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Another reason why State funded education should be abolished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Whitehall regime has a cheek thinking it can tell people how to raise their kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Ban the burka. No more mosques that preach hatred against Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews A British citizen then rather than an actual Briton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews It isn't controversial. More lies from the Lying Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Mr Duterte has the right idea. He is cleaning up his country street by street, house by house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews There should be a cartoon showing what might happen to the USA without the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Mr Trump's ban isn't chaotic. More lies from the Lying Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews It is very ironic that these perpetually offended people want to ban someone from coming to the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Whitehall regime doesn't give a toss about the welfare of the British people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Japs were interned during WW2. It is sensible to intern the enemy during a war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Shut down the mosques where the Muslims spout their hatred against us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Why are they all so desperate to get to the USA? There are lots of other countries on Earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Most predators have to show themselves just before they attack their prey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Rob Crilly obviously hasn't been paying attention. Mr Trump has said that he is going to destroy ISIS/Islamic State.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph If Japan couldn't beat the United States during WW2 then what chance does 'Islamic State' have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The next logical step is to close down the mosques. No more mosques!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Mr Trump should add Saudi Arabia and Pakistan to the ban list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Commie Merkel probably wants the US to experience terror attacks like Berlin, Paris, Nice, London, Madrid etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HerrDoktor10 @Telegraph The Conservative Party must be abolished as soon as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The judge is disobeying Mr Trump's order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Nadhim should definitely be banned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @DavidGauke America won't exist in 50 years time. It will be Ameristan. The White House will be turned into a mosque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @DavidGauke 'Let us Muslims into your country or we will blow you up!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelePolitics Taqiyya - Islamic deception. They claim that war is deception.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did the £530million go?!
https://t.co/QBk311BfXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph 'MP Nadhim Zahawi apologises for claiming taxpayers' money to heat his stables'
https://t.co/ysnDNjEKs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Zahawi treated the British taxpayer with complete contempt when he tried to claim for an energy bill for heating his horse stable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph He should be banned from the UK as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Why isn't Saudi Arabia on the list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph More lies from the Lying Press. It isn't chaos. The new rules seem very straightforward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Mr Trump will probably intern them instead then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph It is sensible for a Government to have an industrial strategy. Private companies cannot just be left to get it right themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@royalsociety 21st century students can learn a lot from this gentleman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use a genetic algorithm to help ensure that I consume enough micronutrients every day:
https://t.co/7IZJOOXZgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did the £530m go?!
https://t.co/e5YM9eKfBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't be long until the Dutch doctors are murdering disabled children too:
https://t.co/Eiv1PbCMjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews How did Dr Buttar arrive at that figure of £146 per patient?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews 'If you want a high-quality, highly convenient service, it costs a great deal.' That won't be the case soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews If Dr Buttar wants more money then he is free to go and work in the private sector full time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMurrayArt @Telegraph @TelegraphNews It won't be labelled. Just the same way that meat &amp; milk created using GM feed isn't labelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews GP have a conflict of interest because they are paid cash when they don't send someone to hospital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews GPs would be less stressed if they spent less time with their accountants hiding their money offshore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph What a load of rubbish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Just wait until Mr Trump tries to force the UK to accept imported American chlorine washed chicken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The next important step after BREXIT is to not sign any trade deal with the United States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Why didn't the Lying Press video include Mr Trump's response to the question?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The lorry driver should have been sent to prison for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclist_london The councils don't even know how many wood burning stoves are actually installed in UK homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The UK won't need so many teachers after BREXIT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph State funded education in the UK deliberately fails millions of British children. It should be abolished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews All of the Labour held constituencies should have new elections without postal votes being allowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good step forward for improving automotive safety:
https://t.co/aAOQjc76Ih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews All cars should be retrofitted with electric regenerative braking systems to reduce brake dust air pollution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews We need a national 'sewer' system for air pollution. Home gas boilers could pipe their exhaust into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews The solution is to capture the vehicle exhaust pollution in a storage tank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Any trade deal that reduces British freedom &amp; democracy should not be signed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph They are just going to bomb them to grab their oil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Remainers effectively want British children to be killed by Latvian murderers. All of the Remainers should be arrested &amp; punished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelePolitics Theresa May is going to stab the British people in the back again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews We need to build a wall around Donald Trump and put bars in the window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews Just wait until Mr Trump invades Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews We will build a wall around May &amp; Trump and put bars in the window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tumble dryers should have fire extinguishers built into them by law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unacceptable behaviour from fire risk company Whirlpool: 'You may continue to use your tumble dryer whilst waiting for the modification']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @TelegraphNews The British people are being suffocated by the Whitehall regime. The Whitehall regime is the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lamb051982 First Mr Trump said it would be a wall and then he admitted that some of it would be a fence. Mexico needs its own full wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The rest of the world should build a wall around the United States to contain the American terrorists there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinusRexmar1 @Telegraph Mexico should have its own wall. The American wall could have doors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Southern Rail management should be arrested and punished for their bad behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Mexico should build a wall to ensure that American terrorists cannot enter Mexico. It works both ways Mr Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Mexico should build its own wall to keep the American terrorists out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scientists4EU BREXIT - whatever it takes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Releasing any pollution into the water or atmosphere should be illegal:
https://t.co/wFnDiSxiLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More lies from the pro-EU Lying Press:
https://t.co/j9NGMxa94c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Railways, energy, telecomms. water, steel etc should all be nationalised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Euro currency will collapse pretty quickly after the UK has left the EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Lying Press has been told to blame wood burning stoves for political reasons. We all know the real reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Politicians shouldn't be allowed to employ relatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph There is nothing to negotiate. We just leave the EU and build a successful independent Great Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Labour Party crooks. They should all be arrested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph John Lewis needs to sort its customer service out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now homeowners in fracking areas face having to spend thousands of pounds for a radon proof membrane installation:
https://t.co/pn2eSBWSTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph A country without borders isn't a real country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Does mean that £530m has been stolen from the company?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did this occur due to the privatisation of railway track maintenance? I no longer use the railway because of this.
https://t.co/Iw3WO01tv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Most of their spare time is spent talking to accountants to work out how to avoid tax using offshore accounts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph Why not just buy toys and holidays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph It should be illegal to release pollution into the atmosphere. The vehicle emissions should be put into a storage tank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph I use titanium coated cookware. It is virtually non-stick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph There must be a better solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph The Whitehall regime has to get the extra homes for Muslim families to breed in somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph More lies from the Lying Press. A Yougov poll is not representative of the whole population of Great Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These puppies were very lucky:
https://t.co/1D6M9vtk4C]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>