<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Louvre visitors learn of attack by loudspeaker, told to sit https://t.co/kXfkuh5F2Q https://t.co/B2RMuQGAHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Iran Treads Cautiously With Trump. So Far." by THOMAS ERDBRINK via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/R3uUQntDdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump administration imposes new Iran sanctions, warns more may follow: https://t.co/i5oWpxO8Fx https://t.co/ynfcQ79ypg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: MORE: Iran says new U.S. sanctions violate legal commitments and U.N. security council resolution that endorsed nuclear deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: JUST IN: Iran to impose restrictions on U.S. individuals, entities helping 'regional terrorist groups' in retaliation to U.S. sanc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump issues orders to review banking law and retirement advice rule: https://t.co/BJvDNUWhig https://t.co/fYXEwC2iz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump administration reviewing Cuba policy: White House spokesman https://t.co/6OQh61X48q https://t.co/NrdHArg5b7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: RT ReutersBiz: Trump's immigration ban risks undermining business-friendly policies like deregulation and… https://t.co/sroCkyDqbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Transgender court hearing set amid fight over Trump nominee https://t.co/tkNG0fJ0bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: BREAKING: White House says Trump administration is reviewing Cuba policy: https://t.co/mt6fBX7gkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Eleven arrested during protest against conservative comedian at NYU https://t.co/72uE5P46E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: 'El Chapo' lawyers complain about strict New York jail conditions https://t.co/GbS0gO35qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. CEOs meet with Trump amid tension over travel ban, taxes https://t.co/NEkX4kSn4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What You Need to Know About Trump’s Statement on Israeli Settlements" by ISABEL KERSHNER via NYT The New York Tim… https://t.co/srRj2icyUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump to issue directives targeting Dodd-Frank, retirement advice rule https://t.co/VjoGMEDHCs https://t.co/zO9aOQJ0Iq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Reuters Select: From how expected visa changes could hit Facebook, to the asylum seekers in limbo in Aust… https://t.co/rRMINCv4dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: More than 100,000 visas revoked amid Trump travel ban: reports https://t.co/S4gk3gA7DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Exclusive: Boeing's space taxis to use more than 600 3D-printed parts https://t.co/1ImAXzO6w4 https://t.co/6n5sC5REQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: BREAKING: Over 100,000 visas were revoked as a result of Trump's travel ban on seven countries - report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. sends Navy destroyer to patrol off Yemen amid Iran tensions: officials https://t.co/9Ac6HRuQuL https://t.co/9W9jOUGCC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump’s Granddaughter, 5, Sings in Chinese, and China Swoons" by JANE PERLEZ via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/OxCJxWivjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Iranians fear attacks and economic isolation as Trump gets tough https://t.co/zaqKzGTBeD https://t.co/KYvIskvlLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier shoots, wounds machete-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre https://t.co/RanuMXTgtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump aide cites 'massacre' that never occurred to defend immigrant ban https://t.co/wRP7850AVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: LIVE: CEOs meet with Trump amid tensions over policies: https://t.co/4IBljaIhct https://t.co/bqqJQ3Pzfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["U.S. Imposing New Sanctions on Iran Over Missile Test" by GLENN THRUSH and DAVID E. SANGER via NYT The New York T… https://t.co/UC7EHTqRYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. warns North Korea of 'overwhelming' response if nuclear arms used https://t.co/ndqogPX0V1 https://t.co/CZbqYFCb4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Louvre visitors learn of attack by loudspeaker, told to sit https://t.co/aYC0sa3iqk https://t.co/Pc5fpnoyx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Jim Mattis Says U.S. Is ‘Shoulder to Shoulder’ With Japan" by MICHAEL R. GORDON and MOTOKO RICH via NYT The New Y… https://t.co/gyyTuGLY2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Travel Ban Drives Wedge Between Iraqi Soldiers and Americans" by DAVID ZUCCHINO via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/lL7cW5aKXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: The First 100 days: Expect Iran sanctions and financial regulation cuts https://t.co/ir7DJ3ZVPz https://t.co/p9a8tRtwxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Oil Spill Near Chennai, India, Threatens Wildlife" by SUHASINI RAJ via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/VG2obYT4gX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[artofwar_suntzu: Thus the good fighter is able to secure himself against defeat, but cannot make certain of defeating the enemy. - #Tactica…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For Quadruple Amputee, Year of Illness ‘Was the Most Brilliant’" by KIMIKO de FREYTAS-TAMURA via NYT The New York… https://t.co/gOoaffEEFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Wonderful Tonight: Taking Kim Jong Un's brother to a Clapton concert https://t.co/LluGBRG89p https://t.co/17rDDwL2L4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Euro may be too weak for Germany but too strong for others https://t.co/vnuNQ3Gv5a https://t.co/tQwFuG7yUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Japan readies package for Trump to help create 700,000 U.S. jobs https://t.co/RuAaNzpAPG https://t.co/ketQYpXaft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. CEOs to meet with Trump amid tension over his policies https://t.co/N8pMn02aIH https://t.co/p0MTmHWPBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man With Large Knife Is Shot At The Louvre" by CAMILLA SCHICK via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/y4vqTAYUcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump to delay rule requiring retirement advisers to avoid conflicts: official https://t.co/XnPsojeYHn https://t.co/qiNDzpAZXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: From settling settlements to asylum seekers in Australia, get your global headlines in the Morning Briefi… https://t.co/zWcu7rzpW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump adviser cites 'massacre' to justify refugee ban via ReutersTV https://t.co/Ee5Ao8oIXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Friday Morning Briefing: Trump unsettled on Israel settlements https://t.co/l82kfeKw1W https://t.co/paCanvVtZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Facebook vulnerable to expected changes in key visa program https://t.co/NQFFbt2UJf via ReutersTV https://t.co/fDfDXfzcCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. CEOs to meet with Trump amid tension over his policies https://t.co/plfQzBqwXy https://t.co/c5c6HeFM8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. to issue new Iran sanctions, opening shot in get-tough strategy: sources https://t.co/fTl0We6mB8 https://t.co/WaxCO1TrMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier shoots, wounds machete-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre. Via ReutersTV … https://t.co/OdVegcZBws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. technology startups panic over immigration ban https://t.co/4l5UR4E1ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Wonderful Tonight: Taking Kim Jong Un's brother to a Clapton concert https://t.co/az1UDA6xZL https://t.co/MYXo7sTG7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: RT ReutersWorld: French soldier shoots, wounds machete-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre. See more: … https://t.co/oa6UIbsN9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Snap shoots for the sky, promises little in $3 billion IPO pitch: https://t.co/YASyLrP7bJ https://t.co/tSBteXK52j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: GE, Boeing, Oracle form coalition to support Republican border tax https://t.co/kfDqMWDWjA https://t.co/MCYT8Fxhex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Snap IPO draft is weirdly switched for GoPro's: https://t.co/gQNyxz4qug https://t.co/vuBjcRIAMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump to delay rule requiring retirement advisers to avoid conflicts: official https://t.co/KjCVCmFcDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. warns North Korea of 'overwhelming' response if nuclear arms used: https://t.co/nx3J85Dxup https://t.co/PWKYfSVwOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: White House says Israeli settlement building may not help peace: https://t.co/REOK3xfzl6 https://t.co/BbZDEmFoFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: GE, Boeing, Oracle form coalition to support Republican border tax: https://t.co/9p9wwus8gb https://t.co/1GoeDGAzIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier shoots and wounds knife-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre: https://t.co/xqcCSHUO2S https://t.co/EKCyYW8kzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: RT ReutersShowbiz: Angelina Jolie slams Trump travel ban, calls for 'compassionate America' … https://t.co/JmAQezpv3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier shoots and wounds knife-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre https://t.co/AiVhHyH4Y7 https://t.co/rUBB2OGr3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier fires on man trying to enter Louvre museum, man wounded: https://t.co/tJJQ3QcN8T https://t.co/jNCIwXZUhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Louvre Museum Evacuated After French Soldier Opens Fire" by AURELIEN BREEDEN and ALISSA J. RUBIN via NYT The New … https://t.co/JSCiUb61Z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fillon Scandal Indicts, Foremost, France’s Political Elite" by ADAM NOSSITER via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/bxeQEpMBPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Dollar recovers slightly ahead of payrolls, earnings support stocks: https://t.co/7V4ae2ctQw https://t.co/6QygiDlFe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Britain says Russia is trying to undermine West by 'weaponising misinformation': https://t.co/rq7AgsqIJi https://t.co/pQtVAwCnHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: North Korea sacks head of secret police amid signs of 'crack in elite' https://t.co/WU7WRJv0eV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. defense chief, in Japan, reaffirms commitment to defense treaty https://t.co/A5mfGKT1Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: French soldier fires on man trying to enter Louvre museum, man wounded: https://t.co/lvu4t8YavW https://t.co/mKDQ60pFFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Pence to attend Munich Security Conference, organizers say https://t.co/mtrvSRRxKk https://t.co/EeYgHXX71u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: RT ReutersWorld: BREAKING: French soldier opens fire after man tried to enter Paris Louvre Museum with suitcase - police source]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Japan readies package for Trump to help create 700,000 U.S. jobs https://t.co/bdRAWFphQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Oil edges up on threat of U.S. issuing new Iran sanctions https://t.co/L2Sr8g3QyS https://t.co/tfdce4ODx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: France's Le Pen to slap 10 percent tax on all foreign workers https://t.co/wIY1lMa3vI https://t.co/YIuTHgJDLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Australian leader faces long-term risk after 'Donald Thump' call on refugees https://t.co/C3ddb38BOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. watchdog agency to review implementation of Trump travel ban https://t.co/e7772k8JrQ https://t.co/ZI5eAwGtfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Nordstrom winds down relationship with Ivanka Trump brand: Bloomberg report https://t.co/cLRMt92Gvj https://t.co/vPLLGzsedR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Office of South Korea’s Embattled Leader Blocks Search of Presidential Compound" by CHOE SANG-HUN via NYT The New… https://t.co/7BF2HEKvHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[artofwar_suntzu: If he is in superior strength, evade him. - #LayingPlans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Asian stocks tumble most in two weeks after China tightens policy https://t.co/NToWnQKsi3 https://t.co/yTZrvHU7G1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump names former 'black site' prison operator CIA deputy chief https://t.co/CU0CzOaJ83 https://t.co/SJ8pZcOY9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. job growth seen accelerating in January, wages strong https://t.co/3UPYLWB1kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Critics decry Trump plan to limit counter-extremism program https://t.co/kQcnIWsWvh https://t.co/Tv1SJm31ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["North Korean Leader’s Top Enforcer Is Now the One Getting Purged" by CHOE SANG-HUN via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/ThgaavZhZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: North Korean defector sees 'crack in elite' in report of minister's dismissal https://t.co/WGmLSDSIKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump vows to end prohibition on church political activity https://t.co/K3LXodTTGH https://t.co/INO4EAzEkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: GE, Boeing, Oracle form coalition to support Republican border tax https://t.co/rUH9EK9IhP https://t.co/q9Oke9duB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Japan's robotics startup ZMP Inc hopes to list in coming months: CEO https://t.co/GXuRbehJKH https://t.co/8Egtl65Da4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Angela Merkel, Meeting With Erdogan in Turkey, Emphasizes Free Speech" by REUTERS via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/XjfqvAZQMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Reclusive North Korea dismisses key aide to leader Kim, South says https://t.co/zcNKuzYXtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. watchdog agency to review implementation of Trump travel ban https://t.co/aLAJdmANin https://t.co/zyLIW8torL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Nordstrom winds down relationship with Ivanka Trump brand: Bloomberg report https://t.co/4xlpxixLeD https://t.co/PfWe5MpYyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Coal rule killed by U.S. Congress, others near chopping block https://t.co/QI3aEWvX8a https://t.co/RRX5G1tfWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Discount broker shares tumble on price war fears https://t.co/DL0JA9wg0Y https://t.co/vQQIYMNM56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White House Defends Commando Raid on Qaeda Branch in Yemen" by ERIC SCHMITT via NYT The New York Times https://t.co/Zzv6X8MHIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Critics decry Trump plan to limit counter-extremism program https://t.co/qIC7KUY0Bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Trump names former 'black site' prison operator CIA deputy chief https://t.co/NvI6yARVDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. makes limited exceptions to sanctions on Russian spy agency https://t.co/0Zc3BFRh0h https://t.co/9DGn5MmH5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: U.S. warns North Korea of 'overwhelming' response if nuclear arms used https://t.co/JUCsZTL3KD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump’s U.N. Envoy, Nikki Haley, Condemns Russia’s ‘Aggressive Actions’ in Ukraine" by SOMINI SENGUPTA via NYT Th… https://t.co/NUuzEhr7v2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters: Exclusive: U.S. expected to impose fresh sanctions on Iranian entities - sources https://t.co/SnrRLNHBTZ https://t.co/I6hlzdx2gR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>