<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Does Anyone Write? https://t.co/XKZiNECNcf via @lithub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Get the government out of my fuckin' snatch' - Veep. Watch it. Perfect. Fucking pertinent. @VeepHBO #TrumpProtest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The summer holidays have passed so quickly! Many tasks completed, so many still do to! #teacherlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduTweetOz Last year I had Lite 'n' Easy lunches delivered from around Wk 6-a bit of extra time+healthier+cheaper than buying on the run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 221 of 329 of The Death Cure, by James Dashner https://t.co/4H218qK6yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 30 of 320 of Cloudwish, by Fiona Wood https://t.co/wivZQOEcqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought Side by Side: Essays on Teaching to Learn (Workshop Series) @AbeBooks https://t.co/hkaHttS7WY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[74% done with The Best Australian Stories 2012, by Sonya Hartnett https://t.co/YrubqhfrqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished with The Fantastic Flying Books of Mr. Morris Lessmore, by William Joyce https://t.co/NcP9wsKDER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG Matt Corby doing his best Ron Bergundy impression. #ABCNYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[42% done with The Best Australian Stories 2012, by Sonya Hartnett https://t.co/sGWCMAcMRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32% done with The Best Australian Stories 2012, by Sonya Hartnett https://t.co/4zzFj2NwxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 234 of 256 of The Book That Made Me, by Judith Ridge https://t.co/wcr4I5uWko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 147 of 256 of The Book That Made Me, by Judith Ridge https://t.co/lF1tUJwWVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 77 of 256 of The Book That Made Me, by Judith Ridge https://t.co/bQB0LMD1j2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50% done with The Sidekicks, by Will Kostakis https://t.co/FMkx1u5iwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20% done with The Sidekicks, by Will Kostakis https://t.co/zGBnBbEqL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought Monster Calls, A: Inspired By An Idea From Siobhan Dowd @AbeBooks https://t.co/Z1Fvtmn8cL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 272 of 384 of Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children, by Ransom Riggs https://t.co/makmjzhLmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just purchased 'I'm Supposed to Protect You from All This: A Memoir' on Fishpond https://t.co/rICnM0f3uY via @fishpond_com_au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this fun idea for how to give a Christmas book to your kid this year. https://t.co/7jAIvjpFuk via @kidaroundsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! This sounds so lovely! https://t.co/gWsnFNuFS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought Pop Sonnets: Shakespearean Spins on Your Favourite Songs (Hardback) @AbeBooks https://t.co/K1lF7ITl3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports. Are. Finished. #somuchreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is always 'books'. #familyfeud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tenet - any opinion, principle, doctrine, dogma, etc., especially one held as true by members of a group. #coolwords https://t.co/i0QbKDiIwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“From little things” by @abcnews https://t.co/h5qQF6KQBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The magnificent 'Arrival' is a timely film about aliens and empathy https://t.co/mxS1HHlovi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought 99 Ways To Tell A Story: Exercises In Style @AbeBooks https://t.co/edNea1B7rO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#etapd has anyone seen my book (on the right)? An English teacher has taken a book that belongs to a fellow English… https://t.co/xtDbGMVEv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whartonag @ETA_NSW @vivimat78 Thank you. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @whartonag someone accidentally picked up my book! Do you think an announcement could be made? It looks like th… https://t.co/yBkCOS7IBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello English teachers - did anyone pick up my book by mistake? I had it to show at the end of my session on Creati… https://t.co/06pHfUz8AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacEnglishAUS @ETA_NSW I can't wait to wear mine next week at school!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My conference spoils! #etapd #booksbooksbooks #teacherlife https://t.co/AKYhzlYIyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't realise that I chose lots of sessions on writing-they've all been fantastic! Adding to my writing toolkit! #writewritewrite #etapd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like English teacher reunion day! It's so nice seeing people I've studied with, worked with, and HSC marked with. #etapd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploration of SH5 and VfV in Preliminary Advanced English: Ideas are Bullet Proof #etapd https://t.co/1cgVVozn4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left three hours ago but we made it to the 2016 ETA Annual Conference! I'll try to be less dishevelled tomorrow when I present! #etapd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 Writing Tips From My 15 Years As An Author via @forbes https://t.co/hsyyX0tjLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read my tale on #TaleHunt https://t.co/Wk1xzF6ng7 https://t.co/GndS57rxQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinElizabee this is the best articulation of our reality! Right on! #facepalm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read my tale on #TaleHunt https://t.co/FqbccKQaCB https://t.co/i0Rknzl1Jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took the quiz "What Kind of Book Cover Are You?" &amp; got "Boy, Snow, Bird". https://t.co/67Ft7kQ11X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In English teaching is there a canon of rhetorical devices? How obscure is too obscure? https://t.co/xPZA37iL8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 250 of 359 of The Scorch Trials, by James Dashner https://t.co/kuyhhk5T87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Got: English Romantic . What′s Your Literary Movement? https://t.co/BXUZA1c394]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mars will come to fear my botany powers.' #TheMartian #mattdamon #SF #awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I need to read Pooh Bear again. https://t.co/lpzHmqatH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I've learnt at HSC marking this year? I want a denim jacket. #hscmarking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[55% done with The Female Eunuch, by Germaine Greer https://t.co/jNUO8kXpT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Got: Impressive! Do You Know What These Extremely Difficult Words Mean? https://t.co/To2wHg1Mil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read my tale on #TaleHunt https://t.co/9hfXEVRSkq https://t.co/PIUg36bDoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So honeycomb is covered in chocolate (Crunchie/Violet Crumble etc.) as a preservative. Delicious and functional. #interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many great clips! Short and engaging! https://t.co/rynACJacZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Four Keys to Helping At-Risk Kids by @SELinSchools: https://t.co/1ivRVf8c3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eeeeep! I just bought White Fluffy Clouds : Found Inspiration Moving Forward @AbeBooks https://t.co/b5yWcJlVXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34% done with The Female Eunuch, by Germaine Greer https://t.co/BnTgZ5TzGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting! https://t.co/Ebi6veYViO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[51% done with The Martian, by Andy Weir https://t.co/ZGcPh4RsjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to get a library card today! I'll be officially a book loving citizen! #yeah #allthebooks @penrithcouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 38 of 359 of The Scorch Trials, by James Dashner https://t.co/ES0QUZ2dIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shakespeare and Company: a 'socialist utopia masquerading as a bookstore' – in pictures https://t.co/u5hZOZHkGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second in trivia tonight! Whooo! #trivia #wentyleagues https://t.co/yA82NfJJlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proprietary eponyms:trademarked products whose names have become generic terms. #coolwords @LukeBartolo1 @talljill08 https://t.co/snkR2skPV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting. What Chinese corner-cutting reveals about modernity – https://t.co/jwoneXsO2q via @aeonmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting Time In Perspective - UPDATED - Wait But Why https://t.co/05XpOMJQpr via @waitbutwhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're Sequencing Every Member Of The Weirdest Bird Species On Earth: @atlasobscura https://t.co/EGnDFBZd3L @LukeBartolo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fantastic speaker! 'My year of saying yes to everything' - https://t.co/2NfmVOBNzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this as I tend to (wholeheartedly) agree. Teachers are not lazy because they “clock off at 3pm”. https://t.co/Lbh80N6bSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have approximately 1546 unused journals... I think there are a few ideas here that I can see myself using. https://t.co/rpTRWqv6aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came across 'Writing Maps'. I bought a couple so I can begin to create a writing wall! #classroomdecor #teacherlife… https://t.co/gf1dDjBAco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Better Reading Top 100 book list for 2016, well counted up in 2016. https://t.co/FVIO3eaMvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love a good list of books! This one is Better Reading's Top 50 Kid's Books of 2016. https://t.co/st2NukICX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortissimo - (a direction) very loud. #coolwords @LukeBartolo1 @talljill08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amorphous - lacking definite form; having no specific shape; formless. #coolwords @LukeBartolo1 @talljill08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effrontery - shameless or impudent boldness; barefaced audacity. #coolwords @LukeBartolo1 @talljill08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saprophytes - any organism that lives on dead organic matter, as certain fungi and bacteria. #coolwords @LukeBartolo1 @talljill08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 38 of 187 of The Chrysalids, by John Wyndham https://t.co/YhqTKo2746]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, @AndyGbooks would it be ok if I spruiked (with acknowlegement) 'Once Upon a Slime' at an Engl Teachers' Conference? You've inspired me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, that brisket burger! @FreightBar https://t.co/tQt0Co5uy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally awesome creative writing prompts from Andy Griffiths. Matching them up with the 7 Steps to Writing Success. https://t.co/cRyXh8lruU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes people have shit opinions, they're not valid, not worth listening to. We all know this. Discrimination should NOT be law. #ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifying, how dare we ostracise people based on who they're attracted to. #marriageequality #Lateline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debate is for issues that need discussion, we do not need to discuss the validity of others' relationships. Pass the law. #Lateline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On page 280 of 479 of The Knife of Never Letting Go, by Patrick Ness https://t.co/RcKABs2u3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliceleung @TeachersFed ohhhh I think I might go for a look in the holidays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torkee possibly a project - why it was necessary, what you did, positive outcomes. Also, working with a diverse faculty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! I am really enjoying Ron Berger's insights. I just bought Management in the Active Classroom  @AbeBooks https://t.co/nfJwnpgFOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought Poetry of the First World War: York Notes Advanced (Paperback) @AbeBooks https://t.co/783kzBOj3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought York Notes on Selected Poems of Wilfred Owen @AbeBooks https://t.co/KSUcz8bvpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness this is beautiful! Paul Kelly singing Shakespeare's sonnets. #love #paulkelly #englishteacherdream https://t.co/obpadbdgoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry Potter Literary Device Posters https://t.co/Pkor18zvKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn is actually quite hard to eat out of a packet. What do you do with all the broken bits?! #messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just donated to @OneGirlOrg, and I think you should too. https://t.co/qGlulznb8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once, someone told me that they had 'read them the riot act' and I wanted to ask if I could read it too... #ooops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kate_Mulvany has a very important underlying message - support the arts in Australia and get yourself to the theatre! #QandA #important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's always discuss plays and art. It's beauty and beauty keeps us alive in dark times. #Shakespeare #art  #QandA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmer_kylie @Kate_Mulvany that was just magical. Could listen to you both all day! #shakespeare #QandA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you #QandA this was a fantastic discussion with brilliant performances. #shakeitbaby #shakespeare]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>