<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to Catherine who won the #photocomp at our Sushi Workshop tonight! #LoveDublin @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/PXHGKr4C4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #sushi workshop is full to the brim of enthusiasm this evening. Here's what one person created. #cookeryschool https://t.co/xzwPvkmX4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @xantia8. It's such a fresh, flavourful salad, which can compliment a more wintry dish or be served as a… https://t.co/ghkNpKdRgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We want to share more stunning restaurant-worthy dishes with you from our 4 Week Cert Course students. Bellisimo! https://t.co/yxjLuiLghl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Known 4 intense and varied flavours, colourful decoration &amp; variety of spices Join our #Mexican Dinner Party 7-Mar… https://t.co/ybPWWpTeHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all set up for our ever-popular #sushi class tonight. Nori Rolls, Nigiri Sushi, even Sushi Balls. Stay tuned. https://t.co/hXNHQpBkN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last up with our 4 Week Cert Course students was Carrot Cake Cupcakes. Perfect with a cup of tea. @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/I6mocIgJ12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unleash the flavours of #Vietnam on our Vietnamese Workshop March 4th https://t.co/03bfma3k8R #dublintown… https://t.co/Bz0jSnEisq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapas is the collective name 4 small and delicious mouthfuls of something savoury Join our #tapas Course Feb 28… https://t.co/quAdA09bzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stirring in some BBQ sauce to our pulled pork on Pork Day with our 4 Week Cert Course students. #chefsintraining https://t.co/qqEYiUGX7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xantia8 @CreativeQDublin Wait to see how our students did. They have all come on so much. They're creating restaurant-quality dishes now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light and gooey treats #macarons are all the rage these days  Join our Course 28th Mar https://t.co/rx71CF6q8Z… https://t.co/4ZQRjciSj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmingWoman @CreativeQDublin @PaulGoatireland Goat is actually the most widely cooked meat in the world so perhaps that'll be next!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiemeimei @kwanghi_ @wildflourkate Great shot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pork Tenderloin stuffed with Prosciutto and Spinach and served with a Red Wine Jus and Hasselback Baby Potatoes https://t.co/HqBVJrfJql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No off-cuts. No short cuts. Just prime cuts" This is the complete sausage making workshop 16th Feb… https://t.co/1x6Y5IfqyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Salads 28-Feb Our course aims to teach you how to make the average salad quite special… https://t.co/BCBw8DxiAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to perfect dishes using only the finest local and seasonal produce on our #Gastro Dinner Party 18th Feb… https://t.co/5xNfWKKW0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a cupcake expert on our #Cupcakes and Icings and cakepops #Workshop Feb 14th https://t.co/oC7P5RcYrN… https://t.co/GIByLAgbNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're making cupcakes this afternoon. Nothing cheers up a Monday more. @CreativeQDublin #GBBO #LoveDublin https://t.co/STqfIwmADo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of how much our Cert students are coming along. This is a selection of some of the best @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/Thx2l4jah0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xantia8 @CreativeQDublin It certainly is. Have a look at our collage of a selection of the best dishes. They're coming on so well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allo allo! Our smooth and sociable #Bistro Supper Club with a distinctly #French appeal 17th Feb… https://t.co/n1D3MpHm2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliceNYRorganic @A_T_Kennedy @dcnyf Thank you for coming along. It was such a wonderful way to spend a Sunday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we made Herb-Crusted Rack of Lamb with Braised Leeks and Polenta Chips. It's Lamb Day today! @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/HR3Jqs3R5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Cookery Masterclass https://t.co/urdgWgqJXM https://t.co/RYzPdGzWjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wanted 2 be able 2 mark special occasions with a cake that has that "professional" look?Join our Course 8-Ap… https://t.co/Mp3VzuQsp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @thehappypear in their very special cook along class and learn 2 make nutritious,whole &amp; seasonal food 25th Fe… https://t.co/8SVdWTIvDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the start of Week 4 of our Cert Course and we are cooking Lamb. What a great way to start off the week. https://t.co/GBAzyuBnET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwanghi_ @jiemeimei @dcnyf Thank you so much for such an interesting - and delicious! - class. Let's do it again next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to cook contemporary yet tasty food on our Essential Cafe Course 6th Feb #gototown #cookerycourse… https://t.co/vfQUTQrtTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcnyf @kwanghi_ @jiemeimei too funny!!! Bought in Heatons 3 years ago for a tenner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a great chef through the mastery of cookery on our Professional Cert. Course starting Apr 3rd… https://t.co/cxJKOeQ3qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're adding dumplings to our platter of masterchef dishes demo'd by @kwanghi_ on our Chinese Cookery Masterclass https://t.co/JwcVg3DyZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucking into some dumplings on our Chinese Cookery Masterclass with @kwanghi_ and @jiemeimei @dcnyf #DCNYF https://t.co/ud241BhGnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our students were delighted to sit down and try the Chinese culinary delights from their Masterclass this afternoon https://t.co/wVoUxfTqBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are rolling out our dumplings on the Chinese Cookery Masterclass with @kwanghi_ and @jiemeimei @dcnyf https://t.co/qcT3N0ADVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our chefs @kwanghi_ &amp; @jiemeimei chatting to our students on the Chinese Cookery Masterclass @dcnyf @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/L8mfq00NjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwanghi_ has just demo'd the Vegetable Lo Mein on our @dcnyf Chinese Cookery Masterclass. Smells good! https://t.co/d5sH3dWZCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have Nigel, owner, of the Asia Market on Drury St to chat about the ingredients you can find there. https://t.co/q86pWDOTfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Salads 28-Feb Our course aims to teach you how to make the average salad quite special… https://t.co/f1Tifdt8ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aromas are really wafting through the school now! It's nearly lunchtime with @kwanghi_ @jiemeimei @dcnyf https://t.co/B8wDROdzKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Chinese food aficionados are getting stuck in to making their dumplings with @kwanghi_ @jiemeimei @dcnyf https://t.co/zdZNdLhtV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are loving this Chinese Cookery Masterclass with @kwanghi_ &amp; @jiemeimei as he demos prepping the hake @dcnyf https://t.co/9HadIsj3oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwanghi_ &amp; @jiemeimei are giving an introduction and meeting our Chinese food enthusiasts before getting stuck in https://t.co/imhiipP9Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All set up for our Chinese Cookery Masterclass with @kwanghi_ and @jiemeimei and @dcnyf this morning. Stay tuned! https://t.co/8CWvYZeH1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master the art of this age old Japanese trade,by making ur own nori rolls, nigiri sushi on our #Sushi Workshop 28Ma… https://t.co/3u14zUqppW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light and gooey treats #macarons are all the rage these days  Join our Course 28th Mar https://t.co/rx71CF6q8Z… https://t.co/qtKj7QaU3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all #Chocolate #Orange Lovers try my torte! Recipe in today's @IrishTimesMag https://t.co/CPPjoRWx3C https://t.co/38ujSJA0UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, he said #ANTS! https://t.co/HWLNUfaHEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unleash the flavours of #Vietnam on our Vietnamese Workshop March 4th  https://t.co/03bfma3k8R #dublintown… https://t.co/Q70xGUbDnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely days round-up with our Cert students and @mistereatgalway @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/vcDbqBaC6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xantia8 Absolutely. Keep a weathered eye on our Cooks Recipes blogs, which often feature recipes from our Certificate programmes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Salads 28-Feb Our course aims to teach you how to make the average salad quite special… https://t.co/DSNxihxIbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cert Course: Week 3 https://t.co/xMhhEYOYkv https://t.co/4NXBmCpDqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're loving this Cookery Masterclass with @mistereatgalway. Stay tuned for more gastro delights @CreativeQDublin https://t.co/q6RdeLnDnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistereatgalway is doing another demo. He is discussing the concept of natural flavour in food. Fascinating! https://t.co/FtAytjeASD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn all the tricks of the trade on our #Seafood Workshop on Feb 4th https://t.co/tx1361LMgw #gototown… https://t.co/cSEURqgmrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like to #bake? A client has asked me to find someone who loves to bake for in-store demos on saturdays.  A great st… https://t.co/0mleuzAin8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No off-cuts No short cuts. Just prime cuts"  This is the complete sausage making workshop all in 1 morning 16th Fe… https://t.co/HXJ7kPbgIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of doing a professional cooking course!  Take a quick look at Cooks Academy.  Enrolling now for Apr 2017… https://t.co/Fva4M7t5vD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last chance to enter our competition for a place on our Chinese Cookery Masterclass this Sun 29… https://t.co/Pz9QmweY3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoke brisket, ribs, hot wings and more. American Barbecue course 25th March https://t.co/ABjk5GYHvY #weber… https://t.co/v1wKO8N7AZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinTown Our Chinese Cookery Masterclass is going to be such a treat. We can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're just about to kick off our Masterclass with the one and only JP McMahon @mistereatgalway #cookeryschool https://t.co/MYV8qirCeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to it! https://t.co/NWLa20aZx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @thehappypear in their very special cook along class and learn 2 make nutritious,whole &amp; seasonal food 25th Fe… https://t.co/qtz3XcnFsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick of always having to opt for 2nd best meal choices? Join our #Gluten-Free Workshop! 18 Feb… https://t.co/iWvprGVYYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all set up our corporate this evening.  Looking forward to meeting the new group. #chefidol #Corporate… https://t.co/zwCoorfmOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xantia8 @CreativeQDublin Thank You, we have a great team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a round-up of today's activities on our Cert Course. Rib roast and Pithivier. #LoveDublin #cookeryschool https://t.co/zrcFQggHKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to cook contemporary yet tasty food on our Essential Cafe Course 6th Feb #gototown #cookerycourse… https://t.co/mnbmm3mjWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBee_Isabelle @CreativeQDublin A pithivier it is, indeed! A very scrumptuous pithivier at that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nathalydemey @CreativeQDublin Thank you very much. Warm and comforting on this cold #Dublin day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last dish of the day is a Pear and Almond Tart with a Creme Anglaise sauce. Warm &amp; comforting on a Thursday evening. https://t.co/soLQ1rX0fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're loving the pattern on this Pear &amp; Almond Tartlet by one of our Cert students. We can't wait to see it cooked! https://t.co/2wKDrTSEfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are u looking for a social and tasty alternative to take-away pizza at the weekend? Join our #Pizza Club 27-Jan… https://t.co/X8Oh9sTATv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #chefidol crew are really having fun this afternoon at the school. Raising a glass of wine to toast their lunch! https://t.co/6ir8zGIW5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A limited number of spaces left on our #Sushi Workshop 31st Jan https://t.co/WQsVh25axK #cookerycourse #dublintown https://t.co/s9AF3wJ2mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pan-Fried Hake, Pernod Braised Fennel, and Aioli https://t.co/2nHcRpl2Ms https://t.co/XlYYSVm7QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're looking forward to our corporate #chefidol event happening at 1:30 here at the school. #LoveDublin https://t.co/5fMpikKaQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace Italian cuisine at our Italian Dinner Party course! 7th Feb https://t.co/GRiCY2k6wk #italian #dinnerparty… https://t.co/BFE8ScscYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gautamnitin Such a great day. We look forward to having you back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A unique opportunity 24Feb 2 be taught by 1 of the Ireland's master Chocolatier's Benoit Lorge of @LorgeChocolates… https://t.co/dgXi7pTHhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Day 14 of our 4 Week Cert Course and it's Sirloin day today. @jackokeeffe9 is showing how to dissect it now. https://t.co/7kNfboyB7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We made Mussels Meuniere today with our Cert students. @CreativeQDublin #LoveFood https://t.co/lZnKKildwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a cupcake expert on our #Cupcakes and Icings and cakepops #Workshop Feb 14th https://t.co/oC7P5RcYrN… https://t.co/S4ArCzCimC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeeny_maltese I got a chocolate fountain from my work secret santa. Will (my kids) christen it with these!  Fab idea..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No off-cuts. No short cuts. Just prime cuts" This is the complete sausage making workshop 16th Feb… https://t.co/6KkMBWTxg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the fundamentals of #Cheese with Silke Croppe on our Cheese Making Workshop 8th Feb @CorleggyCheese… https://t.co/2iGLWNLGdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicy Tomato Sauce https://t.co/ujuQ5s3nvv https://t.co/drL88jjYlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to our fabulous Indian class today with @gautamnitin The place wafted of wonderful aromas all day long! https://t.co/smnrnB42ut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Deliciously Juicy' Learn how to cook the perfect steak on our Steak and 3 Sauces Course 7th Feb… https://t.co/SwT6UnUGmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What better way to eat tiramisu than cappuccino-style? Our Cert students certainly enjoyed it. #LoveDublin https://t.co/nBqgb86wiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JdeBurcaVegChef @RTE_ETTG @CostellosBrewCo @SecondNatureOil you were great on TV last night! Congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's lunchtime and our Cert students are about to tuck into the Fish Pie they have just made #chefsintraining https://t.co/1znkGSohYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all #veggielovers! We're offering a 10% discount on all #vegan and #veggie classes. Just quote 'vegbunny'… https://t.co/jzhFulNP6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready Amigos, to make your own mean Mexican Cuisine. Join our Mexican Dinner Party Mar 7th… https://t.co/8O7mNSZmzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch our #vegan chef of @CornucopiaRest @JdeBurcaVegChef on @rte Ear to the Ground cooking vegan food for farmers!… https://t.co/mjWfjhvzVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A unique opportunity 24Feb 2 be taught by 1 of the Ireland's master Chocolatier's Benoit Lorge of @LorgeChocolates… https://t.co/7tsFcjgJyu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>