<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP @SpeakerRyan In the future, when people study history, the will see how you ASSISTED @realDonaldTrump in destroying the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it matter after he destroys our country. @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls https://t.co/xREXBvXAQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder Oh crap, another Roy Moore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenTedCruz @SenShelby @realDonaldTrump THIS IS HEARTLESS.  Voters should repeal your healthcare!!! https://t.co/7YGjfxUz2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonHall46 @WesSmith123 @realDonaldTrump = Most. Hated. President. EVER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuzanKBuckner @Robert_Aderholt And Republicans just want to insist on babies being born, not fed and get medical c… https://t.co/PQ3cliLRnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregloug @Robert_Aderholt @POTUS Yep. Plain and simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Tens of thousands of Muslims have been killed as well or do they not matter? YOU HAVE NO SOUL.… https://t.co/0oyF6MbsTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have no idea how you have placed our country in danger. You played right into the game plan of… https://t.co/wW7K6kI5vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s34nsp1c3r Go compliment the Emperor on his new clothes.🤥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s34nsp1c3r Oh, I know! That whack job @KellyannePolls has stolen you phone &amp; she's sending out her "alternative facts"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s34nsp1c3r You are as crazy as your boss. God help us all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s34nsp1c3r Yeah? Well back at you spokesperson of a sociopath!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s34nsp1c3r @SpeakerRyan What is this? Some code demanding him to shut up &amp; salute the Fuhrer???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calmedseas @rolandscahill @realDonaldTrump @nytimes This is a dead little boy you heartless .....Christian????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers @MKRIZSA50 God I hope so! #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US is in chaos after 8 days @realDonaldTrump = FAIL  
@GOP Stop this monster! #WhereIsTheLegislature   #TrumpWorstPresidentEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Yes it has Senator Graham . Trump is out of control! Has damaged the US more in 7 days than any ot… https://t.co/HpbXkmKLxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nottinghams1 @TEN_GOP Sub human beasts?? What kind of a Christian are you? Westboro Baptist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenShelby @GOP you say you want to reduce big government, yet you want big government regulations imposed on women's reproductive choices!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paizogony @SenShelby And will there be increased funding for food and medical care for all these unwanted children?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StopPresidentBannon #TrumpIsDestroyingUSA @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls @SpeakerRyan @SenateGOP @HouseGOP #StopThisMadness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @SenateGOP @HouseGOP Help America! Save it from this monster @realDonaldTrump you got elected. God help us all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Blues @reifman @realDonaldTrump SB you're a real asshat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @GOP @MitchMcConell HOW COULD YOU HELP ELECT @realDonaldTrump HE IS DESTROYING AMERICA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegasgrillman @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump Yep. 20% inflation is just what we need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegasgrillman @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump Well, if you shop at Walmart, you buy from China. If everything you b… https://t.co/v4WjovH79A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegasgrillman @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump And, of course, you don't care about anyone who does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegasgrillman @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump Many GM vehicles and auto parts are made in Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegasgrillman Hummm! Since many of our goods are manufactured in Mexico....that means WE will be paying that 20%.… https://t.co/GwrQdHEk7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME @SpeakerRyan @SpeakerMcConnell Have you both lost your freaking minds?? Mexico will not pay for the Waaaal! A… https://t.co/zqHsg9lnJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham what do you think of Trumps considering the use of torture? @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjjoanna Not anything like that! And didn't consider the use of torture! 😛]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackieschaefer @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 America is the ultimate loser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Klaatu905 @daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Typical repug response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertCaresToo @YouTube He's reading from a book, not talking about personally "moving in" on a married woman "lik… https://t.co/4N77RfmH3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabetadamsa Wow. You OD'd on the Kool-Aid. #TrumpIsInsane #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabetadamsa Lizbeth you aren't getting many retweets maybe because #trumpisinsane #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @Dr_of_Nursing Thank goodness! Who knows what this #trumpisinsane would do. #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine @MTmarilyn2 PLEASE explain why Trump is OBSESSED with not winning the popular vote??? Is he insane????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertCaresToo Yes, of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All anti abortion activists must adopt and unwanted child! @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerRyan @MikePenceVP @MitchMcConnell @richardshelby1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertCaresToo Not sent to the First Lady. But I'm sure she has heard all this shit. She's married to the person who did this. #trumpissick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Klaatu905 @daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Typical Repug. Doesn't care about anything but gett… https://t.co/ZZnYRCAu32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Klaatu905 @PattyMurray You gonna adopt all these babies you are "saving". What? No??? I guess the REPUGS will just… https://t.co/omdQxr1sxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls It looks better than you! #kellyannpolls #ifherlipsaremovingsheslying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan #ReproRights #womensrightsarehumanrights #nowirehangers
Will you provide the funds to feed the childre… https://t.co/yirMfUjYX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trumpsobsession why does @realDonaldTrump think there were 3 million fraudulent votes cast in the election? I heard there were 4 votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paul_lander @ckkoch3 @KellyannePolls looks like she fell out of #TrumpsClownCar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristiChat @KellyannePolls My God @KellyannePolls you babble like a blithering idiot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OccupyDemocrats @KellyannePolls all that lying is make you dry up into a wrinkled crone. Try the #realtruth it will set you free!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMDILL1 @DearAuntCrabby @MELANIATRUMP your husband is s sexual predator!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you are sickening. Face it: you got 3M less votes and less people attended your pathetic inaguration! @womensmarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scaryanne Conway @KellyannePolls  don't you get so sick of scooping up the @realDonaldTrump shit?
#draintheswamp = #TrumpLies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maceman1605 @CecileRichards @womensmarch Better still, withhold sex from @maceman1605]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind I hope rump doesn't redecorate the White House with gold crap everywhere. #TrumpLovesPutin &amp; both… https://t.co/ch22PH3oJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump saving babies just to starve them to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan #VoteThemOut  Paul Ryan sold his soul.                 #draintheswamp #TrumpLies  @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/tKlVfiytfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC #VoteThemOut @realDonaldTrump #draintheswamp = #TrumpLie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alondra49094736 @LauraJWRoss You don't have a point alondra. You're just babbling like an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AWillieWood @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 I think that's for you . Careful, don't choke on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alondra49094736 @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss You sound and look unhinged Alondra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam Absolutely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam I drive a 2016 Cadillac CTS 3.6 &amp; the manual says no ethanol gas above 15%. I only see 10% around here… https://t.co/bnrTxnSzpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube Looks like you are in a basement Daby. Crawl out and get a life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baal_hammon_ @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 I've owned a gun since I was 11. I have a ve… https://t.co/vihyH8V3bG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baal_hammon_ @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 And soon you will meet Mr Smith &amp; Mr Wesson. 👺👅🎱🔗🔗🔗]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube Would love to chat all night but I have to work tomorrow. Obviously you don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baal_hammon_ @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Come on Baal-Zebub! Get out of Mom's basement and get a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube Millions are flowing into the Trump Regime for cabine… https://t.co/dBy7oC29pM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube That's ridiculous. No PAC or billionaire organized th… https://t.co/ir4NIwhQ6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube As someone educated in human behavior, it is clear to… https://t.co/NCenpNhMQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube I seriously doubt Hillary is organizing riots. This i… https://t.co/GQIj4EyN7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube From watching news from all over the world, not just… https://t.co/qSN9bcVa3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube Because of a decisive campaign and lie after lie. #TrumpFail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connormtn I've seen quite a few presidents but none who have caused riots in the streets on their first few days in office. #TrumpFail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube You don't realized how much Trump has failed this cou… https://t.co/jJhe8fkBoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daby0729 @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @YouTube You need another source besides the Trump channel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeplorableElle @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Age-hater much. If you are lucky you may live to be 60 which is not t… https://t.co/y4QVVzVZ0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heinzilla Bros in love! What a couple of asshats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam We have 10% ethanol but it's not much cheaper than the other grades. New car manuals say not to use it at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niceandtweet @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 The word isn't the issue twit. It's the sexual assault that concerns me… https://t.co/H7GKacr7QX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam And your point is? Never mind, it wouldn't make sense anyway. Who do you like in game 2? New England or Pitt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam What makes Iowa gas cheaper? Texas has refineries less shipping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam Yep! I 💕💕my Falcons. #juliojones &amp; #courtneyupshaw #RTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyMillam Dude. Can't you read a graph? And learn how to spell lying! LOL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough game #Packers #AaronRodgers #HaHaClinton-Dix #RTR #claymatthews Love you guys. Next year - the Pack!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Trump so hell/bent on moving the American Embassy from Tel-Aviv to Jerusalem? Is he building a new hotel there?#pokethehornetsnest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RiseUp the #Falcons and @juliojones_11 and #Coutney Upshaw are in their way to the #Super Bowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those #alternativefacts are lies and they are melting Kellyanne! @KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/tDYf0rzU9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liberalismislov @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 @realDonaldTrump No. #Trumpisaliar and it started from day one. We d… https://t.co/A71EtDoEBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baal_hammon_ @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Baal-Zebub? Ye have spoken out your arse once again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarriorDeplore @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 #DonTheCon laughing at you guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kriDan1 @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 Drink up that coolaid chump. Check back with me in 6 months &amp; we will see what's left of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baal_hammon_ @myno1doodles @thebkstylez @LauraJWRoss @CarlaBlankens12 I go to work luv. I've worked all my life an… https://t.co/TtJ7vvJ9h8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MONAKatOILS @WentzTheGoat @HowYerDurrin @wikileaks Yes we do. We have a right to know and a right to have a President who is not s liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apasionadochica What is trump hiding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myno1doodles Yep! I love football. Good luck to Pittsburgh. I'm kind of tired of NE winning everything. I like Atl… https://t.co/U8wcKcpj0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myno1doodles Congrats to Clemson. Great game. I'm a BAMA Fan. LOL! https://t.co/SkvBDGdNbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myno1doodles Deplorable. Absolutely. U watch football? Who do you like in game 1 #NFLPlayoffs?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>