<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGault11 can't wait to check it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched Trainspotting in preparation for the sequel this week. Forgot how harrowing Renton's rehab is. Astonishing scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This arrived today and it's an absolute romper. Big ups @youngmallgrab https://t.co/4lYi9IZptw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote about Chelsea's next 5 days - Antonio Conte's chance to avenge twin defeats to Liverpool and Arsenal… https://t.co/1b9sz32mN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer-Nadal plus the Williams sisters in Grand Slam finals and now Cena-Orton at Mania. Are we sure this is 2017 and not 2008?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Reigns ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbacon85 it's not, but it would be worth it for the Rumble haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Royal Rumble over Wrestlemania every.single.time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbacon85 oh, I've no problem with Cena. AJ Styles deserves more than a mid-card role at Mania though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AJ Styles is verging on being the best wrestler I've ever seen. Pity he'll be shoved near the bottom of the card at Mania. Punk was right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AJ Styles' theme tune is a certified banger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Velvet's 'Answering Machine' is one of my favourite tunes ever and should be one of yours too. https://t.co/k92oD1GEGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stighefootball Ligue 1's been bags full of fun this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies a Lannister always wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After weeks of consistent form, the real Roma returns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your dad's favourite acid house band appearing at the football. https://t.co/yb0iWn8O8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barca having their usual Sunday stroll in La Liga anyway. Because difficult games are the exclusive trademark of the Premier League.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer, Nadal, this era. Take a bow. Have to pinch ourselves that we get to watch this era. #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd happily watch Federer vs Nadal every day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there was one sentence to describe the Federer-Nadal rivalry it would be 'Nadal forces the error from the racket of Federer'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishGolfDesk Federer-Nadal plus the Williams sisters in grand slam finals, just like 2008. Back @padraig_h for the Open, so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FussballMundial it's very saucy indeed man. Belongs to my cousin. Unearthed a few gems from his collection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got hold of this absolute gem of a record. The Green Velvet remix is so groovy. https://t.co/0yjadKeinD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure there's Arsenal fans somewhere explaining why they'd be top of the league as well as defending champions if Welbeck had stayed fit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far, Antonio Conte has an 80% win ratio at Chelsea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Pulis' grandchild not impressed with Gareth Southgate's offer of a handshake. https://t.co/Cw2aeWD8Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Life of Lambert https://t.co/hQsdNlYkB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paolo Maldini is a freak of nature. Getting better looking with age. https://t.co/F3kDIQEZT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies well worth the 3 quid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The film in question was Birdman. Shouts out to Edward Norton. Special shit from him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corlelas nah, I stress about very little. My Netflix subscription isn't one of them lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I'm just about to cancel my subscription, Netflix uploads a movie that sucks me back in - the bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature I think I've met one person who actively didn't like it &amp; judged him. Told my uncle to watch but he couldn't understand it hah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature my guess is yes. I've watched clips since and the dialogue is peerless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature haven't watched it in 5 years. Will make time to either this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrHahntastic @Not_Rob_Palmer @TheFinal_Third @concalcio Catania's ground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer vs Nadal &amp; Venus vs Serena in the Aussie Open finals. 2008 me assumed they'd be playing in charity matches. What a time to be alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanliew that makes me a heartless dick too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recognise everyone wants a Federer-Nadal final, but I really, really, really want Grigor Dimitrov to win #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns, fascism &amp; a Scudetto: I wrote about Lazio's crazy 1970s team as part of @TheFinal_Third's #MonthofCalcio… https://t.co/o6jEAvGkHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priya8Ramesh went straight to the video version of Nikes on Frank's website haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty great. I now want to listen to Blonde again https://t.co/awdPI1TyY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wiley's new record is quality. So much great grime at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to admire Mourinho's creativity in finding ways not to conduct a proper post-match interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcbpf he still looks and dresses tops, so I'll give him a pass on the dad posts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry oh yeah man, absolutely. You could equally scrutinise both sides for it at this stage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry tbf, the same could equally be said for the regressives as well man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youngmallgrab happy #AustraliaDay m9 x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GentlemanUltra Gerson, but then I'm biased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GentlemanUltra's top 50 young players in Serie A is well worth checking out. Donnarumma +49 imo https://t.co/Pb1I9vFcfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #AustraliaDay. Any excuse to listen to Tame Impala, really. https://t.co/1r8X5skzQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corlelas yeah, that's probably fair enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl proper football man Tom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMortimerFtbl don't try and diminish anything Shane Long does, Mortimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Long sure loves that far post finish past German goalkeepers. https://t.co/iEKVyI0Kw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be going on there as soon as it's on Spotify. Absolute shirt remover https://t.co/SRxG9CHvdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfield_ things fall apart is one of my favourite albums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made this Spotify playlist of funky and groovy tunes a few months back. Y'all should listen. Swear it's good https://t.co/yNqXdPbjSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They go again https://t.co/0lnthi4KbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The League/CocaCola/Worthington/Carling/Capital One/EFL Cup is far superior to the FA Cup. Don't @ me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Long just did another Germany!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilippeAuclair the funny thing is, he'd have his say say in parliament, if he hadn't failed to get elected on 7 occasions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidpreece12 not ideal bearing in mind your new career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munnelly_ryan best not to dwell on it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skins is 10 years old? I feel fucking ancient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FA Cup offers Chelsea's fringe players a last opportunity to impress Antonio Conte. https://t.co/URSKprKKav https://t.co/b53zie255b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheball @davidpreece12 you're everywhere Preecey. Delightful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youngmallgrab was watching this Chet Faker boiler earlier. Is that you at 1:07:25 - 1:07:37 lol? https://t.co/pJAzkWS5re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Jurgen Klopp needs to solve Liverpool's problem against direct football in order to make the next step… https://t.co/ZH8BDBnie5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horan_james tbf, Leicester won by 11 last year, Chelsea 8 the year before that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbro7 Congrats are in order Brown!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_paras it's a contributing factor, sure. But it also shows that the other leagues are just as competitive imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most competitive league in the world." https://t.co/XeRgsjoCX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 2004 is my favourite, I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal are not worthy of Alexis Sanchez.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Granit Xhaka's role as a Charlie Adam style hatchet man is quite something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, he may not have got his own goal, but Wes Morgan has his say on the game by bundling over Shane Long. The man is fantastic comic value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offside preventing Wes Morgan from scoring the own goal of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youngmallgrab Big ups for one of the sickest gigs I've been at in a long time last night. You're a good one fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauloworldwide @TheFinal_Third @acjimbo he worked Costello song titles into all of the scores. Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of @TheFinal_Third's #MonthofCalcio, I wrote about a classic Gazetta moment when @acjimbo met Elvis Costell… https://t.co/nhNmwF0DVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies yeah, very true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's daylight robbery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, that's horrible for Lloris. So often, he's the man who digs Spurs out of a hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the way to break a record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoke beating Manchester United with a midfield of Charlie Adam &amp; Glenn Whelan. And they say the PL isn't the greatest league in the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I said Llorente might win Chelsea the league, just not in this way. https://t.co/PNRFOuk0Ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublin_damo yeah, totally. Looks like his AFCON departure could cost them dearly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They still should win, but Liverpool are having a lot of games like this recently where they've struggling against deep lying defences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDaisyCutter1 out. This, after watching Messi, Suarez and Neymar. He had nothing better than that to write]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDaisyCutter1 my favourite JJ moment was after City were beaten by Barca two years ago and he wrote about players that City would clear..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDaisyCutter1 what's he done this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen so good, innit? Being in the studio with James Murphy really shows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On an excitement scale of 1 to 10 for @youngmallgrab in Dublin tomorrow night, I'm at an 11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're living in Ireland, he's literally not your President, mate. #Inauguration https://t.co/Z7TGgPRxH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature so baffling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz yeah, two of my mates missed out through laziness - and I warned them as well. Sympathy for those who got messed about though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz *got a ticket btw* no regretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz "Run the who? Are they one of them college American football teams?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouts out to @3FE for the nicest coffee I think I've ever had in Dublin. The hype is real. https://t.co/2gcVJNx5d6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>