<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[First the rust, then the reality of being overmatched as #Canucks fall 4-1 to #Sharks. https://t.co/AJ4M8fYPjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good break for Larsen, who has had a rough night. Point shot deflects off Martin. 3-1. #Canucks #Sharks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double-whammy for Stecher. Crunched by Thornton and Hertl along endboards to lead to Burns goal. 3-0. #Canucks #Sharks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horvat needs to work on his soccer skills. Couldn't kick puck up from right skate after dancing around Martin. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks won 74 per cent of first-period draws yet looked totally over-matched. #Sharks up 2-0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't clear puck around wall, point shot, room-service rebound by Miller, Larsen can't tie up Tierney. 2-0. #Canucks look overmatched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFA Marleau, 37: “I have an idea how far I’d like to go and a 40-year-old player is not uncommon anymore. #Canucks #Sharks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. 500 for Marleau on PP. 1-0. #Canucks #Sharks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy zone exits for Sharks, first on pucks, two mad scrambles in front of Miller. Lots of all-star break rust in #Canucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Miller's contract future buoyed by being in a good place on, off ice. https://t.co/9Llo2dPltb #Canucks #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hansen wearing knee brace, taking alternating line rushes. Said before taking ice he expects to play Saturday against Minny. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more time - with feeling. https://t.co/SmsKgy07v4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howie got it. Think global, write local, teach kids life skills. https://t.co/LtXaSRzhgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget giving you that broadsheet page in KDN at '93 Canada Summer Games because you were pumped about somebo… https://t.co/sdy0taocRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record, #Canucks match shot futility, coach calls out lack of passion in 3-0 loss to #Coyotes. https://t.co/inAoODev7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaput puts loose puck right on Burmistrov's stick for PP gift. 2-0. #Canucks #Coyotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Smith makes left-pad save on re-direct, Crouse muscles his way for wrap-around effort to open scoring. #Canucks #Coyotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, Burrows is credited with first shot at 8:12 of second period, a 122-foot shorthanded clear out of own zone. You can't make this up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That retweet was in reference to Dec. 23 no-show in Calgary. Fourteen shots. https://t.co/chnJHPvWpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The poll is back on. The first #Canucks shot will "officially" be credited to .... ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks did have 13 first-period shot attempts — four were blocked, nine missed the net. Edler missed three times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A better gauge of the rusty no-shot period. Sutter shot wide on a 3-on-1 and Burrows lost the handle on a backhander.  #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, 4+1=5 no-shot period efforts in franchise history. #Canucks https://t.co/wOiZnfyOSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Coyotes have held a club without a shot in a period four times in franchise history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, the drama. That "credited" shot now taken away. So, #Canucks have matched the franchise low of ZERO shots in the first period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks outshot 7-1 after one period. I'm proposing running time, coin flip at the end of regulation to determine winner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Canucks record for fewest shots on goal is one. Daniel Sedin credited with the first one at 14:14. #bringonthebreak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're getting close to a poll question: Who will get the #Canucks' first shot. After 12:22, still bagels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 9:55, #Canucks still looking for first shot. #Coyotes have two. Classic game before all-star break. Keep the clock moving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-Star Game bound Bo Horvat found the perfect off-ice linemate. https://t.co/LNiuxjiabi #Canucks #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larsen in, Biega out tonight. Miller starts.#Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks Post Game: The Baertschi bite, the Markstrom misses, the long Duchene goodbye. https://t.co/SOpe31wwOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily double for Baertschi as #Canucks actually score first, score on power play and actually win on road. https://t.co/29nlvQKIyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite the backdoor PP for Baertschi off Henrik Sedin feed. Let's call it the sidedoor. 3-2 #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaput goes kaput with turnover and Nieto goes between Markstrom's arm and body and we suddenly have a game. 2-2. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markstorm would like to have that one back. Slot shot wiggles between pads and Rantanen there for the two-foot putt. 2-1. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tryamkin &gt; Zadorov, Tyutin. Best Russian on ice nearly convert 2-on-1 with Eriksson. What wheels. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that was easy. Granlund strips puck off Zadorov on dump-in, then goes short side with wrap. 2-0. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markstrom bails out 55-88 by getting glove on MacKinnon slot shot #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks outshooting Avs 20-9.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Horvat-Baertschi-Burrows tic-tac-toe rush was pretty impressive. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hernik Sedin pulling away from defenders, easy access to O-zone, Eriksson allowed to get to net untouched. This one is there for the taking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the ninth time in 23 road games the #Canucks have opened scoring. Did the same in Denver on Nov. 26 in 3-2 SO win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horvat with the bull move from behind the net against soft Avs defence, Baertschi with the rebound to far side. 1-0. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iginla's 100th-career game versus #Canucks. Most of any player. Where will UFA be at March 1 trade deadline? Has waived NM clause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks Game Day: The danger game, Rocky Mountain sigh, Duchene dishes, 'Let's Talk' wishes. https://t.co/heXUw33iZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edler (upper body) on ice for optional game-day skate. Expected to play against Avs. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks finally see goals in consecutive days from defencemen to help drive playoff push. https://t.co/yBt9E9942q #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks believe Subban will eventually measure up to NHL standards. https://t.co/fEDgBJzQnn #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markstrom faces Avs, Miller gets Coyotes. Maintenance day for Edler, expected to play Wednesday. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larsen (concussion) also practising in Denver. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edler is not on practice ice in Denver. Appeared to hurt shoulder or wrist in Chicago. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocky Mountain High: Skille had his Avalanche moments on popular Gladiator Line. https://t.co/VxWKM9Su5f #Canucks #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocky Mountain High: Skille finds off-season home, sick-children charity purpose in Denver. https://t.co/HOtjPeEP2S #Canucks #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seemed more concerned about crappy ice. Maybe he didn't even think Panik would get shot off. https://t.co/08U4ILpw62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm, deflected shot off Edler's shin pad is a designed play? And Miller has to play the shooter. https://t.co/8G8LvtKZn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks valiantly climb out of two-goal hole but late lucky bounce off end boards gives #Blackhawks the win. https://t.co/RfSmyZweO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two goals in 39 seconds as Horvat goes to toe drag around Kempny and deposits the rebound. 2-2. Hang on. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stecher with the end-over-end PP wrister from point that eludes Crawford with Daniel Sedin causing crease havoc. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much-maligned PP1 unit with excellent chance as Sutter hits post on backdoor play. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was ugly. #Canucks sluggish, step behind play, outshot 18-9 and won just 40 per cent of first-period draws. Horvat 1-for-6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sbisa with the rubber stick in the corner and Kane with the water-bug quick pounce, snapper to glove with Miller down. 2-0. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good screen by Hartman as Panik takes cross-ice feed in slot and goes post and in to open scoring. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniel Sedin foiled on partial break and another effort slides through crease. #Canucks have scored first just eight times on road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the way they're calling this one. Biega, Edler could have been called for borderline holding/interference infractions. #letthemplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case it's close later on, #Blackhawks are 18-7-5 in one-goal games and #Canucks are 15-3-6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miller showing why he's on 7-0-2 roll. Good saves off Kane, Panarian, Panik as Hawks hold shot advantages of 6-1, 8-2 and now 10-6. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never gets old. Pellico with old-school keyboards, Corneilson with hair-raising United Center anthems. #dailydouble #hockeyheaven]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks honouring Jeremy Roenick with 'One Last Shift' skate. Pretty cool. They do things right here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks versus #Canucks pairings, goal:
Keith-Hjalmarsson
Kempny-Seabrook
Campbell- van Riemsdyk
Crawford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks Game Day: Bo knows pain game, Henrik knows plateau plaudits, Sbisa knows road record sucks. https://t.co/whRzynb2H0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Horvat: " I saw it (puck) coming high. I just wanted to get out of the way, I turned and it nailed me in the back of my head.” #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horvat on his stitched-up head: “It’s a little sore, but we’re working on a bigger helmet for my (big) head — if that’s possible," #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kane on rivalry: "At one time, and I don’t want to say there was a little bit more hatred, but it's more of a respect rivalry.” #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kane on Sedins: "You look at how they dominate the puck and it's probably one of the tougher matchups in the history of hockey." #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd need at least 1,000 words to salute a 1,000 points for the amiable, accountable and consummate professional Henrik Sedin. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On at 2:35 Pacific to salute Henrik Sedin. https://t.co/X9P9IPNSyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodin 'had issues from the get-go' after surgery. https://t.co/ahzOmjkkOp #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrik Sedin inches closer to 1,000 career points as #Canucks claim 1-0 victory over Predators. https://t.co/ziFLfyglJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hernik = 999. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upon lengthy review, it was ruled intent to blow whistle before puck crossd the line nullified Grant goal off mosh pit. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Predators originally claimed Boucher off waivers on Dec. 3 when the Devils attempted to move the winger to Albany. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Daniel Sedin shot from side for #Canucks 27th-ranked PP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reid Boucher, wearing No. 24, looked like Matt Cooke on first shift Van and nailed Antony Biletto. #Canucks #Predators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megna felled by the flu, so Boucher makes his #Canucks debut with Granlund and Sutter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McLeod Nine: Predators' enforcer packed punch, scoring touch in memorable debut. https://t.co/dwjYkavJDg #NHL #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power-play pain intensifies as #Canucks drop 2-1 overtime decision to #Devils. https://t.co/4JDlOHpA2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two, one and none. Shot totals on three #Canucks power plays against the #Devils.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quincey point shot deflects, beats Markstrom stick side. 1-1. #Canucks #Devils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrik Sedin sets up Loui Eriksson for opening goal, captain collects his 998th NHL point. #Canucks #Devils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Daniel Sedin shot on that #Canucks PP. Trending in wrong direction today. Two shots, one shot. What's next, no shots?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you fell asleep, the #Canucks actually won 67 per cent of first-period draws. So, there's that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canucks 27th-ranked PP credited with two shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biega wrister from point deflects off post. #Canucks #Devils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markstrom saves bad line change by getting piece of Henrique shot in slot. #Canucks #Devils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horvat's skilled, gritty cousin Konecny a fine fit in Philly. #Canucks #Flyers #NHL https://t.co/DRPOQPNZun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanev (ribs) taking morning skate in Nashville. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodin sit-and-watch saga overshadows injuries to Hutton, Tanev. https://t.co/CuFsCr75Zu #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desjardins on Rodin. "They want me to put in a guy I’m not sure of exactly where he's at. His chance will come. He can help us." #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Hutton blocked a shot Friday with his left hand and is "out for some time", according to WD. Likely IR. Expect Pedan recall. #Canucks]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>