<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Gosh this is fascinating, isn't it?" The @CheckpointRNZ #JohnCampbell euphemism for "does anyone know WTF is going on?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hashtags I think I was surely 1st to use - but no. #love_Hz It's a radio station. Why should that surprise me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and it's got a thin skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did that. Know now :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there's a growing assumption that if people don't recognise an obscure abbreviation they can always Google it, so u don't explain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qcrQzKHHJY
Interesting piece, but meaning of GOAT not clear to me. Wd associate "goat illusion" with stage magic, not  tennis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was late to the thought: five already :)
https://t.co/LeYiUAOevo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First satirical saccorhytus/Donald Trump comparison in 3...2...1...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saccorhytus, newly discovered ancestor of vertebrates had mouth larger than its other parts &amp; ate &amp; excreted thru it https://t.co/IYfKp5fe14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pheasants protest &amp; refuse to take to the air. Birds &amp; shooters have a dialogue centred on the word/sound "Look!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZMorningReport And the place where Islam was founded #Mecca #Medina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZMorningReport Not just "why be concerned about someone from Iran?" But why NOT someone from Saudi Arabia, home to most 9/11 hijackers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad the yale, with its backward &amp; forward-pointing horns, makes the list. The heraldic version is blue with gold s… https://t.co/2YMp36joRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that so?
Or: "Look..." (I do wish someone would reprint "Ticker Khan").
https://t.co/GGIppTBAOP https://t.co/NVWieKmjOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone suggests in a female-on-male assault, carrots &amp; courgettes can be sliced in a very threatening manner @NZStuff #maybethatsit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And of course we never indulge in violence"  @NZMorningReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The manager of the knightclub, who wished to be known only as Art, insisted "my organisation has nothing to do with… https://t.co/dvdBulroVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SparkNZ down this week; @vodafoneNZ next week? It happens surprisingly often. Maybe installing/updating the same piece of faulty software?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do some singers feel they have to hold onto the mike, even though it's on a substantial mount? #StevieNicks #SkyArts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, some of what they did was humiliating, but the veg bit is just strange. Fair bet everyone concerned was very drunk. @NZStuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's most popular @NZStuff story. "Girl gang humiliate footballer" - by "slicing vegetables over him" #dontgetit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump hopes to have "a fantastic relationship" with Vladimir #Putin This from a man who has obfuscated… https://t.co/rPqLyKTPz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a misnomer to call this an interview; it's a lecture by the interviewer on what she thinks @ninetonoon #stateownedmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just reluctantly switched off the crime &amp; punishment expert on @ninetonoon because he's barely being allowed to get a word in...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps "conversion [to one's own use]" (as with a car) would be an appropriate word for the offence @NZMorningReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re "stealing water"; it's part of the defn of theft (Crimes Act) that you intend to deprive the owner permanently. That's hard to do w water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mexgutter": Possibly a derogatory term for Mexico. Just heard on @NZMorningReport: "He's gunna get Mexgutter pay for the wall."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel @conorsmith Also a concert-hall doorman wearing his in his top jacket pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmanuel @conorsmith I've seen a waiter wearing a bow tie round his wrist. I guess regulations said he had to wear one, but not where.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisBellNZ @paulbrislen @nzdodo Then of course there are health &amp; environmental "experts" ready to say you can't use certain ingredients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @ChrisBellNZ @nzdodo ...by navigating an n+1-dimensional "surface". Very clever stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @ChrisBellNZ @nzdodo To save money. What other reason is there? They plot current cost of each ingredient &amp; calculate minima...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone honestly think of anything that _isn't_ "easier said than done"? #schoolholidays @CheckpointRNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad he cleared that up. @radionz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're talking to the professor who's running a course on evil" @radionz Nights. "Good evening How are you?"
"I'm good".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArrantPedantry @EditorMark @MerriamWebster Hello preferred. Hullo marked as a British variant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MerriamWebster a cloque is a secret group. And a cluque is a group too  "chicken" to disagree publicly with the majority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WhiteHouse press secretary promises to keep session going for as long as reporters have questions. Invitation to #filibuster?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still an interesting textural scarring effect and I wonder if that will be permanent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What it's doing to my spinal posture is another matter :) But pain &amp; redness less every day. Yay for #antibiotics #Sardinian #sewer #fungus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've got the hang of this now. Set the chair sideways; put right leg on it first; then put the left up on t… https://t.co/hbN2W1GWbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how the top execs of US movie &amp; music industries are reacting to @realDonaldTrump's plans to can #TPPA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...and a flounder that we're going to talk through." @ninetonoon #chinesenewyear #recipes #ventriloquism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspected I wasn't the first to think of this https://t.co/UrhXN3JTgN Is he One of Them? Or 1 of their sworn enemies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pikelet And coinkydinkally, this turns up next to yours in my Twitter-stream https://t.co/HQ5ic78d2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL: the antibiotic I'm taking for #cellulitis was extracted from a fungus found in a Sardinian sewer. Maybe that explains the aftertaste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @xeni Odd place to start the quote: https://t.co/yG92C8GqCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThelemicWaves Ah, Tony the Tiger: mascot of empty calories :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamModiano @shelbyfero I'm increasingly thinking 
Papal elections have the right idea. You keep on till one candidate gets 2/3 of the vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realscientists Almost: They are accustomed to a closed set of curves being used to indicate a solid object's boundaries. #notobvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insert your own missing word in the sentence: "Trump will make America _______ again".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @independent @cnn A lot of yaktivists will be longing for the yaks to fall :) #Tussaud #revolution #guillotine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fritinancy ...&amp; moved to another town. But she did not pound the road with her fists or fall on it.
Is that "literally" or "figuratively"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fritinancy Some1 said y'day "I literally hit the road". Rather than just distancing socially from the situation, she actually walked out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Position 17 is where the dotted line is, apparently #cantseethelogic #keeplosingcount https://t.co/tpEpFVbCHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuff I'm putting on my skin contains "hydrocortisone-17-butyrate".I've never had to count positions on an organic molecule higher than 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Venus, Freddie Mercury, Bruno Mars...Do we have any Jupiters or Saturns? Uranuses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebwriter _where_ they're not needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's discouraging to think of these antibiotics &amp; "painkillers" swilling around the many parts of my body there they're _not_ needed #focus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay_Jeffs @NewspaperDickz ...which is a facility I've sworn never to use, because I think it's insecure.
Must make "tinfoil hat" for card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay_Jeffs @NewspaperDickz I go to slide, then remember &amp; twiddle card round aiming to use chip. Machine beeps. I've paid by PINless NFC...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fritinancy @TheSlot Verifying "scran", I find "scran spanners" (cutlery). Must find an opportunity to use it. Eating-irons, gobbling-rods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fritinancy @TheSlot You might have your bevvy at smoko.
There might be a bevy of you having bevvies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fritinancy @TheSlot If you're lucky, you'll get a bite of scran (solid food) with your bevvy. Northern English originally, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I read "sentenced after drunken dash" I think streaking - not getting in your car to fetch Maccas. More dangerous, but less good story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that last remark was uncalled for.
One reviewer said the same about the sequel to "All Quiet on the Western Front."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have had another look at your #NCEA exam as requested, &amp; you still failed," he remarked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the date ramp led into the warp-lane, it could be the story of a strange &amp; combative relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Joe &amp; Susan had been good friends for years, but were now definitely on a date-ramp". Or maybe it's just a device in a dried-fruit factory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else's mind shift the terminal letters of 2-word phrases? So day-tramp becomes date-ramp &amp; war-plane warp lane...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there should be a general rule that if the result of any political ballot is closer than 52/48, you do it again. #Trump #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have, of course been told to stop taking the first medication.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any real meaning (code) to the colour of medicinal capsules? Eg green = anti-inflammatory. Or is it just branding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner @GreatDismal The word is Dada. The US is beginning a Dada presidency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original medication doesn't seem to be working. Switched to new stuff. Immediate improvement, but is it the new, or the old finally working?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headline of the day? "Bat out of Hell". Wicketkeeper hit by bat slipping from batsman's grasp. @NZStuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly ad slogans: "We do doing" - Warehouse Stationery. Well they do sell rubber bands :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An encounter marked by crankiness, doubts that 1 or other wd turn up, &amp; some WTF?! moves it was thought might be ingenious but were stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump &amp; Putin rumoured planning summit in Reykjavik. Remember when Top USian &amp; Russian met there 45 years ago https://t.co/jWDf1M2yDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Five months free from fleas' antics" #circus?
It is an animal they're talking about, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data collection &amp; "targeted marketing" is so, so phisticated FB is pitching me months' freedom from fleas &amp; ticks. I don't own an animal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce @alexandraerin looking at human bodies in the same light right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis sedan chair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up, w'll reminisce on the life of Lord Snowdon. Meanwhile here's 60s girl-group the Crystals
Don't you love how relevant @radionz is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking (and getting up from soft chairs) more easily. Less pain; but my legs still look like they belong to 2 different people #cellulitis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wedding anniversary (&amp; birthstone, etc) thing is about gifts, so I suppose commerce drives it. But silver, gold, ruby is about my limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why any school syllabus ever should have thought "gaggle of geese, parliament of owls" important to remember is beyond me. But mine did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had to choose 2 topics to lose in order to clear space in my brain it'd be names for wedding anniversaries &amp; animal collective nouns :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought I was going to get another perfect score on @NZStuff #quiz. Then a footballer came up...and a qustion about wedding anniversaries...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emckean So technically, I reckon they were open #performativeutterance. But still closed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emckean The version of that I remember was "sorry, we're closed today; we're having an opening ceremony" CEO had done the "opening" by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In answer to the breakfast host at @radionz (@NZMorningReport's holiday version) the 1st word ever uttered was probably "Hey! or "Look out!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you think up pain numbers in advance for Dr - "it's a 2 normally, but goes to a 6 or 7 if I put weight on the leg" - &amp; he never asks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis @Fonterra Best not to ask how much someone got paid for coming up with that astounding slogan.
"Don't just say cheese - do it!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis @Fonterra Cheese!
OK: Now what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA The other guests are called what: chicks? #notuponthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoraReed @stilgherrian There may be some of comparable age still in active use. https://t.co/7QqN3UBuu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MailOnline Cowbells could be valued by some vegans as warning that nasty cows were in the vicinity #unclean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyMcNulty @publicaddress "Hissing hot luncheon fine" - James Joyce]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>