<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I move away from England for 5 months and everything's gone to absolute shite, never coming back https://t.co/AXdEA0Yvma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another game I'll never forget, can't believe it #WatfordFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not forget these timeless classics https://t.co/mcwXaHNYd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at these games, nothing like watching #WatfordFC bottle it in the last few minutes https://t.co/bEwuMfyYhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Yep, think I'm going to get a car too, can't be dealing with a 4 hour bus journey after a 0-0 with West Brom ever again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley disgrace, glad I'm missing this shit show. Need to avoid relegation, start fresh in August. This season is a write off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Didn't think it could get worse than that Gillingham result...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBradley_95 Nah mate that never happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBradley_95 @JoeClowsley I want you to be ready with a camera for when the inevitable tears start when Palace get relegated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing I've seen all year https://t.co/I5ZEhNTmWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depay was a bit shit wasn't he? A poor man's Amrabat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millwall away in the FA Cup @JoeClowsley let me book my flights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada just lost to the USA in the juniors, whatever that is. All I know is they were 4-2 up and bottled it, a disgrace to the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my mates at home are watching football together whilst I'm 8 hours behind stuck in a lecture ðŸ˜´ Time difference is shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giroud ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ Goal of the season for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowtrain ooh fancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowtrain absolutely true, nothing I'd love more than to be browsing the superb selection of shops at the Galleria right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm genuinely the luckiest person I know, how did I even end up in Canada?ðŸ˜ I got CDE in my A Levels, got rejected from every uni I applied@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few weeks ago I was in a drive thru and the stranger in the car in front of me paid for my order ðŸ˜ Forgot to say thanks, whoever you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a girl on my floor who genuinely tried to convince me that your head is heavier than the rest of your body ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Later on &amp; I finally get given the responsibility to deliver a pizza all by myself and my car breaks down in an intersection ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st day at Domino's:
Guy who's driving me around causes a car crash, spent an hour sitting at the side of the road with crying victims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luke_Sprague RIP a fallen brother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My car broke down 30 minutes before my first shift as a pizza delivery driver, why me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad things happen when Watford lose https://t.co/m9sCArD4RM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 Got a better chance of big Younes coming on and scoring a 40 yard scorpion kick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 last time we dropped Deeney we got absolutely shat on by Spurs, gonna be a field trip for Nolito]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 He has to be on the pitch to score..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 7-0 City heard it here first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished my first semester in Canada, mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Nah, probably not back till August. Watford v Palace on boxing day at 4:30am here, it's the only thing I have planned over xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My uni in England want me to get a minimum of 9, preferably 12 credits from each semester. I'm currently on course to get 3 #believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine conceding 5 goals to Bob Bradley's Swansea. He's a poor man's Henning Berg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know a guy who's dog got swooped up and eaten by an owl. Canada is nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lived in Canada for over a month now, mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never cringed so hard in my life, going to be having nightmares for weeks about tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been to 1 lecture in Canada and I've already dropped a module #WorthThe16HourJourney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 Following the footsteps my dad, pretty sure he's a legend in those parts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbnadin1 ðŸ˜‚ from my experiences about 90% of the people who put shit in those groups are total drips, what uni you going to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to win the PL https://t.co/dsYYxzW7NA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatfordBabble I travel from Surrey, takes me 2 hours each way. Made it home by 1am to watch Nyom, Paredes &amp; Anya fail to cross a ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for that @WatfordFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyFansChants @JoeClowsley love the MLS already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to my final PL game at Vicarage road before Canada, can't wait for my 4 hour round trip to end in a 0-0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeaton__ @WatfordFCBlog Nyom has been shite for ages..wasn't at the game today but sounded like more of the same. Why is he still with us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatfordFC It's 12:01 and I still can't buy them. Disappointing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filling out a "Lifestyle Questionnaire" for my accommodation in Canada, what even is this? https://t.co/DCJidWMT83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pilot at work filed an official complaint about me because I called him "mate" rather than "sir" or "captain" â˜ºâ˜ºâ˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBradley_95 Remembering this tweet for when he scores a hatrick against Palace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isaac Success signs for Watford for approximately Â£12.5m, double our previous transfer record. Remember the name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edris_Delveccio Why not try Coventry? I heard it's live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IfraAshraf @JoeClowsley What size are you mate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBradley_95 @JoeClowsley Absolute bottlejob Bradley senior. Not as bad as when you bottled it for the Millwall pitch invasion ey? ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBradley_95 @JoeClowsley Leave it out Bradley, just been on the phone to your dad &amp; he's in the room next to me.  I'll have words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatfordTweet Will take a minimum of 2 years to leave the EU anyway, so shouldn't change much if anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatfordTweet I read somewhere a month or two ago he had already failed to get a work permit? Not sure if there's any substance behind that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sums it up perfectly https://t.co/DwFMXLL5pX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anscommmmb Ahaha i'm just enjoying all this while it lasts. Too many 17 year old hair &amp; beauty students have been believing Facebook memes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anscommmmb What's logical about having unelected officials making a good portion of our laws?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can say this has been a good or bad decision yet, it's been 12 hrs since voting stopped ffs ðŸ˜‚ Give it time &amp; then do your complaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Just like when Palace won the semi finals but bottled it against 10 men United @LukeBradley_95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Haha no i'm not, I didn't even vote for the Tories. My point was people get loud on the day then forget about it quickly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People banging on about young people getting fucked over by old people like they're more important. We're equal no matter your age, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielstorey85 We never elect Prime Ministers you mug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNadin @alexdoesporn Give this a watch if you can be arsed, I thought it was good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn @BBCNews https://t.co/8Jv8aiXiR2 Not that this example effect my vote, it was just the first example I could give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn So much can happen in the next 20/50/99 years, which nobody knows. Leaving the EU doesn't change our uncertainty of the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn EU Army, perhaps? https://t.co/91O0isQsfH Not so much anything in particular anyway, just the principle. They're unaccountable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn I am not certain what these unaccountable bureaucrats could have done, but now we don't need to worry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn Why? I see it the opposite. We couldn't remove the EU officials who make a good portion of our laws, but now they're gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing now our future is uncertain. It's the future, it's ALWAYS uncertain. Leaving the EU doesn't change that unless they can time travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn Ask @Nigel_Farage He probably knows more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn ...that leaving the EU will stop you from working abroad in Europe. Might make it a bit more hassle though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn Honestly no idea mate, probably means you'll have to fill out more paperwork &amp; shit? I doubt...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexdoesporn We were never in the Schengen zone, you've always needed a passport to leave the UK, so there's no difference in movement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's been such a meltdown from so many 'Remain' supporters, where's ArsenalFanTV when you need them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't be surprised if half of these pro-EU tweets will be the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Conservatives won the 2015 election, out came a flurry of "well, England's down the toilet for the next 5 yrs" Heard nothing since]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy has won. Hoping that in 40 years time we'll look back at this decision and say we made the right choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James__Pereira @Luke_Sprague Sprague you have a little bit of sandwich with your mayonnaise not the other way around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 6 minute video for anyone still on the fence about the referendum tomorrow AND doesn't mention immigration once. 

https://t.co/NHopecrrqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How have Iceland scored the same number of goals as England in Euro 2016 with 60 minutes LESS playing time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is far more important than the referendum. He's priceless. https://t.co/9SSf7udVkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley &amp; he talks about migration but fails to mention the unelected officials making some of our laws, nothing on the EU Army either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley Also this is a short sighted view as people have pointed out. The idea of Brexit is for the long term, not the next 5/10 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeClowsley This guy has just said that a left-led Labour party WITH the Greens would help Britain. I want whatever he's smoking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he goes for Â£30M or more we'll still get relegated. Remember this tweet https://t.co/7T4S3alrzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're almost definitely going to remain in the EU anyway but thought I'd share my view just in case it fucks us up 20 years down the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't have much of a problem with the EU if these people were elected, shame they're not. Going to #VoteLeave https://t.co/sOYHqMCZbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasJDesign this is beautiful @WatfordFC Sign him up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 10 years since England last won their opening game in any major tournament. Useless shite. #OptaNadin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hodgson negative as always, such a typical England performance #HodgsonOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be valued at Â£100m+ for the value of remaining as a Premier League club, without him we'd be down so quickly https://t.co/HOTZLVm3cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sophie_Banham It's because my penis is too big, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sophie_Banham Where was my super like? #Offended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't watch more than 5 minutes of the new Top Gear without cringing at Chris Evans and turning it off #shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to Wembley, shouted "MILL" lots, came home, all for about Â£50 #WorthIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best goal I've ever seen live &amp; I barely remember it  https://t.co/zrLv6KpCBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@finbarjameson @LukeBradley_95 Didn't you support Man United until year 9?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sophie_Banham Sorry mum]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>