<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Recalling some Australian General that no Aussie has heard of from some unheard of position in Hawaii sounds pretty… https://t.co/7s9DeaxLI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling Trump to go jump - the Australian way https://t.co/5H1J8Py4pb via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is true. We named a swimming pool after a drowned Prime Minister. #Australia https://t.co/41aPLFiC6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald the Menace https://t.co/OEQE49Ah79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article. Very interesting man. https://t.co/bSvSQNmvjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pulled or strained a muscle in my lower back and I agree. Paracetamol, ibuprofen, codeine all useless. https://t.co/GD4dkQxacM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-inflammatory drugs ineffective for back pain, study says | SBS News https://t.co/J6DHZtL6gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this smells pretty stinky. https://t.co/XuMMhS5dcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kelloveslife So is the Seattle Tribune a real news outlet or was it hoaxed as well? The era of #fakenews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registered as a sex offender for nursing her own child plus 7yrs prison time. WTAF? https://t.co/KBZnESWXmT https://t.co/vynkt7S6Kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Company tax: big business already pays less than 30% rate, ATO data shows https://t.co/whGEP0WMw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps if she'd worn a dress??? https://t.co/Qk6NmplzHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["to counter what he sees as destablising behaviour." Don't know whether to laugh or cry. Drink. https://t.co/ffrU5GdC1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's dishonorable blunder Down Under: https://t.co/sM1C9zWtw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shows you she knows shit about the Australian political scene. This was the last thing Turnbull wanted made public. https://t.co/3CRPLBx3BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Catholic archbishops in Australia to front royal commission https://t.co/tMWkDCoRjC via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans extend hand of friendship to Australians on unforeseen day in limelight https://t.co/meYDO7702D via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagrammers dispute Tourism Tasmania's use of photos in airport https://t.co/Sunerk82Hf via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SocialDemocrat All my life we've sucked up to the yanks. I'm over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He also told us that the phone call with Trump was all "hunky dory" when it wasn't. We want our PM to be straight w… https://t.co/AS1jndEyDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG I've got 666 followers. What does this mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps Hockey can offer some cigars. https://t.co/tXbTfWUpP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump treating Australians like dirt risks support for alliance  https://t.co/SkKwOqHiho via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the Australian government is now referring to them as refugees because it suits their political purposes to do… https://t.co/JnyWQUoUJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There you go @TurnbullMalcolm - Settle the refugees in Australia, close the camps &amp; tell the US to take their milit… https://t.co/nVAq9ERlOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have kangaroos and we're not afraid to use them. https://t.co/ay71IrDRFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wombats can be nasty little buggers. https://t.co/wAKhZs04v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree. I'm not a Turnbull fan (make no secret of that fact) but Trump in treating our PM with such contempt treats… https://t.co/odRLRZbsSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are the real victims here but continue to be pawns in political games. #bringthemhere #closethecamps https://t.co/zeCqX7JHrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the late, great Gough Whitlam had been on the receiving end of that Trump phone call American military bases in Oz would be no more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull right now. https://t.co/er2gBhvziH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As expected. If the Australian Prime Minister won't stand up for himself when bullied where does that leave Austral… https://t.co/O2xzNgqKfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Malcolm #notmyjob Turnbull will have something to say now or will he curl up into the fetal position &amp; whimper? #GrowAPair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time America wants us to help out in one of their manufactured wars give them the two finger salute. https://t.co/BYAxmdr2js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/FVi2iFojKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia should resettle the refugees here and #closethecamps. We should also tell Trump to bugger off. https://t.co/LoJQSy6btJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/D181q4Jvds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately it won't be about Shorten improving his appeal to voters. Turnbull is vanishing before our eyes &amp; the Li… https://t.co/enzdsjFLou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shorten strives to make politics personal after terrifying glimpse at Trump card | Katharine Murphy https://t.co/QPQsHvTWX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously. Where does she find these people? I think One Nation candidates need "extreme vetting." https://t.co/HaUOzA9Siu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Abetz realise or even care that he's talking about people. People with families, mortgages, bills to pay. Does… https://t.co/UK20m2zvjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abetz urges Government to 'show leadership' and cut 4,000 jobs https://t.co/WOCGKbVf99 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also explains why Turnbull was so narky when he finally fronted the public on election night. He almost lost despit… https://t.co/jQEeWhMFq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for those cheaper energy prices @TurnbullMalcolm was spruiking about at the #NPC address. Clean coal is an… https://t.co/y7TWYh4zCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power prices could double with new coal-fired stations: experts https://t.co/93oJbuxb2n via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell Eric that cutting 4000 jobs doesn't help with that "jobs and growth" thing @TurnbullMalcolm bangs on a… https://t.co/Zh1ipSSL0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillySmith104 @billshortenmp @NannanBay Labor aren't alone in playing that game. Still waiting to see who it will be after Abbott, Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know whether or not Turnbull bought the election with his donation but he certainly bought his survival as Prime Minister. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was more impressive than @TurnbullMalcolm. Direct, to the point, no waffling. https://t.co/lYXa67RWZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#theweekly I didn't do any of that stuff on #AustraliaDay. I did stack hay though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#theweekly I haven't actually seen any of this Trump footage. Where's my "be alert not alarmed" fridge magnet when I need it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HomeDelivery @twopaddocks is pissed off. Totally understandable. Uni education should be available to all. Not just those with money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HomeDelivery Looking forward to my trip to New Zealand later this year. Such a lovely episode with @TwoPaddocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've still got a crush on @TwoPaddocks. #HomeDelivery https://t.co/8a9pvZ37CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TwoPaddocks looking very spiffy on #HomeDelivery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A young chap I work with asked me some time ago "what's fascism?" Now all I have to say is Donald Trump if anyone asks me that again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was raised by my Dad (mum died when I was 9.) He worked full time &amp; raised a family pretty much on his own. He di… https://t.co/8qgLLh39Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor people aren't allowed to have million dollar views. https://t.co/BgLyZ1rZe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are these thousands of Tasmanians and who is H &amp; M? https://t.co/TW2YSn5UXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always frustrated when journalists don't ask the questions they should or point out the inaccuracies in stateme… https://t.co/Z6zP4jS6wQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc Turnbull lambasting Labor for scare campaigns while telling voters to be scared of Labor. The irony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting that @TurnbullMalcolm says if you want less of something "tax it." Except when it came to the carbon tax it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's scared. He now sees @billshortenmp as a real threat hence the "Bill bashing." #npc https://t.co/8iMUsBwaPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc When our service personnel come back from these areas of conflict they need more than your thanks &amp; pride @TurnbullMalcolm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc We may have higher taxes than other nations but we also have a fairer society than many other nations. Or used to. @TurnbullMalcolm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc A $10M turnover seems more than a "small" business to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc Of course small business want the intern programme implemented. A slave labour workforce at your beck and call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LNP votes are more likely to be lost to One Nation. Is Turnbull shooting the wrong target? #npc https://t.co/Bk84GHzT8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc Back on the Labor bashing again. That's all Mal has got.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc @TurnbullMalcolm taking the high ground on scare campaigns. I haven't forgotten the $100 roasts scare after carbon tax implementation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc Well Malcolm's lights may be on but I don't think anyone is home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc "The wind doesn't blow all the time." Seems to be blowing pretty well today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc Turnbull attempted to crack a funny. Key word "attempted."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#npc My eyes are starting to glaze over. Think I'll check my pulse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We "stopped the boats." Here we go again. Same old mantra. Nothing new here. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just played the terrorism card. Expected no less. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Malcolm. Don't hold up the #NBN as a success. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps Turnbull could use all his wind-baggery to provide energy security. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He just said "not to mention uranium" very softly &amp; quickly when referring to energy security.  Interesting &amp; alarming. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go. The "Liberals" are the best friend of #Medicare crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Transparency" says @TurnbullMalcolm. Then release the report on Sussan Ley's rorting. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He actually said it "live within our means." #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull is the "product of great teachers." #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm still extolling the virtues of "trickle down" economics. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hands are too big. https://t.co/0XaTNFeH1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Bronwyn Bishop. https://t.co/vByIXOEcSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lib/Nats, Greens &amp; One Nation all having internal party struggles. Amazing that Labor seems the only party with their shit together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another quality candidate brought to you by One Nation. They just get better and better. What a vile man. https://t.co/favUBEQzr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single mums 'too lazy' to attract and hold a mate: One Nation candidate https://t.co/QIcQeefqal via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can pitch what he likes. Australians have long stopped listening to @TurnbullMalcolm and his waffle. https://t.co/tGaerg1QKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a price. @TurnbullMalcolm in order to get the refugee deal through with the US may risk the lives of Austral… https://t.co/vkKLkq8BQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How an autism assistance dog turned a family's life around https://t.co/IkTRDq6Fr7 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a "mainlander" that moved here 20yrs ago I'd say the Tassie sun packs a bigger punch. I'm also Vitamin D deficie… https://t.co/Sdc428pMPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Tasmania's sun feels harsher in summer https://t.co/Gut2NtHHn9 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lion is a must see movie. It's a strong, compelling story &amp; visually stunning to watch. Kidman &amp; Patel are terrifi… https://t.co/oBrAvd0AJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the haters to reassess: Nicole Kidman really can act https://t.co/r08IwYYWPT via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Existing casual workers will find themselves working more hours at a lower rate of pay. https://t.co/1MCG0Mk5J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government is too cowardly to stand up to fascism https://t.co/45iBvFF1qL via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would assume that Trump has a clever plan? https://t.co/43rzMlvHZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sixth person dies following Bourke Street attack https://t.co/l4y0gpiTr4 via @ABCNews]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>