<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Spy in the Wild on BBC One is pretty amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting, to put it mildly, to see if this ever gets rectified. https://t.co/vrkZDUGKLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very telling @realDonaldTrump doesn't mind what Bannon wears in the White House, he dare not stand up to his boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bowling Green Massacre Victims Fund: https://t.co/iHfiBRDEDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is all of America planning to watch The Apprentice this week? I sure hope so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah I see The Toddler is awake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft writes to Sec of State and DHS chief re immigrant ban: https://t.co/FAA5xkQEAt Makes clear how ridiculous sweeping this law is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; his point about the ISIS recruitment techniques is spot-on, but of course Bannon also wants End Days, so things g… https://t.co/GIShiIcO0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GOP is most definitely America's Nasty Party. https://t.co/THihqUHlIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLeeBBC this is reality of how tech is used vs glossy, everyone surfing, snowboarding, having awesome house parties idea tech firms sell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quentynblog I would say I'm a floating voter but at moment would definitely vote against govt but for who? Split votes help noone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It only took worst UK decision in a lifetime and USA to go mad but amazing to see almost everyone get so political. Almost gives you hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quentynblog yes absolutely. I wish @UKLabour had a viable leader. Would make whole situation more even. And proper future election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robjessel unquestionably but (ignoring violent element) protesting his speech legit. Esp when so hatful. And devoid of fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robjessel not condemning violence. Would not surprise me if violent were right wing looking to justify heavy handed response. State of USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robjessel that was a minority. The majority protested peaceful. Very dangerous to conflate actions of few with the man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robjessel @eldahshan he was invited by Berkley College Republicans, not just all students Those who see him for what he is protested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if this needed reinstating. https://t.co/m7xg1MmT9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anyone in the Tory party of any ability? If May went would you think 'at least X can step up now?'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is almost certainly what happened. Bannon is unquestionably as idiotic as the rest of them on subtle diplomati… https://t.co/rBNu2C1ZQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember Russia poisoned  someone in London with polonium that could have killed 100s. Murder by state in foreign s… https://t.co/dcONrNxfCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just reported American N*zi party to @Twitter. Let's see if they act or find a reason to excuse it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can imagine how quickly reporting fatigue sets in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite sad how some of greatest media outlets in world - @nytimes @washingtonpost etc - have to write stories saying 'this is a lie'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After years of proclaiming the greatness of the US constitution looks like it's time for the nation to prove it will defend it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just straight up crazy. https://t.co/p6wEJuF1sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["[Trump and Putin lie] to assert power over truth itself" https://t.co/AfdLIJTumj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone simplify? https://t.co/XQhnWGRhNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant trolling by Hockney here. https://t.co/GyY1c5OnTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @realDonaldTrump loses another fight. https://t.co/FyHkuc4fy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court order in Virginia asking @realDonaldTrump and CBP to prove they are not in contempt of court: https://t.co/EkZZOkmMHU 12 Days in. Mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see the same idiocy in the US is equally at home here. https://t.co/Tm0HjK6w4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is this? https://t.co/LBweIasH3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephCox Yep. That irks most. Like Piers Morgan, it's not real, it's just deliberately controversial for attention. Yet it's worked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephCox No, although I never thought he would earn the sympathies of the president of US. It's a stupid world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larakiara Probably, in relation to him. It was a TERRIBLE trip. I hid in hotel once we got back, couldn't stand it any longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larakiara Some random trip to Paris for a 'fibre through the air' company. He and the PR (guess who!) sang in the minibus. It was horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went on a press trip with Milo once in 2010. He was loud, boorish, tiresome and it stank of an act all designed for attention. Pitiful man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Plot Against America - definitely worth reading in the current climate: https://t.co/yWntlRTu45 Doubt @realDonaldTrump has read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrifying for the world, but glad the Aussie PM told @realDonaldTrump to get stuffed. Imagine Donald was beaten ha… https://t.co/CB3CwZLRuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The USA is basically the Bluth Company when GOB ends up in charge and Michael repeatedly says “I have no problem with that”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man. This guy. Let's just hope he never gets any real power! https://t.co/PUrWss0sFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh a fascist judge on the supreme court, that'll go well. Expect @gop will just change rules to get him in  https://t.co/4WudJQMI9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't @realDonaldTrump just admit it's too much and resign. No one would mind. https://t.co/6JoAyS2cSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing @BBCWorld has no story on Trump literally threatening to invade Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up. No BBC news alert. Phew must have been quiet day in US. Open Twitter. Arggghhhhhhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least the special relationship means both USA and UK destroy themselves at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth a read. https://t.co/6e0c7J9Es7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come with 51.9% of the British people. https://t.co/KNkWcHh88e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone should make a website that tracks how long since Donald's last tweet. Be fun to see it it ever made 24 hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine if Dems did this under Obama? Their heads would have exploded. https://t.co/B92JdtbdVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MooseAllain "Hi I'm Chris Froome. "...from?" "Yes that's right." "Er..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine if something genuinely bad or momentous happens and Trump has to address the nation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how in about 11 days @realDonaldTrump has made the White House and office of president seem like a surreal joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is about him. Just pathetic. https://t.co/F82bRWgCb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah good, another step towards complete rule of the US by a reality TV star. https://t.co/C1ttbiMovh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Nicholas Soames. https://t.co/vjSsP0uprs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound familiar? https://t.co/lYxABwQqb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If true would the biggest sign yet of major coup underway inside US. But not seen anyone else reporting. https://t.co/BNBmpr9dSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@piersmorgan @hwallop @OwenJones84 'needless to say, I had the last laugh'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GOP is pathetic. Passed her despite endless faults and saying 'she received too much scrutiny'. https://t.co/erpeTAAKR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything about #brexit so depressing. Would never have happened if we'd known what was coming but now shackled to 51.9% vote forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh. https://t.co/HxCUOfIFPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MickeyCaskill yeah....is confusing. Seems naive to assume it's all good but also don't want to be 100% negative. Sure we'll find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems normal, too normal. But cautiously, a good thing. A hint of normality, or at least, not going backwards. https://t.co/xyPDdqU87h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarasyoung haha yes. Weird account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassing how outdated, backwards and downright misogynistic the world of parliament is. Not surprising, but pat… https://t.co/w8sKe0XnM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coup anyone? https://t.co/v4bEacCbpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Why do people talking about the 2018 midterms as a chance to fight back. There won't be any midterms. It will… https://t.co/WF8uv7Pcca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every morning wake up wondering what fresh madness has unfolded from Trump. And each day, there it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Bannon knows all @realDonaldTrump's Russian dealings so uses that to force him to do what he says. Else Trump - jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems the US legal system is all that can stop @realDonaldTrump but suspect moves afoot to gut it from Bannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump travel ban: Protesters speak out. Seems clear @Number10gov misjudging public mood on this. Or don't care.  https://t.co/JtPKJKEWJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Horrible scenes. Nicholas Soames MP 'woofs' at Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh MP https://t.co/t5JQs0bMqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLeeBBC either way great to see @amazon take this stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLeeBBC do they not have enough people to do both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish @SpeakerRyan &amp; @GOP were planning moves behind close doors to remove Trump. But too short sighted to realise… https://t.co/BXEyL9crFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant to see so many UK cities protesting against @realDonaldTrump taste of his visit if he comes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Why don't US politicians realise what is happening. They will find rug pulled from under them. He'll disobey… https://t.co/EzBo4TC4ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @realDonaldTrump @LBC right because protesting things is against democracy. Jeez you are stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical that @realDonaldTrumphas to reduce things to TV ideas around acting. Can't comprehend genuine emotions. https://t.co/vPrkxUcbWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet we think @BorisJohnson is some sort of great wit. Horrible man. https://t.co/7OvgQHUOkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing that's mildly uplifting is seeing Bannon dragged centre stage in all this. https://t.co/BmQS4Bs1Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarCreator wasn't referring to US. All nations. If we get lumped in with this sort of behaviour no guarantees we retain allies over time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peston Nope. Allies come and go and we have no idea how this might affect us. The UK-centric view from… https://t.co/ieKqwC0PvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But references to WW2 prison beatings were ok a few weeks ago. Wow, @BorisJohnson is an embarrassment. https://t.co/l6zAvrWEHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depressing seeing MPs arguing about Trump as if he is a normal politician who needs embracing. History will judge them very poorly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarasyoung Exactly, excuse for more reactionary EOs. Chaos, confusion, internal strife. Remember that from history...but where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful stuff, but wait for idiotic reply from @realDonaldTrump. Plus this division between govt is just what Bann… https://t.co/VHzJwIznck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise. Suddenly the system is handy, eh @Nigel_Farage. https://t.co/nNatXUm6SD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People keep talking about November 2018 mid-terms as if they expect US govt to be functioning then. They won't happen if this continues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, can't use the letter e, must contain reference to cabbage, and be written in wingdings. https://t.co/gFpDBkU2f3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Jobs 'don't flee', you moron. Plus, as a tip, the media would report favourable on you if you did, you know, good things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure most of the people on The Donald Reddit thread are Russian agents in grey buildings outside Moscow. https://t.co/vyJaaY4uRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically a coup in USA right now. Or are tears to blame @realDonaldTrump? https://t.co/QxKJ0b3Rie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You mean Bannon has decided and you do what he tells you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's controllable, thought those around him. We can get him to do what we want then discard of him. https://t.co/tq1a3SHElH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Deluded @realDonaldTrump blames computer problems, protestors and a man's tears for causing nationwide issues from his idiotic EO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While legal residents of US face chaos at their own airports, a Saudi Prince charters 80 seats for his hawks. https://t.co/Me2rkcPl1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is it. They want chaos and confusion. Expect more actions this week to drive this strategy. @GOP through… https://t.co/oxNQK4xJDS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>