<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[dibs on top bunk loser #sneakpeak #marriedatfirstsight #roadlife #missuniverse #vbtins #trump… https://t.co/uqbV8o3feY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helloooooooo possum. 
My names Ron, I'm not the messiah, I'm a very naughty little boy. 
His… https://t.co/jqKrhbhqYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerboy182 we can only pray to the karma/boxing gods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PerthMusicKid he has also said he don't like them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids these days. So inventive #obama #trump #biathlon #graffiti #graffitiart #aids… https://t.co/2AQJJpZmNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old matey didn't want me in the photo. Said I'll spoil the moment #eatabagofdicks #roadlife… https://t.co/P1PoAe02mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @rpcabral18 eat a bag of dicks. @StephanieWei is a gun. Just because she reports in golf doesn't mean she can't have an opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey tin man, you ok? Bit stiff? You seem to be concentrating a lot but not getting your desired… https://t.co/GrqiINz1Ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most rigged machine in the world and I love it. #trump #missuniverse #greens #equality… https://t.co/g51x34HI6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful of those spider legs ladies #MissUniverse #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is not enough bitchiness in #MissUniverse If they were real girls they would be scratching each other's eyeballs #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't one of the girls trip one of the final 13 when they walk past them? #MissUniverse #roadlife #golfextravaganza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what $60 gets you on the road. #roadlife #itiswhatitis #obama #golfextravaganza… https://t.co/hsYHoMXb8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit hot where I've been today. Actually forget where this was. https://t.co/hmRXm66Q9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's some road tripping face. "I have a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes, it's dark… https://t.co/k3yhxDG5NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is how the road trip started. #golfextravaganza https://t.co/MS7LUfXcK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let em come let em come ........ 
biggest small club in the world
#millwall #facup https://t.co/7Jo9TWc2q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @BondiLion @Nick_A_How @jimmfc thanks mate, I'm in Victoria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @BondiLion @Nick_A_How @jimmfc where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @BondiLion @Nick_A_How @jimmfc wish I could come out and play but I'm still on a good behavior bond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BondiLion @darrenmfc @Nick_A_How @jimmfc I might be drunk but I know the score. Come on you lions #MILLWALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @Nick_A_How @BondiLion @jimmfc watching it on phone, so can't tweet, but that was soft as baby shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_A_How @BondiLion @jimmfc @darrenmfc ha, welcome to the club fat stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_A_How @BondiLion @jimmfc @darrenmfc I know your a smart lad but if it was a morro winner it wouldn't be 2 all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BondiLion @jimmfc @ESPNAusNZ @Nick_A_How @darrenmfc I got the app on my phone. It asked what region I wanted then wanted my foxtel login]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BondiLion @jimmfc @ESPNAusNZ @Nick_A_How @darrenmfc go to google bondi and says you can watch it on Xbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmfc @BondiLion @ESPNAusNZ @Nick_A_How @darrenmfc Jim your a star. The app is now called WatchESPN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#millwall is not on @ESPNAusNZ how do I watch it @BondiLion @Nick_A_How @darrenmfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SydComedyClub looks the nuts, can't wait to get there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DennisCricket_ so you're attracted to big blokes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieWei is there any truth to rumor that his previous Nike irons were titleist irons rebranded?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieWei @SaadiyatBeachGC fair enough. Looking forward to following your commentary again this year #classact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieWei @SaadiyatBeachGC why don't you take your own sticks when traveling? #curious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I can speak for all of us and say we'd rather you not. https://t.co/sp2xsHhAca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No suprises that 9 of these guys have appeared on @YKWDpodcast @RiotCast with @robertkelly https://t.co/nR9S6p4wmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's a little late but it's going to be hot till late April so let's hope we can enjoy… https://t.co/V5PNCorsn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say it frenchy say it, chowder.
alllowercase @ Bicentennial Park, Glebe https://t.co/lZF5fbOa2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I say they let the #bourkest driver go. Just make a public announcement of when and where it will be. #publicjustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a little bit of @Ralphie_May about this picture https://t.co/r5tu5zo1pX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @Nick_A_How @BondiLion @millwallmickey driving around rural Victoria on my own playing golf and drinking beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenmfc @Nick_A_How @BondiLion @millwallmickey just realized I'll be away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BondiLion @Nick_A_How @millwallmickey @darrenmfc what channel will it be on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hitsmanalex @bertkreischer @joell51868 @chrisbaileyguy you've not heard of John West then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations third umpire. You now have said rock'n'roll 50 times this match. #AUSvPAK #chanel9 #cricket #aids #ALeague #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drivethrupod @DrYobbo sorry, I thought you were @jimjefferies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertkreischer night night mate. Get your ass to Australia soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drivethrupod @DrYobbo where's the show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimjefferies if you've travelled this far are you coming to Australia as well? #gunter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertkreischer @joell51868 @chrisbaileyguy all this talk about dolphins, but what do they actually taste like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DefensiveCentre @DrYobbo @wwos @MCG @MarriedAU @Channel9 ask Michael Clarke's opinion. He thinks the show is called #bridesmaids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@telegraph_sport if the crickets boring just leave. No decent person thinks this is funny or entertaining. #cheapbogantrash #millenials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh nollsy, what have you done? #strippers #vb #adelaide #radelaide #meloveyoulongtime… https://t.co/RHqXeivo3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertkelly @YKWDpodcast  thank you dude. I don't think you realize how much you've exposed me too comedy wise. Can't wait to get to US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marknorm that's pretty funny #Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just listened to yankee swap episode and it made me laugh and put me in such a good mood. Thanks guys @YKWDpodcast @robertkelly @RiotCast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenningtonShow @luisjgomez @ComicDaveSmith I missed the show. What was the big news? #Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJRussell95 a winning hack!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hank_Mahogoff @imjustriffin I thought your whole schict was exposure. Sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imjustriffin @Hank_Mahogoff you got me there. But why didn't Hank mention @OpieRadio in his response you redneck bunch of window lickers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hank_Mahogoff it's comments like that are the reason you don't have any friends in high school. #whatarecaprispants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpieRadio you've given this clown shoes too much time already. Don't feed the donkey @Hank_Mahogoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DweezilZappa @JuiceClark you beat me to it Julie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @DweezilZappa I see all this hype and enjoy the news about your shows, but what about us in #Australia ? #itsbeentoolong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_A_How you must have a few hours to kill. I pick and choose as per guest. How does one find the time to record all these long pods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normydorrell I only just got what you said #brainsnap #youretooclever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normydorrell How dare you!! Wash your mouth out with soap!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DennisCricket_ it's not a drop in wicket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerboy182 @proshenks dare you to mention that to Sam's face. #KeyBoardWarriors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never would have guessed https://t.co/506fsHkE3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the laughs fellas. Glad you also enjoy my fav @TitosVodka #Australia #whoisfat #bertisfat https://t.co/kxtLXNl1zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY resolution. Beer with @bigjayoakerson convo with @ComicDaveSmith &amp; fight with @luisjgomez See you soon NYC. @LegionOfSkanks #Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AussieGolfer so does that mean half of a ProV1?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just become a premium member of @robertkelly @YKWDpodcast Thanks for the laughs and exposure to all things funny #support #dude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJRussell95 you wouldn't have won. Renshaw was bowled you dill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's not one #beige #offwhite suit left in charity shops across Sydney https://t.co/FOwoB1Tw3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshEarl @dassalo @Bandcamp Better??? I was going with 29% more expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dassalo @MrJoshEarl @Bandcamp I bought Louis Ck's for $5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaintsSJ @juanfarkall what? Not swimming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they can't swim https://t.co/E04rSwx35f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No they can't #youdothemath https://t.co/DIeXgLHImz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Former_legend @fcttb_podcast @normydorrell @sidpunts cheers cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcnewman and he learnt all his tricks at Millwall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luisjgomez is there a reason you retweet your own tweet? @LegionOfSkanks #??????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know where I can get some hot cross buns? #easter2017 #goodtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NickKyrgios can you give your dog a better start to the day other then Pal? #AskKyrgios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the new wheels #ryobi #subaru #wrx #grassisgreener #ashes #vb #bigbash @ Haberfield https://t.co/7DUi4X1syP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bennthompsonn @accordingtoaldo top man would be more appropriate #stevemorrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LateMailMan @ABCNews24 only if they give up the puss!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TimJDillon thought your skeptic tank @AriShaffir was a brilliant laugh. If you don't come to Australia soon I guess I'll see you in NYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How in the hell do they score surfing competitions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOddsBible he does beat up a good apple though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just entered the @crownbet rewards #ChristmasCountdown. Play now for your chance to win prizes daily!  https://t.co/1qGNLRQ9WI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJRussell95 this is just like the phone numbers on the McDonald's wraps. Pull your head in toss bag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @luisjgomez my hat game today. You can call off your gomites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even to Australia? @TitosVodka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do yourself a favor and watch @bertkreischer new special. It's the funniest thing I've scene in ages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @LegionOfSkanks just heard about the merch issue. I ordered a hat on 2 November. Will I not get it? I'm in Australia. This is my 2nd hat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LionsLiveRadio 1-1 Fred O to score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word on the street is there may be a few lesbo's attending the show tonight @TheNickCody @bartlol @lukeheggie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What goes through a ladies brain that does not shave their armpits!! @TheNickCody @bartlol @lukeheggie #mingin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>