<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Early morning shadow and flare https://t.co/LtqLfONJrr https://t.co/8lu6ihfL5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatGirlRenita it really is!! Such a fantastic region to visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇫🇷 The garden cloisters of the abbey at the top of Mont St Michel. We visited on our girls… https://t.co/pI1G6N1tzK https://t.co/USZJwVWdSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inher30s @rhymeandribbons awww, I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhymeandribbons wow. That must have hurt. Not the same but my dad said I embarrassed him for speaking out on mental health issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics || Women’s March – What Next? https://t.co/MlXGykfNDE &lt;- an incredible roundup by @rhymeandribbons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*New* Review: Eli August &amp; the Abandoned Buildings - Is This Darkness https://t.co/epnrUQQaAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzbead Lots of photos of the dorrs but I did not so inside! I'm guessing I made a mistake there??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small detail from the Cattedrale di Santa Maria del Fiore in Florence. I took thousands … https://t.co/0z7W5diVVW https://t.co/h0qNfVfla2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaymoreZA @Illaria I'm detecting that this is not as upsetting for people over there as it is for us here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaymoreZA @Illaria there is only one person I had more than the orange one and it is him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Illaria there is a leadership vacuum at present. If an election was called, likely there would be leadership challenges in both Con &amp; Lab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Illaria David Cameron is no longer in politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Illaria no idea. I care less about how it will impact him and more about removing her from office. Or at least holding an election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonKiwiEmma I would ask them, in the nicest possible way, to put it back as it was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht :) They'll send you a full transcript of the debate too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @Screenjabber and RT for a chance to win Let's Be Evil on DVD https://t.co/iRqTM839MP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daneelolee @RealTimeWWII @ClaymoreZA @RutaSepetys That sounds interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealTimeWWII @ClaymoreZA There is a fantastic book about this - @RutaSepetys's Salt to the Sea https://t.co/mt07KoAheD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht Didn't even notice that through the red mist of my rage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht Yes! And it is only growing. When I went to sign it Sunday, it only had 19,000, grew to 24,000 by time I finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to start a new petition to remove she who is #notmyPM and she-who-we-did-not-vote-for from office?… https://t.co/Taqvt3jq0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pathway in the Lost Gardens of Heligan in Cornwall. 
Twenty-five years ago, Heligan’s hi… https://t.co/yRGLQXZA13 https://t.co/vg6HXA2wx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shewithcapitalV @LaLaLand Me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇨🇿 Made by Praha. 
I often see people apologise for posting old photos and it makes me smi… https://t.co/f3D3g8qOIC https://t.co/usW4uvMb8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelsey_travels Eek. Not sure about that. They are so hard to get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelsey_travels Cool. I think there are flights from LCY to Belfast &amp; we're in Dartford so could possibly be a good… https://t.co/WvB94kMvEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord @DontKnockTwice is scary. Thank goodness I'm watching it during the day or my screams would wake up my neighbours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelsey_travels Always welcome in Casa Southgate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLButler76 They do know! We were so adamant we wouldn't get a male cat but he climbed on my lap and wouldn't budge… https://t.co/IY1psoGKW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree. The best thing I ever did was walk into a cat shelter in South Africa nearly 11 years ago. I picked girl c… https://t.co/n4sIynbP3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifun_inferno That's such a pity. Perhaps you could contact the theatre for cancellations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me, John Hurt will always be Kilgharrah. The most beloved dragon of all. https://t.co/6HinnxJyeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I felt winded after reading about John Hurt. I first fell in love with him when I saw 1984 in my teens. His voice and talent live on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Review: The Mission - Another Fall From Grace ★★★★☆ https://t.co/FavldJ4ZkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht I recalled something slightly differently and found this link: https://t.co/FbOL8R8p2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifun_inferno @lizzid82 @peterjamesuk It's coming to Brighton Theatre Royal on Monday 13 February – Saturday 18 Fe… https://t.co/mfPLGyY0CG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjamesuk You're welcome! It was a great introduction to your work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BriteEyedViolet Goodness, he is cute. Can I have him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scratch_london I just have tons of time on my hands since I gave up Emm in London!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first review for the Blog of Theatre Things is up! Not Dead Enough at @OrchardTheatre  https://t.co/EsL0zvRwbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonKiwiEmma Thanks most lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I shouldn't. He is part of an epidemic of privileged people who apply for jobs they're not qualified for and ge… https://t.co/EHrcBM619Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇮🇹 Most photos on the river Arno in Florence are of Ponte Vecchio but once you get on the … https://t.co/BbCDbkGBl0 https://t.co/mYnnznUkR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm back on @Blogcritics tonight with my review of @eliaugust's latest album Is This Darkness https://t.co/ID5m2PdykB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an incredible story about Dominique Moceanu and her secret sister: My idol turned out to be my sister https://t.co/wqW1pfK13d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*New* Review: The Mission - Another Fall From Grace ★★★★☆ https://t.co/Ys7Ks740wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: @ZooNationUK's The Mad Hatter’s Tea Party at the @RoundhouseLDN ★★★★★ https://t.co/q432EdPuEK feat. @TommyFranzen and @Kayla_Lioness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoanneRealJLS That would drive me mad. Did you know you can challenge your employer for a new laptop under H&amp;S. Me… https://t.co/ciPckBxtKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine firms for sexist dress rules, say MPs https://t.co/V2YQgkz2Kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoanneRealJLS It was exceptionally buggy. I had two browsers open plus my iPhone and only one of them went through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Witnessed a remarkable display of canine loyalty this morning. Husband has flu and Labrador would not leave his side for food or to go pee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so end over a year of trying to get @Elbow tickets. I'm beyond excited to see them for the first time. @thekillers are alright too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Tickets booked for The Killers, Elbow and Tears for Fears at @BSTHydePark on 8 July.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzid82 You're welcome. Please don't hesitate to shout if you're ever stranded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzid82 It's no problem at all. Tweet me of need be. I'll be there in two minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzid82 I can take you home! Call me when you get to Dartford!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzbead Oh, that sounds gorgeous! We're going back in December so hoping for snow and prettiness too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watching Green Room. No idea why it took me so long. I adore Callum Turner and loved Anton Yelchin too. Loving the soundtrack!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolina75011 :) Well, you did ask! It was a glorious time for me, ruined when we moved to South Africa in 1982.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thadd31 You're most welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolina75011 Late 70s, early 80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manff26 Have you updated your Reed profile with a photo? My phone rings off the hook when I reactivate mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here you go... Spoek Mathambo's version of the hit Joy Division track, "She's Lost Control" https://t.co/3Aj53TU1Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my absolute favourite Joy Division song and if you've not heard Spoek Mathambo's version (or seen the video… https://t.co/zpSPousa93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damawa42 Woo! What fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇨🇿 Henry's Bell Tower, Prague

Five days in Prague was never going to be enough. My trip t… https://t.co/NRkKRyMqRU https://t.co/9UrR7RCW1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonKiwiEmma If you ever want to get serious again, you're always welcome to guest blog with me! 💜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonKiwiEmma :) it's one of the reasons I wanted to give my blog a break. I wanted to try put more work into my thinky blog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonKiwiEmma Thank you for writing this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gloomy, rainy London https://t.co/TDwkmn9X96 https://t.co/PWQvBDgbuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JackCroxall @APassionBlog Thank you for the RT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommended doc - The Longest Road (2016) - about Yazidi refugees in Iraq and the effort to make a differenc… https://t.co/yjZo5t3Dxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht I really hope this is not the last performance of this play but really looking forward to what @ZooNationUK do next!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*New* Zoonation's The Mad Hatter’s Tea Party at the Roundhouse, London ★★★★★ https://t.co/mgB6F2ikMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this from @_projectlove_: Selina's Top 5 Lessons on Designing a Life She Loves https://t.co/5VIUj1Jq9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanisThomasMktg @CentralPictureH I might be able to make this one! It's just before a big exam but I've put it in… https://t.co/enwqDJsb39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely loving @ZooNationUK's #MadHattersTeaParty at the @RoundhouseLDN today! Fabulous explosion of colour and dance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇬🇧 A sea of flowers, gifts and love at George Michael's home in Highgate https://t.co/8kIVDtEF2S https://t.co/0QHNi6UDVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheLongestRoad is premiering at Rio Cinema, E8 on 18 February 2017 + Q&amp;A. See it if you can - £8 https://t.co/HC6ggm4x82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching the utterly devastating #thelongestroad documentary about Kurdish and Yezidi refugees fleeing ISIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mysehnsucht As long as you haven't bought in U.K. before, you'll qualify for a first time mortgage if you can accu… https://t.co/zTg46QobY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes, I had to stop watching that horror show because I was scared I was going to kick off on a swearing rage in my office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurrah! Good news as six found alive in Rigopiano avalanche hotel after two days  https://t.co/f0xjfX5rN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScreenjabberStu Yeah, some of them do 2 terms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatGirlRenita Sending much love. I think that is a postscript on many people's experience today. "RL + that other thing"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLButler76 I am on that particular issue. I feel very fortunate. I managed to resolve that. I hope you are too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLButler76 You too. Hard to know what to say, how to say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing chess in Sarajevo https://t.co/tVRUhU6ngU https://t.co/h9KEPq13ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Collidemusic you're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just been struggling for 3 hours to get a report to work. It appears that Little Miss Excel Queen was inputting 2017 not 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casa di Giulietta: one of Verona's main tourist attractions, the balcony where Romeo and J… https://t.co/vWQlDzQMyP https://t.co/SNGRhbZL08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another book-to-film (that we've read) for us to watch @lizzid82 @bookvsfilmclub https://t.co/Ui5PpMoz6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackCroxall That is VERY pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Collidemusic You can also name your price and all proceeds will go to Planned Parenthood. The lunatics are indeed taking over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amazing @CollideMusic are giving away "The Lunatics Have Taken Over The Asylum" ahead of that inauguration https://t.co/2BHLT8Oidg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurrah! Tickets finallyh booked to see my lovely friends in Auckland, NZ in September. Cannot wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Kent. You are looking lovely and sunny today. https://t.co/mrz3cFoXcQ https://t.co/Hce42yErDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow. I think this might be the best article on the present state of pop culture ever written #sherlock #starwars https://t.co/3pJNwj4ygJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jazz26 Oh no! I was hoping it would be easier than Corp Reporting!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>