<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Again....who's driving this train! https://t.co/B7kprCe1Fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone that supports Trump will forever be known as  an accomplice, not a victim! https://t.co/tDMxRnZyPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no......what is Trump gonna do? https://t.co/Cmj9arZmML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is Trump is pro-America???!!! https://t.co/RXkIgafsgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice........why do protests bother him so much.........hmmmm https://t.co/U5OtjfiHij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another BAD decision! https://t.co/KzrSeLRvph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmm.......Now what Donald?! https://t.co/IIkgzSUlFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does she write her own material?    LOL https://t.co/QcJu84Ld9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Publications should back out...... https://t.co/MnFmkp8BLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like we are living on another planet! https://t.co/bDPgVvJmON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Go ahead and hold your breath.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the world is a stage for Trump https://t.co/5SehkQPqX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly the con speaking gibberish again!    LOL https://t.co/SUE5hl6EzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We stand before you embarrassed Americans tonight....... https://t.co/GxUBuxYV75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  THATS ALL?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidWright_CNN @jaketapper @CNNPolitics  What a joke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is going on?! https://t.co/vHO6hBT9Ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is going on!? https://t.co/vHO6hBT9Ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for plain old common sense....... https://t.co/miroxuxFdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusiAaaaaaa @TheTweetwit Trump hasn't thought twice about it since he was there.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump brings out the worst in people....... https://t.co/JjzqPwbaKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would they do this!?  No self interest going on here, is there.... https://t.co/ZaRg5wLBBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NPR If thats the case, no more tax-free status. Can't have your cake and eat it too.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TDPattillo I suppose thats happening in the bathroom........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig Trump just doesn't get it yet, he is just not a likable guy!  Actually the opposite! He brings out the worst in people!  Sad...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KattyKayBBC I can't wait until your FIRED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WELL SAID!  And so true! https://t.co/asJ8Grk64L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost I'm quite sure he was clueless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @tarapalmeri  I guess when u sell your soul for $, don't expect much more....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pharris830 @politicususa WHY!?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too funny...... https://t.co/81N9XHvjBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump was a dumb deal! https://t.co/Ia8mASEGua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom @ericgobucks Trump can't do that anyways.  He just THINKS he is king.....lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Ya right....give me a break!  Milo should be on notice....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC is loosing their mind!  And viewership..... https://t.co/hAyigMzp3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conways family must be SO PROUD of her!  Would love to hear how she explains things to her kids as they grow.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyBeachluver @politico Time will tell.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Whatever!  Thats all the Trump team does is name call!  Can't waait for ALL of you to be unemployed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not nor will I ever be a part of the Trump cult! https://t.co/AR9cLpYs3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggrushko And people around him just smile......pretty sad.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Screw Trump!  Are you kidding me?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope all his business dealings tank! https://t.co/NkY5frCKSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get it!  Really!  When are people gonna realize what is happening here! https://t.co/gFOW1ONpkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracks me up! https://t.co/dV3Cb56O4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, I am blown away that republicans think this is okay. https://t.co/7cAXxwRm8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a jerk!  So embarrassing!  A real dictator! The republicans should be ashamed!  They ALL need to be out of job… https://t.co/0wf2qmzFPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he should wear another ring...... https://t.co/LWMwe1bsqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Don't watch the "SHOW"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOT  WATCHING!  Won't give him the satisfaction of 'numbers'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunterw @maggieNYT   Mother Superior.......lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How quickly Kellyanne thinks we forget! https://t.co/6dhDxxsjBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToDropADime2  Such a pig!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC  Cause Trump said so during his campaign......lol  WOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill So  will the majority........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Just trying to save the country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeltieTX Boy are they adorable!  Maybe he is part.....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeltieTX I really don't know....I rescued him from death row. Has a completely blue tongue though. Weighs 65 lbs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! Paul!  What is going to be a waste of your fucking time will be you kissing Trumps ass!  Don't think he will l… https://t.co/utswALsDyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics @NPR Sean tends to get excited......was he crying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MotherJones I can not even believe these people who represent US would allow DeVoe to be in charge of our education system!  Our youth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix  Only if we accept it is.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @AmandiOnAir @PressSec  As usual Spicer gave it a Community College try.....but BS is still BS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG!  Giuliani a cyber security expert?!  And I'm the Wizard of Oz https://t.co/REtdMgCdh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseCharlesLee @WOgaard Can't change history Sean....no matter how hard u try!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yea...... https://t.co/zTOAvfWh0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe a mere 18 months ago she was a demacrat and a pastor/minister!  My oh my.....what fame and money ca… https://t.co/0mSX8suuX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG!  They really are whacked! https://t.co/q7kSDDaRTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews Disappointing to hear Kelly say that.  Guess he won't be much help after all.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews Not to mention it takes 18 months min to go throgh vetting process.  Give me a break!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @EdSkipper She should be the first to go then.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews  I applaud them!  Trump is embarrassing!  Country before party boys......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  Thats even more disturbing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DirkDiggler918 @jennaportnoy @Fahrenthold   time will tell.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamstack @Susanforney @washingtonpost  What a joke she is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennaportnoy @Fahrenthold  Chaffetz needs to go!  Next election for sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews  Trump sure acts like he missed a few doses of his drugs.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sergenyt @Fahrenthold @nytimes II think not!  Americans can't even trust him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We stand behind you! https://t.co/yJw6JlCSzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touche! https://t.co/G1Dm08oUZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pablorodas Am I the only one who feels like this guy is creepy?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico  All the world is a stage for trump......like he always says....'enjoy the show!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't knw what its going to take for people to wake up! https://t.co/JSobkuoNlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @crampell @washingtonpost  It WILL cost them in the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan needs to go.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully wasn't by any water........ https://t.co/PrYFM7kmqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Win what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What adult does this!!! No less the President! https://t.co/2W3PJVG3vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[READ!  Scary! https://t.co/tQqO8troMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico WHAT!  You need to go if you really believe that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is not making America safe again....he's making it unsafe! Only 10 days into this mess and people r really regretting this presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still want investigation into Russia hacking, want to see tax returns, want divestment of business!  These are not going away with all ur BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is such a divider! https://t.co/493eLTw0do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @POTUS What the hell does he have to do?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is a complete incompetent politician!  Country before party!  Come on people!  Can't believe your not feeling it yet........?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG!  Where are we?  Planet earth???? https://t.co/03Ij2WswkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media!  STOP Kellyanne Conway from news shows. We already know her lies! Its redundant! If she has something new, o… https://t.co/ymt0Qbq68m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REALLY!!!!!  Read this! https://t.co/q2mNtodlDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @puppymnkey   Didn't now this hag was still relevant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Everything Trump is doing is a mistake!  This learning curve is way too unrealistic!  Like trying to teach a toddler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally....a normal voice we are used too..... https://t.co/e3lV7CCmeg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>