<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn Yay! service cancelled! goodbye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn apparently I have to be a network technician and perform a bunch of tests to get my internet that YOU provide me, fixed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn got through to customer service, said they can't help. If that's the case i want my money back, and no cancellation fees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn this happens everyday between 6pm and 11pm but does also happen at other times of day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn the latency can last for minutes at a time during which almost all websites and online services do not work at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn between https://t.co/NjTSsPjtiT and https://t.co/cWIQCYNQH7 there is a frequent periodic latency spike of up to 4 seconds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn Fix my internet please. I'll post a screenshot of a trace route that shows you exactly where the p… https://t.co/jjlRxWlo1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UBET No one wins from gambling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiDarryn Nope, still no call back. I tried calling again but was on hold for almost 2 hours and gave up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iselect I don't think further investigation is needed. iiNet don't pick up the phone, they are unreachable. You should never recommend them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iselect I'm very unhappy with you recommending me @iinet. They have been nothing but terrible in every way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet Customer Service said they would call me back and they never did. Continues to be worst ISP ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet continues to be the worst ISP I've ever had. I'm changing. Anyone know who's good in West Melbourne? https://t.co/jUPHqU1DyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the tune of Britney Spears's Baby One More Time: 
Oops Turnbull did it again. He sold out our lives, for political gain. Oh baby, baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull needs to grow some balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$%&amp;! publishers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know how to monetise India, Thailand, Vietnam and Indonesia? For some reason of they are now 60% of our user base and climbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majicDave correct and fits perfectly with Homer Simpson's advice, never try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updating plugins is still the worst part of unity development]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarNight1100 there's no release date for Major Mayhem 2 yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiBri_ Speed test a couple minutes later when i'm getting bad ping from the same machine on Ethernet https://t.co/9l0IB7i4hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet @iiBri_ Yes my PC is connected by Ethernet. My lap top over wifi also has the same problems so it's no wifi or a cable problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iinet I pay for 25Mbits. I only get 4Mbits mostly and cut outs constantly. I have fibre to the door, no wifi... What am I paying for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda Most of you power bill is not from power generation, it's from network upkeep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda don't worry Australia, Helen Clark has this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@testflightapp I and some of my beta testers are having trouble downloading my app. The download speed seem really slow for some users.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda No. 90% of NZers voting is wrong. Stats say 76.77% of enrolled people voted in the last election, only 3 of 5 mil people are enrolled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda I think we need a new word to be honest, 'It' doesn't really cut the mustard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda Economy is built on growth. If your birth rate is negative you better hope immigrants want to come to your country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if Apple is still rejecting apps that have guns in the icon or screenshots?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kunaalarya @jakeaschulte Oh true. Where are you now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kunaalarya Hey mate, I got a GDC drink invite, thanks. Can I +1?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DallasStars Will you still be providing us a Stars game highlight packages now that https://t.co/0Eq8XQMuVQ isn't doing them anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updating XCode will take my me 2 days! Australia's internet speed is not hurting the tech sector at all! (Sarcasm)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz Dear @billbennettnz, your tweet is inappropriate and NSFW. Is this what you intend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @steam_games: Blockpocalypse https://t.co/OwskXltvZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgreg I'll be using my own UI, so I won't have as many headaches hopefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgreg I haven't attempted UI with it yet. Not looking forward to that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgreg It does a lot of stuff ok... but simple things become horrendously difficult at times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Mecanim.... Sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_caratelli @jboggsie If we both get pasted the Semi's and that's a big IF, it'll be 3AM on 1st of November.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#QandA 'he did', 'she did', 'you did', 'I didn't'. passing the blame... Who cares just fix the current situation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#QandA how many Australians speak aboriginal languages?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay, Abbott is gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorKarl Does nothing require them as a food source?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prime_31 That feature has been in since Windows 8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz Yeah, I'm not sure crowd sourcing would work as well for mobile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz I'll have to do a work count and figure it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz Yeah... subscription scares me. I think I'd go with OneSky for that reason, 10 cents a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz Worth it? I'm looking at OneSky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz Hey, What was that localisation service you're using for Mini Metro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see why no one watches the news in Aus after seeing 2 weeks of nothing but Bronwyn Bishop. I don't want to see her face any more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda Q And A should be on every night...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda Why is Ron Boswell here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailebree Is there a 'request a female driver option'? Maybe only offer it to confirmed female users to protect drivers too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda Why can't cab drivers just switch to be Uber drivers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#qanda No job is safe, change builds the future. Coal is dying, the longer you prop up an industry the bigger the pain when it falls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biggest programming hate: _Object2World instead of _ObjectToWorld, well done, you save 1 character! I'm looking at you @unity3d!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage isn't just for Christians so why do they get to dictate the terms? #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so impossibly hard to find someone you know on Steam?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally after over a year of development my Skiing game is starting to show its potential!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djedery Pay bot downloaders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only one question in my mind about self driving cars. How easy can real drivers troll them and their passengers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama meets @davidattenburro, great Barack has the right priorities. David is the person I want to meet most in my life! So jealous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonyblackett Most people don't want to be angry every day. The easiest solution is to burry your head in the sand, sadly it doesn't help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see why no one gives a crap about politics in Australia, everything you hear coming from the government makes you so f-ing angry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonyblackett I wouldn't be surprised if 90% of their players stop there. It's stupidly hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ori and the Blind Forest was fun until you have to escape the water. Now it suddenly impossibly hard and there are no save points.. WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jurassic Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you write Random.value follow these steps:
Stop.
Delete it.
Rethink what you're doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrischen97 @MrAshleyLeach Nah, I mean the real boring stuff, like Tax!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrAshleyLeach @chrischen97 @chrischen97 You can do all my boring stuff as research!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nixontim nah, gameplay is ok, I'm not too far into it but it's not too hard. It's more a puzzle platformer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nixontim who cares. It looks so petty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ori and the blind Forest is simply beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF 12GBs for Poolnation FX? It's a room with a pool table and it's got more data than the uncharted series...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amazingafroman At least I haven't had to download any system updates... yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amazingafroman Australian... New Zealand is a tiny bit faster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 hours later my new 8GB game has almost finished downloading! Console gaming of the future is here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every game I want to play is over 8GBs.... For anyone making a large game, please make it smaller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange Not really, it's a clone genre, it's like making a C&amp;Clike, GTAlike, CrossyRoadlike game...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do people that hate game clones hate all Roguelike games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PipsqueakGames @appannie Turns out the internet cable from Aus -&gt; NZ -&gt; LA was cut so there have been some issues with internet here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majicDave you're a rich white male, Texan law was made to protect you and only you. Nothing to fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appannie fyi: Seem to be having issues loading your website. There are no images and the layout is completely broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone else had trouble linking  @AdColony for Unity iOS lately?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydw I didn't click anything! Just test views]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've earned 9 cents from implementing and testing ad providers today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chartboost Unity iOS integration was actually the easiest thing ever. Nice work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone got tips on Chartboost vs AdMob in iOS and Android? Which generally performs better etc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a game takes forever to make you have no choice but to press on... it sucks. it really does...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rushdigital I miss it so much! Post me some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mouse click was blocked by an ad I blocked with ad block...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to prove you live in Australia to Medicare, but I bet it's hard to prove you don't to the Tax Department...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost Already collect it. Corner of Elizabeth St/Lonsdale St Melbourne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost just don't worry about it. I'm over it. I'll collect my goods today and just accept that it's damaged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost I have, and answered that question about 7 times for 7 people. I even have to get it faxed to the claims team twice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost Well played @auspost , I give up... I guess I'll just retrieve my damaged goalie glove and accept that this will never be resolved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorKarl Plastic doesn't conduct/retain heat well giving water a place condense before steam is removed from environment..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I wanted to do was make my own games... Now I'm stuck running a company. Sigh...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>