<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Followed, 2 Unfollowed me (monitored by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my new 1 followers and goodbye to 5 unfollowers (FREE stats by https://t.co/Z0xoLtl0EJ)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 24 Hours = 7 Followers and 2 Unfollowers (stats by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO app)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no, I start school tomorrow :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of getting the Canon EOS M3 for vlogging on the new channel!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 50 subs on the new channel! Thanks https://t.co/KQVVjyqRSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any ideas for next video??????????? https://t.co/wFrYG8zJ5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK I'm going to record that video now¡!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K guys I'm about to buy some stuff for a video so I won't be on yt or twitter so hopefully the video goes well! :) bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Video!!?Hopefully you enjoy it ;) https://t.co/aycF85vRQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Morning everyone, it's really bad outside so I can't vlog today 😱]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 24 Hours = 3 Followers and 1 Unfollowers (stats by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO app)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok i finished editing and i really REALLY need to sleep if i want to do a timelapse for tomoz vlog, good night everyone :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who is active? like for a follow!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going to do a record a vlog tomoz for the second channel hopefully its not raining!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to edit my new video now! https://t.co/HHKIbefyg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the new channel if you guys havent subbed :) https://t.co/YX8R64jOzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone can make me a banner for my 2 channels i think they are relly good, i will give them a shoutout. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of doing a collab with someone, if you want to be that someone dm me then we can think of something. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for you guys to see this video! 😂😂 https://t.co/LutkbTp3Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some videos ready for upload! cant wait to upload them :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What banner for the new channel? https://t.co/y1iS83n7Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you guys like the banner for the new channel? https://t.co/kg6UhjTMuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'Chill Shoutout Stream! | Gain Fast Subs :)' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lit Shout-out LIVE! https://t.co/OZ3mPrX80z via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'Chill Shoutout Stream!' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I stream again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @nickthatprick https://t.co/I06V11Emqm New Intro!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshGuyYT its 12:00am for me so I also need to sleep! Good night Josh :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any good, cheap vlogging cameras with a flip out screen recommendations, im going to be doing vlogging on the new channel. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[haven't made a video in few days, I might try to get a video out tomorrow and a video for the new channel aso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeDodsonYT yeah i might not do one now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest Stats = 1 Followers and 2 Unfollowers (tracked by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lachie14_ for cheap!!!!!!! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any good vlogging cameras with flip out screen u guys would recommend????????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if there is a vlogging camera you guys could recommend that would be much appreciated (plz be cheap)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you havent already subbed to my channel make sure you do :) https://t.co/YX8R64jOzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys I'm going to do a $15 gift card giveaway at 1.5k :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for 20 subs on the new channel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im streaming now come and join]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im streaming now plz watch for a shoutout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'My YouTube Stream' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[should i stream now??????????????????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'My Shoutout Stream' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'CHILL STREAM! SHOUTOUT STREAM ' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys I'm thinking of doing vlogs, challenges on my new channel so hopefully that should be fun :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone has a series on my channel I can do that would be much appreciated and I'll give your channel a little shoutout also :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are wondering I'm going to be uploading 2 videos on my new channel and 1 or 2 on my old channel every week :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling of doing a challenge video so send me some! example: chubby bunny, accent etc :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SynDarkPrince accent challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest Stats = 2 Followers and 6 Unfollowers (tracked by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not me!!! Please help https://t.co/6biGNEs5IA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyHK1219 I don't have another account bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people faking to be me?? If I'm being mean to u I promise u it's not me I don't have another account, LOOK https://t.co/UpxKE0N7Be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come watch my first stream it is pretty lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my live stream: 'My First Stream' at https://t.co/ab3Qrd5Uid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome To My Channel! (Channel Trailer 2017) - ImNick https://t.co/FXmKqPcAE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any gfx designers that can be my designer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome To My Channel! (Channel Trailer 2017) - ImNick: https://t.co/0HExixH8Yc via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What thumbnail should I choose? https://t.co/2C2rieKmAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished editing 2 videos and now it's 3:00am and I have training at 9:00am so I REALLY need some sleep!😴😴💤💤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesSuarez1001 I got notifications on but I'm not getting notifications and they are not going to sub boxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Followed, 10 Unfollowed me (monitored by https://t.co/g5ybedKHCg)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*NEW CHANNEL!* Please only subscribe if you are going to stay active on the channel 😄 
➤ https://t.co/YX8R642dHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@X2Jashade really...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🔥If I do make a new channel what should the name be?🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have something to say... *PLEASE WATCH* https://t.co/Fijigfh05H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[K GUYS IMPORTANT VIDEO COMING OUT IN 20 MINUTES??!!!🔔🔔🔔🔔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just recorded a very serious video, when do you guys want to see it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I make a new channel for other things such ass tutorials for youtube?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldblade15 @YouTube @DurvyYT no don't watch durv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlayerGraphics bro it's 1 sub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my new 9 followers and goodbye to 3 unfollowers (FREE stats by https://t.co/Z0xoLtl0EJ)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshGuy_Gaming I didn't get a notification for your video :( but I really did enjoy the video :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sss video and my latest video haven't been doing very well but I'm going to keep trying to pull my self together! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recorded 2 videos today and I think they are going to be my best ever videos ever! Not sure when I will upload it tho :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*New Video* Like, Comment, Share for a 40% higher chance to win a shoutout! NOT JOKING https://t.co/ernK9yLz4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won't be on YouTube/twitter for the whole day but there is a video in about 5 hours hopefully you guys enjoy it 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshGuy_Gaming oh just found it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshGuy_Gaming really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 13 followers and lost 2 (stats by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my video tomorrow if we hit 40 likes in 2 hours I will crack 3 eggs on my head on the video on Friday! Deal. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone makes me good gfx for my channel you will a shoutout on that week! 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go subscribe to @Lachie14_ he is 9 away from 400 subscribers! Tell him i sent you for a 20% higher chance to win a shoutout :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What videos do you guys want to see this week or next week? I'm open to any video ideas 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's active? Just wondering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send me some dares I can do for next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send me ideas for challenges? eg: crossbar, chilli pepper etc :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any suggestions for videos for the future, if I think it is a good one I might give u a shoutout in that video ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 24 Hours = 13 Followers and 3 Unfollowers (stats by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO app)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like, comment and share the next 3 videos you will get a 40% higher chance of winning the shoutout next week. also do the other rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*NEW VIDEO* Watch it NOW! https://t.co/x6uUEOovFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recorded 4 videos time to edit GRIND DON'T STOP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveeTube @JoshGuy_Gaming u deserve it bro, i see you everywhere in the comments :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or...
🔥Upload Schedule🔥
•Tuesday 12:30pm 
•Friday 12:30pm 
•Sunday 8:00pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🔥Upload Schedule🔥
•Tuesday 12:30pm 
•Thursday 12:30pm 
•Friday 12:30pm 
•Sunday 8:00pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@12345678kar I can't upload everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What days/times do u want me to upload?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wondering should I do 3 uploads or 4 per week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 1 followers and lost 6 (stats by https://t.co/g5ybee2itO)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>