<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lola91525202 and also because you put every thing in CAPS doesn't make your point stronger. Lastly go spew your hate somewhere else ðŸ‘‹ðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lola91525202 @ClintLamsdell I am Muslim and obviously I know many others. Stop taking the wrong doings of a few to justify the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lola91525202 @ClintLamsdell what about what Pope Francis said or do you know the Bible more than he does?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lola91525202 @ClintLamsdell And what about the Canadians that took refugees in? It worked out for several/most of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell if you are so keen on talking about Jesus, you should know what the Bible says about refugees...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell Also we have our own homegrown killers (like Dylann Roof). Should we vet all white males then? ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell and this: https://t.co/hkV66fMZPa?
Pls don't give me: This is fake news ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell plus no terrorists from these countries. He didn't include Saudi Arabia or Pakistan. Just saying ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell do you know how the vetting process in place already works? It's already a lengthy and stringent process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell LOL. It's easy to say it's only a few days when your family is next to you safe and sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell listen let's agree to disagree. You try to imply so hard that black voters can't think for themselves. It's mind boggling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell it should be the woman's  choice. No one is forced to have an abortion. Pro-choice is the only chance to have safe abortions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell so should I agree with Trump then? After all he's doing to Muslims and refugees? And what he says/did to African Americans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell  and especially not with Bannon and Sessions in this administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell @CWill101x @rolandscahill plus for years now African Americans do not support Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell @CWill101x @rolandscahill where did I say I was a dem? You are making assumptions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell @CWill101x @rolandscahill the connection you are trying to make isn't relevant ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintLamsdell @CWill101x @rolandscahill should I thank them for doing the right thing? Slavery shouldn't have happened in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Is Douglass coming? I want to join then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blurred_Trees @CharlesMBlow you are Canadian so you get a pass but this is crazy for American leaders esp if you are going to talk abt it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone wondering why we need #BlackHistory month â˜¹ï¸ https://t.co/JCx7HsVh03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonefiasco your polls are always so lit. We need them more often ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crazydionneee @simonefiasco I'm screaming too now. Yaass ðŸ™ŒðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[story of our lives @saeromz ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/MXKeyQaHPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlanoellee I am sure you are still looking fine ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brown_Saraah so dramatic but so much fun too haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJRayle @CWill101x @rolandscahill why would I move? This is my country as much as it is yours. I'll defend my opinions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeDunbar88 @CWill101x @rolandscahill if you don't like my opinions don't get in my mentions ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeDunbar88 @CWill101x @rolandscahill Im sure I'm more educated than you are... Prob speak more languages than you do too ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustMaiaLuck1 @spicysean1971 @gabgizfluff @rolandscahill @CWill101x sigh love is love. Doesn't matter if it's between a man &amp; woman or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @realDonaldTrump we wish. Prob another reckless EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roccobear @BeatoBrandy @realDonaldTrump ugh these people... they'll never learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeatoBrandy @realDonaldTrump we are alienating allies and putting us at even more risk for attacks too: https://t.co/Ubm5EhjdZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeatoBrandy @realDonaldTrump many are getting hurt because of these nonsense EOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeatoBrandy @realDonaldTrump before you vote next time, please read about the candidates' platforms, the impact of their actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeatoBrandy @realDonaldTrump Please read on this. There is difference plus why are we worried about what Obama did? He's no longer Pdt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the last day to enroll in #Obamacare (ACA). You will still be covered until the end of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kissapittman @realDonaldTrump OMG: Did you do your homework before voting? Doesn't look like it otherwise you would have known about Pence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madpiper65 @SirDaveyBoy @NicholasTerry3 @FoxNews a tweet below isn't a correction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews You should take this tweet down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews when are you going to fix this? Are you into #alternativefacts too? You should be ashamed. This is irresponsible reporting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@multiahjussi He wasn't feeling it LMAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsilverman1234 @BuzzFeed @kitchensense They would need to start with Bannon so this is unlikely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mitchsmith_96 I read what you said. That's why I'm saying wait a few hours first before tweeting. Better safe than sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mitchsmith_96 it's important to wait until more info becomes available otherwise you contribute to spreading lies &amp; fueling hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RapinBill Stop spreading lies. The suspect is French-Canadian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan do you care to address the Muslim Ban? Quit tap-dancing around the issue. https://t.co/PIBHyOMyNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if I should ðŸ˜‚ or ðŸ˜­. https://t.co/H0HN1O5NY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aissa_rose Sigh, I don't blame you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The long list of Republicans in Congress who have taken no position on Trump's refugee ban https://t.co/Bpn6GBJJOX via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperslug419 Ah we all wanted someone other than him. It keeps getting worst and worst. Hope we can all survive the next 4 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperslug419 LOOL my bad. I have been reading these Trump Regrets tweets and some people have said so many ignorant stuff. My apologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IHeartDelish @JTgetreal @realDonaldTrump some people don't care as long as it doesn't affect them directly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperslug419 @realMattyOBrien When was he different? I am curious. Please enlighten us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ml2_dl2uGp3rs0N @Sharon_Rins @DannyDShai "Very kind to their slaves" LOL. You would know because you are a former slave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ml2_dl2uGp3rs0N @DannyDShai So Brownie points for not inventing it? ðŸ™„ Just because they purchased them doesn't make it right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the definition of zaddy? #GongYoo ðŸ˜ https://t.co/EWAd5iFgJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCCountryboy01 @AmyMek Sure it's easier to run away when you disagree and have 0 concrete facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCCountryboy01 @AmyMek Also there are more than 1 billion Muslims. If we were all terrorists, the world would be a living hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCCountryboy01 @AmyMek They believe in the same God. Muslims recognize Moses, Jesus and Abraham as prophets. Again, you must not know many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyMoore0525 @realDonaldTrump Did you not care when he bullied Muslims, gays, POC, disabled people? I want to feel bad for you but I can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCCountryboy01 @AmyMek Proof/link or it didn't happen. Also can you take the actions of a few to represent a whole religion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So...? We are going to pretend Pence didn't say this? 
https://t.co/NCzH0RcjUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth Sure. The obvious meaning #alternativefacts? I am done with you ðŸ˜‚ I'll encourage you to read more and to stop spewing hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth Lastly: https://t.co/mSggasfJTB
Please read and educate yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth I gave you that as an example to show how your thought process is illogical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth I am not. Calling me names doesn't help. Can't you have a debate without calling people names or what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth And there are plenty of radical terrorists who are not Muslims. Again, Dylann Roof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth You said it's a satanic religion. Did I miss something? Unless you want to take that back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth This is coming from a fellow citizen who also happens to be Muslim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth Stop using the actions of a few to lump all Muslims together. There are good and bad ones. Same with Christians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth If all were terrorist following a satanic religion, imagine how the world would be? A living hell. 4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth That doesn't make much sense does it? Also there are over 1 billion Muslims in the world. 3/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth All white people hate black people and we should avoid them/ban them 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth These things happen but can you blame an entire religion? If I was to follow your logic, let's take the case of D. Roof 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth You said it's a satanic religion so I am replying. I guess you are not open to a constructive discussion. ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCCountryboy01 @AmyMek I am a Muslim American. I don't think I've ever imposed my religion on anyone. I bet you don't know many Muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanDepth hum did you know Jesus and Moses are recognized as prophets in the Quran? Then what does that make Judaism and Christianity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear America you keep sinking lower and lower #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevenwhirsch99 and you call yourself a Christian? The irony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmiffMadness @MoWiseness Smh. You have no idea how stressed out I am. Every single time I read the news I freak out even more. WELP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devos shows that with privilege and money you can afford to be mediocre #DeVosFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFFerraro @Luvvie He's so zaddie. If only had the guts and brains smh ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScienceMarchDC please think about how people can get involved even after the march!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcomAlvarez4 @realDonaldTrump Are you even for real? I don't understand people like you. Voting is not a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Is it too late to send you letters? I'm sure many will appreciate the opportunity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samwhiteout If we ever wondered what 1984 by G. Orwell truly meant we get a taste of it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissLizzyNJ plus why should we pay for this wall with our tax money when Trump himself hasn't released his tax returns yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissLizzyNJ do you even know how immigration contributes to society? If not, please educate yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissLizzyNJ are your ancestors Native Americans? Pretty sure they were illegal too then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChantelChivon @realDonaldTrump if thats what you think. There is a documentary that the BBC did on abortion in Malawi. Try listening to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChantelChivon @realDonaldTrump You have the right to be pro-life but we should not dictate what others can and cannot do with their bodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChantelChivon @realDonaldTrump this will not prevent abortion. It will only prevent safe ones and limit access to other essential services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetatertot2 Did God personally tell you that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddieHudson @raidernation210 @CharlesPointer2 @SheriffClarke We don't even want to claim Sheriff Clarke. They can have him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChantelChivon @realDonaldTrump Did you do your homework before voting? A simple Google search would have helped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY- Masterkraft ft Flavour and Sarkodie (Official video) https://t.co/06oajGLbIv via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HunterDuncan26 ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¿ Would you mind answering the question though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teachmety @HunterDuncan26 I really want the answer to this question too... I hope he or she replies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Honey223344 @sweetatertot2 at this point, I think she's just doing this for attention....]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>