<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySports_Keith Ulloa news please ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hornets send me one in Canberra, Australia please ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 @ChristinaaRa so was I ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 @ChristinaaRa I'd like to see Cena retire now... I'm sick of WWE all together, I'm all on UFC currently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 @ChristinaaRa at least they didn't job him out, 5 AA's Cena did... Decent match! I'm more upset with reigns at 30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 @ChristinaaRa horrible!!!! No Benjamin, Joe, Balor, Rollins, Mysterio, angle or Aries!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinaaRa worst rumble I've seen since 2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcoraiders @FCBarcelona way too true bro!!! I hate the la liga full stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orton!!! Thank god reigns didn't win... Deffs not watching another show until Benjamin comes back #wweiscrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst rumble ever!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NRLAKL9s @brodiekane @KhanjaniNazanin @TeuilaBlakely can I have a crack at Naz? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed = GOAT ðŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daria_gav I'd prefer Dasha to go all the way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Frampton walking out to will Griggs on fire ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its way too hot, need winter back so badly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time next week its Nines, two weeks later its the trial and then two weeks after that is round 1 ðŸ˜ the off season is driving me insane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viking clap at the trial match anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcoraiders home to the best team in the world as well ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox I take the piss 24/7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox I'm taking the piss ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox haha well I'm good looking so that's all that matters ðŸ’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox watching tennis ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox hmm very productive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelslovatox of course they need me, look at me... ðŸ’ Bit of stalking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavs turn down deal for Melo and k love trade, very wise... Love more valuable to them then Melo would be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersCanberra @giostadium @JordanTurner89 stay tuned for how long?! #cantwait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZacBaileyFOX hey mate! Any official release date on the new channel fox league?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barca_Raiders @gilby_gillard best raiders team since 95!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilby_gillard if he performs in the trial, he is in round 1 for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilby_gillard Taylor over priest comfortably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Culturekings please open up a Canberra store! We need you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addman72 the four horsemen!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be very afraid opposition forward packs, be very afraid https://t.co/EHdASAYUXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsch1996 omg I just saw the ad ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg NRL isn't far away ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/EpDoqY6OLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bloody love Gavrilova!!! What a champion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLW_Mole inconsistent, who knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barca_Raiders @addman72 @RLW_Mole a nice tomato or a few to the head will do a world of good ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addman72 @RLW_Mole Im just curious, seems to gone quiet... Sacked won't happen!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLW_Mole whats gonna happen with papalii? Fine, suspension, sacked?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand new @DangeRussWilson Jersey arrived!! Biggest fan from Australia ðŸ’šðŸ’™ @Seahawks @SeahawksProShop #Seahawks https://t.co/p3niPhEjjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davekosar2 can't say I've seen her in a bikini but I can just imagine ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackLuland @joshpapalii and your boys Fifita, Barba, Gallen the drug cheat and Ennis are all saints? Hahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingHernandez81 @Seahawks back bigger and better next season, hopefully stay injury free...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lee_Gaskin1 definition of lazy journalism ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear my wardrobe consists of only raiders and NBA stuff these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Veteran_Status @marcoraiders I can't wait ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ papalii Dally m backrower of the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcoraiders @Veteran_Status I love papa, he will have a big 2017!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcoraiders @Veteran_Status papa is one of our best players, we all make mistakes... Not like he bashed his wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Veteran_Status @marcoraiders sacked is an overreaction, he hasn't even been charged yet... I wouldn't even fine him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw that @PaoloSchirripa and I were on the season review today ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/7j5iXf6Pnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunderlandAFC11 bisping the legend!! @PaoloSchirripa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 and your boy D'Angelo Russell will be something special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingWallyy1 yep yep, I also love Karl Anthony towns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MckillopTony was that 1995 against the Broncos? I'm so jealous!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brett Mullins was the biggest freak, sad I never got to experience it live #tooyoung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barring disaster... Safe to say welcome to the raiders roster Dave Taylor! Can't wait to see you full steam ahead in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil I'll give you that... ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil well yeah it does, enjoy fourth place again this season xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil straight from the headquarters in Milan... Okay love whatever floats your boat ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil my wallet suggests otherwise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil I am lactose intolerant ðŸ˜‚ the only suits I wear are from Armani ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil he should have but now he's stuck with a perfect child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil did you meet me then? Cheese is foul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonicaLauriola how are Croatia ahead of us? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMTIMMcINTYRE_ like was he snobbish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMTIMMcINTYRE_ he was nice everytime i met him but maybe because I was 10... Was he rude to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back at primary school stuff from 2005 and it's safe to say that I loved Clinton shichofscke and mal meninga ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merryl Streep said football and MMA aren't arts, I've never even heard of her up until today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karl Anthony towns is elite ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karl-Anthony Towns #NBAVote
https://t.co/2TaVt1ioYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReadSunderland I'm interested! Although I live in Australia, would that be an issue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a week or two internship... My field of expertise is being a sports writer, if anyone knows anyone please let me know ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really excited for the @SydneyKings retro gear to come out, really want that warm up shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossdog4 pic collage! The best one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barca_Raiders omg yes! Going to Melbourne on Saturday! Hopefully can get my hands on a Devin booker jersey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barca_Raiders did they sell cheap basketball jerseys as well? Yeah they look mad bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barca_Raiders wow!! Did they have a few teams available? I'll be there Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtsialis @bigleaguemag congratulations!! I would love an internship at big league ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsbetcomau facemask or not it was an amazing catch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring on the Falcons!! Great win... #Seahawks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rawls is on fire!!!! You beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richardson ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rawls on fire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsbetcomau Russell Wilson half asleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on dangeruss, wake up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Rawls is so valuable #Seahawks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #NBAVote is going to Chris Paul, aka #ChrisDeals because he has the best deals around. 
https://t.co/sTu3JvGJ0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[antetokounmpo is an absolute freak #NBAVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LAClippers @JCrossover 2 in a row!! Great start to 2016, wait til we get Blake and cp3 back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLW_Mole just picked this up! I'll know every answer by the end of the night if I don't already know them ðŸ˜œ https://t.co/IxqOZMBDg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NRLFootyShow clay priest ain't a young gun ðŸ˜‚lazy journalism there, Nick cotric is the young gun for the Canberra Raiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RSherman_25 fly me to Seattle from Australia and we have a deal ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ky3wWvGZtW these predictions are making me excited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Milan_Ccs @TheMilanBible no he shouldn't, so he plays not even half the season and scores 2 penalties?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brayanvillalta2 @TheMilanBible Berardi made of glass, penalty merchant...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeslootHozil older relatives using technology? Come on ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NrlBall 
Canberra 
Knights 
Qld
Rapana
Hodgson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seahawks @TRawls810 give it to Jimmy;!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>