<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[An adroit summary of the evidence for human-induced #climate change, an existential threat to civilisation and powe… https://t.co/u91PqRup5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixANZ When will we get The Expanse season 2? Please reply as I've asked 3 times now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those protesters are radical leftist anarchists, many paid actors. No-one reasonable opposes Trump policy.… https://t.co/yYTmuk0B1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand this intimately. Currently in the process of moving to the country from a city flat to try a whole dif… https://t.co/HkI6TpYXAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott did same in Aus using 3 imaginary "crises": govt debt, carbon tax, mining tax, then attacked science, poor,… https://t.co/WGooarsDg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Diet is extremely important to physical and mental #health. With Drumpf's diet I'm surprised he's lived this long.… https://t.co/YWnCKOnFZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia is annexing Syria, China the SC Sea; US run by clowns with guns. WW III within a decade likely outcome. #auspol #uspoli #bifftimeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This path to severe civil disruption will eventually lead to #martiallaw or #civilwar in the US, and global destabilisation. #auspol #uspoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've said repeatedly Reps will use Drumpf to do what they couldn't get away with then scapegoat him. It has begun. #auspol #uspoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this thread. https://t.co/vmt9DiSA8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thing about that piece is I agree with him about crony capitalism destroying the social contract. The r… https://t.co/fzQcgzVm0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUST READ: #fascists tell the #truth about what they're going do do then #lie about what they did. https://t.co/9SU3VvLmTJ #auspol #uspoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham Silence = dog whistling to his party's RWNJs and scared of rise of One Nation. Utterly spineless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so obvious! It's painful to watch Aus fall behind when we should be leading world's #energy transformation.… https://t.co/MKeDtQQalm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus had wrecker Abbott undo Gillard's great work. US has Trump turn it into a fascist state within a week. #bizarroworld #worldgonemad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fix this tomorrow:
1 end diesel rebate to miners 6bn
2 tax multinats 10-20bn
3 end super tax concession to top 20%… https://t.co/fiwZ4HZw2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My answer is always simple: total global funding for #climate research since 1980 ~$72bn; fossil fuel industry ~$8t… https://t.co/v6Ua16QX07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to a wedding in Byron about 5 years ago and the infrastructure was a shambles. Tragedy of the Commons. https://t.co/AG6HVam1G7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaucerburnt I get that, but he should be fought head on. Coward/sucker punching him, or anyone, is despicable and cowardly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieKia I'm still getting "Sorry that page does not exist".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently I took issue with civilised people celebrating #cowardpunching of anyone (fascist or otherwise). Pls watch: https://t.co/TSoMcWQA4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Political #polarisation: during a Drumpf speech I hear a petulant 12yo lying about everything; his supporters hear "it's our time now".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's worse than that: neolib pollies/businessmen across globe are rorting system so as to bankrupt govts. It's part… https://t.co/dDFJxGU6P5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilltophoods I saw you guys play to 30 people in Canberra supporting DJ Ca$h Money back in the day... knew you'd be huge. Glad you are! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J1mMcD0nald Only had 140chs James! ;) @jurylady5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUST READ: anyone can fall for gaslighting, so know the techniques and protect yourself. #auspol https://t.co/zj6I4xJyxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're annoyed by my recent preocc with Drumpf, sorry. But his policies are the opposite of #sustainability, #transparency and #progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of that. His speeches smack of low self-esteem or some other kind of ego disorder - always patting himself on t… https://t.co/8AKVPIjUVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how you stifle peaceful protest: arrest everyone in the area (regardless of their actions) and charge with… https://t.co/o8TB8fqZNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraging populace deep into #debt is a clever pacifying strategy: striking is anathema with mortgage/credit cards to pay. #stagnantwages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In that metaphor Trump is one of the wheedling Trade Federation leaders: a pawn in a game far beyond his comprehension. #uspoli #starwars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I hear "Trump" or "POTUS" my brain now plays the Imperial March. #starwarscometolife #evilempire #darkside #uspoli #starwars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Truthtelling: https://t.co/53HzLGkAmu #science #democracy  #alternativefacts #orwellian  #doublethink #censorship #propaganda @GlobalEcoGuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reforms: 
1 Limit donations to citizens only
2 Cap at $200pa 
3 One vote per party member
#Democracy for the people… https://t.co/73CD9N4Q29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were the best PM we've had in many years: built concensus, made major reforms in a hung parliament. Thank you f… https://t.co/hZxlrQrrGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AustraliaDay should be about #GRATITUDE, not jingoism or competative nationalism. And the date should change. #invasionday #my2cents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGWelch Interesting. Regardless, the idea of corpns suing govts over policy is anathema to me. ISDS stands in way of env/soc justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGWelch I used the word "tribunal" as shorthand. It's really just a panel of ex-corporate lawyers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGWelch Not in ISDS they aren't. The govt being sued does not get to represent itself from what I've read. And there are no appeals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ISDS: multinats suing govts for POTENTIALLY profit-infringing laws in extra-judicial tribunals without representation #TPP #bigscam #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Aus signs bilateral trade agreements instead, examine carefully. If they contain #ISDS they're as bad as #TPP. @TurnbullMalcolm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TPP persistence shows @TurnbullMalcolm's true colours: self-hating govt desperate to hand power to multinats (which he won't tax). #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @TurnbullMalcolm so in love with #TPP? It's a massive power grab by multinational corpns, and Aus doesn't have many of those. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixANZ When will we get to see the second season of The Expanse? Can't wait! Best serious sci-fi series since Battlestar Galactica.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any way to filter my feed to ignore all references to Trump? Otherwise I might just have to delete my account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only self hating govts would sign TPP: ISDS provisions will make policy-making largely irrelevant. @TurnbullMalcolm… https://t.co/VbZfMdujDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that's enough on the #USclusterfuck from me. Back to #sustainability tweets and building the #Hillfort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question to all Drumpf supporters: what will you do when he has tanked your economy, lined his own pockets, and started another war? #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You simply can't make this stuff up! Don't be surprised when the information is verified and impeachment follows.… https://t.co/WMtdUbfZ0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically, IPA promotes extreme neoliberalism, wants Aus to follow in disastrous footsteps of US/UK. And they're getting it done. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaaaahahaaaa. Translators can't translate Drumpf because he says nothing coherent! #auspol #uspol https://t.co/6wC27v2zsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwipaulb I despised TPP for ISDS, IP and pharma provisions. It was a disaster. But somehow Trump couldn't see it was to US advantage! lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the flipside, Drumpf doesn't seem to understand that global popn is 7.5bn and rising and women need full access to family planning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news: #TPP is dead! Irony is it would've been great for US, given their multinats power to control #democracy through #ISDS. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is they vote for the best fairy tale. It's all about narrative, facts be damned. No wonder the world's spiralling. #auspol #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead they vote for opposite: lower taxes for rich, destruction of public medicine. Why vote against your own interest? #auspol #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think poor voters would vote for universal healthcare, raising minimum wage, properly taxing rich and corpns. But no. #auspol #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's increasingly clear to me that most voters don't have a clue what they're voting for. No wonder #democracy is failing. #auspol #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating article - I Spent 5 Years With Some of Trump's Biggest Fans: https://t.co/PTLi7PIOP7 #inequality #welfare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Price can't see past his own blind conservatism. There is clear documentary evidence the WH put out lies yesterday. #theproject #ch10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic summary of the new #electricity cost paradigm. Summary: #renen wins! #climate #energy #sustainability… https://t.co/MU2CY7xCOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - 19% of US population didn't just elect a racist, sexist, climate-denying serial liar as President. Oh no, they did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - humans regardless of race, religion, etc don't share more commonalities than differences. We must fight one another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - rampant wealth inequality is not the main driver of social unrest, nor is it morally egregious. It is the natural order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - vaccines haven't saved millions of lives, don't rely on everyone doing their part. They're a plot to make us autistic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - economics is not fundamentally flawed because it ignores externalities and social good. It is the only way to think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - GHGs do not cause the greenhouse effect and humans haven't vastly increased their concentration. The Chinese made it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - all life on Earth is not related to a common ancestor and did not evolve by natural selection. It was created by God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts - the Earth is not round, does not orbit the Sun, and was not formed about 4.54bn yrs ago. It is flat and 6600yrs old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb insight @umairh. Simple, powerful truths. I now realise that I too have no politics but many values. #auspol #uspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shared values are key to unlocking the polarisation undermining civilisation. The masses understanding this is another matter. @umairh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUST READ: #change is the nature of being, and #values should transcend politics. #auspol #uspol https://t.co/AZ0bCpI2Xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feelin_green No, he won't be able to. Coal is already dead. New coal plants more expensive than wind and solar. He's an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cautionary tale for entitled societies - break the entitlement complex early or reap the whirlwind. https://t.co/RfnvyM2On0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RDNS_TAI Already said all he needs to by deleting climate page from White House website. Quintessential #climatezombie. @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another reason to respect Gregg Popovich, one of the great orgaisational culture builders of our time. https://t.co/8stqiYRHu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repeat a lie enough times and you'll start to believe it's the truth. Just check out #MAGA some time and you'll see… https://t.co/YGgRN9rvO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More armour-plated #cognitivedissonance from noted nutjob Sheriff Clarke. #Inauguration #WomensMarch https://t.co/JmYQG5WvlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sure is armour-plated #cognitivedissonance in the #MAGA crowd. #Inauguration #WomensMarch https://t.co/wgrcNJgvgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...ISIS-led #womensmarch". The Drumpfer's echo chamber propaganda at it's finest. Quintessential… https://t.co/zWGXfCWDAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect example of insane policy driven by captured, utterly corrupt politics. #renewables #climate https://t.co/He9QQ4U8Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MAGA echo chamber re-frames global protests as repressive rather than opposing repression! #cognitivedissonance #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating: inside #MAGA propaganda echo chamber protesters are all "nasty" women who support Sharia law. #cognitivedissonance #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danfromdc Indeed. Cheap shots are utterly cowardly. Bipartisan agreement! Need much more of this in the world. @cya_lata_bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danfromdc I'm a progressive and no friend of anyone who uses binary stereotypes. Cowards arise across the political spectrum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobhRyan Sure. But hit them head on. Show THEM to be the cowards. Incidents like this make resistance look weak and cowardly, not strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobhRyan @thenotoriouscbg To be clear: I despise Drumpf, his deplorables, fascism in every form. But it should be fought head-on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenotoriouscbg I'm not sympathizing with a Nazi. I'm sympathizing with victims of coward-punching. There have been many deaths from them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobhRyan That is not my point. My point directly related to coward-punching which no-one should stoop to nor endorse. @thenotoriouscbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenotoriouscbg I have been six times, just for being tall. It's no joke. Wanna punch a Nazi, do it from in front. Don't be a coward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobhRyan Nor am I. But coward punching anyone is BS. Or are you fine with double standards and behaving like they do?  @thenotoriouscbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenotoriouscbg You totally missed the point, obviously never been coward punched. I have. Punch him front on, don't endorse cowardly acts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for fighting Nazis, but punch them head on, not by surprise from side/behind like a cowardly POS. https://t.co/GFgZar74c0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A strange mix of Orwellian #doublespeak and #incompetence from White House press secretary @seanspicer.… https://t.co/lOVPcPI9nL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drumpf and his Orwellian minions led us #throughthelookingglass into the #bizarroworld of the #Bifftimeline. #TrumpInauguration #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cya_lata_bye I'm talking about the nature of the punch, not the person hit. Square up to him and have at it.  @jonfavs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuthalu I am a progressive, so skittle off back to your NeoCon lair. I'm not your ally. I just dispise cowards. @jonfavs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@antalianna He was punched from side/rear without warning. That cowardly shit should have taken him head on with warning. That's civilised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've been punched from behind by cowardly POS multiple times just because you're tall you'll understand coward punches differently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read my timeline: I'm a progressive appalled by Drumpf and his deplorables. But that doesn't excuse punching anyone from behind. ANYONE.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>