<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This definitely isn't a sketchy thing to do on the same day we made the CEO of Exxon &amp; Vlad's BFF our new SOS. Noth… https://t.co/1yJiJ19Yxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy your last 2 years in Congress, Senator. #Nevada can and will do better than @SenDeanHeller in 2018. #NVpol https://t.co/IZWzNbZrTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Hern his DC line has been full for bascially 2 weeks! Been calling his LV office though. Hoping he pulls through for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice again how "African American community" is followed by "inner-city."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First #BlackHistoryMonth speech just as insane as anticipated. https://t.co/mF0JYGSE0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is happening. #resist https://t.co/8BsyXlL8ee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a real thing that our nation's press secretary really said.. let that sink in https://t.co/CtZs5cfp26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steel yourselves. The hits keep coming. https://t.co/dbHFjayv56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is So Important to Me that My Coffee Cup Must Say Merry Xmas but I Get Mad About Helping Refugees -An American Story #BoycottStarbucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...by Steve Bannon, Breitbart subscribers, and that Nazi who got punched in the face" https://t.co/jEPrk943AN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Timodc @awendell98 "Mr. President, can you quickly walk us through how a bill becomes a law?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a reporter to interview @realDonaldTrump and just ask him to list the 7 countries in the EO without help. #NoMuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 0% chance that @realDonaldTrump can find all 7 of those countries on the map. #PresidentBannon #NoMuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did y'all know that @Delta wrote and signed an exec order barring immigrants and refugees from Muslim-majority coun… https://t.co/3trmXrpOy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Las Vegas native &amp; USC grad was so proud to see @SenCortezMasto &amp; Sen @KamalaHarris together today fighting for #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstcambot not even a never released film?! oh come onnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nottheonion https://t.co/ZnBdjdHqY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're All Lives Matter-ing the Holocaust now #resist https://t.co/ImggGLLMIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, @lyft, for showing the rest what good corporate citizenship looks like w/ a $1 million @ACLU donation. #StrongerTogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty remarkable (remarkably scary) stuff from CBP at LAX and around the U.S. https://t.co/GsEK8lzaqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is important https://t.co/Bg9WKEROMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If somehow you care more about the economy than human beings in crisis:
1. Shame on you
2. You should be angry too… https://t.co/phLvWAUcbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shakestweetz I think about him and his wife &amp; son often. Usually when I know we've disappointed them. Hopefully to… https://t.co/oAthgSK8LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshtpm I hate the idea that she thinks *she* is entitled to live here, tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sem1480 @AriMelber ...by shutting down the vetting process or something crazy like that. Though I'm not familar w/… https://t.co/QnQ4BSRJRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sem1480 @AriMelber Their admittance couldn't be harmful if the U.S. had already determined it was not. Concerned t… https://t.co/p0f5QI3BWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sem1480 @AriMelber What I was thinking; 3 is going to be important to challenge the ban going forward. Judge remar… https://t.co/9IFK0jM7aB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geneven Common sense and the Constitution :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not gonna *not* RT this https://t.co/ZywMpvs6BX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look for the helpers" https://t.co/iLxUa9CQvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found the part of twitter where celebrities &amp; others are matching donations to @ACLU &amp; it gave me hope. Consider donating if you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@timjhogan his office lines have been full all week, too. The silence is loud, @SenDeanHeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at you, @AdamLaxalt - or are EOs only wrong when a president you don't like uses them? https://t.co/VefaWRP66O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you mean anything you say, @SpeakerRyan? #NoBanNoWall #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/nkpJpOttge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the ban @SpeakerRyan &amp; @SenateMajLdr were spineless cowards. Today they are also cruel. History will not forget it. #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In his defense, I'm sure @FoxNews isn't reporting from #Terminal4 or any other airport around the US. How could he… https://t.co/UetRyqtfna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He means every white, Christian, American life. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/HYFYqHgsN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Jackson watches proudly as white men destroy the lives of millions of people, including Native Americans https://t.co/ttvSeQcufq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without ACA, states can do what MN just tried to do: not cover maternity benefits and inpatient care for delivery.… https://t.co/dQ9T6ldCtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assuming everyone at the #MarchForLife is rallying to keep the ACA, right? https://t.co/IHwRtwUqYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @AustralianOpen finals are gonna be 🔥🔥!! #WilliamsSisters #Fedal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, this IS a normal thing for a president to be worried about on day 5 - glad you asked! https://t.co/GWLmSfkHnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The line at @SenDeanHeller's office has been busy every time I've called this afternoon. Good work Nevada! #DumpDevos #StopSessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[202-224-3121
What are you calling about today? My list:
- Sessions, DeVos, Price
- ACA, Medicaid, DACA, refugee ban, border wall, pipelines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When even @jasoninthehouse won't investigate... https://t.co/DTiitWDgAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall White House rally tonight was amazing. Proud to fight for immigrants &amp; refugees. They are what make America great. #HeretoStay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revoking from all Republicans the right to ever lecture me about states' rights ever again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand the future head of DHS keep #DACA #HereToStay https://t.co/37etSzNq4m via @unitedwedream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call for attorney volunteers: https://t.co/ooSmNMU8k4 #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make War Crimes Great Again https://t.co/m3Ka0H1K6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies, it's worth asking your doc if an #IUD is right for you. Soon, before it's no longer your choice to make. 2-… https://t.co/d28nVMAcfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because I know you need to see this right now. https://t.co/ObvUg0iXrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is insane. https://t.co/KUKmisjsTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Residents of Flint still don't have clean water https://t.co/e2mP4vPOV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joycekrawiec You need a blog to tell you to treat others the way you want to be treated? You say you're a "Lover o… https://t.co/Jyjuz487sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is rich https://t.co/qCh2zIMD8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6Yy2fjaY5t #IMarchWithLinda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when the @GOP railed against Obama's use of executive orders? If your guy is prez though, it's all cool. https://t.co/2NB2xqqT8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I just became this admin's new @PressSec, I would delete my old tweets. Esp. this one (presumably a joke) about… https://t.co/cBf3hbhNM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird that none of the Trump team has deleted past tweets, right? Anyway, here's @seanspicer on the Fifth Amen… https://t.co/rqf0i8ktaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocker! Secret plan doesn't exist. Didn't he also say he knows more than the Generals? Why ask them for a plan if… https://t.co/rQGL1PCboD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(To be clear, we also weren't cheering because it was an awful thing to say... figured that part was a given)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This" meaning that conservative media would use that comment to discredit the rest of the amazing speakers and the march, itself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth noting that NO ONE in area where I was cheered when Madonna made that stupid comment. We were mad bc we knew this would be the fallout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so he didn't like the vagina hats then? #whyImarch https://t.co/V802VNzac2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud that @SenCortezMasto represents the great state of NV! We must replicate her electoral success across the… https://t.co/XkWz4IsxrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thread: https://t.co/nFy95XgtuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andizeisler "Area man finds out that children require care, provides that care"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost the article itself isn't bad, but this tweet isn't representative of what the article explains. "Most" was a poor choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A diverse group of women organized the entire event. But "It's the men who mattered most" - really @washingtonpost?… https://t.co/exFiz8roEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine masculinity SO fragile that it breaks at just the sight of empowered women. Now add a stupid hat. Voila! Yo… https://t.co/Mkf1Kg2lIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahkliff @onceuponA I think it also depends on how many enrollment periods insurers think will go by between the… https://t.co/FcQpqm4i5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resist. #alternativefacts https://t.co/UQWDEgVxbG https://t.co/XVukfoazGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economic &amp; reproductive justice for all. #StandWithPP #7in10forRoe (and #4moreyears of fiery dissent by RBG 👑) https://t.co/rGNxfKAmA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying that women deserve the choice to have an abortion does not require you to also make that choice. That's what CHOICE is! #7in10forRoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right to choose if, when, and how to have a child is fundamental to women's economic and social equality. #7in10forRoe #WeWontGoBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tribelaw See also, Kellyanne Conway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being at the #WomensMarch in DC today was something I will never, ever forget. So much love and kindness. So much power. #WeWontGoBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a WMATA "we're improving" commercial that was basically like "we know you're important &amp; we can help you be important" ..DC is sold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait I don't follow Sean Spicer? Oh.. right https://t.co/iSgEZh3LC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty horrifying; cc: @ACLU_DC https://t.co/RbQ5Ff8GxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good news: https://t.co/iec2mBrPPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which donor/appointee/Trump relative (or all of the above) benefits financially from this? https://t.co/H3RX1Huhpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost as if a majority of Americans didn't want this person to be the president... https://t.co/8N4YJWXFVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it for him. HEALTH CARE IS A BASIC HUMAN RIGHT. 
Keep calling: 202-224-3121 #PriceIsWrong 
https://t.co/ujNzCIGZxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story is like Trump admin. bingo: 
- Attacking free press
- Insider trading
- Shady PAC payouts
- Incompetency
https://t.co/frYRrw7NFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although in her defense, that was probably her first job interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest job interview of your life and you didn't prepare? @BetsyDeVos shouldn't be allowed anywhere near the Dept. of Education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew she knew nothing and had no qualifications but she didn't even TRY to pretend that that isn't the case.… https://t.co/HmzDdoiEOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbellzamy @realDonaldTrump putting in a plug for Presidents' Day. "a day to celebrate me - you're welcome"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A new generation sets its sights higher because it has you as a role model." 

Happy birthday, @FLOTUS. Thanks for… https://t.co/HT2PgvODCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GOP healthcare plan? It includes 32 million more people without insurance by 2026. Call your reps today: 202-2… https://t.co/M75IOQcEQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are telling a woman that she is not entitled to make decisions about her body, you are not a feminist - even if you are also a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is disqualifying for a cabinet member on every planet except for the one where we elected Trump to fill a cabi… https://t.co/iBP2Pw5jhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I support the things MLK stood for unless achieving them threatens my status in any way whatsoever"- when Trump supporters quote #MLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[get you a @SenateMajLdr who can do both https://t.co/7bAv4d77VL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These words mean nothing, @SenateMajLdr, unless you vote against the appointment of white supremacist… https://t.co/TDt1Rkbrlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This street looks remarkably clean and that bottle retails around $20. https://t.co/a2U6KzUtJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Hern Yeah, when it didn't look like it was going away, Ds tried to make it a positive term. That tweet is pretty heart breaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably got a nice raise and is now watching the world burn from his/her newly-renovated Capitol Hill townhouse.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>