<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Al-Qaeda says Trump has ignited ‘the flame of jihad’ with Yemen raid- The Washington Post by the talented @LovedayM  https://t.co/NzaLnyZG2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want more info on the spin around the #Yemenraid:  https://t.co/bcQ4AvdDe8 https://t.co/TgQu8D3fCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AZConservative1 @TheChuckMo Very artistic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhiteHouse breaks massively with convention announcing #Trump will visit #MacDill Air Force base on Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pentagon citing video already online as key intel gathered from #Yemenraid would be laughable had so many innocent lies not been lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert @EliotHiggins says #Pentagon could likely have found the same sort of videos by browsing LiveLeak for a few hours. #YemenRaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanKaszeta @EliotHiggins And some 22 other civilians by several accounts...

Not to mention one dead NavySEAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bomb making video clips #Pentagon found on a laptop in #Yemenraid, seem to be of the sort that also found in dark corners of the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports challenge #WhiteHouse #Pentagon account of #YemenRaid that killed a #US #NavySEAL and civilians,inc childre… https://t.co/g1rMPBqONv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yakla, village where #US raid in #Yemen, also had 2013 wedding hit by drone. The groom of that wedding died in this raid, said @BShtwtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military officials have not been able to confirm #SeanSpicer claim that info gleaned from #Yemen raid will "prevent attacks on #US soil"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The raid that killed a #US #NavySEAL may also have killed 59 civilians, according to @NBCNews https://t.co/zmlZFPCqCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekkeree The facts are plain: vetting Syria refugees already +2 years. No Syrian refugee in the program has committed a terror attack in US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngizzi hi John! I did the other day. Just sent again - I hope it works!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekkeree emotions no, facts, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuiceC0 insulting children is lovely behaviour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow here for updates on reports that gunmen have opened fire in #Quebec mosque. @Telegraph https://t.co/u5Zq0uLuZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People wait for an #Afghan war veteran to arrive at #Dulles airport. #NoOneLeftBehind https://t.co/19qrGd4dDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lawyers are finally proving they can be a force for good" Nour el-Kebbi,23 law student. Lots of lawyers gathered t… https://t.co/hxaKgm4pVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jem_cramp wasn't quite the same...!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents seem to be in handcuffs https://t.co/UOaXbJdS8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump statement on #immigration ban https://t.co/fI7jOAbuAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says this isn't a "Muslim ban" - change of policy to last year.... #MuslimBan https://t.co/fGhP32NvUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump #immigration ban shows how little the president cares about his own supporters: https://t.co/HLGe4BDkMq #USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is truly wonderful. Refugees must know this policy belongs to the #Trump admin and not the people they govern. https://t.co/aF3rHGJFX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better late than never... maybe? https://t.co/Q7m3OlJdlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loveunderlaw @RolandOliphant I never thought ordinary Americans were involved. Doesn't change how wrong the Trump policy is now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The executive order showing #Trump's 'secret plan' to defeat #Isis. Point one is 'develop a plan'. #Syria #Iraq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this excellent and disturbing piece by @lindseyhilsum. She cuts straight to the facts. https://t.co/hCSRVa3Csp #USA #Trump #Syria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump is deceiving his supporters with the promises in these executive orders https://t.co/XvzvFOLZR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caligularised @theoldgovanarm1 @Telegraph The refugee quoted in the story is referring to the secret police in Syria;a well document thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State department confirmation that dual nationals from barred countries will also be banned #Trump . #UK dual citiz… https://t.co/ebvvl7ARTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caligularised @theoldgovanarm1 @Telegraph I'm saying the opposite. When this article was written it was more stable than now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dual nationals, including from #Britain, from one of the banned countries willbe barred, says state department. What do you say #TheresaMay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rolo_Tamasi @timothy_stanley Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caligularised @theoldgovanarm1 @Telegraph You seem unable to grasp that situations change in countries. Maybe read a book on Libya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcheritemoss People with the intent of sowing terror do not enter a country through the complicated, slow, and painful refugee process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatcheritemoss Banning Syrian refugees is a simplistic response that only creates more risk. Helps ISIS win the propaganda war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caligularised @theoldgovanarm1 @Telegraph It's not nonsense - it's how people felt at that place at that time. Where you in Libya then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spursbolt Just because I care about the lives of people who have seen their relatives tortured and killed makes me a liberal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahsStowAway @timothy_stanley @Telegraph You have a fascinating take on history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahsStowAway @timothy_stanley @Telegraph What exactly should the Islamic world be grateful to us for? Destroying Iraq? Meddling in Syria?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jews were turned away or interned in #US #UK in #WW2 by people who held similar fears about them, as they do about #MENA refugees today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahsStowAway @timothy_stanley @Telegraph Not exactly getting to know the people of Syria then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahsStowAway @timothy_stanley @Telegraph America has taken in a tiny fraction of refugees from Syria, as you should know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahsStowAway @timothy_stanley @Telegraph  I spent 7 years living &amp;working in the Middle East, with dozens of trips to Iraq and Syria. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunick51 @Telegraph I'm not arguing that a country shouldn't vet. But Syrians coming to the US already undergo several years of vetting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caligularised @theoldgovanarm1 @Telegraph It's a measure of how bad Syria has become, that several thousand have sought refuge in Libya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothy_stanley @baz20796 My thoughts exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP @elaineh51 Where is the evidence for this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elaineh51 @timothy_stanley This harms more than it helps America - it means the US loses the propaganda war to ISIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elaineh51 @timothy_stanley That's not factually correct. Very few lone males coming through, mostly families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baz20796 @timothy_stanley We should recognise that meddling in foreign countries comes with certain responsibilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caeciliusest This does nothing to defend America. Ppl with intent to attack, dont use refugee program, which takes 2+ years of vetting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take issue with those who think #US #UK don't have responsibility to #Syria refugees. We helped foster war; then failed to act to end it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump executive orders are designed only to win domestic support. His administration knows there is no evidence to support his claims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The refugee ban defies logic, as it's already the hardest way to get into America. No evidence of terrorists using this route. #Syria #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those that need reminding of what #Syrians have undergone. They are not terrorists, they are like you and me. https://t.co/iU9Gt4qwl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #RefugeeBan and #TheresaMay's refusal to condemn it represents a gaping dearth of empathy or humanity. We should all be ashamed. #Syria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of all my #Syrian and #Iraqi friends today who have already been through so much only to suffer these slanderous attacks. #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump invokes 9/11 to justify #Muslim country ban. But then doesn't ban any of the countries the hijackers came from...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent explainer on why #Trump's executive order banning people from certain countries may be illegal - https://t.co/0gH0ov14o5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #DickCheney comes out against the refugee banning policy, you know it's serious.... #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AnneFrank was denied entry to the #US, amid a culture of suspicion in #WWII  #America that painted #Jews as communists or even Nazis....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BFriedmanDC Hi Brandon, would you be able to follow me so we can DM? I'm  writing about effect Trump's EOs have on veterans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump mansplains, answering for #TheresaMay when she is asked if she is concerned by the diplo crisis he has caused between #US and #Mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great question from @bbclaurak - #TheresaMay failed to answer, and #Trump threw the 'special relationship' into quandary..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress pushing #Trump to form bilateral trade deal with #UK @Telegraph https://t.co/x0snwyfD8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheresaMay and #DonaldTrump  news is about trade deal, pressure will also be on May to clarify difference of opinion on torture and more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MikePompeo is going to be "another one of the big stars" says #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A lot of positive things are going to start happening and bursting out" says #Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump begins speech bragging about election victory: "They always said Pennsylvania was the bride that got away".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests outside #DonaldTrump #TheresaMay #Republican gathering https://t.co/EAL0OqgueW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests outside the hotel where #DonaldTrump and #TheresaMay will speak today https://t.co/KxY2Y3LBlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer says reopening of #CIA black sites memo is "not a White House document". #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SeanSpicer announcing cuts in funding for "sanctuary cities": "The American people will no longer subsidise this disregard for our laws."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump administration is instructing the Environmental Protection Agency to remove its climate change website]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCarafano Thank Jim. Have retweeted this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking with @Telegraph, @JJCarafano said reports that General #Flynn and General #Mattis are at loggerheads is "utterly untrue".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @Freddygray31 @spectator explaining how #Trump views #Britain and the #EU. A must read! https://t.co/eogCuGGaTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good interview just now with @JJCarafano: idea that #Trump's exec orders on immigration are anti-Muslim is "scaremongering" from the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaheemKassam Hi! Can you follow me so we can DM? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people get together in peace on this scale they become a powerful force. #Dc #WomensMarch https://t.co/dCePn4aOqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the streets in the overflow of the #WomensMarch. Not even the main part. This is #Nixon 72, or maybe… https://t.co/3AejM2jLPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight song by @RachelPlatten the theme tune of #HillaryClinton campaign playing at #Trump inauguration ball. Mockin… https://t.co/CYhNApELc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning. @Telegraph is here live and close up to bring you the inauguration speech. https://t.co/1lHNTN496G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boctok88 Hi Patrick, would you be able to follow me so we can direct message? I have a bit of a last minute request. Many thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My piece from the forgotten Chicago projects where #Obama began the activism that set him on a path to presidency:  https://t.co/0xt9TvvnPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously good journalism by @KimSengupta07 @Independent  https://t.co/fR0t5yPYTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewStadlen Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogeruk49 You're so sweet. Is it nice to be someone who brings light to the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Thanks buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kezekiel @TelegraphNews Thank you Kerry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My take on why we shouldn't discount reports in #Trump dossier yet. Strap in, coming four years will be a wild ride. https://t.co/1z9BQtfASg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The former intell source's information came from communications intercepted by a Eastern European intel agency. #Trump #Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last summer former US intel source told me about #Trump #Russia blackmail details that largely match those in ex-M16 officer report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These three men are the tech wizards behind #Obama's 2008 campaign. Sam Falkoff (left) named their internet servers… https://t.co/v67kdHchKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom and Tina Finch said Chicago residents are "Obama's family" and that tonight he "came home". Pic with their daug… https://t.co/yqI4y2CthF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Evans brought her two children, then 6 and 8 yrs, to Obama's Chicago primary election party in 2008. Now… https://t.co/gySeReFHPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Janaya Shaw says she has come to hear #Obama speak wishing for "one last dose of hope". #ObamaFarewell https://t.co/FUS7Gvhcjy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>