<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 is there beef?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelechiCeri yes I am ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ @kfc personally I wouldn't have that ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @KelechiCeri has never had a KFC krushem so you're wondering if it's too late to disown her ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…I actually hate you ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want my summer tan back ðŸ˜© https://t.co/BvgUXoL6qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelechiCeri @kwabz_7 ðŸ‘€ who is this fat person asking for morleys ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas ðŸŽ„â¤ https://t.co/JvydXKlyG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class runs in the family ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜â¤ https://t.co/QlTX5pUrsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this ain't you ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’@Horrorgan https://t.co/pojTQL56rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this ain't us ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ @kwabz_7 https://t.co/e1RLEAeCuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your baby niece doesn't want to be in any of your snaps https://t.co/WahqrdbUzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you finally remember how to take pictures https://t.co/nskJ7gwZkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're acting all moody but bae still treats you like a princess ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 ngl I don't need you rave promoters on my tl....so if you would please leave that would be great, thanks. ðŸ˜ŠâœŒðŸ½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've only been apart for an hour ðŸ™‡ðŸ½ @Horrorgan https://t.co/MfrYy3ZEPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First night of holiday ðŸ’«âœ¨ https://t.co/AFIQxj64SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is my holiday in less than 24hours and I still haven't packed ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday fool ðŸ™„ðŸŽ‰ @KwameLoso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I'm just gonna come to your house when you aren't there and get your mum to give me more  jollof ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’žðŸ’¯âœŒðŸ½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hang on a second did you not say that you were going to sleep at 21:34? @kwabz_7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sort of pettiness I live for ðŸ’¯ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/MUChML5mMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SosaXCVI @kwabz_7 rah so you can reply to Kwabena but not to me ðŸ˜¶ I see you mr movie star]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How am I on the phone listening to @kwabz_7 and his dad arguing ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing my best friend and he's only been gone no longer than 48 hours ðŸ˜”ðŸš¶ðŸ¾ @kwabz_7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmGeorgieee you tell me to stop doing this all the time ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/CAS5sYYk9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I shall meet you at the solicitors near our house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @kwabz_7 knows too much about the bad stuff in your life so he has to sign a written agreement that he'll never leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those ones when you're airing somebody on snapchat and you keep watching their story just to piss them off even more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operation day today ðŸ¤•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan LOL ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚its satisfactory â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan this is you ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š https://t.co/MFefeRzed6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 where's your office?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I've got video evidence to prove that statement is a lie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can @kwabz_7 say that my life is like eastenders, hollyoaks, coronation street and match of the day all in one ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I would be a bit rude to have a nap if I'm currently on the phone to you ðŸ¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 are you really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking in the rain with no umbrella or hood so I decided to listen to Umbrella-Rihanna ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I'm fully dead ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/jbiHzXXMWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 who knew he could be so nice ðŸ˜­ I'm going to cherish this moment for as long as I live ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸ https://t.co/BEru5Xyt0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 the love I had for you is gone ðŸ’” evaporated into thin air ðŸ’¨ðŸŒ«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 these people are proper messaging you in the hope that you reply ðŸ˜‚begging it much ðŸ™„ don't forget me when you're famous ðŸ¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those times you have to take advantage of the car lighting âœ¨ https://t.co/Nt5MuaVzmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My niece describing my mood perfectly right now ðŸ’¯ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜´ https://t.co/wWxhAFaQcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I'm capable of all of that tbh, remember the time I tried to run you over ðŸ˜‚ @kwabz_7  https://t.co/OHj6dCJ2uE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Deffo that friend ðŸ˜‚ @Horrorgan @kwabz_7  https://t.co/uEmHctyQz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the jollof rice part @kwabz_7  https://t.co/j4Ikwx1ZQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you bump the train and an inspector comes on so you start looking for places to hide. https://t.co/YOajiZqL96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a year and a half I'm finally no longer blonde ðŸ˜¥ https://t.co/Sj7o4iB3BP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 this is actually something that you would do ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/VyQxUPb0zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ which bit did you not understand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 I can see why ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan this one is my number 1 ace â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ lil old me? Never that ðŸŒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashback Friday ðŸ˜³ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾ðŸ˜@kwabz_7 https://t.co/LRQ8ibmYNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was in the process of saying "are you dumb" ðŸ¤”ðŸ’­ the everyday abuse I receive ðŸ˜” @kwabz_7 https://t.co/XIEqVc3sHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're on the phone to someone and they are talking to everyone but you ðŸ˜’ðŸ¤” @kwabz_7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the lighting is A1 ðŸ’« https://t.co/mJxqY4PAH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How have me and @kwabz_7 been on the phone for 3 minutes and we're already arguing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 yes I have ðŸ˜’ it's when I met you it all went downhill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't remember the last time my phone was this dry ðŸ˜« I definitely have no friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to look so sweet, what happened in these 2 years ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Fxg734cYDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did I sleep for 14 hours last night and all day I've been moving like I haven't slept for like a week. ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing you're good at is looking cute" how can a compliment be so insulting at the same time ðŸ¤” https://t.co/Hjn2qdi9fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I cruel for laughing at this? @kwabz_7  https://t.co/FpSkRzhoNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lols at the time I didn't talk to my family for 3 days because they didn't bring me any McDonald's home ðŸ™Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*me breaking up with someone* Hey what rhymes with pringle? Single cause that's what you are merry Christmas and a happy new year ðŸ˜˜ @kwabz_7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwabz_7 you've finally got Twitter, you've just made my 2016 ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My whatsapp hasn't been working for nearly 2 hours....it's made me wash my hair and I've even started revising ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kourtney to my Khloe â¤ï¸ (she forced me to put this up) @Horrorgan https://t.co/0C0BeWSznb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan don't bring my name into this ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ you've actually got problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat: lucyloo_96 https://t.co/geVP9fcQjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My niece is actually obsessed with me ðŸ˜‚ @Horrorgan I thought you were bad ðŸ™„ðŸ˜´ https://t.co/qj87mUSRph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think i hear my jam coming in ðŸŽ¶ https://t.co/UJzE3sK2WS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bxmbinaa this is something you would do ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/LgNtO1Oj2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So recently I get at least one person a day telling me that I act like a typical lightie ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But bitch I'm now confused as to why you're getting angry? ðŸ¤” @Horrorgan https://t.co/I52MyhPWdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigGucci_Idz lol how comes you don't like it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually obsessed with my niece. This beautiful little treasure â¤ï¸ https://t.co/wmVGElT2Mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This precious little angel â¤ï¸ msmc.n you jealous yet? â˜ºï¸ðŸŒš https://t.co/4Pezk6Bm7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyMan_T this will be you soon ðŸŒ https://t.co/BdPcoMhwRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment I actually try to do some work and I've got 8 different people vibrating up my phone #excusetheterribleenglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan you're also that friend who won't actually call back in 5 minutes and lie everytime you say "I'll call you back" ðŸ˜ŠðŸ–•ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ @Horrorgan remember that time in the car with dullah https://t.co/WPsrbgQJkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guilty ðŸŒðŸ˜Š @Horrorgan https://t.co/c7zdoCXKSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan sound familiar? https://t.co/tovqfNqvfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a while âœ¨ https://t.co/nFlZy9eHd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan have you paid for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan yeah MY phone ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the uber driver keeps talking to you even though you have your earphones in ðŸ˜’ like clearly I do not want to talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mum used to come home with surprise gifts for me but now she comes home with gifts for the baby ðŸ˜”ðŸš¶ðŸ¾ such a sad life ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confused as to why it looks like I have a toned stomach when I've never worked out in my life http://t.co/xwekWxrLTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horrorgan Thanks for coming and sitting there for 4 hours, I owe you â˜ºï¸â¤ï¸ https://t.co/XWp9MGdKzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo cred ally_g21 â˜ºï¸ https://t.co/Mzlx5BkhXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ace ðŸ’• Love you for eternity ðŸ’« https://t.co/CygYUVLMF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think she's very hurt at the fact that I never called her back @Horrorgan http://t.co/gpSci1hmJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan photography skills ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½I wasn't even ready for the photo bitch http://t.co/ply7fKIdBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan ðŸ˜¯ðŸ˜®ðŸ˜¦ðŸ˜§ðŸ˜¨ðŸ˜± how could you do this, it was our 8 year anniversary next month as well ðŸ˜¢....ðŸš¶ðŸ½ðŸ’¥ *listens to unfaithful-Rihanna*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Horrorgan I think we need to go on a break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bxmbinaa i have all the qualities that his wife doesn't ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜©]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>