<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Citation_Cormac @Stevenward_ 16,800. Sometimes when a place is less than 2/3 full, it feels empty. This place felt packed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chriskee3 10 to 15 degrees or something, nice enough, but I was barely outside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good chat was had with @SkyAdamSmith on a big year for @KatieTaylor and @ryanburnett01 
https://t.co/SCWqtKF8qC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A goozer at Monday's @IrishSunSport. Fear the headline is wishful thinking but @ClonesCyclone will pull out all sto… https://t.co/seHHusc8xY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FV360Yo_Mikey think it was Avalos he was at, getting pelters from the crowd, was grinning, telling us he loves it, then doing selfies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FV360Yo_Mikey He did the same this week, was loving it. But I did see Quigg doing the same - he came over a few times, lapped it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephena1972 agree to an extent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably just a classic case of 'do as your hero does']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incidentally I often thought the Frampton fans were too harsh on previous rival Scott Quigg, a lesser challenge, but they like Santa Cruz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We'll get him back,I promise" says Frampton at Nine Fine Irishmen, or Ground Zero this week https://t.co/4kR3wz9SYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye Vegas, and bye to daily electric shocks in the MGM #SurelyImNotAloneOnThis https://t.co/kl72niiUzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffrothechamp @RealCFrampton @leosantacruz2 both gave the fans what they wanted, always do. Another be interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Frampton offered Leo Santa Snooze a bed if he will come to Belfast for rematch https://t.co/VfXt6hUZ8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brawler outboxed the boxer, says @RealCFrampton, after second fight of inevitable trilogy with @leosantacruz2 
 https://t.co/ZhiTPnHSUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevenward_ tough to put an accurate number on it, but half the 10000 crowd isn't far off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LSC: If my manager, promoter make a trilogy, let's do it. But there are many options out there too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa Cruz: I always said - he has everything. But I had a great game-plan. If I lost to him twice I was going to retire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton says Santa Cruz can come to stay in his house if he'll agree to a trilogy fight in Belfast, then adds they can do it 4, 5 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton is gutted https://t.co/VeEmogjjBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garcia - I felt it was like winning my first title]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garcia - If Lomachenko moves up to 135 and Arum wants to talk to me, I'll definitely take him on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mikey Garcia - I could be back in another 2-3 months. I'll fight anyone at 135. Love to unify titles. Might have to wait for that though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton was cheered out of the arena]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The brawler was out boxing the boxer." Summed up well by @RealCFrampton, again smarter than most of us who do this for a living!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trilogy fight will be huge. Santa Cruz learned from the first.

Frampton apologies to the fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the new #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/BWIqA8et84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have Santa Cruz by two here, no idea how judges will go. Great fight, one of the best I've been at, two top warriors #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nuns of Poor Clare are needed now more than ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Championship rounds and CF needs both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebb and flow in Las Vegas. Level here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton is fighting and frustrating but LSC staying calm 1-1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton has come out as World Fighter of the Year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key things from Frampton camp. Leo feet slow, power not all that, tactics not as refined. I'm going Frampton PTS, they're going KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant entrances, time to go. Draw is 18-1 here in Vegas #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a fight https://t.co/VEvwOrGk1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millionaires and their whims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Showtime have good mikes https://t.co/HD3NgThEB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayweather going on the box. Hope they ask about his dad v Steve Collins https://t.co/jWYdN7aPvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw might be go time soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd are grimacing at the KO replay, even the Mexicans, given the power Garcia put into those digs. Killer instinct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the more brutal stoppages I've seen. Garcia was superb https://t.co/WO1Pgl7lAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a KO. Zlaticinin badly hurt and still KO'd. Place goes bonkers for Mikey Garcia, Mexico feeling good #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garcia has natural authority, assured defence and power in every punch. All going to plan for him #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotta love here for Mikey Garcia, Mexicans going nuts for him. Bringing up the atmosphere a couple more notches #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last Irishman to headline the MGM with one of the select few boxers out there to have beaten Frampton https://t.co/hv7mKJY0bS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only one Irish boxer has won a world title fight in Las Vegas, Andy Lee. Lennox Lewis 5-0 is best British fighter h… https://t.co/8GWBkCZ5kH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belfast's finest in the house for #FramptonSantaCruz2 https://t.co/PVo55n3waD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redkach took a shot to land a shot there on Brock, who needed to be saved when he was #framptonsantacruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane McGuigan on JoshTaylor win: "I'm happy with his performance. It wasn't his best but he did enough to win." Wants Frampton to convince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw cheers Al, it's all hard work ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw 4am to be safest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton enters the arena to a loud but mixed reaction - cheers and jeers - same for Santa Cruz. So many Irish camped at the bars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Taylor takes points win over Alfonso Olvera 79-72, 78-73 x 2. Showed familiar flashes of class, Olvera good opponent at this stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low blow deduction looked harsh on second inspection. Good clash of styles here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor docked a point for a low blow here in the sixth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olvera probably only feeling the pain downstairs now too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olvera badly hurt by a low blow, not sure he'll still fancy this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spike_osullivan @FloydMayweather @NotoriousMMA @packycollins absolutely, just in spur of the moment I thought Steve v Sr would be a fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juniorhalpin @IrishSunOnline @kenegan30 @Willie_Casey boxing people know the craic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulieDGibson @RealCFrampton so dreamy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talked to Andy Lee and Steve Collins about why it's being claimed that Frampton isn't a big deal in Rep Ireland

 https://t.co/48BE9YOMoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["T-Rex" @RealCFrampton ready to bite down on the gumshield for victory against Leo Santa Cruz, says he's "due" a KO
https://t.co/zZnaWdrQkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Meloni I've never asked anyone for a follow, ever, but I'm breaking the habit of a lifetime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine work @RuthGorman_UTV &amp; @thomaskane1. This place is buzzing #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/imwnOdmHZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As @WayneMcCullough pointed out, in UFC Selby would receive his purse - he did everything that was expected of him https://t.co/cXqwd2ze2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drowned out, ever so slightly. I like LSC a lot but his noise/judges BS from NY is about to reach the next level… https://t.co/PLe5f25oR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room was hopping #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/B6goKJG9rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to the lads at @IrishSunSport who have put time, effort and resources towards the #framptonsantacruz2 fight, No1 paper for boxing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeeThedeeman @IrishBoxinNews @Aaron_LFC_85 was gas, to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickconlan11 check whatsapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickconlan11 I have one for you too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello, here are Floyd Mayweather Sr's thoughts on Frampton, or whatever https://t.co/LWKtdYzUXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sea of green #framptonSantacruz2 https://t.co/uxVZ9aS9AK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Said to Lee Selby the other day, "you're not long for FW, are ya?"

said back "if it was easy to make it I'd be in the wrong division". Shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barros didn't meet licencing requirements so won't be fighting Lee Selby. Welshman: "I'm almost in tears."
  #FramptonSantaCruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Quigley v Glen Tapia March 23 at Fantasy Springs - quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both Frampton and Santa Cruz clocked in at 125lb, comfortably on weight.

It's on

#FramptonSantaCruz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think they're saying 'yes please' #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/98KjcLtWvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Froch is loving it https://t.co/TxeMTI1YG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few showed up https://t.co/mrNRMYRgGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irlsport @IrishSunSport @RealCFrampton @mickconlan11 tremendous headline!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fkn picture, Ramsey. Outrageous #JoeWard https://t.co/4OCHWXUKMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leo Santa Cruz sums up the bullshit so many Americans are facing before he takes on Frampton again #wall #Trump
 https://t.co/6nQbklLbr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We compare him to @ClonesCyclone and @NotoriousMMA but history maker @RealCFrampton is doing biz on his own terms
 https://t.co/U50jXVcnMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boxing in @IrishSunSport Friday #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/qcG9G3fI0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear those things are awfully loud https://t.co/MPy2BHBXD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be of interest to the Frampton fans in town https://t.co/iD9CdgcSrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All told, since 1980, British and Irish fighters have fought 34 world title bouts in Las Vegas, going 17-17 in tha… https://t.co/GChBWUFklE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typo update: Carp Frampton is managed by Hall or Farmer Barry McGuigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Frampton says he can't wait to fight after working out in front of fans https://t.co/M9hDp94pK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lee Selby is likely to face Carl Frampton next but must first get past Jonathan Victor Barros on Saturday https://t.co/vFKciJEOrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish boxer Carl Frampton is the headline at the MGM Grand - he's come a long, long way https://t.co/fcmaSj2Vlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From one Belfast world champion boxer to another - @RealCFrampton on @mickconlan11's chances in the pro game https://t.co/fjCXPccjG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiz for the night owls - name the two-time Olympic gold medallist Carl Frampton has fought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SourMashNumber7 he's a BIG Frampton fan, goes all the fights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liberian_edo @FitzAnto @Ciaran_Gally tried to give up managers for January but there are managers everywhere here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a gawk at Thursday's @IrishSunSport #framptonsantacruz2 https://t.co/RQvz7uoCvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitzAnto @Ciaran_Gally I could just delete it but to be honest I couldn't be deleted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent welcome for @RealCFrampton https://t.co/0wuU0t1Tjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well braced https://t.co/vq4q5oDjlD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>