<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And no one will write an opera about him https://t.co/Mz5zt5k13O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If McConnell's argument is Obama shouldn't have named anyone because he was 9 mo. from leaving office, Trump prob.… https://t.co/VIf00DEtvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National right to work law, long a GOP and big business pipe dream, now likely to be a reality https://t.co/7eVfNni2DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Considers Deporting Legal Immigrants for Being Poor https://t.co/zam2gsOcO8 via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget the haters Donald, it's just you doing you https://t.co/AVjgvtyTdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually on second thought just take the bus https://t.co/aV1GhlSQTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou I assume Dems will make token effort to win WWC voters but not thru racism, instead count on fear of Tr… https://t.co/mt7r0JtTZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou Good thread. But assume Dems can't chase pivotal WWC voters w/o appeals to racism? Econ populism+not ru… https://t.co/sNk5sWCDDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What counts as "detention" the next big legal question https://t.co/Yyai4fUIw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin approach to regulatory policy inspired by Olive Garden 2 for 1 specials https://t.co/XYxPLMNQV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drain the swamp https://t.co/RQ146EhkeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a new one: #MuslimBan is actually meant to protect Muslims from the kind of extremists that Muslim bans help… https://t.co/zCy4yidYmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 2c on @yonatanzunger's "Trial Balloon for a Coup?" Trump piece https://t.co/6g3TJkJqHt https://t.co/0kiGRuTXEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navarro's been reading a lot of Hall and Soskice https://t.co/fg0VTEwziC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak and Incompetent Leaders act like Strong Leaders https://t.co/xXbhy2mVFi via @TomPepinsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disproving the narrative that Trump's campaign data operation wasn't sophisticated https://t.co/5JYxEzxaMq via @motherboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like Pinochet before he was voted out. Advisers told him everyone in Chile loves you! Call a referendum! It… https://t.co/8GGYO6h8ih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only expert Trump consulted in crafting #MuslimBan EO was eminent legal scholar Rudy Giuliani. Ignored DHS warnings on green cards. Amateurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe twitter campaigns can have an impact, at least on CEOs who obsess over social media. Goes for our prez too. https://t.co/GsJ3E8GbY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The airport #MuslimBan protests were great, but I'd like to see the same rapid mobilization every time a factory gets shut down in Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yjtorbati thanks for your updates and videos, they're invaluable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA AG: "This order is in direct conflict with the most foundational principles of our country and our Commonwealth" https://t.co/QpKWb1BYC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would be 287 out of 292 in Congress last I checked https://t.co/xmTQC1i3Gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court halts illegal order because it might be illegal https://t.co/PVr43ngfxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hours after Trump signs Muslim ban, Texas mosque goes up in flames” by @AdrienneMahsa https://t.co/pcUsQ3tZgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal US residents who have committed no crime can be barred from US anyway https://t.co/QGhEKvH5QX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who has ever committed reckless driving is more of "an illegal" than someone who lives here without papers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like calling someone "an illegal" because they once got a traffic ticket. Reckless driving in fact is a criminal, not civil offense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling someone "an illegal," i.e. defining their identity based on a civil infraction, is absurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: being an immigrant in the US without legal authorization is a civil infraction, not a criminal offense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not talking about all of them"...some, he assumes, are good people https://t.co/qN479KRq6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslovegrove @dallasnews ah thanks for the correction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pick for Energy secretary sits on Dakota Access Pipeline company's board https://t.co/rqd41L0FG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy who published these articles tells media to "keep its mouth shut and listen," has a real White House job https://t.co/qNYKrun6F2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of Trump's wall already built by Clinton, Bush and Obama. https://t.co/4ToTLL33oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man of principle https://t.co/SYiHwGs70E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's not how import taxes work. US consumers will pay for the wall, not Mexico https://t.co/CC9lqV4s9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump could publish a weekly list of crimes committed by any demographic incl. native born US citizens and it would be exponentially longer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: With few exceptions, immigrants are less crime prone than natives or have no effect on crime rates https://t.co/gv9kesfImt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyschweitzer @wamu885 it's my favorite show. I think an action packed expense account really resonates with a DC audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, the Kim Jong Il comparisons are justified https://t.co/qgVSNRyS4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only. I'd like to see him live up to a legacy of founding the EPA, establishing FLSA, and expanding food stamps https://t.co/Ven0v4R4SL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, now playing at @fordstheatre https://t.co/MaYSdAPDyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember him promising to bring back torture, but not promising to stop inspections of planes for fuselage cracks https://t.co/Unhwmoz8z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvoNeuro next thing you know he'll announce military parades and declare his inauguration a national holiday and...oh wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPilkman not to mention cherry picking the only poll that shows his approval ratings above 50%. Rasmussen a notoriously unreliable outlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvoNeuro Spicer to WH press corps: "That's what you guys should be writing"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a guy who hates the media, he sure relies on them for personal validation https://t.co/AcAphLehyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new POTUS is issuing policy decisions by tweeting about stuff he sees on the Today Show in real time https://t.co/fOzSMotLdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What revoking DACA would mean: families torn apart to punish kids who've never committed a crime, at a cost of $60b  https://t.co/dwKAPa6eTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It worked so well when Calderon did the same thing in Mexico in 2007. No more violence there! https://t.co/bDfuOzOL5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FHA fee hike ok bc 1)it hasn't gone into effect yet 2)Obama did it too 3)FHA market is either underregulated or overregulated we're not sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bizarre editorial from the Post defending Trump's mortgage fee cut suspension (i.e. your mortgage costs will go up) https://t.co/2yONoVgB9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: Trump's infrastructure plan is a corporate welfare giveaway https://t.co/JhmJ9ccRfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mnuchin says "small number of companies" would be affected by border tax. He should look up the USTR tariff schedule https://t.co/FAq3l6wTk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxpayers Will Defend Trump in Suit Charging Constitutional Violations https://t.co/33iiircU6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration courts largely haven't been able to hire new judges since 2011 budget sequester. Silver lining I guess https://t.co/9iEu7uKUR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a new piece in the Guardian today, on Trump's first #executiveorders: https://t.co/sRkAVZEx5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcartsbeat @NSOtweets well it can't compete with Cameron Carpenter's promo vid, that's for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump telling CIA how intellectual he is indicates he thinks "intelligence" in the gov't context means "really smar… https://t.co/nRVFFCs0L9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameyjasta @piersmorgan ouch.  When Piers wakes up the real nightmare begins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We at the @wcp are proud to announce our web traffic has surpassed that of the @washingtonpost and @nytimes combined #alternatefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cruelly persistent Horatio Alger myth in US politics https://t.co/ae79OmuHRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's what you guys should be writing," Minister of Propaganda Sean Spicer told journalists https://t.co/npQkwZnSJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything in Trump's #CIAspeech was demonstrably false, from "I love you guys" to "1.5 million" to "it didn't rain during my inauguration"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boss is the best organizer https://t.co/mBd4L9IYN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Mayor's office, on inaugural parade route https://t.co/MEs0OeyFiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Xanadu did Kubla Khan / a stately pleasure dome decree... https://t.co/UAAvXToxef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey maybe he really will keep his promises and #MakeAmericaGreatAgain. Also maybe Chapo Guzman really is not guilty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaugural ball features Irish riverdance but no Kanye because hip hop's not "traditionally American" enough. Hm wonder what that could mean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Should I keep the twitter going? Also I have a great idea for a new tv show called Aló Presidente"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I went to a Div III school and our football games were better attended than this https://t.co/aBNcJ4gUJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was on Argentina's @AgenciaTelam, talking about the transition and #TrumpInauguration: https://t.co/7fhQI6Nn46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's already delivering to ordinary Americans. First up: higher mortgages https://t.co/xMXyiMj3SO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was fast: Info about LGBT rights in the workplace have been removed from DOL's website]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guessing Trump mostly wrote that speech himself, except for all the times he said "we" instead of "I." That had to be someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hemantmehta @jlupf Even Chavez mentioned Jesus at his inaugural https://t.co/PHO7yK5kTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgot one more strongman he cribbed his speech from: https://t.co/1CipXIWbtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a take on the #TrumpInauguration speech in @GdnUSopinion, with @JillAbramson @Jamie_Weinstein &amp; @thrasherxy https://t.co/Fvs9Z96NI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good timing. There are still some cabinet posts available https://t.co/jIS6P2ADVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promising to "eliminate entirely" National Endowment for the Arts and privatize Corp. for Public Broadcasting https://t.co/xi2SSYE5CQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promises military parades under his administration: "That military may come marching down Pennsylvania Avenue… https://t.co/PZ1bSsEl2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interns built the pyramids https://t.co/g2tJGnGz5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's raised the bar for trolling, D'Souza's getting desperate https://t.co/PPuJcNKpOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish this had space for Chuck Brown and Fugazi but this is succinct and good https://t.co/WMcbNhwuMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guns for grizzly bears thing is absurd but also a sign that Trump's people feel they can say literally anything https://t.co/yVmbVoVBVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Award-Winning Mexico Indigenous Environmental Activist Murdered https://t.co/8tK0mggqcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey it worked great for Zimbabwe and Venezuela https://t.co/dndH9GXmRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miweintraub83 @liviaisabella13 @javier_osorio @JocelynViterna  @mkguliford but do check @CentAmPolMike's blog, it's an invaluable resource]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miweintraub83 @liviaisabella13 @javier_osorio @JocelynViterna @CentAmPolMike hi @mkguliford, Ive a working paper at https://t.co/VkmG8dqDuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaseMadar I'm sure there will be lots of opportunities for similar pieces under this administration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaseMadar Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The authoritarian roots of DeVos's education reform model https://t.co/sFf2w7mYaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder which is more daunting for a CEO-turned-public official: realizing ppl actually criticize you, or you're actually expected to do work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Trump labor pick Andrew Puzder has voiced second thoughts about nomination @CNNPolitics https://t.co/5rXVSwSPA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich Kids Stay Rich, Poor Kids Stay Poor https://t.co/3iSWYRQn7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minimum wage debate and the curse of Econ 101 https://t.co/O2WbIIwy2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which country do you think Toby Keith will be named ambassador to? https://t.co/7wupaEejOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the third or fourth white supremacist org to set up shop in northern VA, along with American Nazi Party and NRA https://t.co/IRkmRdIqu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful vote on behalf of Pharma by 13 Dems, all the more shameful bc McCain, Paul, Cruz voted for it https://t.co/fwb3ApohoW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>