<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How can we "get smart" when we have an idiot leading the country? #TrumpsterFire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussiaConnects I sure hope the FSB is paying you well to spread agitprop. Then again, given how crappy Russia's economy is, probably not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_J_Maloney I don't think we have one - we could have permanent bases there from how it's sounding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@justinamash is a principled man of integrity. We need more like him. https://t.co/VtoYBkB7fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepDougCollins @YouTube If we don't have the #JCPOA, what's the alternative? I'm waiting . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephland007 @CNN Oh, and I don't really watch TV. I read. Unlike our current president. https://t.co/QahEGD3CJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephland007 @CNN What, &amp; just listen to @PressSec lie through his teeth? https://t.co/5KrWWS3jpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephland007 Trump is alienating Muslim allies, could start a trade war, &amp; threatened to invade Mexico. No, I won't "lighten up"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepDougCollins @davidwebbshow Are you serious? Have you seen the mess #Trump is making of foreign policy? https://t.co/pYoyVqEWJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_pence The 25th Amendment is there for a reason. Huddle w/ Mattis, Tillerson &amp; others and use it. https://t.co/pYoyVqEWJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to go on social media just once this year w/out discovering that Trump has sparked another geopolitical crisis. #TrumpsterFire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump Australia is one of our closest allies. Will you please stop pissing off all of our friends? You are a danger to #NatSec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole world is going to hate us before this is over. https://t.co/tvwNWJnyWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, I really hope he was joking. #TrumpsterFire https://t.co/xLwMkA9o4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article from Republican and former Bush speechwriter @davidfrum on danger of #Trump presidency. #resist https://t.co/ydVbrC3nKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another reason to hate @DrJillStein - she's just as much a tool of #Putin as @GenFlynn https://t.co/Lxr38CQ3rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says that #Venezuela is not getting enough attention - on verge of meltdown. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin highlights the fact that the majority of refugees flowing into Europe come from sub-Saharan Africa, not MENA #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says he thinks we're in for some "rocky seas" in regards to the Philippines. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepMcEachin asks how we can keep Philippines in our orbit, given rise of #Duterte #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says we need to keep sanctions in place on #Russia, especially given their violation of nations' borders #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin questions @Liz_Cheney's characterization of #JCPOA - says he's confident we can detect cheating. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that we need a "sustained commitment" to Afghanistan. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: We need to "tend the garden" of our #NATO allies - #Putin is trying to invade our garden. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Rep_Hunter makes subtle dig at #Trump's alarming rhetoric in regards to #NATO. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: U.S. needs to pay more attention to our polices of strategic communication with the world. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says we have competition for foreign talent. "If you fly into Canada, they have signs -'can't get H1-B visa? Try here!" #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepSheaPorter reiterates #Petraeus's comment that our society's openness is strategic advantage - helps us attract best &amp; brightest #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sethmoulton says that #MuslimBan does not pass #Petraeus's test of "taking more bad guys off the battlefield than it puts on" #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Says "don't make the assumption" that there will be uprising in Russia against #Putin #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes there is a need to revise #AUMF #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that extremists' interpretations are "twisted and tortured." Refutes @RepMoBrooks contention that Koran is to blame #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepMoBrooks engaging in blatant Islamophobia in this hearing. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that Muslims are "critical" to fight against #ISIS #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that we shouldn't stoop to #ISIS's level when it comes to torture. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus condemns torture - is "wrong and doesn't work." Need to establish relationships with detainees, not abuse them. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says #MuslimBan shows that #Trump administration doesn't understand how hard governing is - proper review didn't happen #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that #MuslimBan creates more bad guys than it takes off the streets. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AustinScottGA08 represents my hometown. Dangerously naive about #Russia. Need a moderate GOP challenger who isn't #Trump's flunky #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AustinScottGA08 Seems to be playing apologist for #Russia in this hearing. Also says that #Putin doesn't want Assad to stay. LOL #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nikiinthehouse points out that we need to avoid sending conflicting messages to our allies. #HASC #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus, emphasizes need for #Muslim allies, quotes Churchill "only thing worse than fighting with allies is fighting without them" #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Points out that lack of intel sharing among Europeans is one reason for #ISIS successes. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepJoeCourtney discusses how #MuslimBan has made Iraqi prime minister's position precarious, could undermine Iraq's stability #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin points out that #Russia has done joint exercises with #China in #SouthChinaSea #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Says what #China has done in South China Sea is "indefensible" in terms of maritime law. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepJoeCourtney emphasizes how lack of US participation in #UNCLOS emboldens China in South China Sea #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Says that Asian allies are concerned about America's withdrawal from #TPP - fear they may be driven into #China's orbit #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that with #TPP being shelved, we need more efforts to strengthen Asian alliances. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Says that #Ukraine is the only nation that can change #Russia. If it can be thriving democracy, undermines #Putin #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But #Petraeus says that firmness should not morph into provocation re: Russia. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes that we need to be "firm" with respect to the #Russians. Lauds #ERI.#HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: We need to be clear and "firm" that we will not put up with aggression against #NATO from #Russia. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that #MuslimBan keeps #Iraqi generals from coming to America to coordinate fight against #ISIS #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that despite centrifugal forces in #Iraq, central government's distribution of oil is powerful centripetal force #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: #Putin's aims - consolidate power in Russia, ensure Russia's freedom of action in surrounding countries. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith Says he sees #Putin as "having clear plan" to push fascist leadership in other countries. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith criticizes language around #MuslimBan from #Trump - is deeply damaging to relationship with allies against #ISIS #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that #Muslim allies are on "the front line" in the fight against #ISIS. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith criticizes how #Bannon &amp;  @GenFlynn characterize #Muslims as the enemy - makes it harder to fight terror. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith criticizes Bannon's views on Muslims, given that #Muslim allies are most important in fight against #ISIS. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says we need ability to work well with other nations. Again, a dig at #Trump. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says we are most influential nation, but can't solve problems on our own. Need partnerships. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus discusses need to avoid #ThucydidesTrap when engaging with China. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says US needs relationship with #China that is based on mutual respect. We should shape world together, rather than clash #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MacTXPress says pols need to do a better job of educating Americans on benefits of engaging with world. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin discusses revolution in energy markets - oversupply of oil. But we shouldn't pull back from Mid East. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin says that "deals with Russia will not come easily." Again, a subtle dig at @realDonaldTrump #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin laments that our withdrawal from #TPP leaves vacuum that China will fill.  #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin criticizes how #Brexit has destabilized Europe, " our closest allies." Yet #Trump lauded Brexit. #HASC #Petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: The odds are high that N. Korea gets nuclear ICBM capability during this administration - maybe even this Congress. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin seems to be reciting the arguments of @tomfriedman in "Thank You for Being Late." #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin: Success for us will center on our ability to manage alliances and build coalitions. #HASC #petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#McLaughlin emphasizes that we need international rules to keep world from sliding into chaos. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus highlights the threat that #Russia poses to international order. Counsels resolve in face of aggression. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus says that we cannot take international order for granted. It can "fray and collapse." Trump should also remember that. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes that America's values as "free and open society" help us confront threats. We can recruit bright foreign minds #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes that Islamic extremists want to portray war as "clash of civilizations." Subtle dig at #MuslimBan #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes that most important allies against ISIS and AQ are the "vast majority of Muslims." Trump should remember that. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus emphasizes that "relationship with China is the most important relationship in the world." Need to find balance, be nuanced. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Petraeus Decries "the spiral of protectionism" that caused poverty in the 1930s. #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith emphasizes importance of alliances in countering threats. "Alarmed" about America First approach that distances allies #HASC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepAdamSmith Points out that military size has decreased because we no longer have massive troop presence in Iraq &amp; Afghan #HASC #petraeus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #HASC hearing with #petraeus. Stay tuned for updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican Fausts https://t.co/Vlm8Q4hpsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No, they're delaying because you're acting like a fascist. #RefugeesWelcome #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to be a #lawdawg tonight. @UGASchoolofLaw @SallyQYates #RefugeesWelcome #NoBanNoWall #MuslimBan https://t.co/GS8ZRujdVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some nice activism in tonight. #RefugeesWelcome #NoBanNoWall #MuslimBan https://t.co/oDWyXuYkm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are so full of it. #TrumpsterFire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LindseyGrahamSC walking the walk. #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/b3AgCLzfva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Succinct and accurate. #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/8MqexsVszF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Thanks for ur leadership. ISIS will use #MuslimBan against us. #GoldenShower Donny is helping terrorists. #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if things aren't already screwed up enough already. #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/JSNIbb90dF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EducatorJohnson @KurtSchlichter @RVAwonk They already undergo a rigorous 2-year vetting process. This is just Trump appealing to bigots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rushlimbang There is already a rigorous 2-year vetting process for refugees. This is obviously an appeal to Islamophobes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashcroftgm @MormonNewsroom I'd like a more pronounced denunciation of a facially discriminatory measure. But thank you for speaking up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MormonNewsroom Thank you for addressing this issue. Please encourage my fellow Mormons to reject the politics of hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet so many Americans willfully ignored his psychosis and voted for him.  https://t.co/b23c3L0KXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sensible voice on trade. A trade deficit is NOT a budget deficit. We can have a trade deficit and still be better… https://t.co/ONH3aoVS0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffFlake @Medium Thank you for speaking up.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>