<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Show us your tears, Tommy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still don't want the Pats to win, but seriously, I've got nothing but respect. Maybe a little awe. Some envy, too. Annoyance? Yeah, also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On question of Brady's legacy, case closed. By coming back from this deficit to force first OT in Super Bowl history. He's it. The greatest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadlocked teams, seconds on the clock, winning drive in the making... this is what Super Bowl dreams are made of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Pats' kicker can't do his own job, Brady will do it for him. Twice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's the helmet catch, and then there's what Edelman just did. Gif of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These 'lil twerps are just the cutest. https://t.co/326NzSl5EF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pete Seeger for the #SuperBowl win!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to see Brady's face smudged with makeup-stained tears as if mascara is running down his face. Don't relent, Atlanta!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's lesson in US civics continues. What's a constitution, anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByngBasketball No one told us it was a math class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great defensive dramatics by Saints, but Kits pulls off the win in their last home game before city championships next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kits leading Saints 75-64 with about three minutes to play. I'd be specific but too many lights are burned out in the scoreboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcboysbball 56-52! Fat thumbs!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KG Dragons beat Byng Ghosts 57-52 in battle of the undefeated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoops! Byng looking in control setting up a three-point look, errs uncharacteristically and throws the ball away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Byng turns it over, Yoel blocks the lane, and KG holds possession with 22.2 to play. He then sinks one of two free throws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KG Dragons lead Byng Ghosts 54-52 with 46 seconds to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some parents, I swear... they give opposing teenage players such grief. They're kids. Change the uni, and you're their biggest fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww, aren't they cute!! Parents crying for a "flagrant" foul as their precious gets stopped charging the lane. Game tied at 50.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those of you wondering, KG point guard Yoel's first name is pronounced you-EL. His last won't fit in my tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, refs T'd up KG coach Darko Kulic for vociferous, hyper sideline antics. Tonight, they're letting him do his thing. @kg_dragons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KG Dragons start the fourth quarter leading the Byng Ghosts 44-41.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoachEbe One-point difference, one minute to play in the third.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bromige sunk 10 of Byng's 13 second quarter points to lead all players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoel says, take that! Ends second quarter with rafter-brushing trey at the buzzer to go up 29-26.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End-to-end Bromige matching up against end-to-end Yoel. Classic basketball downtown showdown at KG. You should be here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bromige nails a trey at the buzzer to give @byngathletics a 15-12 lead over @kg_dragons after one quarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before 10-0 @kg_dragon meet 9-0 @byngathletics a reminder: "Never let loss get to your heart or win go to your head" https://t.co/TrVnF3nuZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There it is!! https://t.co/AXCH5Nu3P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope the pedestrian seen walking in the bike lane saw this as an educational moment. https://t.co/P7hWDRioas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderful tradition made terrible today. What a raw deal this is. https://t.co/wPd5P9qmXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are MedicAlert bracelets. Today the #VPD announces a partnership to help locate missing people, including tho… https://t.co/a6Z3f0rFbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking along in the sunshine, casually talking aloud to myself... in Portuguese, so I really would have sounded crazy to most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After an aired-out three sails into nothing, enthusiastic father at junior basketball game says, "That's ok, did you see that great pass!?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paramedics responding to an unconscious man on Water St. Brunch eaters witnessing the scene inches away over their… https://t.co/XvhZQkouqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most shocking is that bodies of last two known Beothuk were dug up and put in a UK museum. What a disgrace. https://t.co/XQpKWBLsbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about pizza for dinner is pizza for breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing in sport like the Williams sisters. They are heroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These acceptance speeches are too Academy for my liking, but these women deserve every platform they rise to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn if Venus isn't stealing the spotlight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else would you most want to hug after a terrific win (23!) than your first and life-long opponent? These sisters. Poetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deserved praise for @htsumura after three decades of important work. Inspiration to many, me included! https://t.co/66VnIjIvlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally blew off a woman I was interviewing because I didn't want her to see me cry as she described families relying on free food handouts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know US runners from Alabama, Arkansas, Indiana, Delaware, Montana, Nebraska, North Dakota, Wyoming? #bmovm is this close to 50-state sweep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a star, Howie. Been at it as long as I've been alive. Can't wait to see what's next! https://t.co/BmYTDF7de2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coordinated dribbling is just wrong. Basketball is not Zumba. https://t.co/EJM4rbKii8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent yesterday writing about performance-based diet and interviewing nutritionists. So why not come home today to KD? #macncheeseplease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These trespassing Brazilian tourists can climb... but not fall safely. https://t.co/oIQ7ALm8Xa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When snow and ice lock down your track, you take training indoors and get creative like they did @ubctrack. https://t.co/EQllxNkFPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I'm sick of being sick, I'm taste-testing mouthfuls of garlic and mouthfuls of oregano oil. Verdict: Don't do it unless you have to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Player: "What team do I put on this form?"
Teammate: "Huh?"
Player: "Curry team? I made curry."
Teammate: "Dude. Men's rugby."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard one of the jocks say, "This was actually way better than I expected." Good food for the win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of today's recipes made and enjoyed by rugby players. The egg and veg breakfast "muffins" were favourites. https://t.co/xc9fLj6X0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost none of these athletes cook with tofu, but they learned to make the cheap, plant-based protein super crispy so they'll cook it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There were a few zucchini slices lost to the floor, but generally the knife skills were good --- and got better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After these rugby players cooked this food, nutritionist advice is to fill plate with a quarter protein, quarter da… https://t.co/03sxTY4LhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Athletes in the kitchen. Today, it's @ubctbirds rugby learning about the food that best fuels them. https://t.co/9R2yeVyzCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's my voice! I'm a word model! (13-minute mark, but don't skip ahead in this fantastic podcast from Barry.) https://t.co/OhCI6O1rse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two wheels pointed in the direction of equality. https://t.co/dqPYznSGSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This came up @ParkBoard meeting just now; GM said he wasn't aware of project and what it means for parks and CCs. https://t.co/5IAmDt6SZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heightened emotions and anger, much of it directed at commissioners and then to the public face of the aquarium, Jo… https://t.co/zd5EicSioW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The park board has decided to get more information on cetaceans in captivity and has deferred decision on pebscite. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loud shouting: "No plebiscite without a moratorium," and, "Moratorium now! Moratorum now!" #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eighth participant in park board meeting is most definitely vocal gallery. Applause, "shame," "moratorium," "sell-out." #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Nightingale, aquarium CEO, sits in back row as park board meeting erupts with calls for moratorium. #vanpoli https://t.co/cA1Ab9BZvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motion now considered to refer discussion to staff for report because referendum is "blunt tool". Put forward by @catherineevans. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussion of cetaceans in captivity at Vancouver aquarium now has full attention of commissioners and a keyed-up gallery. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On motion about cetaceans: 117 emails support and 3 oppose; 4,521 signatures support motion; 557 want end to captivity at aquarium #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the white on white tailored pantsuit that @ErinYVR is sporting tonight for the park board meeting. Where can I get one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are finding we are trying not to rush when we are being told to slow down." @parkboard staff on working with First Nations. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They are working on a timeline of seven generations, really, of dealing with the impacts of reconciliation. &gt;&gt;&gt; #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...that is used to working a bit more swiftly… We are trying to do our best to respect what they are asking. &gt;&gt;&gt; #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;&gt;&gt; "Nations feel moving more slowly is the better way to go rather than moving more quickly. It can be somewhat difficult for staff... &gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnCCoupar asked about timeline on advancing discussions and relationship-building with First Nations. This was staff's answer &gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On docket tonight for park board discussion: should voters decide fate of whales and dolphins at Vancouver aquarium. https://t.co/0xWvq38Yc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of media hanging around @ParkBoard meeting tonight, but first up is a committee updated from staff. Surprise! Up later, cetaceans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders and staff from @KitsilanoCC @WestPointGreyCC and @DunbarCC also hosted workshop on aboriginal relationship-building, as recommended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 268 park board staff, beginning with youth workers, attended workshop on building understanding with aboriginal patrons and people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Lex! Another success story outta @vgba604. https://t.co/WzNGOcDBwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands and thousands in the streets. #WomensMarch #seattle #seattlewomensmarch https://t.co/VRZqnvuH5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking down Jackson St. in solidarity with the resistance of Rosa Parks. #WomensMarch #seattlewomensmarch https://t.co/CF9MlSLaRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will be hell to pay, indeed. No one is free if we're not all free. #WomensMarch #Seattle #seattlewomensmarch https://t.co/vv9eQS0gzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May everyone in the US enjoy the privileges Trump has know. #WomensMarch #Seattle https://t.co/msti2aF1UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay attention @POTUS. #WomensMarchSeattle https://t.co/IYPoI0tpsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pussy power on the way to Jackson Street. #WomensMarchSeattle https://t.co/VFrvb0wIYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KING5Seattle "I've gotta tell y'all, run to your doctors right now." Morning speaker at #WomensMarch #Seattle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police officer told me this morning they initially anticipated 40,000. https://t.co/hTKpPJ5nxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump bops along to the songs with all the grace and decorum of a pre-schooler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless sweet Sweden for this distraction. Sports for the win. https://t.co/JO1igYsbhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Totally unstoppable, bro. Like, jeah. God's got our back, bro. We're bigliest, bud."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's going for gravitas. He's falling terrible flat. Repeated words, weak images, bloated hyperbole. No doubt he wrote this himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump can fake his reality so I choose to believe this choir is wearing pussy hats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus can't save you now. #InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should have said: Mr. President, Mr. Vice-President. Ms. President-elect, Mr. Vice President-elect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like they made the little one stand up. I mean, teenagers, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another one. We feel you, Michelle. It's real. It's the worst. https://t.co/PwSTRH86I0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did one of Trump's junior henchmen just shoo the littlest one? That kid looks so alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March organizers made sure portable bathrooms and breastfeeding stations are set up along the route. https://t.co/zhtHAq6hhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can hardly imagine a more painful public disgrace than watching, from feet away, the least qualified man take an oath you should be saying.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>