<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[TransFormers: The Last Knight. Star Wars: The Last Jedi. Are they working on a crossover - The Last Jedi Knight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's starting to look a little like Hoth outside so this is playing right now. #StarWars… https://t.co/CfQfcqX16I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing on an overcrowded platform at Marine Drive station and an out of service train zips by. Not cool @TransLink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnoxRobbins I think the chances that Snyder directs The Batman is about the same as Ryan Reynolds returning to Green Lantern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S SNOWING!!! https://t.co/kOgv0odiaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HappyGroundhogDay https://t.co/srryskrhkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith  If you're wondering who should direct a Batman film, just look into a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see another store closing. This one really hurts. #riphmv #closing @ Hmv Canada https://t.co/34VEI6YXXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k @doubleofive That's exactly my issue with it. Give me the extended VHS/ first DVD cut in the 2:1 ratio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k @doubleofive I do like the 2:1 framing. I just don't care for some of changes Meyer made to the film for the 2-disc DVD cut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransLink really needs to get rid of the bus transfer tickets. I keep seeing people trying to tap in/out on SkyTrain with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k Actually, I'm all for this. Gives him a chance at redemption. Also, I feel I'm the one person who likes Batman Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k I thought Phantom Menace was film?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Apple Music has quietly replaced the #StarWars soundtracks with the original versions in place of the special editions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshannonburns you're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie number two for today! Time to get caught up on the #Oscar nominees. #HiddenFigures… https://t.co/Ds4m55GqTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for find #TheFounder #mcdonalds #michaelkeaton @ Landmark Cinemas 10 New Westminster https://t.co/1VfgNVbSNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRossBowie @micahdfowler Two weeks?!? Going to binge watch all the existing episodes a few times while I wait. @Speechless_ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheDickVanDykeShow is one of my favourite tv shows of all time. A big reason why is the chemistry between @iammrvandy and #MaryTylerMoore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnoxRobbins Well, if John Musker and Ron Clements get a must deserved Oscar, you won't hear me complaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this relic of the 90s outside the abandoned Target today. @ Lansdowne Centre https://t.co/XUmP3CbDFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrshBakedDisney Never seen it, but excited that I now have a chance to see it. #MainStreetElectricalParade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all my Seattle friends, make sure you see #LaLaLandMovie at the #Cinerama. https://t.co/FeBCeC41aX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always loved how @JohnCleese's character in A Fish Called Wanda is named Archie Leach as a tribute to #CaryGrant's birth name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k Yeah, even if their on alternate timelines it would make sense to keep the same actors, but I'm sure he'll be good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing that it keeps getting delayed, but this is the first new Star Trek TV show in 12 years, it has to be… https://t.co/q052P3uwGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morganhoffman @SpaceChannel @TheCdnAcademy Congratulations! Much deserved. Great work everybody! @AjayFry @TeddyWilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Monday? I thought you said Blue Monkey. https://t.co/r6PfE5ZPSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I really want to see a #StarWars film starring the cast of #StrangerThings. Or at least a young Princess Leia f… https://t.co/E3pndRJGan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahSnitch @FrshBakedDisney If someone says WDW is better, just ask for a photo of Walt walking around one of the parks there. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people worked on designing and building the Death Star. When you download the plans, you're stealing from… https://t.co/KqSGV2M5n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_dante One of my favs (I think I may need to put on the Blu-ray tonight). Glad more people are discovering it. #Innerspace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough loss for the #Seahawks. Here's to next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sylvester Stallone and Carl Weathers! #Rocky #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a sweep! There's your best picture Oscar winner. #LaLaLand #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After seeing the #SingStreet clip, Dad turns to me and asks "do you have a copy of that one?" Yes, yes I do. Turning the AppleTV on... NOW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwhyte @aliciamalone One of the most beautiful women on the red carpet tonight. #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Thor is Marvel and Wonder Woman is DC?!? What are they trying to pull? #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Can't wait to see what you come up with (I think you'd make a great Jyn). Which comic-con are you going to? Emerald City?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwhyte That's not a plug for the Jerry Maguire: 20th Anniversary Edition - now available on Blu-ray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Yeah, I thought it was great. Glad you liked it, too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BestBuyCanada Still no Wallet/Passbook support for Reward Zone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get home and the first #ToyStory is on TV. Have not watched it in (at least) 5 years and I can still recite each line word for word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw someone today wearing shoes that said Stan Smith on the side. Didn't realize how much #AmericanDad merch was out there. @SethMacFarlane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekatiewilson @NBCEmeraldCity Recordered last nights premiere, will have to watch it when I get a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alkali_layke If I had to pick only four from that list - 1. Guardians of the Galaxy 2. Episode VIII 3. Blade Runner 4. Kingsman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Denis8 Well, it looks like Warner Bros won't be hiring me to direct one any time soon, so I think that will have to do for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Denis8 Unlike the games, there has been at least one great #Superman movie. It's simply called Superman: The… https://t.co/kf01SYTpiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for those of us looking for it in Vancouver, it's now at The Park(?!?). #FBFFEST https://t.co/0TnDrCvoQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright! Happy birthday to a Canadian icon, everyone's favourite small town cop and one of the nicest guys around -… https://t.co/YQQZNIT4EC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k Surprised when I saw that on the drive. 2D is in 4K while 3D is 2K. Rogue One and Passengers also did that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Still, I don't mind snow from time to time. But this has been way too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Those temperatures are in Celsius, so roughly the same as what you're getting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu I was just looking at my weather app thinking the same thing. https://t.co/sAy0JloGHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTillyer The question isn't whether or not they made it, question is if they'll release it. Was supposed to come out two years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CineplexEvents Cool. Can't wait to hear what you have in store. I usually like to pull a few all-day marathons each year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @CineplexEvents, what's going on with the #GreatDigitalFilmFest ?When is it? What titles are playing? When do tix go on sale? #GDFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeattleCinerama Happy new year! One of my top goals for 2017 is to make it back to Seattle for a visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year to everyone who lives in the Mountain Time Zone. But most of all to @MsMauz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my calculations are correct, once we hit midnight, the Death Star should be going bye-bye… https://t.co/CR0blc1MPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachel_is_here Still got another 3 hours to go here on the west coast. 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year to all my friends on the east coast. You survived 2016!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost new calendar time. Happy new year! #nye2017 https://t.co/RRBgWt68JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles3k @OldMovieAds I saw it in a building with a DLP screen but we were in a 35mm house (Bicentennial Man was on the DLP).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to reveal my top 10 films of 2016...                1. Zootopia… https://t.co/762dtB5RT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joekraemer Congrats. Hope to help you double that number by the end of 2017. Everyone, please give this man a follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJennTracker I am so very sorry to hear this. Sending you and Tim lots of good thoughts. #heartbroken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am both laughing and crying at the same time. #CarrieFisher https://t.co/hIRppnBvOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never met @carrieffisher but did attend her panel @FANEXPOVAN 2015. She was just as beautiful, funny and charming as I hoped she would be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This entire album might be on a loop for the next few weeks via Apple Music. #lalaland https://t.co/MUsTkBWPOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this come with $13 tucked in the case? Cause, even if it did, still not enough. https://t.co/DGVefyl5RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilmonkeybutt Just saw it. Was looking forward to it for a while and wasn't disappointed. Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's finally happening. #lalaland #emmastone @ Cineplex Scotiabank Theatre https://t.co/BkZlJqozD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watching #JingleAllTheWay - Arnold, Sinbad and kid Darth Vader in this Christmas classic. #TurboTime https://t.co/8ZGEawmLWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be me tomorrow. https://t.co/16AK0RfNN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was waiting for me under the tree today. It's like @MikeOkuda, @deniseokuda, @roddenberry and Santa all teamed… https://t.co/CGtq0oJFOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to all my friends and followers here in the twitterverse. https://t.co/sBVlb9Usqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas movie marathon tonight started with #ChristmasVacation then it was #AChristmasStory now it's time for #DieHard - Yipee Ki Yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Christmas wishes do come true. It's great that you get to spend the day with your family. Very festive pic btw. #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to fight back against 2016. Sending good thoughts to @carrieffisher and her friends, family and fans.… https://t.co/VVvD6Nxptd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thordiakow I really can not wait to see #lalaland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great discussion that's definitely worth checking out. https://t.co/1MzSN2lNPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJennTracker It's been a tough year. Your videos that have helped me get through this year so thank you for that. Hope all is well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacehindu These look great. Congratulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Can I refill your eggnog for you? Get you something to eat? Drive you out to the middle of… https://t.co/0axozXOHCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leah_Holiove One of my favourites as well. Watching it right now. Now Christmas can begin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RogueOne round 2. This time in 2D. #reclinerseats @ Landmark Cinemas 12 Guildford Surrey https://t.co/WyEEeVNq6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsbulk Saw that, so that makes #RogueOne the second #StarWars in a row to involve a #StarTrek film director?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilmonkeybutt  Never had those but I do remember when Star Wars was a trilogy - just 3 films (no prequels, sequels or spinoffs).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally off for three days after working opening weekend of the new #StarWars film. https://t.co/N21jt86Dx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsbulk @SidGrauman Good to know that they're aren't any psychotic robot donuts out there. How was the rest of the screening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsbulk My copy just came in the mail today. Going to try and hold off until Christmas before opening it. It's my Christmas present to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's now 10:00 on opening night, let's talk #RogueOne spoilers! Everyone's seen it now, right? If not, we can just pretend that you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SasakiTime Sadly there aren't any @DolbyCinemas near me. Actually not a single one in all of Canada. Hopefully that changes. @ukboomer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnoxRobbins @jasonwhyte Not sure, was only made aware of it the last night. I know for certain that it is NOT a print.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeattleCinerama Cool, that's all I'm hoping for is that you begin thinking about. Although July is looking packed with big films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Disney is being a bit extreme with this Star Wars promotion. They've turned this city into Hoth (although it's more like Coldth).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: at no point in #RogueOne does Tom Cruise show up and hang off the side of an Imperial shuttle. #disappointed #RogueOneNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeattleCinerama Any plans on getting this one in 70mm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanikuzu Giving you a follow and occasionally sending a supportive tweet is the least I could do. Happy birthday. Have a great year ahead.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>