<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin Keep them coming Quinny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt you always grabbed me by the  throat and the heart. You stand with the truly great.Farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reading a poem a day to keep Trump at bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's axis rattles from left to right as millions shake their heads watching Trump's press conference. Obama to Bozo. Heartbreaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's inauguration will have 'soft sensuality'. Sick in my mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep. Oh my goodness. Very single word landed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick Gower YOU are 'political chaos'. Get a grip man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#JohnKey you were that slightly daggy uncle who told it to us straight when the other adults were pissing about with platitudes. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin yeah dump the vego gastric band. Bike and Kai Moana!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#onesmart the complete PITS! Can't activate card. Waited on phone for 53mins only to be disconnected. Get your act  together!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump headlines become more surreal, more frightening by the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us fervently hope Trump is another politician who reneges on his promises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last para spot on.
Donald Trump's lying far more sinister than distortion of facts https://t.co/KfNVYrnhGu via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played Ireland. Thoroughly deserved. If it had to be someone glad it was you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Amidst the rubble of the collapsing state', this. This premise I deeply believe in.https://t.co/GlqkfAVogf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin That one's going straight to the pool room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilary was magnificent. Utterly. Trump dangerous and unhinged. Utterly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dan Carter is a complete babe. That's all I've got to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stat: 20 players have scored tries in the All Black's nine internationals this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Jessica Valenti: ‘People will say that Trump won simply because he didn’t spontaneously combust on stage’” https://t.co/bsC4Ubc1vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the bar really that low that some commentators are saying Trump did 'well' ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over and out Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What on earth is Trump doing stalking Hillary around the stage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is beginning to feel  increasingly ugly https://t.co/G3eNMU5qK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Athleisure'- who knew this was a 'thing' let alone an entire industry?An oxymoron only the fashionistas could mangle together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you think Trump couldn't cock it up any more. Jawdroppingly atrocious.https://t.co/dItovWjSAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @SnakeMcHardy @NickSpeak13 @johnpagani bit of early slap n tickle then black by 22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look in the mirror Wallabies Argentina is tapping you on the shoulder. Respect Pumas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elated. Exhausted. What a first half #AllBlacks .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have just eaten the perfect fried egg. Just, just so on just, just crisp bread. If that is all I achieve today I will have done enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Deserter'. Tears. https://t.co/2fkZP4CxKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What will survive of us is love.” Philip Larkin. Happy Poetry Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny with a knife in the guts https://t.co/YNi95ABDHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching MastermindNZ. Yuk. Imagine discovering you're only average undies not smarty pants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America never tasted so good as at @hillside_nz last night. Utterly foodlicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gobsmacked at the leave predictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timothy Spall: 'The feeling of doing it wrong gets bigger and bigger' https://t.co/st3Gk3Ydbi
Could spend hours with him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Guardian view on the EU referendum: keep connected and inclusive, not angry and isolated | Editorial https://t.co/esetQ1RVPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welly, Welly wonderful rainbow https://t.co/7A56f4DsMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Observer view on Donald Trump https://t.co/LQbXxFI8Wc 'It's time to tell the ugly truth']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's disgraceful inhumanity to people seeking asylum https://t.co/LAy5NhURMG via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plated then sated https://t.co/JvIXKbFCZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the end of an island at the bottom of the world. They go to get my oysters #bluffheaven https://t.co/Q3tRvMbnzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have struggled with ideal drink between negroni and wine. Found it. Manzanilla sherry. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Little you despicable xenophobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Trump travesty gets more and more like a horror movie every day. Not liking it.https://t.co/EYkwRcQFDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joy of a seat in the shade. https://t.co/BjB0rN9Gpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right decision John Key. Suck the vitriol out of the day - in fact rename it and be done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @BusinessSpec Best commentary on this I've read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin now you know this not to be true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone ever punched their dental hygienist??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found heaven at Hillside. Serious food created and presented with complete joy - devoured in the same way @hillside_nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all stand with France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott is utterly devoid of any moral foundation. This expresses  it so eloquently https://t.co/tyeTZSJmLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oliviahadlow @mark_markhadlow That is your wonderful daughterly influence. Please share tips on how the rest of us can make him behave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YESSSSSSS!!!! Shall convert you yet @philquin http://t.co/bR9DGJu1zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmybain15 give us a hint....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Australia emerges from the Abbott miasma. Enjoy your Hubris Pie Tony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great writing.http://t.co/QGuVtBzuba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmybain15 Well reported. It may be the only way you and I make any money this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone else noticed Colin Slade's vampire tooth? All of a sudden I find him sooo much more interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lived in Aus when NZ took refugees from the Tampa Howard turned his back on. We did it quietly and sincerely.What's happened @johnkeypm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Flanagan calls this monstrous Border Force for what it truly is.
http://t.co/Nv7vn4BE7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmybain15 While his bib shorts are this tight he's all yours !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bloody love this! Men in Black.https://t.co/Icup46IhXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yeah!http://t.co/x0spItpMWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia, you are a country I love and that treated me well, but racial equality remains your despicable blind spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney Swans' Adam Goodes thrust into key role in race relations history http://t.co/M6GQstXQbH via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[' yeah a few selection challenges but we can't spew in our soup' - Steve Hansen, bloody legend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milliner Skudder in warm up like most players at full pelt. Bring it on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mishviews Thank god it's two years later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLUMP. Marvelous word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day two with my mother. If I have to listen to any more talk back radio I will do something violent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tad miffed Richie and Dan's last Crusader's game is being commented by Strayans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything so bleak as the reception room at a dental surgery ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing ovation in Nelson last night.
http://t.co/bwMFcUPKbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAMIL is in Nelson! We open tomorrow in the beautifully restored Theatre Royal http://t.co/G0kZYAqBVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin Well it's tough driving a can -anywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn - felt so good about a 5.30am start, then the text came through. "Ferry delayed'. 5.30am sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how cone John Campbell gets dumped and Justin Marshall keeps his gig?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#JohnCampbell class, integrity, humour and heart to the end. Thank you. Come back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that's how I named my company.. https://t.co/DZGBWRnQqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn this dude looks comfy http://t.co/AzXqqsVnT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuff does this mean he's moving through the island. #runforthehills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sob. He gone #JohnCampbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Harrycanes forever! Brilliant new moniker for tonight's right royal game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop whoop go Kiwis! What a win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderful taste of the breathtaking exhibition at Te Papa http://t.co/OFB2iof2ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh TV3 treat us with some respect please. This tat is not news. Ebloodynuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really, there is no one on earth who can out bogan Jimmy Cowan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place you'll find intelligence and heart on TV meedjuh. Hands off TV3. #SaveCampbellLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can barely believe Haddin's vicious comments. Thank the moon and the stars we're 'nice' rather than the boorish oafs Haddin represents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11.54 and already the heart is pounding #BacktheBlackCaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this Taylor's Stephen Donald moment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin Hurricanes don't need a second verse. We on fiyuh!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin are you succumbing to a certain rosy hue of corrective eyewear?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs Abbott,please take your husband aside and suggest he dismounts from that absurdly lanky horse he's been bouncing around on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chose the only pocket of high wind and torrential rain to go walking this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a finish Kane Willinson. Pharrrrrk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Australia - reverting to type.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>