<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder did he or did he not sell his stock? and how can we find out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians invite California, Oregon and Washington to join Canada 
LOVE IT !

https://t.co/l6nhzPcdSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugees have committed 0 attacks in the USA: 
AgentOrange is mentally unstable.  FACT
@realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/aW38aDRqrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a good manchild or we'll take away your Propecia. Your view of the world is in dire need of adjustment.  Mentall… https://t.co/Fyyvs3j7Wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you saying they weren't doing their job before?
Shame on your lack of intelligence !
@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/jkd9MWXpHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really think we are going 2 watch a so-called wanna be king's interview?
Suck it upButtercup, you buy your ratings,… https://t.co/ioTzmVDyWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC Dept. of Finance Confirms Trump Has Been Lying About His Income 
IMPEACH @realDonaldTrump
https://t.co/UmTzZFhHDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC News Hits Trump Hard With New Scandal, Leaked Documents Prove Guilt 
WAKE UP AMERICA

https://t.co/ZhSgsT3Cqg via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Posted A False News Report To His Facebook Page And Got Thousands Of Shares 

https://t.co/HQigtwdUTV via @davidmackau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin Is Back On SNL With A Cold Open To Top Off Trump’s Rage-Tweety Day (VIDEO) 

https://t.co/YLkxX6PQaW via @gopocalypse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lawyers are busy getting your impeachment papers ready.
Your mental illness is rapidly progressing.  Seek Help… https://t.co/BCzmIU9w6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fabricated a terrorist attack on the Louvre. This French woman’s response is perfect. 

https://t.co/8gzIdO7LWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're having a mental breakdown, seek help immediately.  
Our sanity is important, yours, not so much 
strait-jack… https://t.co/fYM8Vmsvvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP Just Revealed Documents Showing Trump Still Has Direct Ties 2 His Businesses 
The lies continue
@realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/TveJHelCjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fukushima: Japan Declares State Of Emergency, Reactor Leaks Into Ocean-  NOT GOOD 
https://t.co/cFjGRogtlG
Via - @NeonNettle
#NeonNettle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this coming from an illegitimate president who lost the popular vote and has the lowest presidential approval in HI… https://t.co/CZaFVdpN9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is wrong with cleaning up our own backyard first?

@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/k39ieVjvM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We often think what life would be like if your mother had not immigrated to America. Wishing !
Anyone have a time m… https://t.co/jZZvixPw2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump Also Promised to Resign From Family Business &amp; Hasn’t FiledPaperwork 
Apple doesn't fall from the tree

https://t.co/mVQN0kt1Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi suggests Donald Trump get his mental health checked 
Bellevue has room reserved
https://t.co/fiTX9Fnh8B via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump AND when are you leaving?You are top of that evil list.  Not a legitimate president.  Low ratings.… https://t.co/edATMrqrkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Judge in Seattle Just Blocked Trump’s “Muslim Ban” Nationwide 
YES YES YES
https://t.co/PKqdxnKnAy via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team takes credit for a quarter million jobs created under Obama 

LOL..give credit where due
 
https://t.co/DsOY7pjKPM via @shareblue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump said the man-child who lost the popular vote.  If Pooty hadn't helped you would still be on the ap… https://t.co/UJ0y0rzcjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump did you bully them into giving you and your staff burner phones? https://t.co/OwIRkMlTx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[about those phone calls @realDonaldTrump.  Why did you shut off the phone recording when talking to Pooty? Read his… https://t.co/L4b09RaxUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump that is because you are an ignorant bully playing in the worlds playground .  You are in over your… https://t.co/7MPxNYkY0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's talk about paid protesters &amp; fake supporters.Your proof?  Saying it does not make it true.  YOU paid ppl to c… https://t.co/qiuo8NEvc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nordstrom has officially cut ties with Ivanka Trump's brand 

https://t.co/3nYAhdufvK via @BI_RetailNews

@realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a photo-op at the expense of a fallen https://t.co/3cRaIdmBey are responsible for his death and everyone els… https://t.co/W5SjXNFZMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explain "put on notice" Think that is going to scare them?  LOL
Go to bed now...Bannon is waiting to read you a sto… https://t.co/uy7xyz0pDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cupcake YOU really need to get your facts straight.  Spend some time reading, instead of tweeting.  Kiss Bannon goo… https://t.co/WZmq6QVEcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Admin:TrumpLying About RaidThat Killed Navy Seal 
trump thinks military school makes him smarter than generals
https://t.co/LrhPv35IZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puppet master: Russia’s FSB announced Donald Trump was lifting sanctions before he did 

https://t.co/d1GZnQJW6a via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Just Killed Obama’s Rule Blocking Mentally Ill From Owning Guns 
trump can now buy a gun

https://t.co/4sqOxkUdUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s White House invents Iranian attack on U.S. ship; Pentagon admits it never happened https://t.co/lOIvgRvimR via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Law Lets Husbands Sue Doctors to Prevent Abortions 
Men are wanting to control a woman's body 
https://t.co/RLSDxQJvMz via @law_newz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Military OfficialsJustBlamed Trump For Disastrous RaidThat KilledAmerican Soldier
trump will blame someone else

 https://t.co/1G49vmqCBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/IOBfzHnjL2
Might want to check out just who gave...do I hear boycott?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have Psychological Evidence That Trump Is Seriously Crazy
 
LOL something most of us already knew   Bellevue calling
https://t.co/g65HrokJJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans Just Voted To Allow Dumping Of Coal Waste In Rivers - 

no end to the carnage 

https://t.co/ki8gMRsmdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans Just Voted To Allow Oil Companies To Hide Foreign Bribes 
A big F U to those who voted for trump
 https://t.co/jUI69kPJOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is NOT right ! https://t.co/FQce5ZPpSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics No surprise. Don't think even a marriage counselor can save this one.  All females use extreme caution when around small hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ WTH did they expect? Apprentice Supreme Court had to be in prime time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Flirts With Softer Stance on Russia's Conduct in Ukraine 
Bannon 2 get trump in line, sees dollar signs in future
https://t.co/DvgBkZrYcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Bannon's coup in the making @CNN
You can thank those that voted for AgentOrange for this 'coop' 

 https://t.co/FYGSSYAkkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NATO issues dire Ukraine warning as death toll hits 19
Just what Putin wanted.  Good little Donny 
 https://t.co/33JC2Ep1Wp via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Steve Bannon really does need Senate approval for National Security Council appointment https://t.co/Ftbv8BiSCE via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump may not move to Washington as planned
Does this mean trump
on the prowl for replacement?
Women beware

https://t.co/ae2bQNAiEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The psychology of why 94 deaths from terrorism are scarier than 301,797 deaths from guns https://t.co/SRSPS4ajE9 via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AZWb76cLWx

NO NO NO  do not destroy the National Parks  in exchange for the almighty oil $$$$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity Asked A Smart A*s Question On Twitter
and got burned !
https://t.co/8g6OYjEjKZ via @LibAmericaOrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Bannon Hit With Serious FBI Federal Election Law Complaint By Democratic Coalition https://t.co/xVzxi0gXFV via @HuffPostBlog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military situation in eastern Ukraine worsens @EurActiv 
AgentOrange/Bannon are causing a deflection 

https://t.co/WfJMTY8AVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro wish he would go back to reality TV.  Then we can turn him off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What were Beavis and Butthead doing there anyway? Again just another photo-op for the AgentOrange and his cult.… https://t.co/AcS0ODIaNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House insider: Steve Bannon made racist remarks about Supreme Court pick 

https://t.co/emTONppCKD via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under A New System, Clinton Could Have Won The Popular Vote By 5 Points And Still Lost Changes needed for fairness

 https://t.co/YUeP1C9fcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorism by Muslims accounted for .0033% of American killings last year.

 https://t.co/QcrOK5dqzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A White Man Allegedly Murdered 6 People At A Mosque, But Fox News Is Still Identifying A Moroccan As A Suspect

 https://t.co/iofwrseBPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U law prof Richard Painter sues Trump over ethics 

https://t.co/qR9W1dxUs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yMUjPpYCbo’re-falling-for-it/

Deflect  Divide  Destry is AgentOrange and Bannon's agenda 
@realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump didn’t realize Steve Bannon needs Senate confirmation for National Security Council https://t.co/adRZ1fG2qz via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's voting fraud expert was registered to vote in 3 states 
LOL@realDonaldTrump
https://t.co/tG3O20p4zc via @HuffPostCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ikea cabinets are better than your picks.  Get used to it cupcake, the resistance is just starting.  Bellevue is calling !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian protesters decry Donald Trump’s U.S. travel ban; urge Justin Trudeau action
@realDonaldTrump must go
https://t.co/2l4769zbkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chances of a refugee killing you - and other surprising immigration stats @CNNPolitics 
take a look @realDonaldTrump
https://t.co/rz82o2fABm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 million Brits just signed a petition to ax Trump's state visit 
@realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/HD0gzCDb53 via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trial Balloon for a Coup?” 

Time to get AgentOrange and his cult out of WH
@realDonaldTrump

by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/1X3ajKkMps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TheBrodyFile @CBNNews LOL, is that the best you can do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump exhibits classic signs of mental illness: shrinks 
@realDonaldTrump  twitter tantrum coming soon

https://t.co/JQWDqqAXaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China 'deploys nuclear-capable missiles' in response to Trump

You can thank those who voted for AgentOrange

 https://t.co/tuVvN2vkME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[speaks volumes.  AgentOrange is destroying America https://t.co/6RamYQtUl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Federal Judge Just BLOCKED Trump’s Executive Order On Immigration 

GREAT NEWS 

https://t.co/4tz1S1pnvt via @POLITICAL DIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you put a madman in charge.   
Thank a Republican

@realDonaldTrump 
@WhiteHouse https://t.co/UaRu0oyegP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s PM Offers Message of Solidarity to Refugees Turned Away by Trump

The Canadian way

@realDonaldTrump 
https://t.co/VEx7WvQTee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how the world is responding to Trump's ban on refugees, travelers from 7 Muslim nations 
@realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/ct6jBobrVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPMcCallum it's so sad I am American by birth, Canadian by choice.  This affects so many of my friends and family, Blessed to be here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery death of ex-KGB chief linked to MI6 spy's dossier on Donald Trump 

https://t.co/QmJEzeFHH7 via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suck it up cupcake.  You will always be known as a LIAR.  No national monuments for you.  Take your meds and resign… https://t.co/qwK3Ofs22C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear World, From America
Said so well
@realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/8nNYzfxYdN via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff who is the unholy trinity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: You can’t defend Christianity by being ‘against refugees and other religions’  https://t.co/ZmfVaLLFP9 https://t.co/Cw9lfrMn1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: these not-terrible things have also happened since Trump's inauguration  
https://t.co/P7HkVQncGL via @HuffPostCaLiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins’ Top Psychotherapist Releases Terrifying Diagnosis Of President Trump 
https://t.co/v9UNbHgHa4 via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is eager to undo sacred tribal monument

Why would anyone want to destroy this?
Oh yeah, the almighty $$$$$

https://t.co/pFTUvP5d5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's voter fraud expert owes US more than $100,000 in unpaid taxes 
No honour among thieves @realDonaldTrump

https://t.co/rM5qd0wAwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada, Netherlands discuss fund to counter Trump abortion order
US is no longer the leader of the free world.

 https://t.co/rApFTUK6d9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credible sources say Agent Orange misspelled his name on all those EO's, making them FAKE !  Meltdown happening !… https://t.co/uG3hGS3099]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 1 wanting wall is AgentOrange and his cult.  Seriously YOU need a mental health exam !  Deflect and destroy is… https://t.co/NY0rY5dVx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anti-Trump movement is calling for the boycott of these 32 brands https://t.co/PIByYMACfC via @BI_RetailNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you can thank AgentOrange and his cult for this !
@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/owym6BI9aC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, This is Why Women Really Marched 

https://t.co/i9j5lCqmg6 via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMAO...#NOTMYPRESIDENT ... imperative you seek treatment for your mental health issues ! 
@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/Ngwct6Uhhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you want us to watch? LMAO YOU can't make us love you.  YOUR mental health is volatile !  SEEK HELP !… https://t.co/0y8DeZGZwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TrumpWhiteHouse senior staff have private RNC email accounts 

AgentOrange will just pardon them No worries he says

https://t.co/D3x7fQloYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacker Group Anonymous Releases Huge Trump Cabinet Announcement (TWEETS) https://t.co/IbmrEyE6tD via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. Just Tried To Block China’s Access To Oil – China’s Reaction Was Terrifying 
https://t.co/D5OJpJthUG via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is already trying to muzzle leakers — but government employees have broad free speech rights https://t.co/lSgEhGbmtQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>