<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer says Trump has respect for the PM of Australia but then repeatedly calls him "Prime Minister Trumball" #Turnball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Gorka guy speaking on Trump's behalf on @NZMorningReport this morning reminds me of Lord HawHaw (look it up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babalonsister very little, I suspect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@army1man1 @FoxNews @KellyannePolls of course it's not, why do you think that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnews @kellyannepolls Kellyanne Conway is a disgrace.  Random stupid violence by teenagers is not equivalent to Trump’s behaviour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump surrogates burst into song... https://t.co/5oYiYKiMi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy has this guy missed the point of the last few months :) https://t.co/SA56i9RcgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS yes still some way to go :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS me too but it appears not. The world is getting weirder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsavage ok sorry :) it's still a remarkable comment though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming @JJPalethorpe what does he mean, race"hustler"? Strange expression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roguishpole really? It's not really that difficult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @Pseudony_Ms no, her comments use same technique. Only she didn't realise apparently. Perhaps she hasn't read  newspapers, ever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Michelle Boag has learned what casual racism is. How nice. Now could she explain where she's been for the last, I don't know, 30 years??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting :) thanks for this. https://t.co/ceFS0xhkeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Boag comes to Peter Leitch’s “rescue” and makes things infinitely worse https://t.co/IpMs5eCm4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind you, Trump's aggressive tweets on North Korea aren't likely to work either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear Hillary Clinton is going to Trump's inauguration. "Peace in our time"? Not sure if appeasement ever works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @realDonaldTrump had a brain, he would denounce Russia too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also why report it @nzherald ? Who cares about Max Key, really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouisMMayo @NZStuffPolitics the question is then, who is Michelle Duff and is she, like, 12??? Or actually Michelle Boag :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouisMMayo @NZStuffPolitics it's Matthew Hooten interviewing himself, that's what it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oo yes, lets have Judith Collins for PM #not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Deborah Russell is running for Labour’s New Lynn candidacy to replace David Cunliffe.  Has anyone else nominated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler @ninetonoon NZ and some US states only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m starting to think the worst thing about the 3 strikes law is giving that fool David Garrett a public platform again @NZMorningReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek no it's fun. Do you not know about fun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluewaterdays yes thats very true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mofette yes! sorry for the delay :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendyWings there IS one now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsunami warnings for both east costs @rnz_news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RT_com this is five year old footage. It's 1.30 am here. You idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babalonsister @grantrobertson1 @NZcivildefence advice is, go if you aren't on high ground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking @BBCNews not that big but lots of 6 or so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoPaddocks lots of big earthquakes, weirdly from Taupo to Christchurch- this isn't normal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[111 is out of action and there is now a tsunami warning #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicheleACourt @noellevivien as if this week could get any worse :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailaharre @toby_etc love your sarcasm Laila. David Cunliffe is to the left of Attila the Hun. Doesn't say much, or says it all :) You pick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliIkram do we have to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia well, agreed, but the vitriol being heaped on Hillary seems as much to do with her gender as anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia really? What would this election be like if Trump's opponent was a man? America still seems very sexist, from this distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajthompson13 @BrettArends nice one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth @SirWB you could pay it in $5 instalments, in 10 cent pieces?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jofromgreylynn @Suzyiam hmm, not sure about that, interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzyiam @PublicGoodANZ even if he does win, there are huge up front costs. Someone must be bankrolling Williams, surely? @NzMorningReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing I don’t get is who is paying Jordan Williams’ legal bills. 4 more weeks suing Colin Craig! Surely it can’t be Williams’ own money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LianneDalziel has the house completely gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AddingtonNZ hey 
race 10 no 1, its pronounced “say lerr” - tell Mark Macnamara - I can’t figure out how to tweet him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7.1 #eqnz near East Cape, Civil Defence advise evacuation, presumably for tsunami?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Foster-Bell in the background to Horr. Judith Collins, what a sycophant! Is he her wing man??or job-hunting? :) https://t.co/Xf3T4b3zQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He’s starting to look more like Donald Duck than Donald Trump  https://t.co/Ijjbe7i97h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzmorningreport @radionz very disappointing - some of us don’t listen to the radio as such, we listen to it on the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @NzMorningReport @radionz somehow you haven’t actually broadcast some of the interviews esp re Natalie Rooney - just no sound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Barnaby_Joyce on ABC just now sounds like he thinks he isn’t going to win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bomb on twitter.   No matter how it happened :) https://t.co/mxqKmUTocL https://t.co/oQL3Iw7VOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnkeypm well that turned out well for you. Not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Is AMC giving out vibrators to go with that?” @hardwick re @wwwbigbaldhead on @AMCTalkingDead nice shout out to gay fans :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PsychScientists @troubledmozza where has this guy been all my life?? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paula Bennett slags the Labour Party in the general debate but she is so sadly stupid.   https://t.co/K4yhIqG1mN She is a glove puppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_UK I like to dress like a Queen Ma'm, when I can :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case it wasn’t clear before Caitlyn Jenner is an idiot https://t.co/xdtlf4XLrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack I wonder if we can find out if he pays for those privileges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me, or is Max Key a little privileged bitch? https://t.co/wO24xQfqNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@singulari_ty yes she doesn’t appear until the second book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@singulari_ty except she doesn’t swear enough compared to the book version.  She’d be much better potty mouthed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubPolitics @NewshubNZ she shows no judgement does she]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @stevenljoyce @NewshubPolitics and if you're not actually doing that, would you please start?? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jonobasile that's funny, coming as it does the day after a report that says the media prefer toadying to the Nats than reporting the news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostarcnz @halloweenmike1 @annetolleymp if only you could choose your parents!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people keep tweeting that something's " breaking the Internet"? I mean I can read their tweets so it seems like it's still working...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HalloweenMike1 @AnneTolleyMP I suspect she'd be right if there were enough jobs for all those who wanted them... This govt's too hands-off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Judith Collins jiggery-pokery (hat tip, Justice Scalia) https://t.co/tyzhNh7IV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking @ShakingStick @MrDuttonPeabody @kylemacd the rest got invited and were, no thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking @ShakingStick @MrDuttonPeabody @kylemacd I was on the Hero Board for the first Big Gay Out, and only Labour would go, then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Ginsberg resigned now as well, that would interesting... #RBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamMarcoNV @marcorubio yes I think they are saying, why would an originalist oppose a President's right to appoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook suggestions for “similar posts” to one about Scalia’s death includes this one :) https://t.co/gKNSkIAER6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth to be fair I posted this within one minute of hearing the news :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shakingstick I think God might have something else in mind for Mr Scalia :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY GOD! Scalia’s dead!  What a huge opportunity for Obama!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly its very helpful if you want to “succeed” to be the son of a Prime Minister in this country these days https://t.co/J2DkCWrBNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judith Collins isn’t being straight with @NzMorningReport when she says she never criticises Judges https://t.co/oKfF4THMs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For gods sake, who cares? (except those whose business it is) https://t.co/uNfo3v46Mf https://t.co/ey0NzR33uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judith Collins is only 5 minutes back &amp; already in breach of good Ministerial practice  https://t.co/vhm9QIpn30 https://t.co/7Asky8izQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judith Collins is only 5 minutes back &amp; already in breach of good Ministerial practice  https://t.co/vhm9QIpn30 https://t.co/NjuTevzv9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehancasinader @onenewsnz Sorry I’m too busy watching the radio :) @CheckpointRNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie @johnjcampbell me too before but its working now :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheckpointRNZ ok it's working now :) the whole site did seem to be having a little traffic meltdown though :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[grumble grumble can’t access RNZ checkpoint page to watch the radio… @CheckpointRNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen haha I said exactly that too :)  I also have fewer regard for people who can't use goodly English…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key acted deliberately yesterday and that makes it worse https://t.co/eLaroUSJA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key accuses @NgatiBird re political stunt. But then has a press conference with Turnball announcing nothing. Who's the stuntman? #xmasisland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just the tip of the iceberg. Notable Wellington restaurants should be next https://t.co/iPZhStTrCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on Sarah Dowie, stop pretending you don't support #8moreweeks paid parental leave https://t.co/MIu3pFnLOR Cross the Floor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @jacindaardern in Invercargill yesterday - lots of selfies! http://t.co/mjlOxmYCFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe, but it's true... 19 degrees in Invercargill at 6am http://t.co/LPyAXCiILP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterDragNZ hasn't anyone told you it's always like this here yet? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy days! Kim Hill favourited my tweet about her :) #fanboy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @nzherald Judith Collins as leader of National would a brilliant gift to Labour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to tweet in code about my unexpectedly diverting weekend but this might be the best I can do]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>