<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@spacetwinks I watched a documentary on skinhead recruitment and it was the physical counterpart - a backwoods shack for angry/lonely kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilCBC They'll take anybody from what I understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_warring @NeilCBC @washingtonpost Bigoted how?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 Quick googling shows the spill was going to happen if left alone and the #epa got stuck holding the bag. Your call is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump the judge is actually enforcing the law. Your EO violates the law and the judge is fixing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How bout the White House?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinawilkie @realDonaldTrump This is crooked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saywhat98288052 @realAlexaParker @Jeannielouise64 I don't care who it is, it's awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeffrius @mr_blonde_1 @crucibroke @bmlzootown @kharyp Look out, man, he might be a navy seal with over 300 confirmed kills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katemcinturff @Carolyn_Bennett @FLAREfashion @JulieSLalonde reach out and get nothing back. But you miss every chance you don't take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katemcinturff @Carolyn_Bennett @FLAREfashion @JulieSLalonde I had a roommate whose bf hit her and put her down. It's not easy to always...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump We do not agree on that. Your toxic yellow river argument falls flat with a googling of the current situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Does not agree with whom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Hey yeah. I wonder where that water came from. A quick Google and... Hey look at that, the mining companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump And I bet you never gave the substance of their complaints any consideration. Just libtards, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Again, no business is worth safe drinking water, clean air, or a stable environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Nothing. And it will only get worse for the ppl #trump is supposedly going to save.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Not you. And that's a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Any mom and pop shop that costs a community safe drinking water is not worth leaving open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump That does not happen and is another bogeyman you've bought into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Remember that when the world doesn't buy your overpriced American products. They will abandon you for cheaper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Avoiding conflicts of interest is precisely required and he hasn't done enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Also env regulations are for health and safety. Families don't die because they safer and healthier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump They affect businesses profits, not destroy them. "Job killing" is a bogeyman you've fallen for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump Also why is his empire anyone else's problem? If he hands it off to a blind trust, it's not destruction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS The Pew report he cites as proof of voter fraud doesn't say what he thinks it says. That's on record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump reconsider how he is messing up relations with allies and making himself an obstacle to world progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump If saving things that have been built up over a long period of time is a priority, then he should ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS No. Two separate crimes, but can be committed in conjunction. Your prez doesn't know the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Is getting the base "2 descend" on a person something someone in any position should do? Encouraging mob mentality are we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS @realDonaldTrump #Trump was prez for only 11 days of it. Will you find out how much was to @BarackObama's credit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Also are you using your profile pic to kiss up to the boss? It even shows the sparse crowds on the white ground covers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @realDonaldTrump You're really okay with him giving control of his companies to his sons?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your spokeswoman, @KellyannePolls, doesn't seem to have her #alternativefacts straight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTodd And if it did, it seems none of them made it out to the 10s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTodd Rock and Roll never had a torch bearer through that decade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Aside from MLK bust mistake, how is the press not fair to him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Google Quebec shooting. Flynn is itching to bomb Muslims. Env regulations protect kids' futures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump You and the @POTUS need to learn the difference bw voter fraud and voter registration fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump I do not and will not trust that he's clean w/o release of tax rcds. Also, he didn't do enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Fine. Don't agree. Also press only has been "unfair" if fair means beneficial to Trump's interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Wrong and wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Exactly like that, only daily and with clear malice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump trade deficits exist at the demand of the American consumer, not as a result of policy. He's lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump saying that the #MuslimBan is going "very nicely", letting his wife trail, etc etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Steve Bannon, silence on #Quebec shooting, giving #michaelflynn a job, war on the environment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump drawing false equivalencies w Obama admin, war on vaccines, lying about voter fraud...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump lying, bullying, fear mongering, abandoning those that rely on the #ACA...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump won't release tax info, clearly refusing to properly divest himself from former bzns ops...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump short term thinking on economy, untrustworthy or incompetent cabinet picks, attacking the press...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Threatening relationships w allies, issuing alternative facts, ham-fisted clumsy EOs...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump The job he has been doing is objectively atrocious. Everybody knows it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Can it be confirmed that #trump said the assailant was Islamic before that was confirmed by French authorities?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_foote @BillRoberts2879 @CBCAlerts @CBCNews @NDP_HQ @stephenharper @JustinTrudeau I forgot about the prorogueing. That too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiranger223 @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Omnipresence does not equal popularity. Especially since he's blatantly bad at his job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Where is "GET SMART" supposed to lead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Get smart to what? That Muslims are dangerous? Is that what you want to say? Is that what you want people to think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump He moves in the opposite way too - his tweets get 1% likes and he thinks he's popular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Where are the parents of the kids with the offending accounts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulakoala1234 @CBCNews the problem is those accounts could belong to kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your clumsiness, ineptitude, bluster and lack of foresight have proven the point of those that voted against you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You celebrated 10k #Walmart jobs being created.  Are those the  "good jobs" that Americans want?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Two weeks in and you're already hanging up on allies. Are you going to do that or worse to enemies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #michaelflynn wants an excuse to bomb #Iran . You'll give him any green light he wants bc you're impressed by his madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I still can't believe you're bad mouthing the star of a show you're listed as producing re his performance ON THE SHOW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nord_Eh @psiphyr @cxcope @AlexanderEmmons @theintercept Business idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psiphyr @Nord_Eh @cxcope @AlexanderEmmons @theintercept I think at this point we should all show up to protests dressed as stairs or germs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews @realDonaldTrump Canadians, your closest allies, will suffer thanks to you and the world will note your total untrustworthiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews @realDonaldTrump You do not understand the definition of the word "fair". You think it means "beneficial to me", which is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IraBlacker @chess3558 @rahulsood @WeAreGodsMan @realDonaldTrump Thieves, drunks, sexual assault, think a few steps up from mall cops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnTory Criticisms are valid. The housing market is practically inaccessible for young Torontonians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Romanticide @MaryECovey @ShadowTodd Stage diving in a wheel chair is nothing I would put past him and even might sell more tickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ObliObla @ShadowTodd Currently having my phone blown up by people who believe it was up to Berk to contain the riot. "Control" has support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petersthoughts @chess3558 @rahulsood Sexual assault, which uni's routinely mishandle, differs from riotting, which they often can't handle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoldableHuman Yeah, but "I told you so" increasingly seems like all we can hope for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaxterDerrick I agree that crimes were committed. But at the scale the riots were at, it is beyond the scope of the University cops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Axew22 @chess3558 @rahulsood A huge distinction exists bw the capabilities of a campus police dept and city police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adam_Puzio @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump he's one sided, unproven, and suspicious. And "might be decent" isn't a great starting point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Axew22 @chess3558 @rahulsood Rape and a riot require two different responses from campus police. One they can handle, one they cannot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHMashburn @LaughsWithKas @RamajEroc @realDonaldTrump Not riot police. Campus police deal with thieves, drunks, and sexual assaults.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chess3558 What else should they have then? Bomb squads? K9 units? Helicopters? Campus cops are there for for thieves, drunks, and gropers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeAreGodsMan @longislanddon @chess3558 @rahulsood @realDonaldTrump #trump's talking about defunding #Berkeley, not #California.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chess3558 @BretzBlitz Who? Everybody who was there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randalusa @chess3558 @rahulsood @WeAreGodsMan Flatly untrue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longislanddon @chess3558 @rahulsood @WeAreGodsMan @realDonaldTrump But a university shouldn't be expected to have a riot squad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeAreGodsMan @chess3558 @rahulsood @realDonaldTrump That flatly does not follow from his tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chess3558 @rahulsood Have you ever seen campus police? They're not equipped to deal with riots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 150B is not enough to save a nation of 77.5M on its "last legs". You don't understand what you're talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Clumsy, stupid, inept, foresight-less, dangerous, inflammatory diplomacy. You have no idea what you're doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump Doubtful. #trump hired him bc of his connections and deep voice which Trump saw as charisma. Rex ain't ready.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaughsWithKas @RamajEroc @realDonaldTrump A university is not a law enforcement organization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chess3558 @rahulsood @WeAreGodsMan @realDonaldTrump A university is not a law enforcement agency. Expulsions, sure. But not arrests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kouban @itstherapcritic @evandahm Granted, for more than those cynical reasons. Reference "boat mcboatface". But you're still right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archpundit @kombiz @tufkaa #michaelflynn sounds like the kind of guy that is itching to bomb someone and would use the word "crusade".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Nice of them to deal in specifics. #michaelflynn is a paranoid delusional hateful man itching to bomb somebody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think you need to understand what the definition of #fair is. "Fair" does not mean "nice" or "beneficial to me".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CdnPress A strong people. #canada is better for having them here. All the best to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Many of those he follows are his own family or properties. That's quite the bubble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to note that @realDonaldTrump doesn't follow more than 50 people bw that acct and @potus. Shouldn't he listen to more people?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>