<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@timleng It's true, she's a buxom wench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adebradley @JamieBGall It's the only one I've seen. It was scary ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smalltown2k The situation has been remedied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anandamide Was it not porn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBGall Easter eggs have loads of free space. Keep shovellin']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adebradley This is a compelling argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much longer until it's socially acceptable to be in my PJs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tfor_Trouble It is however an essential ingredient of that Chinese dish I can't remember the name of that is served in lettuce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From pizza to mining tweet metadata for insights. https://t.co/oDnjo1Kvtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My watchdog has been violated apparently: https://t.co/6lQxSeWDSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pierskarsenbarg ðŸ¤” maybe subconsciously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathonMarx I'm so clever and totally planned that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apophthegmist It's ok, I'll get a second wind later ðŸ–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I *may* have over-ordered on pizza to hit the minimum delivery value...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else get paranoid about getting locked out when they're home alone and carry their keys around in their pockets while inside?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philford Also you: I'm not waiting for the night tube. I'll get a taxi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one on the right in Pointless right now might as well not be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyheron Off to Belize?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeparry The pub I worked in as a student did "pig racing" and it was these: https://t.co/weEJkjzDAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeparry Is it real pigs or toy pigs though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's enough Alexa-ing for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apophthegmist Same. In my head "anonymous" people have the same voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apophthegmist Dots between letters FTW. Or F.T.W. as Alexa needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronHEllis @JamieBGall @mattyheron @BlackburnJA I think that calls for a sherry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status: trying to get Alexa to say "DLR" properly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBGall I thought bottom left one was something else at first glance...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully the USB-C to mini-DisplayPort adapter I just bought will restore me back to a 4 display coding dojo since I got my new laptop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TayloredBites @mjc_photography Always so happy before an iced ring?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_mighty I doubt it affects you, but beware they won't work in VS2015 once you do. I'm holding off merging my migrations until 2017 RTM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beepea Haha. "Alexa, gimme my flash briefing fam"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattTheOtter This is the nerdiest sentence I've seen today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good. My internet is down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travelling_wolf No, I've already been up and gone out and been to the shops and e'rythin'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am now going to spend the rest of my day off working on my Alexa skill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SEPhysics @PrideinSTEM Thanks. All signed up now. ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danjelv 1 please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight I am nowhere near entrepreneurial enough for such larks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Through my DNS provider. $8 each.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mutablejoe We are the heroes now. *Opens GitHub issue*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Oh I see. No, I just bought two vanity domain names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Is it wrong I don't know what that is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrideinSTEM @SEPhysics I can't submit the Google Form as it has the data types for job title and employer as email address.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight I bought a uk one yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gah, when will I stop getting thing and think mixed up? I'm 0x20 this year FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL .now is a TLD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL Twitter things https://t.co/ppCUXJlUkv is a URL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_mighty See also why https://t.co/ppCUXJlUkv makes me sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adebradley I've not been to the Soho one but Jackson and Rye is nice. Nordic bakery is nice if coffee and bakery goods suits you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all gone downhill now. Also I think it's actually Heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackFinch My dad does tbh. And Ricky Martin, Celine, Anastasia, Cher... ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveyBlahBlah I might've known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@an0key How very dare you. I'm not from Manchester.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackFinch Your dad likes Belinda Carlyle and the Backstreet Boys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apophthegmist I think listening to Belinda Carlyle fits more into another grouping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cafe plays Magic FM and right now the tunes are ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the__littleman So how long have you been on the register now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philford The sass, not the situation bbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philford Oh, this did make me laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Ruline Steininger haunts the fuck out of the great Wotsit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willhowells Thank you for bringing it my attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willhowells Its fine. I'll just stand at the back, get drunk, and send sing-y SnapChats, so basically I'll be you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBGall @mattyheron And who gave you the idea Matthew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That last RT. Pow, right in the feels. ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reader, I caved. I've now got 8 months to come to terms with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a day off 2017, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnastasiaDuck @JamieBGall Invisible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBGall That's less me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I'm in denial though as really I'm Niles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part-channeling my inner Frasier today so I'm going out to get scrambled eggs. No tossed salad though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaysteruk Not far though. You could go to Blackpool ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has little firemans' boots ðŸ˜ https://t.co/6228XY4mDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted to go to one of the NFG 20th anniversary shows, but at the same time that means admitting I'm now one of those older guys at shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flint_writes I stand corrected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adebradley I had great fun reading this earlier on the BBC News website. The last quote line is the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beepea It didn't do it again, but usually just gets confused. I said "The husband is eating flies" (long story).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Box office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Reminds me of a sign I saw in Vegas... https://t.co/QF7SAHtdYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting bug reports over iMessage now which is novel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJDodders Fuck those look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy sat next to me on the tube is myoclonic jerking all over the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One idle office conversation and then suddenly I own another two domain names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBGall Stop gossiping then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willhowells *Throws Faridge down reactor shaft*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Auriga__ These people are so fucking stupid it defies belief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philford Option 4: itchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And where the fuck did February come from all of a sudden?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveyBlahBlah Haha, gutted bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveyBlahBlah That's far less exciting that I imagined. And she's totally in the wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Craver Is Commify() something to do "1,000"-type formatting of numbers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a learning excercise, today I set up a CDN for my website. Such glamour. Much nerd. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onawintersnight Was it cold?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secretfox23 I bet your breath is a treat rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyheron That's quite a niche trigger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love it when a computer senses being given a stern look and then starts doing what you want it to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PadrinoMatt Is she still your friend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackFinch @illucifer True definitely have something extensible, but me being me I'd go all in from the start...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackFinch @illucifer And is the hard drive an SSD? If not ðŸš®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackFinch @illucifer I'd have more than 8GB personally. 8GB is nowhere near "top-end" the spec seems to be trying to tout itself as.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willhowells I like that one also ðŸ’…ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_liam_hall This is also me with long beard. Also the fact it's four different colours.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>