<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course built environment both space in which creative people act but also a space to which they react. Cities r… https://t.co/omMTjNNbb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to generate a conversation. Bigger, dense cities create contradictions of greater connectivity&amp; alienation, w… https://t.co/OUVX58hwnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, here miners push 'clean coal'.. a disaster that would push up power bills: analysts… https://t.co/JDg7IMbpoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thmcmahon Mm. A woman I mention- lacking sleep is not long out of uni. Dreaming of a city for all ages, more non-retail spaces for 'play']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello @thmcmahon.Likewise, think there r positives but keen to see the conversation thickened, not developer-led &amp; about quality of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for RT and to amazing @richardsennett for the inspiration. https://t.co/Z8XjvTwtYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed. Ballard’s dystopian novel reveals a vertical world, hard wired to alienate and divide. A little bit of Frit… https://t.co/Aw6yqyAg9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahvmac All cool. I was sad to see end of SundayNights. Wrote about it. Need rigorous radio on religion&amp;faith.Good luck with the new gig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rightfuture @matt_nesham They'll be a buzz about that city living but with intangible costs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The downside to high-density living in Canberra https://t.co/sHBAQjMHd9 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does seem sad and pathetic though that this is what the PM is asking of the U.S. when that country has enough on… https://t.co/ktpZqEgQyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't do diplomacy through Twitter. Besides @POTUS was schooled in real estate.. https://t.co/uZ30XZWeLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry encourages wonder. Why it matters that Trump has No Inaugural Poet https://t.co/fNsQlgoBAO via @BrowBeat    FYI @grhutchens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EleniePoulos Belated thanks. Enjoy life after Uniting gig. What's the next challenge? Lord knows the world has them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ban appears to take effect tomorrow Feb 1. Mobiles are an essential lifeline for detainees! Tell… https://t.co/KafLkpgv2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackGJessen @sarahkendzior Trying not to be paralyzed by fear. Fear is the ultimate enemy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely chilling and comprehensive horror forecasting. "Checks and balances is a metaphor, not a mechanism". https://t.co/o2gf5AGIrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for this@JaneCaro. I would stress the 2nd info revolution is both tool for emancipation&amp;control. @POTUS uses it with chilling effect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My university's VC Brian Schmidt @cosmicpinot of ANU shares "alarm and deep concern" about @POTUS Exec Order https://t.co/mdRvfqW3la @BIAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's ban not only mean-spirited, it shrinks #innovation&amp; science. Yet innovation-loving PM is silent, gutless https://t.co/BpSnS5caiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our PM is showing an absolute lack of spine. History will not be kind. https://t.co/20HIomIiuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worse, in emulating the U.S. non-stop testing risks 'sucking the blood out of education' @skrashen… https://t.co/SEGIxZ9lxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 2 keep positive about human rights this week https://t.co/a62mu0nusg @amnestyOz Establish boundaries, celebrate wins,reconnect locally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahvmac @NightlifeABC Peter Martin  please note, is the Economics EDITOR of The Age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aggressive Trump campaign is being translated in office. But there r breaks, one hopes, with Congress &amp; courts, to… https://t.co/fOs4RpMTkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeb Bush: Melania Should Confiscate Trump’s Phone https://t.co/tLK91XvLPx via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brain-drain &amp; purge truly underway. Expect more of a sweep before March. Guthrie's Murdoch lackeys unlikely to… https://t.co/4rGb5ZdcrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ending this Jan26 with Stan Grant's Quarterly Essay, Aboriginal econ migrants who struck out in a country that rejected them #changethedate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the gift of time in retirement @AlexSloan. Been meaning to say hello and see what the journey ahead holds. https://t.co/7qZblYq3ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PEN America's @Andrew_Solomon told @LNLonRN he saw a bookshop sign- "Post apocalyptic fantasy has now been refiled… https://t.co/G6CFpvSqxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too! We know enough to change the date and talk about this differently, support @SatPaper push.… https://t.co/9hJ5MC2Ib1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notable that the legal case is being waged by a card-carrying Republican. Terrific interview by Stan Grant. https://t.co/xP1kqn6PuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now published. Nat. Audit Office report critical of Immigration Dept's management of offshore camp contracts https://t.co/2m94dThvL8 #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aziz is not just funny but brilliant. Pleads with Trump to calm 'lower case K.K.K' down. https://t.co/qjkRqXVoUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All talk &amp; no music makes Aunty a dull broadcaster. Music shows lost but effort 2 engage #ABC Head of Radio continue https://t.co/5WtFHntorN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important @Oxfam report shows worsening global inequality. Just eight men own same wealth as poorest half of world https://t.co/jNDfVBQItu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed you may ask @HeathJAston. The whole thing is Incredibly petty. #posttruth https://t.co/FtXtpxnR6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative governments by their very nature do less than progressive ones - but this is getting embarrassing https://t.co/6XZWumqSZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieLeask always a tension between creativity and control ;) When you back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I smiled throughout it. Suggests we've come a long way. #diversity is our strength https://t.co/5KY7rXBbFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January is a great time to do a chore audit at home... for greater equality and less resentment. https://t.co/v6HwskHDV5 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens I hear you (the drive to surf #awesome). But when people have a safety net in place, they take more risks #PeltzmanEffect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful, essential speech from a distinguished artist who takes aim at the President elect and his "instinct to hu… https://t.co/HzeZ2pxAMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vital discussion @KSeibertAu As big a problem is sound consultative-based policy 2 often ignored.. growing dissolut… https://t.co/qJsQTsjnJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. "In over-Googled world, it's nice to be surprised by what lies over that ridge." Me thinks being online a lot… https://t.co/UjrA6VzpJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political candidates annointed by God? With Trump about to take office, timely piece on perils of apostolic power https://t.co/Vf9ivjLiKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can cultures forget the benefits of not working all the time? ‘Right to Disconnect’ takes effect in France https://t.co/FPtMLOvJEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoot for justice. Vigil now in Braddon outside Dept of Immigration, #Canberra. 14 men dead in Aust detention camps.… https://t.co/5LN1qnb0s8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today mourning &amp; honouring the life of #Faysal by pressing the government to #Bring Them Here #CloseTheCamps 
Prote… https://t.co/VKQEe7g20c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello @grhutchens @surfline. A lesson there about modern comforts making us less alert?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you John Berger for the profound way you got us to think about art, the language of images https://t.co/MgjRQQZWZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yes. Especially important for our young people who are plagued by angst. Keep a gratitude journal to put things… https://t.co/GS8xymJKuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopeful and happy new year all. Enjoy the simple pleasures of the sun and surf that equalise and energise https://t.co/gXcn0Z8Ogv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a last minute Christmas present? How about the gift of your undivided attention https://t.co/LdxDX86NPS #children #technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that would be a miracle https://t.co/LdxDX86NPS https://t.co/KsGjn4Q2vc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan 26 ignores the millennia of knowledge &amp; traditions of our continent. We need to mature as a nation… https://t.co/aLjMqJJqzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about authors but readers  of which there are more. And needn't be either/or :) @1petermartin https://t.co/GpPQ1ubu4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC board demands director of radio explain Radio National cuts https://t.co/UbTyz6fd7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and he gets in his school report a D for disappointment https://t.co/xyG84UG8TW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like someone else we know about. If only it was members of Republican Party deciding to not work with their… https://t.co/WuInKWoEd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the ABC can look and sound like their commercial rivals? https://t.co/YaF0dH090T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newstart is anything but a new start, at around $262 a week. Politicians staying in Canberra get $271 per night! https://t.co/EQBnFJiuAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, and they are generalists https://t.co/rHeVX6NZCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific contribution #KasyChambers. ABC management yet to articulate the findings, if any, of a review for anti-ch… https://t.co/gRw7tStxCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education efficiency should start with Grattan compromise https://t.co/wJoCJgHsbW via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Labor was serious about inequality then it would have the guts to want &amp; plan universal public system, cut priva… https://t.co/fPu4PAhpBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes indeed @SteveWorner. Because all scripture and sacred text invites reflection on power and politics, and church… https://t.co/ElfVfLvPTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so much meagre rations but, even with budget cuts, a strange will from managers to weaken the broadcasters's ve… https://t.co/dmHneJaIfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alarming, yes @bairdjulia https://t.co/cMxHgOUsIf Demise of experts also at ABC with more perspectives v knowledge #catalyst #sundaynights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An especially great idea in the festive season and to counter the local and global forces of alienation and distrus… https://t.co/g4OoXnU4H5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get the absurd place he is coming from:  Born a Crime,’ Trevor Noah’s Raw Account of Life Under Apartheid https://t.co/Kvtw2lrc3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last few days to catch vast and solid #soagradshow16 @ANUschoolofArt Some favourites... https://t.co/nrY0s6JN8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a complex &amp; perplexing world we need specialists &amp; sophistication at #ABC, not less https://t.co/US2UfxFJny @mattpulford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The death of specialisation at our #ABC. Why I'm grumpy about the axeing of #SundayNights https://t.co/avvZd377tJ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want my vote, revamp the ABC board: senator's latest ABCC bargaining chip revealed https://t.co/IjJv9jk14Q via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grattan on Friday: The government is compromising Malcolm Turnbull's commitment to inclusion https://t.co/Y3AemiLhUD via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary evidence from resilient leader naming a "religious protection racket" in #Newcastle @abc730… https://t.co/BMBE24OcF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC staff move no confidence motion against management over radio cuts, loss of specialists 
https://t.co/cdDangv7nF via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughtful art show on seasons of birth (profundity, delight &amp; pain) now on at AustCentreforChristianity&amp;Culture,… https://t.co/N4oUOOuBmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had hopes @TurnbullMalcolm. But plenty disappointments already from baseless attacks against renewables 2 pathetic jousts with #Triggs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former #Newcastle Bishop Farran says #Anglican Church of Aust has "very poor record of doing things together nationally" #CARoyalComm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a 'village' to prevent inst abuse of children &amp; young people. My oped today https://t.co/nOu9wcWihv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't agree more. https://t.co/Fe1Pwdf4Oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to 'meet' you @mathiaswasik Good luck with the team, important movement post election @allout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Offers to Restore British Rule Over United States https://t.co/es7QNoL3s2 via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Moore’s post-election plan goes viral | The New Daily https://t.co/hlPbCtogIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alittlewave Easier 2 tear down. There's no plan, just vague rhetorical calls. Media must be brave in face of Trump's bullying  #USElection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such bad news for tackling #inequality in the U.S. Obama legacy will be wiped out. #Obamacare #Electionnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump terminated by The Terminator as the Republican Party moves into deep, deep crisis. https://t.co/RJbYzEBqUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free tablets for students: an ACT election sweetener without nourishment or evidence. My oped today. https://t.co/8klOAL1UxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solidarity matters.. at today's Nauru Files Reading Vigil at Immigration Dept. Braddon Canberra #closethecamps https://t.co/XQu47ipgKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intriguing and lovely work by @ANUSchoolofArt graduate Sally O'Callaghan now on @ccas_canberra https://t.co/9TVlqiwHc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant Alan Atkinson https://t.co/Owstgtigue. Aust's refugee policy traumatises conscience &amp; int aid is a measure of national conscience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucieCutting @nettybruce @canberratimes Oh dear. Low # is so definitional.  How about we stress the quality our connections!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor body image is a public health issue. Families &amp; schools have sig role https://t.co/9ba71U0zYw #LoveYourBody @LucieCutting @nettybruce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We wish? G20 ends abruptly as Obama loses his cool with Putin https://t.co/SuUEFjUGYT … via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unixbigot @nytimes @1petermartin Mm. Yeh, me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you speak Australian? Take the @nytimes quiz. https://t.co/BBJkZKqLFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't feel too sorry for our angry white men https://t.co/PqzYIznSk1 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree, a manipulative show. It pushes romance over meaning &amp; perpetual female types https://t.co/9harV58e5B https://t.co/OtQabkfeZb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>