<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love ❤️ making coffee in the waste disposal!!!! #sigh #flomoments https://t.co/rVT4SyxPds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging. With Kels. At @quincemartini @ Floriditas - Cafè &amp; Restaurant https://t.co/W7oTsQby4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yummo sister! x https://t.co/zsyUMifm8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realise she has no snacks after school and too sick to go back to supermarket… https://t.co/6DJR9wBv3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, I think we've been there for awhile https://t.co/YvmYoFybtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha I was thinking you looked fab tonight! Amazing what actually happens behind the scenes lol x https://t.co/Gku0KCJ4KC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRock  - my special needs nephew sending you a challenge xxx https://t.co/6YtXy9n4dY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worthy candidate to follow #bopregionalcouncil elections https://t.co/v5dchh1kc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday morning with my big boy tythun - the Wellington food and beverage network really do look… https://t.co/kDfj4pJ4aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing for Nana #winners @ Jerry Collins Stadium https://t.co/Zq4ozvEv9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MFATinAuckland So so so so proud of this programme! Good to see it has continued and has strengthened! #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love her! https://t.co/TYmYNkNa6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a good teacher transforms into a great teacher! A handwritten, posted postcard that impacts… https://t.co/53YjFgRD8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alfagatto  kahlua - ok whatever https://t.co/pEIRhzsFhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your desk starts to look like you're at home! #worklifebalance https://t.co/GlHXhU741E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a big ask to tell me to walk between the cones! It's me -… https://t.co/oKyjjBuEaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a big ask to tell me to walk between the cones! It's me - Florence. I have a stride that… https://t.co/gVUMUhI9CA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a #michael #kors day today! #fashionflo #inspiring… https://t.co/ox71dkIyXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that my kids are well aware of catfish online creeps!… https://t.co/AsfiOHbXUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner at Tyson's on a Friday night. #bigarms @ Mojo Featherston https://t.co/VsjkLHibtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my recommendation - GO HERE!!!! :) xxx @ Petone Beach - The… https://t.co/vNOMqjaG8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thorndon in autumn with Summer - in the rain. x https://t.co/tmYuogBJyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autum in Thorndon. Twilight swimming party with #Summerlicious xxx @ Thorndon Pool https://t.co/uoIjLwl7U1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Frank's" on The Terrace. Is super cool!!! So proud of him #arise @ Wellington, New Zealand https://t.co/ZJhB9XKj68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ thanks - I feel sorry for those who have been waiting over 72 hours then - paid services not being accessible tsk tsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ hello from the outside Vodafone - what's happening to my DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ cool do you want to follow me so that I can DM you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ @lontalius so your phones won't get answered and we've been on "under repair" since yesterday arvo. What's happening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like the islands with all the trimmings #loveorion @ Orion Springfield Central https://t.co/FGJykf1s2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never take for granted #sisters -
My celebrity squad xxxx @ Sirromet Winery - Lifestyle Wine https://t.co/4r1pyyM3Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific fofo must work!  https://t.co/DHzXP8Ot4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing randomly in the presence of heavy weight royalty! #dior #prada #fashionflo #karenwalker https://t.co/lwQmeB45Nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Player of the Day #netballantics #proudmama xxx https://t.co/5CUQonWvnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netball antics https://t.co/mEqOlYC2lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at our fancy-pants silk scarfs!!! Thank you for the lovely gifts, Kelly!!! Always believed that… https://t.co/nvoXz2iUMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Beau seriously had me at 'Roimata' Fab result!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fashionflo Changing guard at Kirkcaldie &amp; Stains xxx https://t.co/Hc6lPRtuW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@CaseyBreves: 15 seconds of "I'm Not The Only One" from last night :) https://t.co/axdT5H62uh” Love this talent!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filled with goodness! #pacificstars #dreambig #spp @mpiapacificstar http://t.co/hu6d6A716L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these amazing #pacificstars who gave us a drum tribute over the weekend! Talent!… https://t.co/8wl7VnaFit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juicey set of coconuts at Pasifika Festival! @ Pasifika Festival - Hayman Park https://t.co/w40sCeb7g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brunch. Bronson. Backbencher. https://t.co/ECwIZ4xqRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WC Hoorah! Shot Coll. #mcevedy http://t.co/5kFd3lAxCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stoked with my purchases this weekend. Origins from France - Medx region and Montussan. Magazine… http://t.co/174IcRu4J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a 'Salon-day' today ;) #Summerlicious xxx http://t.co/VuP8Vtuaf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonovanWearing Thanks for being amazing! Pushing me until I landed somewhere awesome! Gutted. Sad. Loves. xxx #bestboss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir HNY gorg gal! ;) beaut pix! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbseymour crack up on 7 Days! Good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched the 2nd debate with my 70 yr old mum who cleaned the Beehive for years! "A dirty office means dirty politics!l" Great insight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hdpaNEWS that was a great piece tonight on McKenzie, Pauley and McIsaac! Even the kiddies wanted me to say so. Nice! :) x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's inspiration - 'Say Something' cover. Powerful rendition by my friend's son - Hans Peder! WATCH! https://t.co/8OhsZb62pL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handbag. Shoes. Friday. Choice is everything! http://t.co/Rdgh63yRPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JussyMurray purrrrrrfect! Yip, keen! And thanks for retweeting my tweet - poetry right there! LOL.x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JussyMurray did you see Ali's post on Matariki thingy. YOU need to do! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matuashane you're a great tulafale Mr Jones! Go well and, ummmm, I do hope you had a whiskey shot for me too ;) x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JussyMurray maybe within the month. lighten the mood during election build up. actually that should be our theme! ha! working on dates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JussyMurray hey sweets - live performance at my place in front of a small group - you in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julianwilcox it's your 'fav press sec'! Ha. Hope all well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tofiga do you like how I 'favorite'd the tweet before actually opening up the clip :) - I'm clever like that LOL - opening it now!!! xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day of second school term. Daughter has attitude. Mothers Day looming. Kids better make some good decisions this week! Sigh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an important story - it needed to be protected in a glass case awww ;) Love a good sibling story @slevave xxx http://t.co/DErynWBNNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slevave shot babe! We had absolutely no doubt!!! Proud much. Alofas xxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Sanita Levave, made Black Ferns! She's #gigatownporirua! Just saying. Oh Longi did gr8 job on my hair! He's #gigatownporirua too. Snap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At my fav famous #gigatownporirua breed hairdresser with Beyoncé! So famous Hurricanes &amp; ABs love him! Who? http://t.co/3SloQtkQsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickoleggett totes my #gigatownporirua friend!!!! xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwilad007 @GigagigaPorirua @nickoleggett eek didn't know can do that in non-#gigatownporirua twt! Ice-sk8ing is best in #gigatownporirua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people think this is fun! 2 secs on and HATE IT! Summerlicious did well though! #dumbice http://t.co/dbGl8GBzQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MutchJessica must be so moving to be there. xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little girl sleepovers are soooo overrated! #exhausted http://t.co/hwE7tEp4Sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, I would absolutely argue that there is nothing wrong with my office desk 'utensils'. These… http://t.co/0ext9Kw60h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing the kids soooooo much! xxx @ Felix Cafe http://t.co/IPqIbBqDWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North. Coffee. And all important mirror! #rugbymad http://t.co/sfR13wl00U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry kids we can't Skype tonight - we are soooo tired @ Corporate Club-Westpac stadium http://t.co/eMEE959Ssl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye parentals! We are out of here! Happy holidays! xxx http://t.co/72qO2d8b2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Joy Hill in the House today. She is truly amazing! Soul. Swag. Style. #arisechurch http://t.co/b3gRikHpcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chillin at Scopa - love Wellington #passionateconference2013 http://t.co/PLvs5j5fS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can roll your eyes all you want - "Fix your face!" Lady Joy Hill - love her attitude, speaks my language! #passionateconference2013]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pass the parcel - but not the chocolate biscuits! #passionateconference2013 http://t.co/Dp619lXOXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How crazy - this stranger sitting next to me says my Dad had dinner with her and hubby nearly 38 yrs… http://t.co/pMPDx6jMFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary when a complete stranger next to you says "oh are you Florence from Porirua? Malama's daughter?"… http://t.co/R4721VK7J1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at it tonight! Loving on Stan Walker - "Everyone is significant - if you are available, God will… http://t.co/WVUwHD0TiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church with Stan Walker - "...He wants to give You everything!...Who you are is good enough!" Love it! http://t.co/Hx8AAVoELN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first flight to Auckland this morning - with us below! Good brisk morning for a paddle - why not!n… http://t.co/GWlbsWKZub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tehilah's birthday party - Aunty Fay needs to event manage Summer's party too! Great Easter birthday fun! x http://t.co/QInnZnsYi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Girl. Hope Anchor. Stan Walker. Soooo much happening at Arise in April! http://t.co/Fblr9HGchY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbiewilliams gutted! On my flight today x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London through the eyes of Florence. That thing behind us is famous! Its an arc. Ark. Here is my gorgeous… http://t.co/GKyvBK8UjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So great to have coffee with awesome old friend Neil and family in central London. Thanks Neil and Sandra… http://t.co/nVN5iUsf0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@TheCLASSYKiddo: Keiran I'm the press sec Hun. Thirza's a secondee and resigned from MPIA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow - news to me! “@TheCLASSYKiddo: P.I Affairs Press Sec from Hekia Parata's office resigns.@TovaOBrien @patrickgowernz @MutchJessica”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pix from my office this morn. Kid in yellow Wellington Coll jacket gathering his friends - my son… http://t.co/yJKfTimQwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo http://t.co/MXhVHPEoAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My awesome Aunty Yvonne let me swim in their pool for the afternoon. Best date day ever! http://t.co/ITAuRpIaNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ear pierced and new bracelets. Happy date day for me! @ Waikanae http://t.co/xru4UPyDIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yummo! I ate this! Summer xxx @ The Long Orange http://t.co/II7p6B0ick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you think I ate? What do you think mummy ate? Summer xxx @ The Long Orange http://t.co/gTWuZCeYR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Date day with mum starts with missing our first event at 9am, sitting at local cafe tuning mum out while… http://t.co/PCWYHbfS3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing Todd xxx  Loving Carol xxxx http://t.co/P8HkoexECK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBs baby! Welcome back BBs! xxx #backbencher http://t.co/uxKzFEQxZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niecey Georgia in Wellies yay! xxx http://t.co/yaW1lxrKMs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>