<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation new GAD tables for capped drawdown will apply from 1 July - not 6 April as previously suggested https://t.co/j4eSLi3uVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How and when should property play a part in retirement planning? https://t.co/yaUA78BjJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK I think you need an 'all of the above' button!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to see trainspotting 2. Hoping it lives up to the hype #movienight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions @RayVay I think some providers believed it was a short time to make system changes, as well giving customers notice of change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe HMRC is going to defer the implementation of the new GAD tables, possibly to July (was going to be 6 Apri… https://t.co/t1azHEMYjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£6,000 each - how the new pension freedoms resulted in a cash bonanza https://t.co/NXwnw58Xvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCJLandale was my MP when I was young. Wrote to him when I was at school &amp; he took the time to send a very informative handwritten reply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nic Cicutti: FCA needs to admit its PI mistakes - Money Marketing https://t.co/54NhbV2jJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PensionsMonkey @Bikingkeebs looks like you should finish that off tonight. Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PensionsMonkey @Bikingkeebs you only like that strange Japanese stuff so you could send it to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMRC has published new pension freedom stats which show £9.2bn has been flexibly accessed. Some thoughts here &gt; https://t.co/JGszsuTe3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HigherEdActuary @jonstapleton case by case. Usually quote done similar bens (maybe not multi escalation rates). May look at re-shaping too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRalfe1 @jonstapleton if we take health etc into account then no sometimes higher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedCircleFP @SmartSacks @jonstapleton mine were 33x and 30x. Seriously considered moving one of them. If nearer retirement would have done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRalfe1 @jonstapleton good question. Some multiples seem v high &amp; not sure fair on all mbrs. But for individual we may be able to help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedCircleFP @SmartSacks @jonstapleton I did one of mine a few months ago (not HSBC) and it had increased 70% in 15 mths]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonstapleton yes exactly. Annuity personalised to their circs (health, death bens etc) often matching starting FS income. Plus money in IDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonstapleton yep seen a few over the last few months above 40x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachellacey77 Hi Rachel, obviously I'm not an IFA but happy to chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PensionsMonkey Is this just a Friday afternoon statement or do you foresee another wave about to come crashing down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of annuities: beginning or end? https://t.co/thUMWviUFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OAPs are using their homes to top up retirement spending https://t.co/n0yIRtzg6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SippySlicker I think more will move to FAD but I guess that was probably inevitable anyway. But I share your cynicism given the timing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revised GAD tables for those still in capped drawdown &gt; https://t.co/lrbUJLI5uj these extend below 2% yield for the first time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another excellent @ILCUK event (as always) at House of Lords today discussing #dbdeficits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complex train track building for a Friday eve. Not sure my brain is up to it, luckily the 4 yr old is doing fine https://t.co/kGz8TkB4GK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJBellMike @Triciaaphillips probably enough to be going on with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about when to retire and how to survive on a pension https://t.co/iJtnVqBpaF @triciaaphillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nucleus calls for cut to Lifetime Isa exit charge - Money Marketing https://t.co/aaulbE26TC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a gentle day yesterday, back to work today with the joy of an easyJet flight to Bristol. Then I need to present. What do I do again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @edtheatres to see the panto with @RayVay on the last day of our holiday #ohyesweare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedCircleFP @richardosman I think in the semi-finals I'm voting for the least worst option. A bit like British politics really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely bracing walk around Arthur's seat #beautifulEdinburgh https://t.co/4DCRO0IDRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayVay @ProfPensions may not seek advice but many will need advice should they wish to transfer as value above £30k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidTrenner11 I think HMRC will just continue to tighten the rules around overseas step-by-step]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New HMRC newsletter today confirming position on scams, MPAA, lifetime allowance and overseas pensions &gt; https://t.co/gcEjpnGBn0 #pensions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official start of #Christmas with santa steam train ride https://t.co/GVozYioZoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBishopUK @stevewebb1 @Moneybox difficult to summarise in a tweet, but my thoughts outlined here &gt; https://t.co/uty6k7lH76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed discussing final salary transfers with @stevewebb1 on @Moneybox . Many better staying put, but transfer can be good outcome for some]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevewebb1 @Moneybox @RoyalLondon thanks Steve, good report. FS transfers shouldn't be a taboo. Decision down to individual circumstances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJBellMike @stevewebb1 although that is also possible in a hybrid. The annuity offers the certainty with the drawdown giving flexibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK's pension 'apartheid' is the worst in the developed world, OECD says https://t.co/NXtESBxoFQ via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAF_IFA stakeholder introduced in 2001. And with the exit penalty and initial units don't believe it's a stakeholder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAF_IFA it mentions initial units too, so doesn't sound like a stakeholder plan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pension Freedoms could leave retirees with nothing https://t.co/YUzyHHHnzX via @moneyaol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annuities should play a key role in retirement https://t.co/2RvQgl6i3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investors ready for the festive stock market ‘Santa rally’ https://t.co/4fQfuVXHDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent a while last night telling my parents - in their 80s - that phone message from 'HMRC' saying they were due tax wasn't real #Scams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universal withdrawal rates: Why one size doesn’t fit all https://t.co/qEQ2Yvpa5L via @Retire_Planner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just confirms Darren's work was a key driver in getting this done https://t.co/qdYGtTWwqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REVEALED: More than 15 million workers now automatically enrolled into a pension scheme https://t.co/UbutMBw94H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annuity rates on the rise, up 10 per cent over three months https://t.co/KnD8sG8CkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRalfe1 @JosephineCumbo @MerrynSW @HigherEdActuary seeing a fair number around 40x mark at the moment John. And 30-35x seems 'normal']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo and doesn't take into account any 'internal only' annuities as no visibility of the rates in these cases, so could be more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huzzah! Some good news on annuities... https://t.co/26VXhGisNd via @CityAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last few events in our uk tour in the cold north *shivers*. Carlisle yesterday, Newcastle today and Bolton tomorrow #adviserevents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five-minute guide to planning for future changes https://t.co/OYAiBeZwYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annuity providers told to offer customers rival deals https://t.co/CIlvejUB5u via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Insurers must display rival pension annuities https://t.co/Xlf8XoYUkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions @JosephineCumbo I don't think so. I agree the pooling changes but there are still benefits above self-insuring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK @PensionsMonkey @JosephineCumbo our view is around 60% of people qualify for some enhancement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions @JosephineCumbo a whole range from high blood pressure thru diabetes to serious, eg cancer. But more income than standard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo it's a step in the right direction. But won't by itself suddenly mean all annuity buyers get good outcomes. Much more to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasselby @JosephineCumbo or force all into the external market. Can still buy from holding provider but need to get other options 1st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo major to me. 60% qualify for enhanced. Many may think small benefit to shopping around when could get much more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo although important to note this is only standard rates, won't flag health &amp; lifestyle rates where many can lose out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCA annuity comparator doesn't consider problem of those qualifying for enhanced annuity who buy standard. Significant hole in the proposal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very impressive natural history museum for the #FAawards #dinosaurs https://t.co/4Pf1Y8JL5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As confirmation of MPAA reducing to £4K won't happen until march budget, little time to communicate to customers b4 April implementation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pension cold calling ban mooted in Autumn Statement https://t.co/SWEbu0m08M via @ThisIsMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our adviser events have been continuing this week at The Lowry in Manchester and the fantastic new stand at anfield https://t.co/y3V3Lx6nx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PensionsRaj @JosephineCumbo although that's not so helpful if it's employer contributions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayVay @AJBellMike @katefstar @JosephineCumbo presumably think there is too big a tax leakage - and that takes priority over flexibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Autumnstatement to be abolished. Spring Budget to be moved to Autumn after 2018. Spring statement to be introduced. That's clear then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation of a ban on pension cold calling. Largely thanks to petition by @RedCircleFP #Autumnstatement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[personal allowance to £12,500 by end of Parliament - as previously announced. But thereafter increases linked to inflation through 2020s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money Purchase Annual Allowance reduced from £10k to £4k. Restricts further pension contributions people can make after they draw benefits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[salary sacrifice changes coming from April 2017. But pensions, childcare and cycle to work continue as now #autumnstatement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triple lock staying - for now anyway. Sounds like it may disappear after 2020 or be downgraded to a double lock #autumnstatement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cold morning. But it means we can appreciate how busy the spiders have been https://t.co/sAC28qXzsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news. Well done @RedCircleFP @philbray73 https://t.co/LYTkXwkMG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plans for stripping pension cash revealed https://t.co/Eb5uGsoSSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up for the first of our Scottish events at @Gleneagleshotel  a very grand ballroom https://t.co/w40PnYWPRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Tully: Lessons from the defunct secondary annuities market - Money Marketing https://t.co/w9fGGm0oZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five-minute guide to making the most of retirement https://t.co/Vdphnuwozr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great atmosphere at #Wembley tonight. I think a few extra scots fans may have sneaked in https://t.co/XcRY5czBHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the going down of the sun and in the morning, we will remember them. #ArmisticeDay #Somme100 https://t.co/KkZFHg0qOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK agree no harm in having it. Can always ditch it at a later date]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK probably as there is nothing they can do with them. Hmrc's online checking system isn't live as yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fever pitch: The real story on DB transfers and insistent clients https://t.co/OgIm63PQZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After #brexit the Americans obviously thought - anything you brits can do we can do too, but we'll make it bigger #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our keynote speaker @BBCJLandale talking around the political aspects of #brexit https://t.co/AWiRT5H0Oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely view on a cold crisp morning for the latest in our round of autumn events - at the Globe theatre in #London https://t.co/nI0R1PFakZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to dump the idea of a ‘safe withdrawal rate’? https://t.co/tGI1P0bG0K via @retirementadvan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAF_IFA excellent result for mitt Romney considering he's not on the ballot....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five minute guide to putting paid to the pension scammers https://t.co/xIfD58CMGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naive pensioners face drawdown penury https://t.co/xXWgS6hCWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing first episode, looking forward to the rest.....although maybe with less snakes chasing newborns https://t.co/OKeDObogU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest HMRC newsletter out today &gt; https://t.co/g5o2u0Imjx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>