<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[BBCNewsnight very mixed message there. Did not add up. Eg, liberals in general are for more equitable distribution… https://t.co/RjAqRLW8UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight surely the question is that Trump policy is against international law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc Ciara can you ask about kefir re prebiotic.  Tks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkFM  Ciara can you ask about kefir please read prebiotic.  Tks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#poorturnout #trump #WomenMarch Specsavers should employ Trump and Spicer for next ad campaign. #spicersays #spicer https://t.co/soJmRXiTwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaajidNawaz check out Home Sweet Home / Apollo House in Dublin. Not same but similar scenario. TA. J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Ross: Support the Galway to Clifden Greenway https://t.co/bfaqYOe7vz via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatKennyNT Pat, can you discuss landlords who are not registered.  How do they fit in with all this? There are plenty of them. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/RtELR9fCpD how about "dope"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheresaMay good luck with That! https://t.co/g4ztDBhxvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/QQzBfGGoyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump #TrumpPresident  #WomensMarchOnWashington #WomensMarch #womensmarchIRL #TrumpCheck https://t.co/93RVamun1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch #WomensMarchIRL Thanks Bernie ! Very appropriate song. https://t.co/tAPufy1QxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#spicersays https://t.co/Wp4hJY7s8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trump #spicersays Spicer,  your pants are on Fire! https://t.co/U3hjOmfAg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me thinks they protest too much. Smoke and mirrors. We do have eyes in our head. https://t.co/U3hjOmfAg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no it wasn't! More delusional rubbish from Trumpet team. What about metro figures on the day for example? Smoke… https://t.co/30FvX1Bqwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abso****inglutely https://t.co/cLGTgafbgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will someone please take Twitter from this eejit. OMG he is US president - how did that Happen?! https://t.co/KMQ0zSCtr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen at Galway March today #WomensMarch #WomensMarchIRL https://t.co/DvJbTqlYu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch from Galway today #womensmarchirl https://t.co/6EcVFnCY8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarchIRL info for Galway Anyone? https://t.co/7he4D9DnGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomensMarchIRE info for Galway March Please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galway info Please? https://t.co/3KCRWiXHNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info for Galway please https://t.co/YMXexUvF8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomensMarchIRE where and what time is Galway March?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Janefonda Thank you for speaking out as always. Preditor-in-chief must be called out. And LOVE Grace and Frankie! You and Lily are a hoot.x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#presidenttrump So after all, all it boils down to is that US  tax dollars will be spent on military.  "Great" indeed. I don't think so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an eejit Gove is https://t.co/HwQZAi4AHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GreatBritishRailwayJourneys why is Dublin on this Programme? One doesn't wish to be petty and am not anti-brit but Dublin not in Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will have the power to launch a nuclear war in 4 mins! Obama has 4 days to stop him-sign the petition: https://t.co/OBtRFnwr8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRosAtkins why no mention of Obama speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatKennyNT no mention of all the nurses and midwives who were offered early retirement a few years ago. Paying for it now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghook Mr. Hook, one can be against anti-sematism and still criticise the Israeli government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red and Pink? https://t.co/IG3fhNEbDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for Ellen. What does Mr. Williams have to say I wonder. https://t.co/uv5Yh0xISl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of other mums and dads out there who take equally good photos I am sure. https://t.co/SXqNyScmBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business as usual for DT https://t.co/PcVqYtjocd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed.  And Leonard too.... https://t.co/HM0hOpsYfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed. GC must be a right happy camper.  Remembering Jo and thanks again to you for keeping her spirit alive. I wi… https://t.co/hkGa9nPiRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrendanCox My sympathy to you and your family. Thank you for all your positive efforts. Jo is my hero.  Let us hope 2017 will be better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbassadorPower Thank you for all your amazing work. Lets hope 2017 will be a better one for all.  JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to Pierce, Brexit hasn't happened yet. https://t.co/FqGA0z7zqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This from a man who has been part of Allepo hell this while. Give me a break. DT is clueless. https://t.co/y8WFgy184Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could US Mayors, Governors, and CEOs stop Trump from wrecking our climate?? Find out:  https://t.co/Q8zhckSado]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcnewsnight Evan Davis is a treasure, national or otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand safe and urgent passage for the civilians trapped in #Aleppo. Sign now: https://t.co/cOuepIAC0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delamere best on show https://t.co/J6fkzc9F0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always knew Kanye West was a tosser. https://t.co/V46Hbdn5Ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing pics Gerry. https://t.co/5tBcRGTpuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed. If today's gaf with Taiwan is anything to go by, trumpet will be putting his foot in it everywhere. https://t.co/Pwhz2xsAAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlabedBana I hope you and your family will be safe. Am not religious but pray for you all, if I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cliche but AJ best PM UK never had. Any Chance? #bbcqt https://t.co/y2kDBjQgn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will we make 9/11 stop in Syria? https://t.co/lNKkmA3COO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So do you recommend we give up democracy and get some socially progressive dictator? https://t.co/Z1WoD43OTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't like to make fun of anyone's appearance but in this case will make an exception, as Trump likes to do so, esp… https://t.co/7tbM7CyH1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jess, where can you buy that Dyson? Tks. https://t.co/AKyn0ketVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vile and shameful. And Trump wants to heal the Nation?  When he is the one who stirred up all this up.... shame on… https://t.co/s6GLArtsFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repulsive and worrying is right. https://t.co/V55AESKFmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vile and outrageous.  Should be denounced by Trump. What hate has this man encouraged. Shame on them. https://t.co/9HVp876nHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical https://t.co/dEAulBfogv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical https://t.co/1tjzHF1HfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed, at least in part. https://t.co/jcpToKKmRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahchurchwell you hit the right balance of rational argument and justifyable anger.  Thanks again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?! https://t.co/7JomGudag2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminism is about fairness, so fair enough. https://t.co/WQbXvrindK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical https://t.co/bgRPvO8nQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't compare A Merkel with Mr Thatcher just because she is a strong female politician. MT was very differen… https://t.co/hs87JBrZhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed. I see RK is all puffed up of late. Was much meeker when stepped down from ukip leadership race. https://t.co/Ho2eHWZ6IX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes please don'the leave. People are needed for 2020. https://t.co/R30Y2wdRay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Matt. https://t.co/Ki9puTWV31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is 'leader of free world" term still used?  If it is then would have A Merkel over Trumpet of course. https://t.co/HKwe300WCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahchurchwell just wanted to thank you for your formidable contribution to Question time on Thursday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odious woman. She also seems a bit derailed. Why was she on show in first place? #latelate https://t.co/Be1qiLffQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed. And what was with the black glove look. I know her fingers probably cold but she looked a bit left over fro… https://t.co/B8aoWflgVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter has a book to sell and profit from, not to b trusted. Also, Emily shd have asked her about Trump's comm… https://t.co/KsFqPPhMC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich coming from someone who befitted from the system when it suits him and who outsources overseas when it suits h… https://t.co/TaaiV5fJlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanTubridyShow Dave Fanning most annoying - why all the purile sniggering every time he said TG4? #TG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Trump supporters not upset by this manipulation? https://t.co/scv5uPfGdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#KevinsAmerica am not paying for my TV licence next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein why are u only criticising Hillary Clinton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK has been ill served by the petty ambitions of it's politicians. https://t.co/EMYadqtj9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will look forward to that! https://t.co/w71zVdLnez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about ever. He shd nvr have gvn in to tory euro sceptics. Now everyone will pay for his weakness. Nice guy, sha… https://t.co/CIvfrT5SUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Tapes one has to question timing of these tapes. Just in time for GOP to replace his nibs bfore too late. Xpect Trump is toast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein would love to c u do well but not if it means Trump gets in. Wish US had French 2 tier electoral system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump, if u really want to make America great, then you might want to pay your federal taxes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert De Niro was told to give a neutral speech asking people to vote. He didn't listen, and destroyed Trump https://t.co/ltvyzcpSjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please. Not a time for protesthe votes. Campaign to change to French two tier system instead. https://t.co/G2t8OGz20S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Thank you Robert. https://t.co/61rj2rW8Ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Marian Mary Kenny u cannot compare 1916 to brexit. Also are u saying Kilburn irish little England are themselves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One hopes. But then he has squirmed out of a lot more. https://t.co/zmNiqKLTMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beggars belief that this man has received so much support from women. https://t.co/ud1kN1DnkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indeed, cd not believe NT cut best show on radio. Well done Sean - you deserve award. https://t.co/v7bbxLSlI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And his latest victim opposite him in icu - even more ridiculous. He seems to be getting more care than her also? https://t.co/DvCqRM8Uxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#the fall so yer man Paul gets a nurse who fits description of woman he likes to kill. Ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed this petition, will you join me?  https://t.co/v0PX9qUPWw via @UpliftIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianRTE what about great Irish bake off?  why are we so tuned into UK? JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about Xylatol? #FoodUnwrapped https://t.co/vITqrGL5lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AmalClooney really admire Amal but wonder why she took husband's name .......?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>