<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Devastated about Many Clouds! A gem of a horse.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Long not that?? Perfect for a dipping half volley! What a fem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoshida to score anytime! Not even my worst bet of the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulski1978 very poor week!  Luckily I was playing the bottom team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hazard as captain! Epic failure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Un-Abel to play football!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstyleo @rharragan Sanchez as captain aswell to the top it of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting on Giroud to score anytime and he does nothing productive all game! Typical......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50/1 RAB! Excellent work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazalaar @Oddschanger I had £10 on it! Brilliant end to a poor betting day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan @ShazF21 one 9/1 winner and a lot of ffs! Cracking day though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't back it because it was 10/3! Drifts to 7/1! So frustrating...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstyleo @rharragan worked out even better as he was 4/1 to then score a double #slickclub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstyleo @rharragan well that was frustrating! https://t.co/HkQkAuE71W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK so last 4 jumps selection have fallen!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't want Danny Rose to back me up in a fight after that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wins at 3/1 and I backed it at 9s! Well done Flaming Spear and Robert Winston!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe the last 3 horse I've backed over the jumps have all fell!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be gutted if only Carlisle not scoring again let's me down! https://t.co/9huW2TxCw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 goals away from around 8 plus grand! Northampton hopeless, Everton to score 2 plus, I'll blame myself putting Cowdenbeath bts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you need a jockey to pull you out of trouble! I'd always choose Colin Keane!! Gent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan 36/1! Pity Palace are dire! Fraser was 5/1 alone anytime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fraser, Crouch and Benteke anytime scorer acca and Teke dragged off at halftime! :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I take Harry Kane out my team! It has been a shocker! Such a bad game week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dab is the dumpest thing ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't change my fantasy football team in team and it was looking slick.... That's going to hurt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gary_priestley my cliff horse!! Pretty much all I need to say....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah my good old cliff horse Buywise rattling home for 3rd is what I expected to hear later today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's the last time I'll back Cogry! Jeezo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beat in a photo! How often can I hit the bar!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow need to find Sanchez into my team!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4/5 anytime goalscores! One away again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan  @tomstyleo ah Ramos! I did look at him when he was 6/1 but left it...true story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan  @tomstyleo narrow it down? All bets are my favourite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9/1 the field! Good luck......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/3 anytime goalscorer! I've hit the bar alot this week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstyleo it definitely needed a change. Channel 4 racing was getting boring and the less said about The Morning Line the better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited! https://t.co/UdZbp3uzii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking it's goodbye Lukaku and hello Harry Kane!! #FantasyFootball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPL_Fly he is sitting on my bench! Another poor week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeJohns always back Davy Russell at huge prices ew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50/1 3rd! Not a da start to the day, I did only have about 5p ew on it! Meh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Rochdale goal away from a 244/1 coupon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah when your selection decides to put itself in reverse! I'm sure I could run faster.... :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has Pedro not scored today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sell Mata and put Clyne on the bench!...red arrows coming my way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst fantasy football week ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took Mata and Ozil out my team! No doubt they'll both score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet 508 appearances #SkyBetClub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerial drifts to 12s! Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeJohns Buywise's run was identical to last years! My favourite horse and the most frustrating! My cliff horse, we've all got one!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buywise rattling home again!!! This bloody horse!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another loser at Cheltenham! My favourite new phrase!! Hopefully tomorrow is better.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing Spin Doctor win after deciding against backing it, soul-destroying!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided on Ozil instead of Hazard! What a poor poor choice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need a QPR and a Benteke goal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How were Reading as big as 2/1! What a great price..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstyleo @rharragan just bet on the breeders cup! Gent or dry lunch... We'll soon see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan @tomstyleo I've completed it mate - #bantz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharragan you should maybe pay attention to fantasy football and not my Scotrail rants #tunamelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Scotrail service another out of order toilet @ScotRail! I can see my my £2700 season ticket is well spent!!… https://t.co/kPw4uO24aG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I fit KDB, Sanchez, Hazard, Augero, Lukaku, Costa, Coutinho and Firmino into the same team? the joys of being a FFM #FantasyFootball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dembele couldn't score against them are home to cost me a coupon, but away from home he bangs one in! Football betting eh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you wake up to find out it routed the field in the Melbourne Cup and still finished 2nd! Cracking run from Heartbreak City!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a goal that would have been!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody Cardiff! Always one team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully Augero finds form today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might be the only one without Sanchez in my team! Yikes! #FantasyFootball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPLadvice swapped him for Mata, hopefully it pays of!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going into a gameweek without an Arsenal attacker! The stress of fantasy football! Hopefully a Moyes masterclass!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogma beat by a neck!! Gutting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since I backed Wyfield Rose and was miles back, she has went on to win 4/5 races! Very frustrating....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Ritchie, the Ozil of the Championship! Loves an assist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLinfoot Spin Doctor was your tip of the day LTO, glad I followed again and got 20s!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to invest in Chelsea players in my fantasy football team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A missed penalty and a yellow card..I'm running out of patience with Sergio after his last few performance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last tweet!! That was well timed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a brilliantly taken goal! Awful defending again though, anyone still with a Man City defender in their fantasy football team..yikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully this is the day Matt Ritchie becomes Sir Matt Ritchie or at least a gent! #newcastlevipswich #boysdayout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportingLife why can't I watch replays via your app on an IOS device?? https://t.co/gwMHcY4R1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caspian Prince, what a brilliant horse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShazF21 We ALL knew this!! https://t.co/cbJ68RqibP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks BT sport for ruining champion league weeks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a name like Jesse, you'd be better settling down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a miss!! The whole goal to aim at and you fire it wide!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few after work drinks #WorldSmileDay https://t.co/SbDviBVZYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurgerKingUK 10 mins queueing for an Oero shake, get to the register and they have no milkshake! A waste of my day..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurgerKingUK don't you think your shops should display big signs informing the customer before they queue if the are out of something??..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail is the 19.22 Edinburgh to Helensburgh Central running on time??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Udinese and City not scoring lets a 95/1 coupon down! Getting closer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy football this season - nailed it!!! (so far)...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Udinese! Absolutely hopeless! All you had to do was score once! One goal.. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 minutes in and I've only realised Coutinho is playing! Yikes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail @ShazF21 so I had to pay out for a weekly ticket while this is resolved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail @ShazF21 this has caused a lot of problems to myself as my company wrote a cheque to Scotrail and this was rejected...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail can you explain why @ShazF21 was given different information for the same question?? The initial aswer was Scotrail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail can you tell me the cheque payee if buying a season ticket by cheque at booking office? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a Matt Ritchie goal away from a 70/1 anytime goal scorer acca! Always another day....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did this team ever beat Man utd? They have been woeful!! I feel bad for them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ross Barkley is absolutely dire at the moment!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>