<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Social Media Trends for Businesses in 2017 - https://t.co/TYEj7VXyeE https://t.co/qCKVikIS2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Peter is an author, entrepreneur and corporate keynote speaker" https://t.co/77WqSZdBQ1 #PeterShankman #Superpower https://t.co/5CfNN60dJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Care to share cards are a simple but effective marketing strategy. https://t.co/LLF6O0L7LF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In this episode, of the Savvy Dentist I chat with the author of The Smart Business Exit, Geoff Green"… https://t.co/aeMcQuKwXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Avoid Sytems Mistakes and Get Your Business Running Like Clockwork https://t.co/GEruh1WWBu #drjessegreen… https://t.co/KJAcdsEHNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[44. Diamonds And Ferraris: How To Design A Luxury Experience, with Karl Schwantes https://t.co/LbDO2zl3cs… https://t.co/8MGVuBeszZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I teach my clients to use a “Care to Share” Card https://t.co/kdbhtPEb8N #drjessegreen #moreidealpatients #marketing https://t.co/4TKmUNuJ1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tim Ferriss Guide to Beating Procrastination: 1.  Break It Down https://t.co/Z6zrIjHkfK #drjessegreen… https://t.co/osqrgyPOdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All new podcast No 46. Building A Profitable and Scalable Business Through Exit Planning with Geoff...… https://t.co/bKC4Dm2w0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just published a new article: Create a Profitable, Scalable, Sellable Practice – Now https://t.co/dShQjDyt0S… https://t.co/OVK3U3b0Uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45. How to Accelerate Your Business Growth Without Losing Your Mind with Meryl Johnston https://t.co/J39HzYPCBz… https://t.co/sibB9x2s0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 life lessons we learn too late - https://t.co/PIczR6mHxA https://t.co/Q2QmUpFMEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savvy Dentist No. 44 I chat with the owner of Xenox Diamonds and luxury experience designer, Karl Schwantes… https://t.co/5hUMLhoooV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most effective ways of gaining patients is to focus on internal marketing - or word of mouth.… https://t.co/htF8S5PrtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great service stems from clear systems. Want help creating good systems? Check out https://t.co/NJYqjOiRic) https://t.co/G5kNUsuIcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nathan is the publisher and editor of Foundr Magazine, a digital magazine for young entrepreneurs… https://t.co/ALGwGArDr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recommend taking control and creating a strong business you can rely on. https://t.co/VQ12w8dVCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Createing a fabulous customer experience is invaluable. https://t.co/4W4Bla08by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keys To Successful Delegation" https://t.co/mYEDZfzPeK #Delegation #Work #drjessegreen https://t.co/9tgVOkRwK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab a place at Profitable, Scalable, Sellable before it sells out! https://t.co/NJYqjOiRic https://t.co/SYNnj0vWPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New episode: How to Accelerate Your Business Growth Without Losing Your Mind with Meryl Johnston… https://t.co/rLN6IsN20y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Daily Habits to Build Resiliency - https://t.co/ie0EdxSe5c https://t.co/1G0bVOna0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food, Sleep, Exercise: Why You Seriously Need All 3 to Be Successful - https://t.co/0meP8Nc8k5 https://t.co/OZQGqQXlCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Little-Known Reasons Martin Luther King Was An Amazing Leader, Human - https://t.co/xzys1k22WX https://t.co/2M7UHSXOVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Toxic Habits That Are Slowly Wearing You Down - https://t.co/c5XhrMNXeM https://t.co/oZl5iwizMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new article: 5 Systems Mistakes Killing Your Business https://t.co/GEruh1WWBu #drjessegreen… https://t.co/VlkaLuyb3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Minimalist Guide To Gaining Ideal Patients, Fast" https://t.co/kdbhtPEb8N #drjessegreen #moreidealpatients… https://t.co/x1YxaoUQbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Only Five Email Folders Your Inbox Will Ever Need - https://t.co/bnvPjWceIV https://t.co/O38pg7awCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the global tech trends are and what they mean for your business. https://t.co/YjumedphlZ #Technology… https://t.co/oodULkDpmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Profitable, Scalable, Sellable event in February is selling out fast. Discover more here:… https://t.co/ipYhAzZHHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solitude Can Be Your Most Powerful Thinking Tool - https://t.co/x1QRToXddF https://t.co/PtklvFvHZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savvy Dentist No. 44. Diamonds And Ferraris: How To Design A Luxury Experience, with Karl Schwantes… https://t.co/MhkJd0yOmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Brain Will Age Better If You Do This - https://t.co/V8ZNRAfTaf https://t.co/fJMY7wmmzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know how scared you are. If I could say anything to you, it would be 'Relax, it's going to be OK' ” Oprah"… https://t.co/2LzooM6Yqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[43. The Secrets of Successful Entrepreneurs, with Nathan Chan of Foundr Magazine https://t.co/oM8tMNlilK… https://t.co/d0OyJJkdY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[42. Unlock Your Business Superpower, with Peter Shankman https://t.co/77WqSZdBQ1 #PeterShankman #Superpower https://t.co/en3X60OIRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Food, Sleep and Exercise Are Critical to Success - https://t.co/TO3V56kJGt https://t.co/Kz47uQdPE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Podcast with The Happy Family Lawyer. She shares how to challenges industry conventions and why you should too"… https://t.co/bO8XHssf2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Practices for Making a Good Impression - https://t.co/QRQqdg83a3 https://t.co/23DcaWEd7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Do Less But Still Get More Done (Delegation Made Easy) https://t.co/mYEDZfzPeK #Delegation #Work… https://t.co/JwPGVHHFud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just published Savvy Dentist 44. Diamonds And Ferraris: How To Design A Luxury Experience, with Karl Schwantes… https://t.co/SoKQJ6KFYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Tim Ferris Guide to Beating Procrastination" https://t.co/Z6zrIjHkfK #drjessegreen #timferris… https://t.co/aGvXjzI2K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new article: The Minimalist Guide To Gaining Ideal Patients, Fast https://t.co/kdbhtPEb8N… https://t.co/JRgex81luG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["43. The Secrets of Successful Entrepreneurs, with Nathan Chan of Foundr Magazine" https://t.co/oM8tMN3Huc… https://t.co/7h9ZGNB8iE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover Peter Shankman's radically new ways of thinking about customer service, social media, marketing and ADHD.… https://t.co/joqwWt11hR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executing and implementing your plan may sound simple, but it can be easy to ignore.  https://t.co/zzymP4KFkm… https://t.co/LEHrYxVtL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How To Do Less But Still Get More Done (Delegation Made Easy)" https://t.co/mYEDZfzPeK #Delegation #Work… https://t.co/1ZSkn8hKBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new podcast: 43. The Secrets of Successful Entrepreneurs, with Nathan Chan of Foundr Magazine… https://t.co/vmsM6MqtMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Tim Ferriss Guide to Beating Procrastination" https://t.co/Z6zrIjHkfK #drjessegreen #timferris… https://t.co/krOOzw1uE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gina has over 7 years of social media marketing and digital experience. https://t.co/cQSkbQMilO #socialmedia… https://t.co/64r7GrckZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just published a new article: How To Do Less But Still Get More Done (Delegation Made Easy) https://t.co/mYEDZfzPeK… https://t.co/qPp4a2lRDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Savvy Dentist #42. Unlock Your Business Superpower, with Peter Shankman" https://t.co/77WqSZdBQ1 #PeterShankman… https://t.co/aBrJgmfL9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[41. What technology disruption means for dentists, with the PE Geek Jarrod Robinson https://t.co/YjumedphlZ… https://t.co/nOp1leVHXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["1.  Success is the Result of Focus" https://t.co/a1iIr1vE00 #Business #drjessegreen #success https://t.co/NZnju3JjL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New podcast episode: 42. Unlock Your Business Superpower, with Peter Shankman https://t.co/77WqSZdBQ1… https://t.co/cMJlsulzqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tim Ferriss Guide to Beating Procrastination https://t.co/Z6zrIjHkfK #drjessegreen #timferris… https://t.co/yeLGXEgMAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Luck is preparation meeting the moment of opportunity.” Oprah" https://t.co/tOy0Aax9Bp #Oprah #Success… https://t.co/CoYksLzB87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to give effective feedback. https://t.co/WAilqKWgo4 #Staff #underperforming #drjessegreen https://t.co/YubUtA4O1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40. Challenging Industry Conventions (and Why You Should) with Clarissa Rayward https://t.co/98QpGljETA… https://t.co/8ci10CDzzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Patient retention is Key to business success" https://t.co/RLoD87oI5l #Dentist #success https://t.co/6aGyar1dSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Convert Price Shoppers Into Loyal Patients https://t.co/WLQrigeclB #priceshoppers #drjessegreen… https://t.co/kCv58iiOO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take Relaxation Seriously" https://t.co/5tUjopj9aR #burnout #drjessegreen https://t.co/cfGW6CZP0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Increase The Amount Patients Spend" https://t.co/Tb9NOvPQAr #Marketing #Revenue #drjessegreen https://t.co/juxU4jGeC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new article: The Tim Ferriss Guide to Beating Procrastination https://t.co/Z6zrIjHkfK #drjessegreen… https://t.co/eM7CLkKYBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want a great relationship your staff you need to know how to read your team https://t.co/SL2yX9wGrG #Staff… https://t.co/F7d7zCNK31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use the 'refer a friend' method to boost your patient flow. https://t.co/phFaKKYsId #patientflow #drjessegreen https://t.co/ZRCct6gtdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling with internet speed? 6 ways to speed up your Wi-Fi at home - https://t.co/VWpRV6x9yY https://t.co/e3jIr5lUuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This week I’m joined by Jarrod Robinson who is better known as the PE Geek" https://t.co/YjumedphlZ #Technology… https://t.co/1u8Q6f0uXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 simple ways you can be smarter about your money - https://t.co/BlrWa4FVlf https://t.co/eTPqYANFrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dr Ayesha Aijaz run two practices on autopilot. She shares how she does it" https://t.co/AbHmqw1seL #Practice… https://t.co/uAJSBilPFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Things I Learned from Talking to 9 Millionaires - https://t.co/NKJ5zxqvt3 https://t.co/OZnEkVpbuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meditation Has Become Big Business - https://t.co/qde3leW7Iq https://t.co/Hjpuaf8X0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just need to run that race as hard as you can." ~ Oprah https://t.co/tOy0Aax9Bp #Oprah #Success #drjessegreen https://t.co/CVsPcmf8oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I disagree on this one: If you want to get rich, start working 95 hours a week - https://t.co/wRj2I6Tojt https://t.co/dNEWzF6wX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" Clarissa Rayward talks about challenging your industry’s conventions, and why doing so will set you apart."… https://t.co/dJhMMHPT6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Ways to Keep Your Attitude Up When Life Tries to Bring You Down - https://t.co/QIdNfW548n https://t.co/5as9AUWuQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to control and solve problems before they get out of hand.  https://t.co/zzymP4KFkm #drjessegreen… https://t.co/Qu6JdoNUzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This CEO gives his employees a 3-day weekend every month and a $2,000 vacation bonus - https://t.co/jMBZJhAj44 https://t.co/k8PWUWPngm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 Tips to Take Control of Your Life Now - https://t.co/KkUzVyWEeD https://t.co/NlrFQ7hLF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Wealthy Mentalities of Successful People - https://t.co/aPHDWSx2ov https://t.co/ficFpPb72j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Qualities of Wildly Successful People - https://t.co/opcdi7RYoN https://t.co/NrL6TLDtPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a millionaire by busting these 5 myths - https://t.co/tQTUc5FKng https://t.co/0M7S2VUpCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Essential Lessons I Learned In 20 Years Of Managing People - https://t.co/hecgH95LiJ https://t.co/ltIJuYb0kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilising psychology in your marketing with Gina Lednyak https://t.co/cQSkbQMilO #socialmedia #drjessegreen… https://t.co/m1M3gDomV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Campbell Learned From a 101-Year-Old Tomato Soup Recipe - https://t.co/0nMaU404r2 https://t.co/OrzFUPaS2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["41. What technology disruption means for dentists, with the PE Geek Jarrod Robinson" https://t.co/YjumedphlZ… https://t.co/PekqaC5wGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re secretly being trained to break your iPhone on purpose - https://t.co/fCPe5dilVq https://t.co/ANR6f3OuJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Social Media Trends for Businesses in 2017 - https://t.co/korCfKw8Wn https://t.co/DbJFULrTzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["40. Challenging Industry Conventions (and Why You Should) with Clarissa Rayward" https://t.co/98QpGljETA… https://t.co/XvcPmc2oBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oprah’s Top 10 Rules For Success https://t.co/tOy0Aax9Bp #Oprah #Success #drjessegreen https://t.co/OuOsk10Hc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Things I Learned from Talking to 9 Millionaires - https://t.co/NKJ5zxqvt3 https://t.co/cWZ7X3dDRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 5 Maxims You Need to Create a Successful Dental Practice https://t.co/a1iIr1vE00 #Business #drjessegreen… https://t.co/QVvcCaPvXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Expect to Get Any Work Done for the Next Two Weeks - https://t.co/tXlk4zxKky https://t.co/9pI6gm8Iu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new article: 41. What technology disruption means for dentists, with the PE Geek Jarrod Robinson… https://t.co/a2AavsvINf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to Live Remarkably? 9 Things a Navy SEAL Says You Should Always Do - https://t.co/3W0WFcJbuK https://t.co/vmg8JtPkZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How To Create a Prosperous Dental Practice" https://t.co/zzymP4KFkm #drjessegreen #dentalsuccess https://t.co/brgCJRyg52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in business you're a show person. You have to get up, dress up, show up and never give up. https://t.co/525jB73Pgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our podcast: 40. Challenging Industry Conventions (and Why You Should) with Clarissa Rayward… https://t.co/RRPUdrDZ3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our new article: Oprah’s Top 10 Rules For Success https://t.co/tOy0Aax9Bp #Oprah #Success #drjessegreen https://t.co/QQOXDVNwob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Deal With Underperforming Staff https://t.co/WAilqKWgo4 #Staff #underperforming #drjessegreen https://t.co/pBclU2KCAp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>