<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And that he's a jackass carnival barker https://t.co/50G39QtgVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Including, most importantly, opposing litigants. https://t.co/p3tzt3Xu5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invertebrate briefly on Wikipedia
#PaulRyanIn4Words https://t.co/IuoFIgvHjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rational Security listeners--don't miss the end. @shaneharris @tcwittes https://t.co/OvV70xjXjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mugs they REALLY won't be expecting it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: This is what a real president looks like on Twitter, guys. https://t.co/SQO1KX2OLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SylviaEowyn I didn't know you were in upstate NY. I thought Bay Area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SylviaEowyn are you the person I think you are? Sylvieeey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bartona104 where do you see the lineup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And just to be clear, it still very much is one. I used the past tense only to explain why we were pleased by the project from day 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawfareblog was a response to an impoverished debate. We support all efforts to enrich the debate. @just_security was a very important one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slrtybrtfrt that's a good idea. @Susan_Hennessey @tcwittes @shaneharris @qjurecic waddaya think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: Thought experiment, @GenMhayden: if you polled IC professionals, how much lower/highe… https://t.co/vX8DMFDQtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArcticBoy63 @jimsciutto I'm not a conservative (at least not recognizably so to any real conservative), but I'm certainly doing my best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamWatt ignored and lied about so that we can keep 5 year olds out of the country and prevent Iranian Americans from visiting their...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamWatt ...right thing and protect the country while respecting people's rights under the rule of law--and have them be denigrated,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamWatt I hear ya. It's a terrible thing to have great expert agencies with countless men and women striving every day to do the ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnceaSloan and thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnceaSloan I particularly like what @georgebthird and company did at the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamWatt Don't let my tone be too comforting. Alarm is the right response here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: A brief video with some stuff that's been on my mind. https://t.co/HF7Jg1vtRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nobody, and I mean nobody, by whom I would rather read an explainer on these injunctions than the great An… https://t.co/YYQE2sB8H2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: The CoalitionOfAllDemocraticForces acknowledges @jendaskal, @gabeschoenfeld &amp; @JRubinBlogger for their service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: This is a very important piece. You should all read it. And you should all tweet it. https://t.co/FYlh7YfnX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: If any aspect of this excellent piece by @chongathon seems hyperbolic, consider @intelwire on Quebec. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: If you've never heard of Avril Haines, you have no idea how much our nation misses her right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCarafano all the more reason to screw up relations with them, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: The #CoalitionOfAllDemocraticForces salutes McCain and Graham for their service &amp; for… https://t.co/UcMd53cxB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrainSpurts read what I mean, not what I type. My thumbs are really tired!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: Having fended off Mexico and Australia, Trump should turn to Micronesia, Iceland and Costa Rica. #NewThreats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: Heck yeah on indecent subversion, which is BTW the metal band opening for Extreme Vet… https://t.co/2yQQbqVjBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 15: Feeling grateful that we have a White House that protects us from 5-year-old girls and the Australian Menace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slogan of the CoADF: 
When the peasants are storming the gates, you don't ask the guy handing you a guy what he thi… https://t.co/QVSPZ1DD0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden Cheers, Dude. #PrayWithARaisedFist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden I agree. You've never--even in hurling obscenities at us :)--engaged in that particular misunderstanding of our work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden conversions. our point is that we're all in the boat as expressions of the same value systems that we started with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden I fully agree with that. But a lot of people have assumed that we're in the same boat because we've had death-bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden our posture. We felt a word of explanation was in order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden agreed. It's just that the magnification of the duty has put us in a position in which a lot of people are surprised by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden As you know, I am not spending my time taking shots at civil libertarians these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden I hope it doesn't come across that way to others, but if it does, for my part, that's certainly not what I intended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden the costs to effectiveness, that is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden ...effective outcomes than if you believe it's an apparatus that doesn't produce effective CT at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden decisionmaking is necessarily higher if you believe those systems have a lot of integrity and tend to produce...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden our point is just that the costs of the war Trump is waging on the apparatus of intelligence and national security...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaz @GenMhayden Gosh, it really wasn't meant as a shot at civ libs at all and I'm terribly sorry if it came off that way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlankenSteve around the office, @Susan_Hennessey and I have been known to call @qjurecic "quintassential."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmulford @CSIS @morningmoneyben I'm actually an @oberlincollege grad but I've become a kind of honorary @KenyonCollege person somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll find out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were one of the large group I talked to after panel, get in touch. You're asking all the right questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: Very moved by young @KenyonCollege alums interested in the #CoalitionOfAllDemocraticForces at @CSIS tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is profoundly important point. https://t.co/1QL1Do1twd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: @GenMhayden and me on "The Special Obligation of the Advocates of Strong National Sec… https://t.co/IFDcPmS9H7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the spirit, man! https://t.co/VwMwkvs8IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: It is profoundly important to make fun of the president, to needle him with small things. He cares. So do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: Also accepting nominations for names for US forces embedded with Australian forces and vice versa in this war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: We are accepting nominations for the name of the first Australian-American War. Use hashtag #WarfareDownUnder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My work on this planet, folks, is done. https://t.co/7J1MDYT3I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: On behalf of the #CoalitionofAllDemocraticForces, I commend to you @notcolloquial.… https://t.co/qpRUXu0SUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notcolloquial gotcha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notcolloquial You just deleted the awesome tweet of the day! Put it back so I can feature it on notes from under trump! The CoAD needs it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: The great @iraglass of @ThisAmerLife discovers @lawfareblog. 

You should too. https://t.co/7vFozFS6ma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold right to do it, and I'm actually not afraid of embarrassment of anything in those emails. But I do resent it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold I am not without resentment of even lawful inquiries into the relationships we have sought to build. I don't question your]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold are inseparable from the trust we developed. And just as you likely resent lawful leak investigations to get at your sources,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold find that our intimacy with the deep state gives us credibility. I just want people to understand that those relationships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold People who were offended by our refusal to publish classified leaks--a policy essential to our credibility within the IC--now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold people who accused us of being toadies for @NSA mysteriously find that @Susan_Hennessey's voice is really valuable. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold ...relations with the bureaucracy that we have now. A lot of people are seeing the benefits of those relationships now, ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold I tell you why it bothers me: We worked extremely hard over many years to develop the kind of constructive above-board ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold @BenjaminEHaas I didn't take it personally. But I noted it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold @BenjaminEHaas and @BobbyChesney's too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold @BenjaminEHaas that news comes as a surprise. most of our interactions have involved your FOIA requests of my comms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: If anyone should know that I am not a law professor, it is the @PostOpinions section!
https://t.co/3ke3t7c07f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 14: Never resented a motorcade for Obama, Biden, Bush or Cheney. But CT Ave blockage for Trump-Pence burns me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminEHaas FYI @JasonLeopold is not a fan of my stuff. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: Hearing from IC peeps that these tweets are inducing smiles. America loves you, folks. Pray with raised fists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: I can't blame her. Would you want to live with him? https://t.co/oNfxQlwQoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSVaknin I'd take Putin pretty fast too, but I feel differently about that, as he's a phony martial artist who stages shows of prowess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSVaknin I could take trump down with one kick. He's significantly overweight and 70. It would be an absurd match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSVaknin I would never spar Trump. He's not remotely at my level. The guy doesn't even have a black belt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joyofsuing I don't think so. parlo=I speak. Right @Susan_Hennessey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: Listen to @marty_lederman and @jacklgoldsmith debate Sally Yates's action and firing. https://t.co/qBNwUqXbU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Huddled Masses" Edition - The Trump administration’s executive order on immigration spurs chaos and... https://t.co/PHUfPOfiSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farhadrizvi I suggested in my piece that this was not vetted by competent counsel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: @Susan_Hennessey and I are at @zaytinya. Great food and a courageous chef-litigant ag… https://t.co/fC1nzHeWhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot say why, but he did his country proud and deserves thanks from people who follow #NotesFromUnderTrump. Pray with a raised fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: On behalf of the #CoalitionofAllDemocraticForces, let me acknowledge @RosenzweigP for service to the nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: This morning's fun is talking to @iraglass of @ThisAmerLife about Trump's EO on immigration. #excited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geology_rocks I could not agree more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geology_rocks I'm not saying I expect to agree with the guy on any number of things. But that has never been my standard. Elections matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheerhumbug it is a beautiful exchange, one for which both Graham and Kagan deserve credit, one dems should study for Gorsuch hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheerhumbug there's a wonderful precedent for that btw. See the exchange between Lindsey Graham and Elena Kagan about Miguel Estrada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheerhumbug gorsuch would agree with me about garland. Zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheerhumbug well, different garland nomination but that one was a travesty too--although one that ended well. I have no doubt tho that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimHenke1 I don't do predictions--as I haven't made a right one in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSMichaelWhite fighting the wrong battle when you can't win is the definition of stupid. The dems need to be strategic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As @SalmanRushdie wrote in "Shame": "Life is long." Fight that battle another day, when you have the forces to win it. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: My only reservation about this appointment is the deep wrong done to Merrick Garland. My advice to dems? 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotesFromUnderTrump, Day 13: Neil Gorsuch is a first-rate judge, a fine man, and a lovely person. Even a stopped clock is right twice a day]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>