<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tombatron which part? I can go days without an issue but then it can crash three times on the drive home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump I have a bold idea for an executive order... make the metric system our nation's standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard this on a bus of 8th graders (I'm chaperoning). 

"Let's put it on Facebook so the old people can like it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a great time yesterday @Gr8FallsPark! https://t.co/5m7xwm0N8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @paulkrugman they were posted 16 hours apart. Did the numbers change in those 16 hours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrd_84 Attrition on the original Titanfall is still fun. I already returned Battlefield 1 and will be keeping Titanfall 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jen_Face I will trade you a lonely mother who can't figure out her daughter has two L's in her last name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonKindle Gone With the Wind. 

I have a few hours left to go!(according to my Kindle)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pdftables just saved me from hours of retyping PDF tables into excel. 

Even if I have to jump to the $15 option, it will be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JM_Underwood that cat looks just like our favorite little guy that passed away last month. He was an awesome cat. Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brewhas_Keepers  I am no Shimizu. Thanks for letting me back in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brewhas_Keepers yes. I'll take any team. (Even my old one) :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am attending Mount Mary University's MBA Open House on the 27th https://t.co/jm3MRROEY0 #constantcontact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeweggService I already emailed and they responded with a "too bad so sad". Searching social media and I am finding more people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracels you have to zoom but it's very patriotic. Red, white, and blue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@odd111out @newegg did they ever resolve this for you? They just shipped a package of mine to an address I don't know. They deny everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brewhas_Keepers is watterworth interested in selling the swampnuts back to Milwaukee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMander if the shelter had no means to protect the women and children then they did the right thing. Sent to a shelter 30miles away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracels 2) nobody needs hands on instruction on how to place a condom on anything. Either in the schools or home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracels 1) I finally read the article. It wasn't even sex-Ed. It was a kid describing what a sexologist does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracels how hard is it to figure or try on your own at home? It just seems a tad bit too sexual for school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracels I might be considered left of center and I think that is taking sex Ed too far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert @HowardKurtz @FoxNews how does Marco Rubio win a "botched" GOP debate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brennanator look at the date of this article http://t.co/mKK2wf9HrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpwilloughby @realDonaldTrump I think Trump is more Ron Paul than Obama. Btw "sheeple" is a word only used amongst the sheep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Souders did you go into the app first? That was what was odd for me.  I didn't engage Bluetooth from settings but within the connect app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mathew Marher's Darknet was a thriller! I have been very pleased with my Kindle Unlimited choices. http://t.co/fS7AXnvy7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son at #HanksHangout. Go Brewers! http://t.co/2SU2NVlmSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally watched this week's @Castle_ABC.  Much better than the 1st episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcenters @andrewjclark see the whole story here: http://t.co/daiUtp1G7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyBeardGuy I found at least one card meant for me (unless she has another husband)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a special stash of cards for your wife is only romantic if you remember where that stash is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crl_fitzpatrick Feingold/Clinton (Bill)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I let my 10yo son mow the lawn for the first time #cropcircles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I side 82% with Bernie Sanders, Rubio @ #2, and Walker @ #3. Am I a centrist or just crazy?

http://t.co/cbwm2Dv7v5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best local Craigslist ad I have ever read http://t.co/LCabraWeU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was just awarded the "village idiot" achievement for shredding my car's passenger side tires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmanjoo try @usbank for a good web/mobile experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You find the funniest things when switching cell phones. http://t.co/rzi5beGBRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkhajdin Wilson's "David vs Goliath" has always been my favorite commercial.  http://t.co/ZA2JfpCMoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dread what the snow plows will bring overnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be one of those sharks for Halloween.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just broke my toe while changing shoes #lame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byjoelanderson I also remember being taught that respect was a two-way street. "Don't respect somebody who doesn't respect you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliRubenstein @MittRomney how is Romney any less "new" than the other candidates? He never held office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son at @SportsAuthField today http://t.co/BbtVtTqn4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I clearly was not prepared for 2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just noticed my personal hotspot tab went away after switching to @Cricketnation . Saving $ but that hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbaierl an Irish twist helps even more "Apoth O'Cary"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't say the word "apothecary"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't we due for a Tango and Cash remake? I think Will Smith and Chris Pine would be a perfect duo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Michael Jordan pumpkin will make me millions. #TakeFlight http://t.co/jZJr6cu0MH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amazon I just noticed the no-cost get a $1 credit back shipping. Brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwitterSurveys your survey is broken. The follow up questions don't make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess which city I was I visited today: http://t.co/yN7grHMv6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angelicaduria @fox6wakeup @fox6now Gmail users should add Google's Two Step Verification https://t.co/LRUblXez55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite picture from last week's trip to Camp Nawakwa (WI) http://t.co/8UxCySjrQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Popehat your book's older brother (40 years old) http://t.co/PQ9yxOpeDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The youth expo is the best thing I have seen I at @wistatefair in years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgusting... Yet brilliant! http://t.co/LlglvxUeNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We share memories of GI Joe and the Transformers. Our children will share memories of @stampylongnose and @iBallisticSquid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both @JerryMander: Helicopter seeds, brilliant or evil?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should I make a complicated password if it is just going to be stolen (again)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am happy to see the Wisconsin state bird has arrived in Milwaukee. http://t.co/uv6lslHNdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbaierl is that the only rule to be concerned with? I rinsed the meat (per wife's instructions) and gave the guest non-dropped meet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just dropped the raw chicken on the concrete. Salvageable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously thought French bread could be vacuum sealed. It obviously did not recover. http://t.co/2Jmu5F7WXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cortana is not really the type of girl you bring home to mom https://t.co/zGILpyT0lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave my son my tie to wear and this is what he does with it #bachelorparty http://t.co/eBluTJR3KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did America end up with this health care system? http://t.co/vU2WI8k7jD via @pittsburghpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbaierl or maybe they meant 0--]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am no math genius but I am pretty sure it can't be negative zero outside. http://t.co/1sWNbiursQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a quota on ties in the NFL this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great book! RT @AllKindleDeals: .@paolobacigalupi The Windup Girl is the #audible #AudibleDailyDeal for $5.95! http://t.co/x4DD9XmYYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who steals a man's spork?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouisatheLast mandatory minimum wage drives up the cost of center-based healthcare. Will always be an issue until robots can care for kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouisatheLast center-based care is typically 6am-6pm. You are paying a premium for flexibility. It isn't for everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stop thinking about New Diggings, WI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Benji in standard definition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbaierl Did you guys get the call? MT http://t.co/VBjhMayuda’s glitches prompt Obama to call in more experts http://t.co/RFVzmkuHdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have read the local opinion pages for 20 years and this is the first letter I have seen on the state of IT  http://t.co/cMkLvmFUPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishspy I think he worked less than a year as a medical sales rep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishspy is there a Scott Walker clause?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyssareads we really like the football card game, “Jukem.” We tweaked our “house rules” to our liking but the “stock” version is still OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why U.S. Health Care Is Obscenely Expensive, In 12 Charts http://t.co/fI6JFlbaUx via @HuffPostBiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mubuzztap Golden Eagle attacks a deer  http://t.co/FF3XjDBmbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I side with Libertarians (69%) on most political issues, Republicans (56%), Democrats (55%)  http://t.co/PszHCiR2PF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Wauwatosa West soccer players being called heroes http://t.co/v6Po4v7E0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The local news is covering a toilet-papering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdomenech wouldn’t lie #4 affect public and private education?  Her article is very anti-public education with no private data to compare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbaierl my son was brought to tears by a cute fuzzy caterpillar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That embarrassing moment when you find out your son is deathly afraid of caterpillars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it taking 25 minutes to rip the Hootie CD I found?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish fry tonight at Lakefront Brewery http://t.co/4cAg4JdnHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I dream the whole "Lucky Rabbit's Foot" thing? We all had one as a kid... Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs certainly benefit when owners have short-term memory problems. I think I fed the beast three times this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who uses all caps when requesting a fantasy baseball trade? #freak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: low profile ceiling-fans are called “huggers” #homedepot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whoozley now you are starting to lose me. These people probably loved you and shared their personal beliefs. Was it a sales pitch or love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[???? I got America’s Next Top Model! What Reality TV Show Should You Be On? http://t.co/FAPjitrFs7 via @BuzzFeed]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>