<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParrotOfTheDay Mr and Mrs King Parrot enjoy an early dinner. https://t.co/Tb8XMTRtg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErnestMalley @AusLoafer @jamesmassola @RachelBkr algae quite heavy off the CYC For my Sunday kayaking. Wish I was in Tassie this summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErnestMalley @AusLoafer @jamesmassola @RachelBkr sailing in Canberra is pretty terrible. Fluky winds, blue green algae and Qbeyan cemetery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErnestMalley @AusLoafer @jamesmassola @RachelBkr @anusha_srini Canberra Yacht Club fish'n'chips are v good. As are their potato scallops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane my young rescue kelpie is a good dog, cheering up my 12yo kelpie who was miserable when the kids left. https://t.co/ULDCzZseHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParrotOfTheDay Mr and Ms King Parrot eating early to avoid 37c heat later in Canberra. https://t.co/Q5VkFhLYGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParrotOfTheDay @GidgitVonLaRue pity you're in Canberra in summer. The town has plenty of gang gangs in cool months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philtastro @ParrotOfTheDay be careful they don't start destroying your fly screens etc once they're not fed. Mine does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham my pleasure. Love your books. Delighted to make a tiny contribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParrotOfTheDay Mrs King Parrot will sometimes sit on my hand to feed. Those are the best days. https://t.co/BioOiudjh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralanryan we head out to Thredbo tomorrow and home 3 January. Catch up then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralanryan how many fish have you caught?.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralanryan thanks Alan. Just the tonic I needed. Was in floods watching that. Happy New Year to the Ryans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @JohnLithgow agree Lithgow becomes invisible as Churchill. Amazing characterisation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennaPrice you're lucky, he'll keep the mozzies down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenmfanning it's a cushion cover, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer Bruce highway South]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny @Lobes @TonyHWindsor I've followed Chris K for 2yrs to broaden my views, but it's all just cheap scorn and hubris. Enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionaKatauskas look in the cabinet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham thanks heaps have been keen to see what happened next!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Domaincomau @smh seriously you're not helping yourselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham catch and release with luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusFielding2 it's race mate https://t.co/ZpBmpZyLlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barriecassidy regional processing in Hawaii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon oh dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ElectionDay https://t.co/U4aeVeg9KR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will ABF set up a refugee processing centre in Hawaii?? #ElectionNite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantjmcd @CDAInstitute congratulations from Australia Dr Boutilier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCraigEmerson breaking up is hard to do , and Oh Carole.. Both Neil Sedaka?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBarronUSA @Salon sorry John we were so engrossed in The Crown that we missed Planet America! Great show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeWMcGregor @ABCTV thanks for a great show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenJ @HillaryClinton does this make Trump the ultimate 'useful idiot'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump doubles down on criticism of Reagan.... Hillary scores another taunt. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open mouthed that Trump won't accept election result. There will be deaths #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuinnRod sorry Rod, but my Salzburg and Heidelberg cards are too sentimentally valuable...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosswilsonmusic found myself wandering Alexanderplatz in Berlin this morning singing Mondomania sotto voce. Thanks for the tunes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralanryan lots of photos on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralanryan it's been damn hot here! 50km ride today. Cold change tomorrow, happily. https://t.co/lZntG6Fo57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny sounds like a bonus track on an Angels album circa 1979]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @noeltowell @canberratimes how thin-skinned are these bosses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 Tom Petty and the Strikebreakers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewCatsaras if this was a Reyne song, it would have hidden meaning, but Guy McDonough lyrics not as nuanced. May mean nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewarthase very sad to hear that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane that sounds funny in a Mexican accent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanrya80668883 Goodoh. I'm home from noon for rest of today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoubleJRadio The Sun by They Might Be Giants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane no. I've got a bad feeling about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucanBoy1 @joshgnosis @petertaggart that beard is a Townsville Special. Says it all really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradleywoodAU @ANUBellSchool @alanrya80668883 check out Bob's slide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sallyjsara @rfidler tweet of the night . Hilarious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane @racing_qld All those horses are unhappy. Look at their ears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjrowland68 @BreakfastNews racist af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@domknight @Colvinius thanks for the tip. Just ordered this book thru Amazon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewarthase will probably do some more teaching after Europe trip in September. Short term gigs... Catch up if you come to Canberra!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewarthase great thanks. just retired and catching up on deep housework deficit over many years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham every birthday my darling daughter makes me chocky crackles. Yum. And otherwise all the Copha piles up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama there is no How. Only assertion. Maintain your commentary please sir, it is important. Thanks from Canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon @cathywilcox1 @benharrisben Monster Island?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosswilsonmusic #SongsWithLowerExpectations Baby let me bang your letterbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've Grown Somewhat Accustomed To Her Face #SongsWithLowerExpectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBlaxland1 Farage has done a Root'n'Boot to the entire country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb @al_ryan78 @leighsales you'll be flat out with the spatulas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davpope quite so. Now I will read two chapters of Far From The Madding Crowd to settle down. Roll on Insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davpope desperate flailing.  He mentions the ABCC now? After eight weeks of silence.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb thanks to you all for hanging in there. Best panel ever, a great positive vibe. Get some sleep!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjrowland68 well done hanging in there, thanks for your coverage tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greensdawn @Greens voting green against the camps and for progressive social and climate policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut needs more sauce!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harme @CultureStAus best dip: 1 jar Corn Relish, 1 Phillie Cheese. Fold together. Only Chicken Crimpys will do for scoopage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcww1 @Colvinius affecting and sombre. Well done repersonalising those terrible casualty statistics. Lest we forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraMemes yep. Election phrase bingo and a book on when St Antony of the Green calls it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo thanks for your analysis. Enjoy your Sunday night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InsidersABC I love #insiders, but today seemed to be a procession of gotchas, leaving substantial matters in their froth. I live in hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanOnselenP But Churchill, despite flaws, did something enormously right and important in his first term. No comparison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last gig with @AustCivMil. Privileged to help build overseas crisis and disaster response for over three years. https://t.co/VDNk11kODI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilFinn that looks like an electric fence... Kinky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petertaggart @mrbenjaminlaw sing 'Accidentally Kelly Street' and we will judge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Eurovision2016 that Croatian lass was dressed as Nero from the Star Trek reboot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon check PM for Gundagai scan. You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon ok will do. In bed now. Is email address on Grauniad site?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon I do. Can scan and email tomorrow if you like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny oh joy an actual joke. Glad I have hung in for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GChristensenMP @TimWattsMP you haven't studied communism at all, have you George?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite PMs injunction am definitely feeling #MistyEyed about refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon @CoralSeaOz cheer up Nemo, worse things happen at sea.   Oh dear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bowling for Bunnies https://t.co/FnOZjMTqrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane your use of 'mate' in the aggressive form is exemplary. Props.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosswilsonmusic commiserations to you, his family and mates. Few get to bring such joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef that's meta of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewarthase what about grace? The metaphysical? I don't have a clear view, but it's another dimension, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon it's a long way to the top!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo how good was Sufjan Stevens? And he mentioned unicorns in Canberra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenpage nice site but had a glitch confirming sign up to newsletter. Twice, so mayhap a design error. Nice new single too! Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipAdams_1 A Transport of Delight for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham here's an earworm for ya 'Aint gonna bump no more, with no big fat woman...'. That should bump Boz off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezNews thanks for a great broadcast. Well played on a wet track.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling privileged😊. Thanks for trusting me Mrs King Parrot. https://t.co/ksAZ6S3USv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heatherewart1 thanks for a great series, full of heart. Roll on Series 2. Towns will be lining up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWallace00 great article mate. Happy new year from Thredbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickieLeeJones HNY to you from Canberra, Australia,- still remember you Naked Songs show here as a great night. Fair winds for 2016.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>