<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“All of them had a life and a story that Europe cannot ignore.” There are refugees in Europe that need our help too https://t.co/4aFnGmA6x6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’ve just tested the country’s willingness to capitulate to a fascist regime". This is terrifying - https://t.co/MynUVl5jrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So MP Nicholas Soames, grandson of Churchill, 'woofed' at Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh in the commons.Old boys' club indeed. https://t.co/r0UNdsuZPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's musical protest - Straight to Hell by The Clash https://t.co/xfxBEbSs6r sampled by M.I.A in Paper Planes https://t.co/eJra64RQW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just going to leave this here: https://t.co/SlJikB7DzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's 8.5% of all eligible to vote at the last election, and 12% of all those who voted in the 2015 gen election.… https://t.co/3ZMa1BkYmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funding opportunity for those working in hums/social science including independent researchers (good job, @_ISRF) https://t.co/RuLsSaTgW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI yesterday, these are my three reasons why/how romance is political https://t.co/VHrPo2ysIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mayak46 @CLAficionado @camillehjones Oh yeah, all kinds of gender ickyness still going on in many cat romances (although improving).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care about the Queen &amp; not sure it will stop Trump's visit, but if only to register my disgust I've signed: https://t.co/74wlUDxwdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romance IS political - some thoughts inspired by @camillehjones https://t.co/VHrPo2ysIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nufanglenesse ...make the same distinctions between research and teaching/learning development that we do (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nufanglenesse I wonder about this too, not least in organisation of my department (which contains both). Not sure academics... (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After @camillehjones' thread yesterday, here's a blog post of my thoughts on how romance is political https://t.co/VHrPo2Q46Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jontymartin Spot on! Great job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was thinking this exact thought this morning... https://t.co/xXHuWGzjED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jontymartin Actual date is 1878 if you want to show off with some reverse Roman numeral wizardry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're trying to remember roman numerals to figure out the publication date information in this old book #archiveproblems @natlibscot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you teach @EdinburghUni I'd recommend this workshop!  https://t.co/wkwtFiEPT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread: romance is political (I've argued as much for sheikh romance). https://t.co/0IdrdVoweS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez this is so messed up. https://t.co/3F2ZsLr8Lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup yup - several times over. https://t.co/F1krxljOaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling angry but powerless? Here's something we can do. https://t.co/PFIVuFnNAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think exactly this when the UK insists it 'can't take any more refugees'. https://t.co/DLzqRBRWM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uniteforeurope That's great, thanks for sharing, but LDN still a long way to go. Given pro-EU support in Scotland, a march here make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted in a 1944 novel by Helen Douglas Irvine in @natlibscot that meets "authorized economy standards". https://t.co/IYDCp9ovcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweeted about this before - it looks terrific!  https://t.co/eqohZamyLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out with these gals @natlibscot #romance #scotland #scottishauthors https://t.co/vwkC2ibMKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What made those marches so big (collectively and individually) is that there was one happening near to everyone. Activism needs to be local.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Brexit march by @uniteforeurope is a good idea, but I think we need local marches to capture #womensmarch size and energy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uniteforeurope Any plans for marches in other cities? Edinburgh? Glasgow? Manchester? London's pretty far (and expensive) for many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great post from @DrLauraVivanco  https://t.co/8DZTHlnYYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrLauraVivanco @natlibscot Having just tried it with 2 colleagues on our carpeted office floor I can confirm a smooth surface is preferable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In further archive exercise news, the action these women do at 00:23 is my new signature dance move https://t.co/i9uUD2lWQV @natlibscot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MARVELLOUS 1953 silent film from Scottish government on 'Fitness for Women' "to help smart young girls of 20 or 25" https://t.co/nIkFPsyP8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not an expert on this but these folks probably are and they seem worried about UK government leaving #EURATOM (… https://t.co/7eIoX5xVZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timeshighered It wasn't always easy to point out where we'd gone wrong, but I learned SO MUCH from the process (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dramyburge @timeshighered We published a reflection on our methodology for a research project (1/2) https://t.co/ovrJq4Clax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @timeshighered piece on research mistakes made me think about how we reflect on what goes wrong with research https://t.co/ImaOrSjQRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all medievalists (esp. POC) who want to publish on race/ethnicity in the Middle Ages &amp; medievalisms! https://t.co/sxeNAlk12T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching gender studies this year? This site (with videos, book, and a teaching guide) is very helpful: https://t.co/o0pFaN9Gkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsmith_edi @guardian Exactly. It even sounds a bit like the medieval advice I've been researching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The employer guidelines at the bottom of this article on dress code discrimination are awful.

https://t.co/CDemeZZUjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day early #BurnsNight tights #thisishowacademicsdress https://t.co/hDr2CLPz5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I long for the day when it's no longer this easy to write a piece on children and gender stereotyping https://t.co/osMZYrKJhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, hadn't heard about this (but probably should have). Time to rethink my digital footprint? https://t.co/jWg23MXisR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinburghUni #FutureTeacher events look great! Flipped classroom, videos, digital assessment and more https://t.co/xmwebSWWYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities Only works for those students who get to see their originality reports, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities It helped demystify TII (as 'plagiarism detector') &amp; pointed to where students cld synthesise &amp; paraphrase their own work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trouble in the archives - this event in London tomorrow looks great https://t.co/nxiTFe4vFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities At current institution I made an online course with colleagues using Turnitin originality reports to improve #acwri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities I have in the past - 1st year UG module on writing for mgmt students. I learned a lot about Teaching essay writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities Well it depends what the problem is, but reading and dissecting the work of others to see how it is constructed is helpful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. I mean, it's not as if history has already made that obvious or anything... https://t.co/8xkFfsuKjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities Literature to education (still with a gender focus). I work in educational development now which seems like a bridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities I started in literature, and moved to Women's Studies. I now consider myself first a gender person and second medievalist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WetheHumanities I'm thinking seriously about a discipline switch mainly in order to widen job prospects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent collaborative count for #WomensMarch numbers - I just added an estimate for the Leeds march I was on! https://t.co/qrRun4upL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem for many post-PhDs is that unis often play it safe and don't want *actually* interdisciplinary staff bu… https://t.co/kgoipTXBmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Important to remember how it felt to be part of this and what it means to so many of us. https://t.co/AWPHf8jj8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great charity, not least because the excellent @doberina works there!  https://t.co/ZtrlqGAM2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headlines like this give me the shivers. Didn't think (but hoped) I'd see this in my lifetime #WomensMarch  https://t.co/WuDWbtFbVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My personal favourite #WomensMarch Leeds https://t.co/NBhBCbv9Ig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double urgh. And can we also stop with the whole science vs Humanities thing please? https://t.co/66IPG9LhLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said it before and I'll say it again - https://t.co/b8oMgCThvy.TY. https://t.co/cjaNnQJSWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thestooshie @SamIAmRyan Clearly thinly veiled political commentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thestooshie @SamIAmRyan It's just all the words you say that refer to it instead ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this mean women have shaped only 15% of 'modern Britain' then? Can we claim the nice bits? https://t.co/nwwjIurXkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice bit of data visualisation here - Women only said 27% of the words in 2016’s biggest movies:… https://t.co/kcvZp6JOOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on Twitter after a little relaxation in Lisbon - this is a lovely post from @menysnoweballes about what… https://t.co/tkkNMLfowA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to self - do not schedule two meeting presentations and a three-hour workshop for the first day back after a holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty accurate representation of what I've been doing for the last 5 days. https://t.co/BiuIAcr5Pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thestooshie @paulhorrocks @gregtyler @NathanaelSmith I feel our Resistance playing is tense enough already...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coree_Brown She really is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely thoughtful of Manchester Airport to provide the snow that will really highlight the contrast with Lisbon. https://t.co/yiGH92vSiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, my heart: https://t.co/l7ZJx59Rg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classy work snacks. Or, as my office mate @NeilLent puts it, 'vegetarian mussels'. https://t.co/kJ4dezjA3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired by @emselinger - Here by Robert Creeley:
  What
  has happened
  makes
   
  the world. 
  Live 
  on the edge,
   
  looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no such thing as 'only makes tea' in my book. https://t.co/uyj60u8JL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up with followers - my gosh, you're an interesting bunch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duolingo seriously underestimates the number of days in my wine week. https://t.co/lPCPvo0xaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-women shortlists to genocide in three sentences?! A thrill ride indeed. https://t.co/odcos4lBcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh this is going to be great! The Disability in Romance Project
https://t.co/5rawJSKfww Good job @riacheyne !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. Isn't this what, ahem, LIBRARIES are for?! https://t.co/6CyLSPBFA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs, Ms, or Dr becomes a whole lot more important when combined with gender, race, sexuality. Great blog post. https://t.co/4mFlTeCGJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrLauraVivanco @natlibscot Not quite this time! Some amazing books, though. All will be revealed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarashinton Koala definitely edges it for me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Friday night, and this researcher has finished her day job and heading for the @natlibscot #researchlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooray! My PhD (and now book) are also on this. Great to see an EETS volume finally! https://t.co/H886kR02x2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome stuff from @RosemaryLHill as usual. https://t.co/HF19PrelWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't really about "the myth of romantic love" as the title claims but about interactions online vs in person: https://t.co/by0XMxGIPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um, yeah, I've been doing this for years (along with lots of others I would guess). https://t.co/nNMyIhR6zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder I've been feeling unproductive and stressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've recently come to realise that I'm trying to maintain the research output expected of a full-timer while unpaid and working another job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is actually very good advice. Be productive and look after yourselves in 2017! https://t.co/lZ9jkePXqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is cool. Even more so cos it's a collaboration between teacher and students #collab4life https://t.co/efkKJu6oxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the end of my first day back at work since the holidays and there are just 7 emails in my inbox. SEVEN. And now I'm going home #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hadn't really thought about it before but this is a VGP (very good point). https://t.co/vAjESUy0fS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Candlelight, beer, and @brassgumbo at the Cellar Monkey equals an excellent NYE Eve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK the bit where Ronnie O'Sullivan falls over offers some light relief.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>