<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nauru overrules Australia over decision to transfer sick pregnant refugee https://t.co/YXscYbrUWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says Trump gave him personal assurance of refugee resettlement deal https://t.co/I20E77K1bg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House confirms US will take 1,250 refugees under Australian deal https://t.co/7JBNovWWzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rac_sydney @heldavidson Secs can uphold existing int agreements if they choose, but not obliged to. Doesn't exempt MI-N cohort from bans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rac_sydney @heldavidson I can't say I agree: there is no exception for MI and Nauru cohort to be exempted from bans. The clause says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rac_sydney @heldavidson It's no carve-out at all. There is no obligation for Secs to accept refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rac_sydney @heldavidson top of clause:may jointly determine to admit individuals... as refugees on a case-by-case basis,in their discretion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbenjaminlaw @stephharmon @gabriellecj @georgiedent @lucykateclark First they came for the cappuccino drinkers, and I said nothing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US could resettle zero refugees from Manus and Nauru and still 'honour' deal https://t.co/7obOzjmpxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee sent to Manus Island as a child seeks asylum in Fiji https://t.co/WegWtVxmyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US refugee deal grows shakier by the day. Turnbull must find a humane way forward | Daniel Webb https://t.co/tA2J5DxWX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors plead for pregnant refugee on Nauru to be moved to Australian hospital https://t.co/6XX7hzyLei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manus Island asylum seeker charged with rape https://t.co/WcrvsaI4Ve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aziz is The Messenger: one man's story @behindthe_wire on Manus Island. Extraordinary podcast from @michaelbgreen https://t.co/IsPq6duAQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MelissaLDavey chooses to understand, rather than pillory, Melbourne's homeless. Fine journalism: https://t.co/igngT2RAvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aziz is The Messenger,an autobiography in instalments from @behindthe_wire on Manus.Brilliant podcast @wheelercentre https://t.co/IsPq6duAQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-Australia refugee resettlement deal appears to be proceeding - US official on Manus - interviews next month: https://t.co/nYNoSeIV6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Jacinta the not-very-good-at-embezzling numbat' is my new favourite @firstdogonmoon character. Brilliant Dog: https://t.co/kvUvXdZ65N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacularly profligate @DIBPAustralia spent $2.2 billion on offshore detention without authorisation: auditor says https://t.co/laYZTdllFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manus Island refugee who had breakdown found 'hungry and homeless' https://t.co/byCFRNwDYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewhdean It is a truth universally acknowledged that a young man in possession of sound front-foot technique must be in want of a ton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PNG minister defends Manus Island police accused of assaulting refugees https://t.co/bGqQk4rGbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Before I came here I was scared': Karen refugees find a haven in Victoria - lovely piece from @Callapilla https://t.co/PmcPRnTx1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian refugees on Manus allegedly assaulted by PNG police https://t.co/ZR9ondhPd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee pleaded with doctors on Manus Island for help before his death https://t.co/pSV0psj058]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lizpennell Us with not a word of Turkish, they with no English: they were perfectly gracious. Strange match-should have gone 2 Galatsaray!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamid Kehazaei's risk of 'life-threatening systemic infection' 'didn't paint a picture of urgency' to @DIBPAustralia https://t.co/cYXAveOJJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@murpharoo off the long run over Frydenberg's craven capitulation: searing and spot on... https://t.co/3uhPIwz9Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamid Kehazaei left critically-ill on Manus Island because @DIBPAustralia official didn't check emails for 13 hours https://t.co/kR0jDOjbAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email to @DIBPAustralia to move critically-ill Hamid Kehazaei wasn't read for 13 hours while he grew sicker on Manus https://t.co/Pk2C2k44HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disagreement, dysfunction, and the missed emails in @DIBPAustralia . How Hamid Kehazaei got left on Manus: https://t.co/Pk2C2k44HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamid Kehazaei inquest told immigration bureaucracy left asylum seeker stranded extra day https://t.co/YYPIJjJ0pL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeniport A glass full with sparklers coming out the top! Tell Mr Tippet thank you very very much, most grateful. Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumitaguchi Thank you very much for your kind words and generous support. I'm most grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sister_ratched Thank you enormously, I'm grateful to you and thank you for supporting The Guardian's work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@della79 Thanks Dela - you're too, too kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BObservatory Thank you, you are very kind. I'm grateful the story resonated with readers and people felt it was important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamid Kehazaei inquest: faulty machine ruled out use of vital drug https://t.co/V1H87cPB6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DIBP officials routinely ignore medical advice on detainees, inquest into asylum death told: https://t.co/S1kdOBnNHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus immigration officials routinely ignore medical advice on detainees, inquest told https://t.co/W1KAlmBLwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian immigration officials routinely ignore medical advice on detainees, inquest told https://t.co/S1kdOBnNHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DIBP delayed critically-ill Kehazaei's move from Manus, despite 4 Drs agreeing he needed to be flown off 'urgently'https://t.co/0dl66Ju2rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where will I send my poems now? https://t.co/f3XlRHniQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pox on both your houses: rise of the populists. Great insight (and lovely writing) @LachlanFHarris &amp; @Charlton_AB  https://t.co/2WGQTpvCUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shifting sands of the semantics of asylum - terrific insight from @miriamcosic https://t.co/tjtNqcAfZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Existence of 'pivotal' letter from Scott Morrison on boat turnbacks revealed https://t.co/zXqWXKKqgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamid Kehazaei coronial inquiry underway. Paramedic who treated him giving evidence. Kehazaei's last tortured days: https://t.co/mGrNRRzh0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day my friend Hamid Kehazaei died: Behrouz Boochani https://t.co/iXg7AuorZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Manus, Hamid Kehazaei had to clean excrement from the body of another asylum seeker : no-one else caring for him: https://t.co/mGrNRRQRRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tortured final days of Hamid Kehazaei on Manus Island. The coronial inquest into his death begins today: https://t.co/mGrNRRQRRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Castro’s legacy: how the revolutionary inspired and appalled the world https://t.co/9QGWvqcjnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fadwadaniens Thanks for your interest, hope you find it interesting/useful. All best, Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fadwadaniens Hey Nicola - this is the link to my Oxford paper. Can download here: https://t.co/YMXvMXbevw (or at the second link I sent b4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fadwadaniens https://t.co/qPhKaQwOXK and https://t.co/moUXItimtx Happy to send specific articles if there are any you're looking for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian gov't admits it is relying on evidence obtained by torture to detain an asylum seeker for four years: https://t.co/zvFkIutZ6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian government concedes evidence against asylum seeker was obtained by torture https://t.co/U027spSN7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theatres and presidents... not always 'safe and special' places. Lincoln had a terrible time. https://t.co/xHnwIaPTpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific column @murpharoo - what becomes of the fourth estate in a post-fact world https://t.co/NwABQHSLCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7piliers and the sun has not come out this morning...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prescient sign on wall of Brooklyn hipster bar. https://t.co/aTPJ3l4VZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration official says department is 'freezing' release of documents about Nauru https://t.co/wchgRS9NmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlJazSydANDREW G'day mate -belatedly- good to meet you the other night. Flick me a note when you've a chance and we'll catch up. Anon, Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielhurstbne @walkleys G'day old chap! Thanks for the good wishes, we'll see how we go at the big dance. How's things over there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors freed to speak about Australia's detention regime after U-turn https://t.co/IEdNAW6zXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia will not support negotiations to outlaw nuclear weapons https://t.co/3TPagVlEsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willfully blind to the damage of offshore detention: https://t.co/H2IDsOF9A5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heldavidson Not holding breath... how many different ways can we say it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's refugee policy is one of deliberate harm. And there's no claiming 'we didn’t know' | Ben Doherty https://t.co/aJB64KMpEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian woman with family on Nauru pleads for end to offshore detention https://t.co/Z4Nwl4SQ9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wilson Security hired investigator to find sources of stories about detention centres https://t.co/WbDD7DWLwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia 'coercing' refugees back to countries where they face persecution/torture, Manus I staff tell @GuardianAus https://t.co/4rQI4db98X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It’s simply coercion': Manus Island, immigration policy and the men with no future https://t.co/P8b9vFbywi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Communication guide' given to detainees at #Manus Island detention centre today - Centre to close, deportations lo… https://t.co/0RIfVqVW8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says secure borders vital for public support of immigration: UN Sec-Gen condemns Border Force secrecy: https://t.co/IcJ3vcA4fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nauru refugee who set herself alight 'denied basic social support' in Brisbane hospital https://t.co/eruPxPcTX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly leaked Nauru reports detail harrowing accounts of sexual abuse and self-harm https://t.co/PAgZoLrGQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nauru refugee denied emergency evacuation after suspected heart attack https://t.co/9dbmXyi1dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The false dichotomy of the 'bad' and the 'good' refugee. Powerful and poignant from Shukufa Tahiri #DearAustralia https://t.co/doRVXdbjjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Australia: Sandy Walker, the sprinter who ran from war – video https://t.co/OwfufqL7Wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexPigot @PDSutherlandUN Why most refugees don't go far (typically countries next door) - intend one day to go home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WilsonSecurity joins @ferrovial and @broadservices in abdandoning offshore detention. None want more contracts: https://t.co/SEVuiJcRPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wilson Security to withdraw from Australia's offshore detention centres https://t.co/TpNo0mlFyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retired judge, 88, offers 'body swap' with a refugee on Manus or Nauru https://t.co/a9tdw4vKLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trenthornibrook Repeated par was actually my email to subs who'd queried. V lucky I didn't swear (so often contaminates my correspondence)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trenthornibrook Ooh yes-I see now. Subs asked for a clarification of that par and somehow it got repeated in production. Shall fix. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The remarkable story of the @lesmurraySBS https://t.co/HVbsiLktso - &amp; for more, Mark Davis's most excellent mission: https://t.co/ybqE2xrBwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeySlezak pretty solid effort for the rapid file at 11pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sophiemcneill @DatelineSBS @lesmurraySBS Yes, have seen it, like everything Mark Davis does, it's bloody good. Compelling story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lesmurraySBS knew a people-smuggler once, a young man called Julius who risked his life to give others freedom: https://t.co/HVbsiL2SAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['What kind of country is it we're trying to protect?' The inimitable @lesmurraySBS , a former refugee on borders https://t.co/HVbsiL2SAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miriamcosic locked and loaded. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nauru files provide the evidence. Malcolm Turnbull can never plead ignorance | William Maley https://t.co/ZhDaK7F230]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zaki Haidari and the transformative power of education. His story of coming to Australia so he could go to school: https://t.co/GOsAqLALQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayne_hay reply, been hectic). Hope you're well too mate. Doubtless, we'll cross paths again somewhere, someday. All best &amp; thks again Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayne_hay Hello mate, thanks for the kind words and support - it's been heartening to see the story resonate with people (apols for slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pussyethics Follow me so I can DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the Nauru files, how can Australia go about ending offshore detention? https://t.co/qN4Vc51gTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don Dale to the Nauru files: political response to the outrages couldn't be more different https://t.co/WV4bApYmh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WilsonSecurity had name &amp; position of guard who hit 5yo girl, but told Senate it could not ID him #naurufiles https://t.co/tuDFI940DA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WilsonSecurity regularly downgraded reports of sexual assault, self-harm and violence in #naurufiles @GuardianAus  https://t.co/hXRl2HWiAY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>