<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ @paulbrislen @JBHiFiNZ Same - the guys at the Albany store helped me last time - give them a call :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks #nzsecretsanta! Great choices, and thanks for putting the card in too :) https://t.co/O9KbDN66Iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaS_JBnz @JBHiFiNZ Did you have any luck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaS_JBnz @JBHiFiNZ sounds good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBHiFiNZ @AnnaS_JBnz any chance you could help me out? I was sent a standard reply, which didn't work, and no further reply..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBHiFiNZ I'm getting nowhere fast with your online team, trying to pay for an order with a combo of gift card and credit card.. help?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg we won!!!!! So exciting!! :D #nzsecretsanta @MurrayJulez @ShaunFisherNZ @Aimee_Tweets_ https://t.co/78FK54lrXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like reading books, listening to music, and creative writing. I like presents that make my brain work.. #nzsecretsanta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nzsecretsanta I like jet plane lollies but I'm not sure whether I want them as a present]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling a little to think of ideas for #nzsecretsanta :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for #nzsecretsanta! Now I need to get sleuthing and figure out the ideal gift :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be the 108,474th human on @BackerKit for Fidget Cube: A Vinyl Desk Toy | Thx @antsylabs! https://t.co/evg0dZECkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ @MurrayJulez @MissSNZ @ShaunFisherNZ @shugz3809 @BasedSebs so exciting!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ @MissSNZ @ShaunFisherNZ @shugz3809 @BasedSebs @MurrayJulez absofreakinglutely!! :D it's gonna be awesome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/YpjXd9qH76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurrayJulez Nawww, I'm quite fond of you too! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come along, take a look at our sky through telescopes, and support Child Cancer fundraising! https://t.co/CD7tvL4cvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a walk to the Jack's Point lighthouse to do some aerial mapping in 2D and 3D, and I took some photos... https://t.co/tFknj8G2vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Cancer Survivor Day.
Can I ask a favour?? Just a few of you will do it, and I know who you possibly are.... https://t.co/zeUMc0gmXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried some autonomous flying on Saturday with Robert and Heather, aimed at using a predetermined flight plan to... https://t.co/3WfRSAB6Vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay it's finally happening!!! https://t.co/7qZFgFxgdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ombsg #winter https://t.co/6k711XXTlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMBSG #winter https://t.co/mriGrlgWy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMBSG #winter https://t.co/ewjGdqVMuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duxMike Would you still have a copy of the presentation you made to MUM NZ 2015 about EoIP bonding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaymentExpress Having any issues with NZ services at the moment? 0800 PAYMENT seems to be down and we have POS Client's not working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelegood_nz you're welcome :) awesome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelegood_nz Welcome to Twitter ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAXfocus Hey guys! Need a hand with Cryptowall 3.0 for a client using LogicNow RM - not getting any response on support lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ yep :) doesn't bode well for my sleeping patterns though :) glad Night n' Day and Pizza Hut were open though :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ :( that's not good
In other news, I woke up just in time to get a thickshake :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xCoLeZx @Aimee_Tweets_ Some marathons are so worth it :) #OneTreeHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a fly this afternoon to take images of Gleniti with Robert, Shaun, and Josh :) http://t.co/iCuiOUs0wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DJIKnowledge Use of Epson Moverio BT-200 Glasses with DJI Pilot app on Android, with the @DJIGlobal #Inspire1 - https://t.co/CnuTINe4Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of Epson Moverio BT-200 Glasses with DJI Pilot app on Android, with the @DJIGlobal #Inspire1 - https://t.co/CnuTINe4Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Not sure but I certainly had a headache when I left work today :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ I think it's because they're harder to discern - we feel what we feel, without clear reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@facebook is back :) bye for now @twitter :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many people will call emergency this time :/ #facebookdown
#1stworldprobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's going to town :p #facebookdown #instagramdown
Great for @twitter though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st World Problems :p #facebookdown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@facebook is trending but not in a good way :/ #facebookdown
https://t.co/zZ1A8OVz9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a rare sight :/ #facebookdown http://t.co/4nUir4Hznf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite unusual to not be able to use @facebook messenger :/ #FacebookDown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to tweet :p @Facebook is down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ That's good then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ They really need to fix their issues :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ lol sounds typical - never know how smart cars actually are these days :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ Nope you're not :) The trick is to realise while near a town/city ;) So far I haven't failed at this :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ I do that too :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ yea I know what you mean! We had a 7 hour wait to see a doctor last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Aww here's a photo of my line to cheer you up :p
@ShaunFisherNZ it's my first ever line :p http://t.co/0epGql5Ijq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ Yay for thermometers :) thanks for the thought :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ At least you have a sense of humour :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 10 will be a free upgrade for Windows 7 and 8.1 users http://t.co/v5udq1yrck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing battery life from my OnePlus One #OPO http://t.co/mxsLDgMlyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Yep it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Yea I know the feeling - I guess its important to step back and remember what really matters :/ depends on the thoughts tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Yep they are :/ Any thoughts in particular?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2015 is getting an extra second and that's a bit of a problem for the internet http://t.co/jkzv2Zv6iR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Spread Those Facebook Copyright Takedown Posts http://t.co/UAdXINczEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ I guess that's not as bad then. Still annoying though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Yep it does. Guess it depends whether it's deliberate :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ I think it's the heat. I woke up at 6 and can't sleep, so I'm going into town anyway :) :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ yep it does :( I've had chest pain issues recently too, it's not pleasant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Tweets_ Sounds good to me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best wishes to everyone for 2015! :)
Do your best to achieve any New Years resolutions you may have made :) I... http://t.co/9jSwilri6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twentyfurbabies stuck in the traffic jam? I think we're at 30 minutes so far :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the annual Caroline Bay traffic jam :) :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great fireworks at Caroline Bay for #NYE :) http://t.co/S57We6vX4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year everyone :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, who's going to be at the bay tonight for New Years? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A well written Christmas message to all Scouts in NZ, from Kelly, the most outgoing and positive National... http://t.co/Rw3MCjyHNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heather and Robert gave me a quadcopter :D http://t.co/oNP0rg1iCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntelliPathNZ thanks to you guys and gals for building a great service!
MAX 2014 was awesome, a really valuable learning experience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrostew Merry Christmas to you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone! 󾌵]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the family bach down at the Waitaki Mouth :)
Got reasonable coverage through Vodafone New Zealand :) http://t.co/xIlWaFwdd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christchurch quake survivor restores church organ http://t.co/c5xovmhl3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch us decorate the house for Christmas at JibJab! http://t.co/jJg7cLt2Sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GFI has published another useful blog post, this time about file system permissions :) http://t.co/4IfxJqzzE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunFisherNZ @Uber_Auckland Great to see that they care about their customers :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@powershop Your service sounds awesome, but I see that it's not available in Timaru at this time :(
Any plans to expand to new areas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some songs just make me want to dance :D
It's collaborative! Add songs that make YOU dance!
http://t.co/p5538DN6UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome movie :) — watching Step Up: All In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great post that explains the various permission models in general terms, and explains principles governing... http://t.co/iV4BvK3ijn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everykey: No more Keys. No more Passwords. http://t.co/j8WNsGmJ0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excerpt of my favourite part of this article - I can relate to it, particularly the idea of always searching... http://t.co/Y2wKDiPgTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Hollywood-caliber drone comes to a smaller, more affordable package http://t.co/gAfkTMd8FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bluetooth 4.2 is faster, safer, and lets lightbulbs connect to the internet http://t.co/OnkgQd6act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twentyfurbabies Good idea, but I'm renting and can't have pets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An awesome photo of the Horsehead Nebula :) http://t.co/vCcOc45ugn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a nice walk around Glenwood tonight :) Bit lonely walking alone though :/
Probably going to walk every night from now on :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a MikroTik User Meeting (MUM) in New Zealand! :D http://t.co/nVfMDqsrLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnxlove I think it depends on frame of mind on a given Monday. I'm having an awesome day so far :) Hopefully your day gets better :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwitubby @SamCallander @ChorusNZ Glad you're enjoying your UFB Helen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how's everyone in #gigatowntim this morning? I'm having a great day so far at @VettaTech :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What lies ahead for drones? http://t.co/iKEeCfbEt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancer's a bitch.
Listening and talking to someone is an priceless opportunity to make their life just a little... http://t.co/nZBqjeNs2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying All Of The Stars
Ed Sheeran • The Fault In Our Stars: Music From The Motion Picture on #Spotify http://t.co/x9sVwHqGzO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>