<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[starting with the "bad dude' doing this https://t.co/CFpuIc8b6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really needed https://t.co/Svm4SqhTDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and all my fears right there... welcome to the 2018 hunger games...
https://t.co/sO0YSB8qm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, bye, bye Disney and HP parks, and Hawaii. Seems I won't be travelling that way for a while. https://t.co/07W7Mjge4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0.o https://t.co/esRrcjBhaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; there's go another Driving Miss Daisy kinda of Oscar https://t.co/qeBHVfDxyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems the actual attitudes of America didn't change much. Land of promise for a selected few 😕 https://t.co/Lj86vt8O0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and that is the real problem. https://t.co/qBfQHyksJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the world turns and turns https://t.co/pR0q36E38c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[need a time turner and more patience than I have at the moment :-P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much feelings and thoughts and so hard to translate them into words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the good people really go for it. It's getting harder and harder to chose the least awful https://t.co/c2cy3bv9mP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When that slacker starting acting all hard$%* to impress the new boss...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my options of contra-attack might me consider politically incorrect https://t.co/83MtxaSFve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#faceinthings @facesPics There's an owl parked at my door https://t.co/YG2tMkUdJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally understood that all those terms fun real estate adds really mean silent auction. You just don't know what you against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to consider the world without this country. Maybe we could just go on making new deals and working towards a n… https://t.co/jD8VW93FPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not the person you think it is. https://t.co/RBWFczi8P1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0.o https://t.co/A8PIPpyLE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They keep using that word (honesty). I don't think it means what they think it means. https://t.co/T2DK5SpoN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#planesthoughts #whenwifiisback Where did they get those brace positions they show on planes' security videos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#planesthoughts #whenwifiisback the crotch check flight attendants do to see if you're using seatbelt can be weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so pump up that isn't even funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freaking out. As in don't know what I gonna to to fit all in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danipohlod welcome home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0.o https://t.co/QJ8ll3VvVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danipohlod I gowith 'yeah, yeah' and stop listening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone put together photos of men whose careers suffer after they were accused of abuse. So sad that this is the r… https://t.co/tteCnxDzAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If more politicians risk pregnancy there would be less discussion and dismissiveness of birth control. Everywhere. https://t.co/IYOflJcN9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about teaching men not to do it instead of asking women to avoid it? https://t.co/GNFdkisdCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behaviour tests also should be administrated. :-P https://t.co/vp5SLHpn49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read this as a story about in-house production, non dependence of imported material. What about globalization? https://t.co/GgMovKyXAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been working hard these last years to get to this point. No more excuses, no more fear. Just do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is that the fan film is better than what Paramount and NBC are doing. https://t.co/j4GCdQ4sFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locked.outside work.i think they didn't renew my access permit
 🤔😑]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early morning grumpiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to mention all the babies and toddlers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for my luck from my 6 flights, I had a big guy sit by my side in 5 of them. Space is a luxury that don't come often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time I'll Goa ahead and bring my bags with me like everyone else. 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ  already seen T least 4 other people with 2, or more, bags boarding. Not so forcefully enforced rule, huh 🤔😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You made me checkin my cabin bag, @FlyAirNZ . If I seen anyone with two bags in the plane, I'll be pissed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm back in kiwiland! 🤣😎😊😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New area for Rio's airport is quite good with lounge and everything. Air-conditioning still loses to the heat though. Service is so-so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe "man who confronted police dies from injuries" is better? https://t.co/mCAWiuyT2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st time since I arrived that is possible just to sit by the window &amp; not die.from the heat. I'm leaving the afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windy in Auckland? She should try Wellington..:-p https://t.co/uotER6ObZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's nice to be pleasantly surprised. I expected a repeat of the last drag. It was actually really good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many things I would like to say but my mother would probably want to wash my mouth afterwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My days are like a rollercoaster: hours comatose bc of the.heat and stress filled moments running after bureaucratic solutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being awhile I didn't feel as out of place as I have been feeling these last days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely disgusted with the bureaucracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creepy hands https://t.co/FscT7ezV98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How it should be https://t.co/m2dZGUFmmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elidanz not a chance. The only time. Went to the beach it was night. :-p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elidanz nice! Happy #newyear! Envious of the mild weather. Here is like being in a microwave on high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#copacabana #newyear #fireworks #riodejaneiro #2017 https://t.co/Ufj0qg4k6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#newyear #copacabana #riodejaneiro if you are in the town, you must go. I think it's the law. https://t.co/Myx9JFucGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impossibility of feeling comfortable is the biggest issue with this thing people call summer  and I call microwave for people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson so sorry. He's memory will keep guiding you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice but some of those milestones were from 2015. Seems 2016 is still a bit of a.naughty year https://t.co/uoUaNbBRG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another one... https://t.co/EiZ2tk2g20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double.wham. 2016 is going for the record. https://t.co/demZ0NSWH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hate those. Not journalism at all. https://t.co/jhUgQovtZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double wham https://t.co/rueYODVeT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a little afraid to bring attention to him... https://t.co/DTUFFVignQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT without comments. Because what can we say about this? https://t.co/hGtUrVmrc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And let's hope 2016 do all it needs to do this last week. No tainting early 2017!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One can only hope https://t.co/UoHJUymt1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jetlag or the weather, I'm sleeping better after lunch than at night. But it does my day out of shape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elidanz right back to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hate when I'm sure I have something but can't find it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicer planes but bus and and stairs in the middle of the airstrip?! Thought this was long gone. 2 of my three flights today use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ sad that these delays seemed.to become the norm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unpicking: the one thing that can turn you off of sewing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I never b*$@ed some at as I did this year. Resolution for next year: be pro-active instead of complaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troubling question - Working Daze by John Zakour and Scott Roberts, December 19, 2016 Via @GoComics https://t.co/AxxJhiyVbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard view but some truth in it. If the West interfere, it's messing with their lives, if it doesn't, it's let them… https://t.co/uFItodZNLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a painting. Take a peek inside the Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar https://t.co/MNgGaAUoIY via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RogueOne #rogueoneastarwarsstory Great movie. Loved @K2So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to adopt this https://t.co/miKrkft5RU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, look, Hunger Games is coming to a stream site near you https://t.co/9JskgV25iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me for a moment, while I close the door and you cover your ears: AAAAAAAAAAAARRRRRRRRRGGGGGGGGGGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could run away.... https://t.co/p9m1iZ5vIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all the photos from Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar. Today is gorgeous! https://t.co/MNgGaBbZAw via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaping up to the be a true Wellington summer day. https://t.co/AnDiyUSxHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sshhhh, let's keep it a secret :-P https://t.co/PgGKvKuvPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ tops list of world's best countries https://t.co/3bwGpiu1wM via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[molesworth st building https://t.co/4BcjUi9DsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there's always a strong female character as a counterpart to male ones in all movies https://t.co/pAENCFJaWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it will come to something to something for those responsible. Where we saw that before? https://t.co/8YvZfRo2Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really bad allergies today. Tired of sneezing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a peek inside the Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar https://t.co/MNgGaBbZAw via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of worrying. It seems I'm the only one doing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year has been so shaken that i'm having serious trouble with my balance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pearl Harbour was the reason USA went against the Germany/Japan/Italy in WW2. Not for politics or belief. https://t.co/CqgxBoU9X5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very impatient. As soon as I chose someone's Christmas present I just want to give it and not really wait for the correct date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[know the saying 'you made your bed, now lie on it'? https://t.co/2QtEbKwIXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danipohlod as long as isn't black and blue tomorrow :-s just painful at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marsiaj  and nobody noticed! Good thing, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 1st.: Slipped in the bathtub and bagged my face. I do prefer separate shower for this exactly reason :-(]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>