<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[first day back and i'm greeted by this https://t.co/qEG3V2gQAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow so last night really happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realstevegray Yes mainly witchcraft https://t.co/81Ea7opAY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realstevegray It's all filters babe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns Congratulations!  Awesome news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guy on lambton quay just now in a Marine Le Pen for President t shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[metamorphing hard out in the garden today https://t.co/WVOIry806P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reinvention @Jubbb Christ Joey get a futon already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sold a thing on Trade Me for $25 and spent $23.50 posting it out.  Not sure I'm doing this right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophie_speer I'll bring one of these in for you https://t.co/2pPjGdmR8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got a free cookbook with my BBQ and CHECK IT OUT https://t.co/IQLCB7hv4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richie_thornton at the @snuglounge_np #newplymouth #summer #gaysontour https://t.co/aAF6fpwt0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my favourite neighbourhood cat https://t.co/PxlHXIck4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been in the sun for an hour and I am barely coffee coloured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is my life right now help me https://t.co/uxw9KFqy3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[negronis by the jug!  #NewYearsEve #NewZealand https://t.co/uZsJvyWNhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenThomasNZ Parker Lewis can't lose!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was that a quake or just my hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M__Gibbs i am so very country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[walks around Wellington offer a lot of up and close cow encounters https://t.co/I1wYP9WMUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just at new world and they sold meths to a homeless dude who could barely stand and I don't know how to feel about that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bit of quake demo tourism in Wellington today https://t.co/J7axAqk1Gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching a show about cooking with marijuana and it's called Bong Appetit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaQuishaStR what shall we try next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstevnz by the skin of my teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackGeorgieff @HWilliamsNZ yes that wouldn't be creepy at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWilliamsNZ hear you babes - have been into neighbours garden three times to retrieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWilliamsNZ totally - we just need time to be less shit at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[literally all we're gonna do this summer https://t.co/P9ciTJtx5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellClarkNZ sure did.  and four kinds of cheese beforehand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC this is the best xmas tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST WHAT I WANTED https://t.co/jNw0wj8l28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns early night for us.  we've been caning it all week.  but we'd love to see you both soon :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns sorry we missed your birthday.  had work xmas do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns nothing less babes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES WELLINGTON https://t.co/0mgtJ6TGT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dairymanNZ good work.  i'm making my way through this. https://t.co/P0K0CJHKkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth he will of course being election year but I imagine the reception will be WINTRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if @honbillenglish will front at the Big Gay Out next year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snuew works fine here as in the US :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks @nzpostYouShop for yet another awesome thing https://t.co/sXk9NFDqPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @MetService no sign of it yet! https://t.co/UgD9drcWec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns shameless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[saw these and just had to buy them https://t.co/VQMHrKvOwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrikaRika Mangawhai cliff walk if you can handle the drive north]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[splitting the atom or getting this guy out of bed today both as hard tbh https://t.co/uiB5HSCkuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so we bought a fog machine for the office https://t.co/loRcGH4Qhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicegear just ordered mine - excited to try this out tomorrow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought concealer and I am NOT ASHAMED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstevnz how about we get an outsider to lead the all blacks?  An anti-rugby player.  Drain the swamp and all that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sorry last weeks bananas: didn't work out.  it's all about this week's bananas now. https://t.co/VTaKCqJNey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today is clothes shopping and being asked if I have much planned for the rest of the day like eighty times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key:  
"If Labour loses, Little is finished"
"If we lose, ¯\_(ツ)_/¯"
#MtRoskill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's the People's Party done and dusted #mountroskill #byelection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstevnz everyone encouraging  'michaela' to 'chug']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very drunk party of girls next door all belting out Justin Bieber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington you BRINGIN it today #whywellington #summer https://t.co/fGWjQ0D4pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up with my nieces be like https://t.co/IS5S1ViTNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[government house making a huge racket https://t.co/UuwGtci5vG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf do you need an article or the whole paper?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad:  what would you like to drink - beer or gin and tonic?
Me:  its 9:00am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petergraczer it's ironic seeing how he fled communism 40 years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just opened dads iPad and see he's joined a Ukrainian marriage agency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kaipara Heads from @FlyAirNZ https://t.co/0sXMNH4mHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the only time i ever hear commercial radio is when in an uber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hund_im_Schnee worse if they scream and ran away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is doing the rounds.  It's actually my house and I'm nearly 40. https://t.co/WsplXdjgug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pointoforder part of it is to use their own terminology to delegitimise.  or so they said on MSNBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ easy if you're one dimensional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life in Wellington:
Monday:  Apocalypse
Wednesday:  Hurricane Katrina
Sunday:  Club Tropicana
Next Week: ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ahhmandah did you see what she ordered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_w_burns @justin_lester it's now a thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we call @justin_lester J-LES?  Please can that be a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went to a BBQ in Ngaio and legit there was no 4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sums up this week tbh https://t.co/kvWfVNWdLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh my god this actually happened https://t.co/TIFl5ekrUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adikohler enjoy it while it lasts :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[off home now to make dinner and cause massive aftershock #gayquakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealgregjack this one would borrow the car, wreck it then avoid me for months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlyfrozen take him away.  please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a moody teen cat.  I feed him tonight and he gives me 'I hate everything I wish I was never born' eyes. https://t.co/wHVgN7dPYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JGreenbrookHeld I see yes easy to misinterpret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JGreenbrookHeld its not actually happening.  Why would you make a claim like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack snow leopard and eagle.  sounds like a bad taika waititi film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack snow leopard is pretty badass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JGreenbrookHeld just checked the broadcast and website but nothing there.  Are you sure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planet Earth II and Chill https://t.co/UEj6aCw6rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CateOwen she looks like the love child of Cletus and Avril Lavigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetService ok great but we are TOTALLY owed an amazing summer after this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetService we can totally beat this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[afternoon coffee is now afternoon coffee and whiskey shots #eqnz https://t.co/Ok0tkOZwIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyWxBaker the refugays cleared out but will be back to finish the chianti later today.  Thank you for your ongoing concern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burgers for breakfast.  Because quakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted in Newtown #eqnz https://t.co/ZQAX9JIYhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of bottled water at Countdown.  However there has been a run on brioche buns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC SEND WHISKEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hcirePT if you can tack on a weekend at fafa island its an attractive option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got my building consent!  now to find half a million dollars... https://t.co/Zndcxh1I6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Christ here we go https://t.co/74AmtilNF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellClarkNZ one more poster and i'm sure would have been different]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>