<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamilSam And the tap splashes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's as if fhey've just discovered units https://t.co/TauIIS7Hac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was a great speech today! https://t.co/qFvYeWvlHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama @fakegeoffdellar But if they do (and leave the EU), what can stop them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's deliberate design, isn't it? Trump wants bilateral relationships so US can be relatively "stronger" https://t.co/tMs5Bf1oPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this! You will learn things! https://t.co/xRzNi2BYTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recall a thought experiment during my MA - what would it take for Aus to substantially cooperate or ally itself w… https://t.co/5St4S0lApM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama @NickMGreen And guns. Potato cakes with guns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama @NickMGreen Are you just trying to be the peacemaker between in the potato wars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama @NickMGreen Which is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama @NickMGreen Or potato cake. They're interchangeable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen Potato theory is nuanced and demand careful consideration. Meetings may not be the best forum for considering said theory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen Did they buy it? Are all potatoes mutual substitutes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fraserkendall less for cash!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge Wheel of Decisions! #Fallon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great read https://t.co/cL1hP61jyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davispg @Henry_Belot Or that once there were states without clear territorial borders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esseeeayeenn @WLTaskForce Perhaps Julian could reflect on his role in the US election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @dubiousfeline Love this account!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick Wait till you hit 40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 I try to be honest, in a gentle way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US politics could be mistaken for  dystopian Kim Stanley Robinson sci-fi novel at the moment #KSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocked https://t.co/dF6OThkp3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HumansFirst, not Australia (or any other country) First https://t.co/bVTgWT0K5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And beds and busses! https://t.co/KeKLVr3jqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many math friends are from Iran and other targeted countries https://t.co/axjW9QnypH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisbrereton @WestWingReport Appropriated symbol of the new Trumpian order?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotus plants at the Botanic Gardens #Sydney https://t.co/zqSHS0E26E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manifesto at Art Gallery of NSW is excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerrymandering, voter ID laws, and partisan/inconsistent electoral administration have made it a flawed democracy f… https://t.co/uBBVuDqPHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSHennessy Yes it was! Like nothing else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSHennessy There is much campaign material from unsuccessful candidates!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrysherrell @GeoffPolHist While they 'work out what's happening']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrysherrell @GeoffPolHist You're assuming it's rational!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A shining beacon for the world...' 😳 https://t.co/uyHLEUXtSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astroehlein He probably knows and is using it deliberately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Individual agency! https://t.co/1Gk9wknCR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within the uncertainty of the present https://t.co/gn6tdjRRE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see the SPD has a new leader https://t.co/HzgVigNCjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed seeing Jackie this evening. Great performance and sets/costumes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best you can say about the LDP's Aus Day facebook post is that it's offensive and illiberal. Alternatively, it's racist and offensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow I don't think it will stop Brexit https://t.co/G2bl7owhb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Wham Bam thank you Ma'am - some of the best comedy for ages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting https://t.co/YaOA6BrB5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kymtje Yes! A natural evolution that no-one will blink at within a few years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Day should be moved - it should be inclusive of everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaVisentin @bencubby The bus from southern cross station is pretty good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a human security issue, and one affecting Australia too https://t.co/UBWGDs8E7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistent with AfD's behaviour https://t.co/Xb6HEu3uiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee it's good to listen to Prof Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now speaking on qantum computing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Simmons (UNSW) speaking on the scanning tunnelling microscope in Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JB_AU @williamslachlan I'd never heard of them before 6 months ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Blaxland on security impacts from fall of TPP on @abc730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamslachlan Perhaps they are a self appointed organisation who tweet against the left side of politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But also, some people might be unwell from celebrating on Aus Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the incentives when Thursday's a public holiday? https://t.co/rFundVe4SY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really interesting piece on state ownership of SOEs in China - read it! https://t.co/sHivmnGUV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he also oppose people dating more than one person at a time? https://t.co/e1DlGtFOrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrjoeaston @GladysB @JuliaGillard I saw it across Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful rain in Canberra overnight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick, count them all! https://t.co/TyfAfdGPwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamilSam perhaps - don't think it will work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau I go outside to see slightly crazy weather (e.g. the near-gale a week or two ago), but not all rain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markberman @xayma What do you expect when you have a salesperson as Pres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakegeoffdellar We're on blacks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakegeoffdellar We potted all reds. Now the green]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakegeoffdellar Just potted the yellow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so sad and, frankly, stupid, for an adult man to say. https://t.co/4kCtE8joY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billiards is a hard game to play!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics is definitely not a spectator sport. Get involved if you want to change things!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadenKirgan @smh No - let them waste their money!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree, and ASEAN countries https://t.co/ZavVxmJ9aP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HumansFirst - not "humans in one country" first!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["[my country] first"? No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's an explanation for a bushfire! https://t.co/LdbPpMDf9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time visitinv Barangaroo - v impressed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a report on China's GDP growth. Today I read another story about how one region had falsified its GRP figures. What to believe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the greatest? https://t.co/xAb5s1AVWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We no longer need to carry 10 and 20 cent pieces around with us! https://t.co/JBTzCLdQ0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney, so much rain!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlyxG @cd_hooks Has to be satire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acaderama In a superposition of states?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, throw into the mix the mutual relations among all the Mekong delta countries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damming the Mekong - tradeoffs between food and economic security. Really interesting to research (I did a paper on… https://t.co/mjXS6AhhvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mostly, 'he wasn't realist enough' - but some of the other critiques have strength, especially assuming others were… https://t.co/OnKs37sJeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doublethink? https://t.co/fl29kjGQeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamilSam Some no doubt. Much seems reactive rather than circumspect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profbensaul @bencubby Scientific research about how long whale sized creatures can survive out of water?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGFchairman This may be true for all future years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump attacks Merkel's 2015 move to offer humanitarian asylum to ~million people - says a lot about him https://t.co/8jaUTtYv74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSligar Probably prestige real estate story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfullilove Can we inaugurate Alec Baldwin's Trump on 20 Jan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Human rights' https://t.co/lB98QZU9QS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Country at #Midsumma !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egadheg @swearyanthony 'by the Queen's most excellent majesty...']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egadheg Fine thing to do for a few hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egadheg @swearyanthony Interesting to think about how 'automatic' disqualification provisions are operationalised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a lovely time at #Midsumma. Remembered to wear my hat this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Smoosh, smoosh them together' https://t.co/AHwWW2CtjW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>