<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KoryStamper Shh! I'm trying to take out the chocolate cream of the mausoleum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Japanese candy kit looks fun. Let's run the instructions through Google Translate and ... oh. https://t.co/gu2zJpZB5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucywaverman My first glass of California OJ was a revelation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring can't come soon enough. Neither can Friday. https://t.co/wQtQNQNuQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret's out. Political Blind Date will air on @tvo later this year. #onpoli #topoli #cdnpoli https://t.co/PVX485vPXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to get me to click on an article about particle physics. Well played, @smithsonianmag. https://t.co/XKMxuIvC2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biocuriosity Under the Bus is a decent name for a pub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us on @tvo's current affairs team. Deadline extended till Feb. 3 in case you need a bit more time.… https://t.co/UcBr9sNx70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mom, do you know who Rick Roll is?"
Yes, son. Yes, I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef @balkissoon Forget borrowing. They can keep the sugar, tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I feel a bit better. https://t.co/8flAC1DckC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhh I'd settle for a DM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhh Has @infinite_scream replied to you yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti @shawnmicallef We can huddle by the blazing bonfire I'll make from my pile of New Yorkers and pretend we've read them all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti @shawnmicallef TOO LATE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti @shawnmicallef I never worried about this UNTIL NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef Only half joking. I've got a CD-ROM drive here, too, somewhere. Lord, life before modems. https://t.co/csAuY0sQLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef I can help you out with the G3 power cord. Also, we can put your files on floppies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc I'm trying to picture its stance ... Did it have its right hand on the doorknob?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Meeting those milestones!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a question for @spaikin? He's listening. #tvotheagenda https://t.co/E9D05Znavf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigSilverman @elamin88 You guys just wait until @spaikin starts going through your clips 23 years from now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, a job! Write for @tvo’s current affairs team: https://t.co/0NZlIzOjZR https://t.co/uHmwBY55RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful news to start the year. We'll be hiring soon. https://t.co/yvVtnN18y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattderienzo I'm so sorry for your loss, Matt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dskok @Busta_ The Daveeed is the tricky bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooking up a printer involved the better part of an afternoon, dip switches and possibly tears. https://t.co/UDwdrrUlBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling long-distance on Christmas Day and getting a busy signal because the system didn't have enough capacity. https://t.co/UDwdrrUlBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dayslikethese I still have some of that paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef @ivortossell That's just offal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karenkho @lindseywiebe Such toque in my feed all of a sudden. https://t.co/lsu7yEdpcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this powerful piece by @namshine about what refugees leave behind. https://t.co/gIR8ZpsFbf https://t.co/nLAje9r686]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza @ethiopienne I didn't say it was easy. This thing makes it go way faster, but I was at a cottage. https://t.co/HjdV3DH87I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethiopienne @chantalbraganza Hand mixer, pfft. I've whipped cream with a spoon, a chilled bowl and the strength of sheer desire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Grind 'em up and use in a dessert. Sprinkle on ice cream. Dunk in what-have-you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza @ethiopienne That purple font crime, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethiopienne Sorry! Forgot to copy you: https://t.co/tUKh0mFEpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Tried making my own last year and they turned out like almond-y macaroons. Yum, but not right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Related: why is it so hard to find good amaretti? The kind that are soft in the centre and come in pretty paper? IN A TIN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza @ethiopienne Saw a panettone tiramisu recipe online last night and about died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanmerkley @seriouseats Ha, did these tonight with a lamb roast. Am in a rosemary-garlic stupor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That reminds me, @CraigSilverman, I 🦑miss 🦑 the 🦑 giant 🦑 squid 🦑 news 🦑 of 🦑 yore 🦑.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addarioandrea Aarggh, sorry. I've been putting off checking but turns out mine is a Robot Coupe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@believethewomen Not known to me ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who are wondering, the subway pigeon got off at Rosedale. A woman's foot might have been involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pigeon elected not to disembark at Davisville. Is now trudging toward front of the train. https://t.co/EbVtrtvQo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a pigeon on my subway. A man is sharing his Pringles with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbcurio Do they have those boots in a size 7?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drakefenton @JordanTimm *clicks suspiciously*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgrimbly @lizrenzetti Oh jeez, and I thought the Star carpet was bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimfox Oh boo, you can't see the fox? https://t.co/K9FWcqa2H5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourtière with chicken and mushrooms? What is this -- peas in guacamole redux?
https://t.co/2MMAybfCQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell @nytimes They missed the opportunity to interview ROM ornithologist Mark Peck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@linwood_barclay "It's Complicated" World.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell I'm still miffed about the final episode of Lost. Setting myself up for similar level of dissatisfaction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell And we're the complicit audience/participants? Or we're Victoria/Dolores? Gah, Ivor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you're already a day behind with the advent calendar and have to eat two chocolates to keep up. #holidaystress https://t.co/a0E5Fg4BLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is a vertical vertical? https://t.co/kcHofviEUm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMosco They were literally on my doorstep the day after I saw your strip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMosco No questions from me but I could send you a photo of winter moths in flagrante delicto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti @DougSaunders Congrats to the Architektur-Theoriepreisträger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelEastwood I think I had that sweater in the '80s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s @janicejourno, @stackhousejohn, @CraigSilverman, @jayrosen_nyu,   AND @zeynep. All-star panel, indeed.… https://t.co/by4bFTTwLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juruwolfe I used to love the roll ends. No ink!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addarioandrea @chantalbraganza Produce? Reproduce? I got nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Oh, for the mom-and-pop sock shops of yore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmurrayca So difficult to keep up these days. Don't you dare sing either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coyleWERDZ Same folks have come four years in a row, raising funds for a medical mission. I gave them five bucks, said please don't sing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Christmas carollers knocked on my door a few minutes ago. First overwhelmingly Grinchy reaction narrowly quelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I'm pretty sure that's a drop of blood on the bottom of the envelope. https://t.co/HMZgEEnmfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if this is addressed to me or the coyote. https://t.co/A20WzApXP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillKrajewski @wolfewylie Back up to 3.8M!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wolfewylie Weird. He's back, with 159 followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt Strangely, I find Toronto winters worse. Damp. Unrelentingly grey. At least you get sunshine there, even if your face falls off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt Some nights after edition @ Citizen, one brave soul would go start all the cars. Then we'd wait a bit before the mass scraping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt Gotcha. I grew up soft in Toronto, where block heaters didn't exist. Tires never got square.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt Have you lived through an a Ottawa winter before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use powerful images, advises the American side of this web conference call. Yep. https://t.co/LICM552fs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnLorinc @MaRSDD But it doesn't look short or stout ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, gosh, @CraigSilverman, whatever just happened, I'm really sorry. https://t.co/WjnjCnchWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Nope. My mother-in-law's secret recipe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chantalbraganza Opposite end of the spectrum: Petrify a banana in two easy steps. 1. Put banana in cupboard. 2. Fo… https://t.co/tDjACyIXo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subscribed to two so far today! https://t.co/8LqNFIGbIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef I have inherited all those things. Antimacassars. Fruit nappies. Coins of yore. Hug your mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef ON A DOILY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addarioandrea @CraigSilverman Maybe drink it once the coffee's gone, whatever it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_gee @CraigSilverman @pdmcleod Election SALAD? Well, I never.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigSilverman @erin_gee @pdmcleod What are those tubs of stuff in the foreground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TTC crew member sighs as she exits the train: "Oh, thank gawd that's over."  All righty then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, yes, I *am* tweeting about a birding video. https://t.co/CL877nmReD https://t.co/v44p7zFl9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell @jm_mcgrath Guys, just say you're sourry and make up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_mcgrath Just noticed the stickering of your living space has begun. Got some left over here if you need more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywiebe Really? Give it your best shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywiebe I needed that. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgrimbly I was trying to sound like a timber rattler, Grimbly. &lt;Clicks again, repeatedly&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisanjutras I would rip through the paper with 0.38mm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisanjutras No thoughts on Muji?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisanjutras @DakGlobe @ericalenti @sgrimbly You can click the button threateningly when agitated, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisanjutras @DakGlobe @ericalenti @sgrimbly I saw a Uni-Ball FB thread yesterday, but meh. These sweeties have a retractable tip. No cap.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>