<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Nauru... https://t.co/hWYXjhDDJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TIL that without a strong autonomous women's rights mvmt, countries who ratify #CEDAW go backwards on women's righ… https://t.co/16SoqvBpXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEndrey You should up the odds for the next one: impeached v flees to Russia, freegan v run a marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACFID Responds to foreign policy white paper terms of reference https://t.co/2czBSIpiVn via @ACFID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feminartsy @thebookclubABC @slamup @clementine_ford if Goodwood isn't already on the shortlist for next year, I'd highly recommend it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule @rubyhamad *waves hello*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubyhamad Are these in reference to your article on Castro's death? I thought it was the most intelligent piece I've read in ages - thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust's commitment to #DID through Development for All strategy needs to be backed up with funding through a growing aid prog @SenatorSiewert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens @SenatorSiewert highlights importance of advocacy from orgs like @ADDCnews to ensure disability inclusion in aid #IDPD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bi-partisan commitment to looking fabulous at @ADDCnews video launch as @SenClaireMoore points out @Senator_CFW's dress of Tongan fabric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenClaireMoore acknowledging the leadership of Bob McMullen in championing #DID #idpd2016 @ADDCnews https://t.co/ZlHPpiiSNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister for International Development and the Pacific @Senator_CFW talking about Aust's commitment to disability i… https://t.co/2sNaRq6sdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Parliament House celebrating #IDPD2016 with @ADDCnews. Jackie giving a run down on acronyms #DPO #CRPD #SDGs… https://t.co/iMnkwBRAfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece drawing on NGO research on the unexpected risks of women's economic empowerment to #EVAW… https://t.co/C5QpKdZ6az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erincgillen @maddydell I ranted about white ribbon to my fella this week so he arranged for his office fundraiser to go to @DVCSACT instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workmanalice I can't even tell from the descriptions which of these are serious and which are parodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing from people with disability about their experience of disability inclusive development.… https://t.co/TyyXkB8qFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting read on the need for progressive mvmts to not shy away from calling out bad behaviour amongst our own https://t.co/FuBzSxTYM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's speech ended and a massive hailstorm broke in Canberra. Feels about right. #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyjforster *David Attenborough voice* and here we see the female president in its natural habitat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 4 November, it's 'All systems go' for the Paris Agreement. Let's celebrate the agreement's entry into force! https://t.co/RisT6I2wUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we ask, #MelbourneCup : https://t.co/wEgVPprqUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to stop adding 'and children' or 'and girls' onto the ends of sentences and find integrated approaches @mccann_siobhan #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear from Amihan Abueva about the work of @CRCAsia - using regional forums to enable children's participation #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tools are there to keep us safe in the cyber realm and they work - none of @FarrellPF's sources have been exposed #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both the risks and opportunities of digital tech will only grow from here @StephAmnestyOz #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@archielaw calls for a show of hands: who uses signal? I had to google it: https://t.co/iPM0ffTxhZ #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you collect confidential info on people, you have a responsibility to understand risks and how to protect the info @FarrellPF #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2015 was a bad year for digital privacy, that's why @norton_tim founded @DRWaus #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a comprehensive Human Rights Act, not piecemeal approach to rights @EmilyHowie #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Common response to online misogyny "if you don't like it, log off" is unacceptable; we live online now @EmilyHowie #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open source cyber security is a collaboration challenge, says @StephAmnestyOz #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When orgs don't have adequate email security, staff use personal accounts, transferring risk onto indvs @StephAmnestyOz #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're making a trade off b/n convenience &amp; security; digital activism can have real impact but has security risks @StephAmnestyOz #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austs metadata laws the most invasive of the 5 Eyes countries @EmilyHowie  #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've been asleep at the wheel on changes to metadata legislation, says @EmilyHowie #ACFID2016 No evidence it assists with prosecuting crime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We wouldn't expect to see police trying to expose journalists' sources in a democracy but we are seeing just that @EmilyHowie #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now hearing from @FarrellPF about the real risks faced by whistleblowers and journos exposing situation in Manus and Nauru #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great practical tips on encrypted messaging apps and other digital safety tools from @StephAmnestyOz #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @FarrellPF https://t.co/qBtwYpT8Fy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating discussion on digital rights happening at #ACFID2016 @norton_tim @archielaw @EmilyHowie @AmnestyOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved winner of the @ACFID Media Award @LMARTI, for her series on VAW in PNG #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @ACFID Human Rights Award goes to @GillianTriggs, for her work on children in detention #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BobBrownFndn throwing down the challenge to #ACFID2016: get people on the streets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Brown reflecting on his time in politics: always take a staffer with you to Aussie's or a coal lobbyist will sit opposite you #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you scratch a logger you'll find an environmentalist; if you scratch an egotist you'll find a humanitarian @BobBrownFndn #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You have to take on the people in power, but you don't have to be nasty about it' Advice from @BobBrownFndn to #ACFID2016 @ACFID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aunty Georgina Nicholson wore a platypus pin givn 2 her by @BobBrownFndn for welcome to country today; Bob wearing a matching pin #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a discussion between @BobBrownFndn and @JenBrockie around how to achieve social change #ACFID2016 https://t.co/Sd8Y0AWb7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ausprogress &amp;@ASRC1 research found language used by advocates in this space didn't work - now working to reframe… https://t.co/4DJ23D2rS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kerry_change This is a classic eg of an area where we are waiting for leadership - we need to create urgency now… https://t.co/gMu5npRpN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If govt won't act, we need leaders independent of govt to create change, @TharaniJega https://t.co/zYiXntf7Jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key issue here is that political parties won't act if they think they'll lose power over it; we need to convince th… https://t.co/EGHnOh6Fn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Thom suggests 'transformative scenario planning'; needs to be a cross sector partnership to create authori… https://t.co/AlDwJcYhce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clare Petrie sets the panel a challenge: how can @ACFID members collaborate to implement res'n on offshore detention passed @ AGM #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measuring successful collaboration takes different metrics than success in other areas @TharaniJega #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlikely partnerships have impact: if *those* two are saying it together it must be important @GedKACTU #ACFID2016 @ACFID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@croche123 on advocacy eco-systems: we need insiders AND outsiders, and collab shouldn't soften those on the radical edge #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk should be managed, but it shouldn't prevent collaboration @TharaniJega #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Thom learnt the most from collab b/n @WorldVisionAus and the extractors sector: the real risk was *not* engaging #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to challenge the preconceived ideas we hold about each other in NGOs and private sector - @TharaniJega #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a common language like SDGs, and orgs to connect the dots b/n sectors @TharaniJega #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design process needs to be collaborative if collab is going to work @TharaniJega @ACFID #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most influential advocacy orgs in CC are less than 10 yrs old; Nick from @ausprogress asks if we need a revitalized aid sector #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to decide who speaks, about what, and when @ausprogress @ACFID #acfid2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ACFID2016 #collaboration #impact https://t.co/boOkBBrX5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes collab is working across value-systems; sometimes we share values but bring different skill sets @ausprogress #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GedKACTU for unions and climate movement, commonality was a focus on just transitions #ACFID2016 #impact #collaboration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collaboration is risky when there's a feeling you don't share the same values - need to find common ground @GedKACTU #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GedKACTU says collab between unions and the climate movement needed to overcome perception that unions were anti-climate #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to learn from other sectors about how we can collaborate for impact #ACFID2016 https://t.co/qAEKQZsXw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The need to engage w national interest arg for aid was a key theme emerging from #AustAheadoftheCurve, now echoed b… https://t.co/vZTLCgSb37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of transparency in data collection, not the data itself, is concerning #futurosfeministas #ACFID2016 @ACFID @iwda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenging discussion about the politics of intersectionality #futurosfeministas #ACFID2016 @ACFID @iwda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should those who don't experience poverty /marginalisation get out of the way or use our privilege for change? #futurosfeministas #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to harness the power of digital feminism #futurosfeministas #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self care is a collective act, not an individual one #futurosfeministas #ACFID2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking #futurasfeministas at the #ACFID2016 side event with @iwda https://t.co/fj2i5XPIiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @RealAvocadoFact, have you seen the avocado v capitalism debate that's happening in Australia? Good stuff: https://t.co/4F9OT8BGsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEndrey can you vote more than once in that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catgiorgi @ACFID Anytime! It was great to hear more about what you're doing at @purposeaus !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, what a cracking opener!! Wasting no time getting to the heart of the issue with repealing 18C #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbenjaminlaw Spoiler alert, they were all doing it. But at least they were buying flowers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbenjaminlaw The sitcom idea is legit- my grandma was a florist in Canberra pre-internet &amp; she knew who all the pollies were sleeping with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brocklesnitch you should call this hotline: https://t.co/nWQqtuQcuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is spot on! via @marcuskelson  https://t.co/he8FuN5RTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This person deserves a Nobel prize. https://t.co/GCvCJr9Pbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @GuardianAus, this is a great tool, but the foreign aid figure should refer to % of federal budget, not GNI (aid/GNI only at 0.25%)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice from an avocado here. https://t.co/glGkiCDpS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane great ad placement though! https://t.co/cwdvnKsDF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an appropriate amount of condiments in Chilean Patagonia, evidently. https://t.co/FP98mWYWVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinnigan @annabelcrabb yeah, I think it's valid criticism but unfairly directed. BUT I'm always for criticism that shakes things up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feylith See if you can get the fail written off as a non-complete on your record through special consid'n!(yes I'm procrastinating at work)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bacon is 100% fatal (for the pig). Thanks @firstdogonmoon! https://t.co/OQHBbchCbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinnigan @annabelcrabb But since we generally don't hear those stories, is it wrong to amplify the powerful? 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinnigan @annabelcrabb but I hadn't considered the power dynamics. Ideally we'd have this AND stories of the marginalised 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinnigan @annabelcrabb I really like KC b/c the way male pollies respond to a woman asking them to cook speaks multitudes 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feylith Depends whether 'failing' is the result or the cause of mental stress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feylith haha, love the essay plagiarism service fav-ing your tweets about essays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feylith no way, countering just means you're not making a straw man of the other side of the argument!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>