<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to play a game that makes you feel like an absolutely worthless human being. Look no further -&gt; https://t.co/p2ZTHhZ5Hz #GGJ17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GGJ2017 #screenshotsaturday Not sure if I should post this, maybe giving a little too much away to Hawaii. https://t.co/OhZ6hpmJsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances we still got time to change idea right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfRize is it just the terran cheese is too strong atm? I thought protoss lategame was generally ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SC2Nemesis @MaynardeSC2 @SKT1_Dark I heard jak been playing pretty well as well, but keen to see cure again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1FProYours I'll have to stream our games, although I've given up all forms of good manners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1FProYours Nice work, I saw that one. Where's the strim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caseylindesign if i click the images it returns to the home page! Also more detail please, we want specifics here.ðŸ¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you were looking forward to Pig casting but turns out he's just too good at the game. #OSC https://t.co/CvNMv4uigG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamese awesome! thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamese I swear I saw an example presentation from #KiwiGameStarter online somewhere for reference. Do you know of any that are accessible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smixity just look, wow, amazing, its to die for. #MonkeyIsland https://t.co/FLJ8FmnhRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smixity Monkey Island 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZepphSC2 casting Innovation vs Solar! Too good to be true, or is it. https://t.co/zkSYK2Sil3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gonna be siiickk https://t.co/gZs8iiVpIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LowkoTV Google's investing into it. Everyone wants VR to go viral on phones so that other platform investments become viable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pokebunny @Artosis Unless you're saying Korean success is due to genetic superiority and not their insane work ethic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pokebunny @Artosis Interestingly education institutes inadvertently promote this view, although it is wrong. Work ethic trumps all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levelupwgtn Do you guys take visitors? On the hunt for a space in Wellington, even if nothing available would love to meet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZepphSC2 @ROOTiaguz and if they don't keep their promises Zepph will just hack all the banks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FieroNZ will have to come and see in person :o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huuge earthquake in New Zealand, had to run up the hill because of a tsunami warning at 2am. Hope everyone's ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's interesting how quickly a conversation can get deep when you talk about relationships, even with someone you don't know too well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SludjGames @Playdead it's incredible I'm still talking about the game Months after playing! More please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetanoKid @Playdead the hard part now is trying to keep from spoiling the game when you tell people how amazing it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenovaChen just started reading your flow thesis paper. The real question is how do I pronounce Mihalyi's unpronounceable last name o.o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaKaTaKtv started drinking tea, time travel possible confirmed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfRize uni's don't like failing students, just fix up whatever you've got until you have to hand it in, you'll do fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfRize you can, get your ass down to uni and finish your shit. Just take your hard drive to your IT tech if you have to they will sort you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfRize just take the hard drive out and move it to a friends pc to get everything on a portable one, then just go work at uni.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elusoryx You'll get him next time &lt;3 Just keep practicing! Every loss now is a win in the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designbycl maybe this one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designbycl this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haydenjweal Congrats! Exciting stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickRothfuss well to me you're a success because you try. Keep being an inspiration to all of us younglings. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy! I've #justsponsored Adam lyne, who's fundraising for @macmillancancer on @JustGiving. Donate now https://t.co/HiQxxpoi2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances How hard could it be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfRize thanks man, you too! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm taking a step back from Starcraft 2, thanks to everyone who supported me ;]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgda Just played through Gone Home yesterday, an amazing experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yzibelle :O I'll watch the recording.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STARLEAGUE HYPUUUU, plz @SC2ByuN show us the way, you got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Totalbiscuit @nathaniastv Watching the ShoutCraft Kings Vods right now! Already so hyped, thank you guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiLiPiLi96 Noooo, now who am I meant to predict to win :[]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nerd chillss @JinAirGW Rouge you got this! #GSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances a twitter link on twitter O.O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances what sort of information are we talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaynardeSC2 no glass, I just drink from the tap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaynardeSC2 or both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathaniastv Nah both games he just sits and macro's, doesn't work too well on ladder though since every protoss does a different allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathaniastv and SSL Cure vs Billowy KSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathaniastv SSL Cure vs Hush, Dusk Towers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psiNoRegreT @onfireNeeb @dPixScarlett This is amazing! Nice work, much excite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The LeTod Curse strikes again! #WCS #DHVLC16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playoff's hypee! https://t.co/mHnpHFHHay #SC2 #gaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xKawaiian Still no zergs are in the round of 16 for GSL, even Taeja who was spending more time playing overwatch made it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taeja's ghost control, game sense, and army positioning is still just ridiculous. WP WP WP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@th3ace223 Oh he wasn't on the list when I checked &gt;.&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No events or Terrans on atm, so lets stream! https://t.co/whfreAKzhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I joined a team :] https://t.co/LWwfU6mSvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to practice more vs protoss, there are just none on NA ladder atm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x5_Tilea is from New Zealand??? I've been worshiping the wrong god all this time @syfCrimson Please forgive me senpai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artosis This is the group of death IMO. MC and Solar haven't been performing as well lately as the players in group E.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfSoundwave @syfChadMann @GiveSeither @EnDerrPH He's a true memer now :'{ and so young, such talent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaynardeSC2 It can only ever be a good thing to be choosing to do more of what you love and are interested in, all the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaynardeSC2 Yeah what just happened. I thought Reality's composition was better then widow mines just charge in by themselves???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZepphSC2 ya, raising more than a few eyebrows I'm sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who made #WCS possible, amazing production, awesome games, great casters and observer. 10/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfChadMann thanks man &lt;3 ill practice TvT for the next one haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GG's! Had an awesome weekend, bit of a drop off at the end but apart from that played really well ;]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances Straight after these two play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances i was pret close :}]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to vs @GiveSeither in 14 hours, gonna have nightmares for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ascarecrow101 @syfInsano @ESLAustralia @dethsc2 @ZepphSC2 @MaynardeSC2 @mOOnGLaDeau thanks guys, loved it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuovoGaming @NUOVOiaguz @fixer_Seither @EnDerrPH Ahem 2dSparrow &lt;- :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfChadMann @syfCrimson i was kidding, but after tomorrow yes yes and yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you're spamming so fast in the early game that you're afraid you'll slip, cancel your barracks, load your CC with SCVS and then lift it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfChadMann OR TOMORROW, who wants to practice with me???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfChadMann I only practiced one style, and only on ladder :[ I'll try to get more practice partners for next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psiElusory :D All the games were pretty darn close though haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syfChadMann :D twice in 1 month what's going on here. Literally all because of playing marine split challenge for 30 mins every day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dethsc2 I had to leave the clan, I'm sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fell apart that last series but rest of my run was awesome! So nervous &gt;.&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixer_Seither @CrimsoNZL @ChadMannSC2 @xendra_x the stakes have never been higher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrimsoNZL @ChadMannSC2 @xendra_x doubt that 1 good streak is all it takes to dethrone senpai uncle ben.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rizeasdf I don't know any foreign terran players who boast having strong TvZ either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rizeasdf if it were soo easy we would have more foreign terran players to cheer for for once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rizeasdf the matchup is just soo bad atm, either play at the highest level and stomp zerg, or play a tiny bit worse and get stomped by zerg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualified for the next Proxy Tempest Monthly tournament after some close games against two GM Protoss https://t.co/lbDor01LxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarreNSC2 Just mute em, Gotta love that pause bm when they realise it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJENTUS_MC have my children plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?! They started a new FPL round without announcing it??? I've been checking everyday waiting for trading to open and I missed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpATreeZelda @mYiSmiile Doesn't really make sense to not pair it with a late game nerf also the real Impossibility is winning late game TvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SC2HL giant widowmine bait game 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixer_Seither they don't have guns, you can't upgrade hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLFrances @designbycl can he do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is going on today the games are just so one sided]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuStAzure @x5_PiG @SLCN_NXZ You'll have to ask @fixer_Seither he has the same problems but seems to still do well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x5_PiG @SLCN_NXZ I'm gonna do it, really had trouble controlling small groups of units, this should help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x5_PiG @SLCN_NXZ My muscles are amazing! If i ever come to Aus I'll let you touch, but only once.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>