<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Government censured for ‘illogical’ drawdown policy https://t.co/bqrTJ9xqFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big thanks to @JosephineCumbo for her tweets from TUC conference yesterday and the pensions bill the other night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quasi compulsion, and has potential to hit low earning self-employed hard. https://t.co/gA8Zis5Ija]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree. https://t.co/fsIll9r0qZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were ramsquaddled last night hope you're not wamble-cropped this morning &gt;&gt; https://t.co/zuMShOTlcE via @BBC_Culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pickfos true, but there will be capital protection funds in a S&amp;S ISA. Just better not to give option of solely cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extending coverage of AE is big challenge for 2017 - 12m will miss out on AE without government action - research https://t.co/UPTHhgOgeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The curse of long-term cash - so why is HMT and FCA allowing a cash Lisa- makes no sense https://t.co/ZNZ34PqpVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another early start. Off to London today and a busy day ahead. Going to be a good one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Selby: Why the Chancellor should think again on MPAA cut https://t.co/P9ozG5Rl6n via @Retire_Planner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoyed presenting in Inverness today. https://t.co/1qsiz1sJvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived in, erm cloudy, Inverness. Looking forward to a good gathering. https://t.co/E6Iokp8IjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a reoccurring message, but one never really addressed. https://t.co/TOKgB1GCn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up far too early for trip to Inverness. But looking forward to @nucleuswrap 1st 2017 Technical Roadshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a lovely tribute.  https://t.co/weHum66MUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Tata Steel: Union ballot to start on pensions offer https://t.co/e0eHrauTgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fannymelrose will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmcgagh I'm sure I will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what arrived this morning! Looking forward to starting it #weekendreading @mmcgagh https://t.co/ZDvmHXRv7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP pensions: piecing together govt's savings strategy https://t.co/ZikA4jp1VH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK @Justin_Cash_1 Now you have (for income) 1. Capped - full AA, or 2. FAD - MPAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK @Justin_Cash_1 And annual allowance was £50k up to April 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions I'm hoping to be down over next few months. Fancy a cup of coffee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions unfortunately I didn't get to Bettys. Not good time management! And I was looking forward to a cup of tea and slice of cake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unprepared for the cold in Harrogate. Been forced into an emergency purchase of a new hat. #anyexcuse https://t.co/rW3Fwtukms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It might be dull, cloudy, and very cold, but #harrogate is still beautiful. Looking forward to a good day here. https://t.co/UOlggTD6cJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo @FT thought all points were covered - good article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complex decisions. To avoid use up TFC or draw capped drawdown income. Those already triggered MPAA may want to use… https://t.co/bHLiKAwPKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo @DavidPenney10 @Charlene__Young @JohnRalfe1 could have been made redundant needed cash then got new job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the £9.2bn figure is accumulative presume every quarter will be a 'record'. https://t.co/MuMizl0iTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you packed your scarf Darren - it's a bit nippy down here https://t.co/gv9lxpBvr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting development for thorny (and opaque) area of IHT and pensions. https://t.co/w3bZEUvRdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a train speeding down south for a meeting tomorrow in glorious Harrogate. Guess the haggis and a wee dram is going to have to wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AJ Bell: Where does the Lifetime Isa fit into a financial plan? - Money Marketing https://t.co/vuk3mDEjaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hammond was fairly clear at the Autumn Statement that the triple lock was the next Chancellor's problem. https://t.co/yXX4wfiwFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_reeve that's my understanding but that's the problem with myths and legends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Niggle98 @PeoplesPension @HRNewsdesk I meant we need to help more if ppl aren't engaging. But yes I think it would encourage more awareness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto enrolment doesn't mean auto engagement with pensions. We need to consider raising the minimum contribution lim… https://t.co/jJNDXt4Qs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_reeve But he did it to prove to his minions he had no real power and the sea wouldn't obey him. Whereas Trump .....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SippySlicker @PensionsSimon @KatieMorley_ @TelegraphNews must have been a 'golden brown' chip instead of a 'yellow' chip. Avoid them!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the colour guide to chips that's got me. https://t.co/Da8w5kdgDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree - shows why dual objective products can be tricky https://t.co/Qz1FHdbvyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I quite fancy the idea of a gap year when I'm 60 &gt;&gt; Does living to 100 mean we'll work forever? https://t.co/2TfCA20zqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunningham_UK @Charlene__Young @Justin_Cash_1 @thomasselby you can transfer in from other ISAs without counting to £20k limit but no bonus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Tom @PensionsMonkey https://t.co/yVByLHqbAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be interesting to know the estimated take-up &gt;&gt; Hargreaves Lansdown and AJ Bell preparing to launch LISA products https://t.co/rt0e7kkCIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisers' £36m Sipp bill sparks permitted investments list call https://t.co/nelbcoYFgk via @FPTodayNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know you will approve @Jon_Gwinnett  https://t.co/8MzGaIJ3ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffprestridge your blog really hit a nerve. I was interrogating Pensions tax manual yesterday and struck again by how complicated it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be interesting to know if increased private pensions are DB or DC based. https://t.co/lMaXQzK2My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MPAA consultation - Money Marketing https://t.co/QwVGzzkMG4 via @PensionsGirlie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasselby @Cunningham_UK Officially there's 4 types of Isa, but the fact we are having this discussion shows how complicated it all is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nucleus: include advice as non-charge withdrawal in LISA | Financial Reporter https://t.co/mF0WpkY48B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa should have penalty-free adviser charging like all other Isas and pensions - Money Marketing https://t.co/vVg8OieOOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck Phil. I know with your expertise and emphasis on quality you will be a great success. https://t.co/VdpdrKDWtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaunkirtley I remember being very reluctant to throw them out out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaunkirtley those were the days. Before we had simplification. Now look at us...... Oh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That speaks volumes #tinkering #pensiontaxchanges  https://t.co/LEEN2Fk7rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa has potential to be complicated, and many will benefit from advice. Need to allow penalty-free adviser charging https://t.co/Fp2X3YgOTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to be sure 25% charge will stop significantly more people withdrawing early compared to 20%. Not sure it will https://t.co/UVlmQWXQw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PensionsDave @JosephineCumbo could also add 'some' before ISAs in the header (no mention of innovative finance ISA)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting research about attitudes to working longer. More people would if employers offered flexible hours. https://t.co/zc7DYvBDZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016: the year of the hokey cokey for pensions https://t.co/w5A6i8cMkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions @Malcolm_Mclean @JosephineCumbo the problem is we don't know what it's about. And therefore it's misleading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMcQueen @nick_reeve these articles are helpful, I just would like Govt to suggest people get financial advice as one of their tips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In out in out, shake it all about. https://t.co/Q02V0gqgMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appears yesterday was a practice run. Today schools are back, husband's at airport, and I'm rushing to leave house on time. #christmasisover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also - don't forget the pension. Often the biggest or second biggest asset https://t.co/7RYrO1FPge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katefstar @Will_Robins No mention of innovative finance Isa either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katefstar @JosephineCumbo Absolutely - roll on 8th March!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katefstar @JosephineCumbo Increasing contributions has to be part of the conversation this year - even if the action is planned for later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephineCumbo Happy New Year! Other big issue is automatic enrolment - how to cast the net wider and how to up the contributions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What the financial services industry is missing is emotion" Girls, girls, girls https://t.co/nZtWWEC3h0 via @faithliversedge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it was brilliant. Love a panto! https://t.co/iwCbqjrGOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this poem. Relax and concentrate on the things that matter at Christmas. Winning Monopoly. Happy Christmas.  https://t.co/sIGQmpvYLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out for a much-needed coffee and breakfast. Fabulous way to kick off the Christmas holidays @pensionstully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CashQuestions got to be Peaches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pension dashboard is not an easy build - ABI: dashboard challenges will not stop progress - Money Marketing https://t.co/IVWYC6Y5Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurray! Santa has been delivering chocolate at work overnight #nucleuslife @nucleuswrap https://t.co/UwA7m8fm6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's going to rain up North as well. Stay in the pub is my advice. https://t.co/KLchFOWdcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W &amp; P committee want a 'nimbler more proactive' regulator. https://t.co/2gXHydGDFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the speculation on pensions tax relief starts ..... now! https://t.co/Tp35Q37OmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_StevenCameron @pensionstully not sure that would make a fun lunch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional Christmas lunch out with @pensionstully looking forward to some serious steak #meat https://t.co/UUDqr9O3CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At my last Sunday Step of 2016 with @vickyfit going to smash it! #sundaystep #santastep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy morning making #christmas cookies https://t.co/6DqePP9OCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katefstar where's the selfie Kate? Hope you're joining in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my favourite tweet of the year! https://t.co/rKl5osmvgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Webb: Re-writing the DB transfer rules - Money Marketing https://t.co/kazaXRH1UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasselby @AJBellGroup @AJBellMike Congratulations Mike!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average bonus was £530. https://t.co/p7Bqviuo2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three in ten will not seek advice about DB transfers https://t.co/nB4bJ7cgN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People could get more help on Lisa if adviser charging allowed as charge-free withdrawal. But bonfire needed for LTA https://t.co/N1DFGbLn3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just an administrative tidying up exercise. I'm still far from convinced a 6.25% charge on investor payment… https://t.co/JkxNPLZpEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidPenney10 @dontdelay @Charlene__Young @uktisa agree, a charge of 6.25% on member's contributions is way too high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinWellbeing always face the music. Be fully aware what money you have &amp; how you spend and save it. Then you plan how to use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to allow adviser charging on Lisa as non-charge withdrawal &gt;&gt; MPs reject lifetime ISA advice requirement https://t.co/8YEtNeK4E7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan to encourage UK self-employed into pension schemes https://t.co/ulWiZn4JvN via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope @Jon_Gwinnett is having a fun time in Norwich, spreading the pension word @nucleuswrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at a @uktisa course yesterday discussing Lisa. Some complicated bits. Not sure I believe the blurb that ISAs are a simple product.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>