<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Schindler's Pissed #TakeAFilmDownUnder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@b3rri73 @FuzzyWuzzyTO Find Fuzzy a big strong Commie man party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/7MFgPwc8CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's anti-Nazi song is All You Fascists by Billy Bragg. Written by Woody Guthrie in 1942.  https://t.co/nlbCWTKiEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need some cheering up? Then check out the results of a nuclear blast in your city! https://t.co/IuxOhwPvse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QCrankypants It doesn't count when you're a Conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@throwitinmyhat What she calls anti fascists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO What she calls anti fascists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via Skype using morse code. https://t.co/7apbIlI9V6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian musicians release a charity single for the victims &amp; survivors of the Bowling Green Massacre. https://t.co/CTG1IcquVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your daily reminder that Richard Spencer is a fucking Nazi.  Free speech stops when you advocate Nazism. https://t.co/7Z0YK3vASu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusBojangles Fire up the Missy Elliot DJ! https://t.co/ry52zjsKse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusBojangles Well that sucks. Sounds like you need a weekend of being kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a dating app for those of us who prefer the dark side.  https://t.co/lmmfSHeMbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout-out to the 100+ cancers that the human body can get.  Today is your day! #WorldCancerDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget that only three things will survive nuclear war - rats, cockroaches and Guy Fieri. #doomsday https://t.co/W9WJ7XK8fE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lydialanguish @CatSlacks Don't forget to pick up today's cheese for She-Ra. https://t.co/MUxXcmH6wh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realised what root means in Australia.  #ReasonsTrumpHangsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatSlacks The Lady needs to buy you a block of cheese a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile @FuzzyWuzzyTO West of the Don they're the third best on George St.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile @FuzzyWuzzyTO They're the best moobs east of the Don river.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile @FuzzyWuzzyTO I do find the tuba playing while you dance erotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO @VainHostile He takes cards too Fuzzy.  But the swipe doesn't always work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile @FuzzyWuzzyTO I can only have so many terrible lap dances Peaches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile @FuzzyWuzzyTO I thought you were a dancer at Filmores.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO Oh she's a journalist.  In an alternate universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normwilner Does he know that I don't live there anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twenty million Australians respond by calling Donald Trump a giant fuckwit. https://t.co/RhxwENgRIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most amazing thing about Frederick Douglass is thst he was able to do anything without Donald Trump. #TrumpHistoryMonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump announces slight change to Statue of Liberty. https://t.co/5rqIL21on1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada to launch preemptive strike against Trump's US. https://t.co/ocNmBffTiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadiancynic Actually, I'm looking forward to bring your uncle who killed his uncle on your dinosaur to bible school day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ezra Levant launches new crowdfunding campaign on the Rebel after the makers of his collectable doll forget the gla… https://t.co/9mgnF9XdMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO @FaithGoldy She is a journalist.  For the Reich Ministry of Propaganda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump claims credit for Beyonce being pregnant again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February used to be Black History Month. Now it's known as - Trump Oppressed By The Commie Cuck Left Wing Mainstream Media Remembrance Month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're about to watch a top quality film when Mario Van Peebles is the director.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO @marykilmer I believe the 19th year means parole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By human rights Ezra means white power rights when the person who says they're white wouldn't be under Nazi law. https://t.co/yurbvTPZ5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been offline all day. Who knew outside was in 4D?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're sorry, but this elevator is out of services until January 1st 9013 due to routine maintenance. https://t.co/nOrwgY3FQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MizMisanthrope @piersmorgan That's deeply offensive.  Cunts are wonderful useful things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm old enough to remember when the United States wasn't run by a right-wing Nazi junta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask them what 2 + 2 is.  You'll know they're a Trumpzoid when they say Radical Islamic Terrorism. https://t.co/BdTBRRlX4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump orders that his Secret Service guard only be referred to by the first letters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tip for Trump's Supreme Court choice tomorrow.  Roland Freisler. https://t.co/13Z69GHtdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrulyTafakari Frustration at missing your bus pails in comparison to entire families being slaughtered. Nothing changes without struggle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satire brings down fascists. https://t.co/PKJqjt0al6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO @Belgraves Ezra would shake a tin outside Auschwitz if he could make a few bucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian makes me ashamed to be Australian. https://t.co/0lGkUM7PDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@416raccoon Use a cat door to steal human money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give it three more days before Sean Spicer's blood pressure makes his head explode in the middle of a news conference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trial balloon for a coup? https://t.co/6tlCkxy2dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen up bigots and Nazis.  This is Mitochondrial Eve.  All modern humans derive their DNA from this one women in… https://t.co/9EaGY2P8b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees are not Jihadists in disguise.  They're fleeing certain death from the fascist Jihadists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the animals are getting out of Dodge. https://t.co/uYghX6Nzj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current narrative from the President of the United States : Muslims are the Borg.  All acts are violence are their fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Torontobear @maggiecassella @JProskowGlobal If I'd left you'd have a distraught Maggie to deal with. No one wants that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggiecassella @Torontobear @JProskowGlobal I just might if they start a war. #mayorofbartertown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggiecassella @Torontobear @JProskowGlobal You all owe me an apology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Torontobear @JProskowGlobal @maggiecassella He was responding to the original tweet. Not you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggiecassella @Torontobear @JProskowGlobal Trump is blaming Muslims for what a Nazi did in Quebec City.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like the Rebel to shake the tin for money.  At all. https://t.co/4TXY7DaDQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This.  The Ostrogoths are in the Forum people. https://t.co/ARx78ohHdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehistoryguy Westminster Hall actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehistoryguy His head was on the Tower for years.  Till it fell off during a storm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect America.  But fuck everyone else. https://t.co/n2laoRV4Md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsbie Ezra would stand outside Auschwitz and rattle a tin if he thought he could make a few bucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember reading about the Wannsee Conference of 1942 when the Nazis met to decide the Question of the Jewish and everyone else problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fortyfs Hate creates money and power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonjames @fortyfs I for one welcome our napping Overlords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaValenti @LP_LaPresse But yeah, people fleeing for their lives from fascist Jihadists are the problem.  Not Nazi misogyny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordMacey @realDonaldTrump How dare all those Jews be exterminated by the alleged most cultured nation in Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to have Kyle Lowry's babies. https://t.co/qZn80R3WNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you support Trump and his junta of generals, then you're a fascist who rejects the founding principles of the United States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Tory supports people who advocate racism. https://t.co/EkFbcAavfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can have your vagina and eat it too. https://t.co/oKJ0TL4C57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BoycottStarbucks is nothing but racist, bigoted hatred that further erodes the liberty that is the dream of the United States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VainHostile Explains why you're in heat right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusBojangles @AsYouNotWish Probably thinks India is a the shit because they had dudes on bikes doing tricks.  https://t.co/oVRiPn4F7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LR279 I haven't heard anything about what we're doing to help Turkey and co deal with the millions they've got there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LR279 That's our Justin........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LR279 It's easy to hate.  Not so easy to stand against it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusBojangles I've yet to see an article about your personal theory of dialectical materialism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LR279 I always remind people that if the Holocaust could be perpetrated by the most cultured country in Europe, Nazism can happen anywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusBojangles Hey hey hey.  Leave five year olds out of this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish You're boring.  Delete your account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the world needs now to save it is an Australian in Canada who likes napping and bacon on pizza.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish Oh I do pumpkin.  But we're talking about Hindus buttercup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish That's why he has 14 milli....followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish Which Hindus have never done.  *couCASTESYSTEMgh*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish Then you'd know the Taj Mahal was built by a Muslim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I demand a full apology.  For the Ninja Turtles. https://t.co/usoAm3F2GL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish You clearly have no idea of India's long history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISCH91 @MissusBojangles @SjPTI @paidanchor @Wolf123rt @AsYouNotWish Righto Hindu Nationlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuzzyWuzzyTO @RichardBSpencer Hey.  Use this cricket bat too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This needs to be a musical with Matthew Broderick and Nathan Lane. https://t.co/IATHcKUELZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come for the beauty, stay for the Fascism.  #FailedAmericanSlogans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in other news, Miss France won tonight's Miss Tsar Putin pageant.  She wins a whole year of assisting noted cuckservative Donald Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aamer_rahman I feel bad for any fist that touches him.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>