<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanoG1234 can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamRyanMc can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cian_Morrin can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josh_Gray97 can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CroninDayl can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 can I get a WOOT WOOT for my bday?? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell more people that you love them. You never know how much they might need it. - Chris Brogan #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may never know what results come of your actions, but if you do nothing, there will be no results. - Gandhi #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A goal should scare you a little, and excite you a lot. - Joe Vitale #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the one who teaches other people how to treat you. What do you teach? - Chalene Johnson #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can dream it you can build it. If you can build it, you can live it. - Pam Moore #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Palomaa_Mason thanks ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 it's my bday! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ’” everything I wanted...... ain't happnin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Scottish, I fuckin hate Trump, therefore imma use this tag! FUCK TRUMP!  #ScotlandAgainstTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2hrs till my bday.... wow.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the midst of change we often discover wings we never knew we had. -Ekaterina Walter #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious. - Albert Einstein #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All things are difficult before they are easy. - Thomas Fuller #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to fight for something than live for nothing.- General Patton #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your creative juices flow and don't be afraid to take chances! - Joel Comm  #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@30SecondsFight @InternallyIost @VineCreators @brendan_m96 check this out ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 it's my bday tomorrow! ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy bday baby bro ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ (pretty sure he's now 12 wow) love you ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ https://t.co/Qj8c8tnRaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like almost 24 hrs till my bday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 lovely seeing you back in my notifications, missed ya ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 @feelslikenow omfg how did u find this ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm such a horrible person!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of being a bore is to tell everything. - Voltaire #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your value doesn't decrease based on someone's inability to see your worth. - Ted Rubin #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't appreciate what you bring to the table.. then let them eat alone. - Unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find myself really really funny ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘Œ and this is why your my fav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indifference is expensive. Hostility is unaffordable. Trust is priceless. It's all about Relationships. - Ted Rubin #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never seen a problem that was solved by only complaining about it. - Steve Keating #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistently investigate what gives other people energy. Be the fan that fuels it. - Darren Rowse #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I myself am made entirely of flaws, stitched together with good intentions. - Augusten Burroughs #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the thought of this.... being there in Glasgow! Kills me! Would love to go! But...... yeah... ðŸ˜“ https://t.co/1x3zT2NVuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 @junkkouture my bday is coming up! Hopefully I get a ticket! Gawd! I need to meet Brendan ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been 11 days lol guess who's still not forgot you ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all born ignorant, but one must work hard to remain stupid. - Benjamin Franklin #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josh_Gray97 slightly creepy ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't exercise your freedom of speech until you have exercised your freedom of thought. - Tim Fargo #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating the mind without educating the heart is no education at all.- Aristotle #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up what you want most, for what you want now. - Zig Ziglar #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @ella_13xx via https://t.co/InZ68Wt6MY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @mizjo88 @QuoTweety @weyheyhometown @hometowntara @avamoloney11 via https://t.co/InZ68Wt6MY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For this I bless you most: You give much and know not that you give at all. - Khalil Gibran #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me who the bathtub babies are in scream queens! I can't take it anymore! I NEED TO KNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a choice. Optimism is a choice. Kindness is a choice. Giving is a choice. Respect is a choice. Choose wisely.- Vala Afshar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lad ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ he deserves everything! ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜ @brendan_m96 https://t.co/Ve9BKDP4M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 been waiting so long! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ thank you so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 ðŸ˜ hello please can I have a follow ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 can I please have a follow? ðŸ˜ would make my day complete ðŸ˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 11:11 ðŸ˜† (not 11:11 but a follow from you would mean the world!) ðŸ˜€ been waiting so long!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life does not get better by chance, it gets better by change. - Jim Rohn #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ask me what I came to do in this world, I, an artist, will answer you: I am here to live out loud. -Ã‰mile Zola #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 seen a bit so I put it on my speaker and blessed the family with it ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ Everyone go check this! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ https://t.co/8qKLNJnTZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can normally tell how intelligent a man is by how stupid he thinks I am. - Cormac McCarthy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you've ever dreamed of will often show up in different packaging than you were envisioning. - Brenden Dilley #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you can, with what you have, where you are. - Theodore Roosevelt #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from. - Cormac McCarthy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimMcCarthyyy @Josh_Gray97 got me in stitches ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ŒðŸ™ˆ Kim you look very blessed lol ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanoG1234 if u grab a map and look just up above England there's that shit place called Scotland... that's where you'll find meðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people just never fuckin happy for me ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch your mouth: The language we use creates the reality we experience.-Michael Hyatt #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The miracle is this, the more we share, the more we have. - Leonard Nimoy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big question: what are we going to do for humanity? Serving others is the essence of leading at a higher level. - Ken Blanchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence is knowing the right answer. Wisdom is knowing when to say it. - Tim Fargo #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not always tell you how they feel about you, but they will always show you. Pay attention. - Kim Garst #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched Fantastic beasts and where to find them and omfg! BEST MOVIE EVER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 @brevilleUK I am lol it's well good! ðŸ˜€ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 @brevilleUK I've lost my voice and it sucks ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 @brevilleUK ouch.... I'm ill so I'm in bed watching Fantastic beasts and where to find them while drinking a cuppa tea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 @brevilleUK lol u not at collage or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 @brevilleUK  no I was too preoccupied wi all that arm hair ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 @brevilleUK mmmm that actually looks really good ðŸ‘Œ mind bringing me over some? ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shiz! Fell asleep at 7, now I'm back up.... when I fell asleep I was dizzy.... now it's worse! Gawd thot sleep was good but I was mistaken!ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other side of fear lies freedom! - JB Glossinger #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To live a creative life, we must lose our fear of being wrong. - Joseph C. Pearce #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait. The time will never be just right. -Napoleon Hill #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life doesn't get easier or more forgiving; we get stronger and more resilient. - Steve Maraboli #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude is a little thing that makes a big difference. - Winston Churchill #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk a lot! It's so frustrating coz I'm loosing my voice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 it's a new day... and I have a bad throat and now can't talk louder than a whisper! HELP ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 I don't even know what my biology teacher is on about like evr....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 lol see I did really bad in my biology prelim ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 ahahaha funny... naw I didn't take chemistry coz I can't do science.... or biology ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 gawd! Thanks ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜˜ will Defo need the luck coz people love talking bout my relationships in biology ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 hahaha I didn't get a sleep in coz my baby niece decided to walk into my room and start screaming ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjo88 @brendan_m96 ah fuckin hate Mondays ðŸ˜‚ I hate Sundays more coz u actually have to do homework ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went thru a break up and got called a slut! Lol! Gawd I don't feel shit all about it! #ImNotHurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendan_m96 YASSS! Thank fuck today is nearly over lol IM A SLUT! YAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May your faith be unshakeable and your will, unbreakable. - Tristan Bishop #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness. - Ralph Waldo Emerson #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder. - Rumi #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to be big. You have to be remarkable. - Joe Pulizzi #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Havin such a shit week already and idk who to talk to.... fuckin sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that we see or seem is but a dream within a dream. - Edgar Allan Poe #quote]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>