<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianlucey mainly family and we hope to build a house if we can secure planning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Best" fake news and alternative facts awards should be launched before it's banned or something by exec order. https://t.co/knsgltXURT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any budding horticulturalists in #cork looking for a new job? Voxgrow house is looking for ya Voxpro Horticulturist https://t.co/MNmlD1cXcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally secured a gaff to rent in Bandon! House is now up for sale and is almost packed. This is getting real :) #cork here we come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone using imagine fiber speed lte wireless broadband in Bandon/#cork? If so what speeds do you get?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eir @eirBusiness is it possible to get broadband in Crossbarry Cork CBA1_E01 on map https://t.co/J5OlBYTsUu  address based line checks fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmcclean true .. in the process of selling ours too :) Only thing more difficult is getting planning permission!! fun times all round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clonrf yep and have family on the ground keeping an ear out. Looks like there is limited supply of houses an a lot of demand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm blown away by how difficult is is to secure a house to rent in west #cork close to Bandon. Not an easy homecoming! Am I alone on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal_cahalane nice I land full time in cork mid Feb too :) let me know if I can help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal_cahalane when will you be ready to host a growth hackers Cork meet up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE nope all good I phoned in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE hey is your "my virgin media" account section down? I can't seem to login or reset my password. Error: SDP not available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone looking to buy a MacBook Pro in great condition? https://t.co/Mi9iWDbHdT https://t.co/NHDAJFRxdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm moving to #cork in Feb with the family. We are looking for a 3 bed house to rent in Bandon. If you can help email me jason@roe.ie &amp; RT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough day at the office for Benny after a morning in the groomers! https://t.co/VsAHXlhuFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last one .. Humanscale freedom task chair for sale https://t.co/x8qVQxP8n1 https://t.co/i8jwVHF1Cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a fetish for high end used  office chairs! :) All must go to make space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlse Eames ribbed style black office chair for sale. https://t.co/KxJaVm90L5 https://t.co/Vkf8HG1Xxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice popup Christmas card from @HubSpot this morning with some wine and chocolates. https://t.co/jHQ85933Ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RediscoveryCtr @McGarryDerek @wiser_life looks great .. what is the big glass bridge coming out of the back of the new building?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm doing a workshop in the @TheLirAcademy today called Confident Voice, Presenting with Confidence.… https://t.co/CRx11UDqnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new mattress is a worthwhile investment. Instant returns. It was my first time ordering a mattress online and I'm pleasantly surprised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccrossan @genemurphy great to catch up sorry I had to run off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talideon yeah I was around this evening but I had to run off. I'm still around tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cfdan @irlTopper @teamwork hope to make it over tomorrow for the office opening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrangeWeb I have considered it .. it would not bode well for property values :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve never been more excited in my life to be ordering a new mattress. A six week old will do that to you :) https://t.co/K2hnvAzzfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamreddave @CiaranCuffe I see what you did there! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanorourke @eoink @congregation13 hope it was a good weekend! Sorry we couldn't make it. Maybe next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know any good family friendly brunch places on the north side Dublin? Just had a mixed experience in @TwoBoysBrew with no high chair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iarfhlaith still looks my for board members if you know anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iarfhlaith I have mixed feelings. The standing board all resigned. IEDR made a good proposal. 3 new potential board members. Hope remains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamoGrant are we kicking off at 17:30 sharp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanearley best of luck with the move :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinKCostello will we see you there later? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianlucey I think all former board members should qualify to share their opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryPConroy will we see you there today? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claredillon will we see you there tonight? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinjcasey will we see you there? https://t.co/cI0DqAyKFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noirinnilaocha will we see you there? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanearley will we see you there? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianlucey will we see you there? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnyryan will we see you there? https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irelandfan1 will we see you there? https://t.co/QJRwp442Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would ask that all IIA members and previous board members attend this evenings @iia AGM https://t.co/QJRwp4lEiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulsavage I thought that was a paper bag at first! Looks great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews good to know. Can you update the real time signs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdsb20 @dublinbusnews that's were I am :) bust just arrived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the 11 is backed up @dublinbusnews bus stop real time has said 1min for the last 30 https://t.co/1WUzQapRCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birthday gift for someone in @HubSpotDev from @AungierDanger https://t.co/snb6iJqcUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jet lag sucks! 7am start and I can't sleep (after my trip to Boston last week) :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debating if i should go shoe shopping before I leave Boston! There were some great deals in sketchers! No space in my bags tbh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Hubspot Marketing Free .. https://t.co/8mLxFgV934 its free with Contacts database, Kickback emails and other Integrations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way to find someone at #INBOUND16  get them to take a photo @chrisbrennan_1 https://t.co/dzFKM912NM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisbrennan_1 I'm around today if you want to catch up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I take it back .. gin is no longer my jam! Sore head today :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin/7up with a hint of apple juice and ice is my new jam! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to be in the US 🇺🇸during the election.. should be interesting to see what the locals make of the results. #INBOUND16 🇮🇪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortword @anthonymcg  also what about potholes .. can it avoid them too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sodshow @jkeyes @twospots_ie @DoneganGardens @TG4TV it's a grad big mug too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortword @anthonymcg what's lithe self drive like on a an aul country road with grass up the middle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoneganGardens @TG4TV can't beat a cuppa https://t.co/NH3JXrY2EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icedcoffee @shortword @anthonymcg yeah I think there is s soft key via software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortword @anthonymcg don't t mind me! I'm just envious. How's the self-driving motor going for ya?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortword @anthonymcg  don't they have an adapter yet for the Esc key?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day back in the office in a few weeks. I've been hanging out with these two while on paternity leave. Still h… https://t.co/S3MCLGkYNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iboconnor never noticed it before ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the night mode view new in the twitter app? https://t.co/tptIAF2X42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Con_Keppel @chrisbrennan_1 nice one .. hopefully I'll catch you there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Con_Keppel did you get sorted for Inbound in Nov?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Con_Keppel was it that bad in NY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VR is so hipster! Not in a good way. https://t.co/YNjg8Anxpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you make of this @johnnyryan https://t.co/Vn31qLuXPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby Helen Roe arrived last week :) On paternity leave in @HubSpot &amp; lots of love from @hubspotdev We can add this… https://t.co/UJHk1DNbpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won the euro millions. €4. https://t.co/umS64TmwGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinsblog also kinda sad that Ireland still cares more for the welfare of sheep over that of the self employed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to admire all of the Samsung puns made on this tweet. Hope nobody was injured. https://t.co/2X1gKnx2V5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rteplayer ah i hand an old version of Flash .. Is flash not a bit old school these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is RTE live player down ? https://t.co/v6z72D7Rbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buymie_IRE have you considered a cross border delivery service? Order via your app and delivered to your door..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also check out Slack @ AWS Usergroup MeetUp #16 October 26, 2016 - Button Factory - Temple Bar! https://t.co/8703QfNbUN via @aokcloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in attending a new Open Data meetup in Dublin? #opendata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patphelan they were on a hiring spree in Dublin about 3 years ago. Similar setup to lionbridge but for multilingual content farms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowlinshoes hopefully you are not talking about work? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously is this what bray has done to the Golden Arches? https://t.co/kf3JoVtkbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BigEnergyHack will the data be published as open data using an open licence?@ESBGroup @ESBNetworks
0 retweets 0 likes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need your help to get @ESBGroup @ESBNetworks to publish open data before the Big Energy Hack. https://t.co/PdaZPQ1yNB Like &amp; Share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I bring back slide to unlock on ios10!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejournal_ie not to mention more deaths in ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf .. @thejournal_ie deaths on our roads = broken poached egg??  Bad choice of photo guys! https://t.co/qJsKiu9ssZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call from an unknown number on my mobile at 3am is not good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this open data initiative. Have some fun and win some cash :)  https://t.co/YoB6uFEiH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louise_Johnston I remember being sent to collect stuff but I did have to pay at a till]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louise_Johnston oh? Now that is good to know :) in just buying doors to child proof our book cases!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karl_murray I knew it was too good to be true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe this is a stupid question but can you do click and collect in Ikea dublin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need your help to get NCT data published. Share, Like and comment on this page. https://t.co/Rd1CDUYanh https://t.co/Zq2zpW5vdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[since when did the m50 toll signs on the m50 change to purple?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @NoelRock can you help get this data released as open data on https://t.co/pWz4fUZPt4 ? https://t.co/MSuCYczkr2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>