<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - it's just a wee heads up to say that the gym will be CLOSED tonight after a very long day of traveling... https://t.co/ga9QqA76rO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - it's just a wee heads up to say that the gym will be CLOSED tonight after a very long day of traveling... https://t.co/Npe8JG7l7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the way home now - very frustrating day in the office for us down in Barnsley on the Sandee Super Show. BIG... https://t.co/cbOTnUuwy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a heads up that we'll be meeting at the gym at 6am sharp tomorrow morning for our journey to Barnsley guys ðŸ’Ž... https://t.co/UejHF7P1HR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sparring &amp; open mat training from 1.30pm - 2.30pm ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey troops sorry for the late post but i am afraid that i am still working and not able to open the gym tonight... https://t.co/JxmYhLiYmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It all starts this Sunday in Barnsley - Lewis fights for another title! 2017 is a busy, busy, busy year for myself personally &amp; the gym! ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai, tonight from 19.30 - 21.00! Working on thai boxing basics! 

Don't miss out guys! Consistency in... https://t.co/beWGfy2IGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I rate DiCaprio - this is just ridiculous. https://t.co/RZmW6Uys68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesdays training schedule @ Black Diamond:

ðŸ”¥Juniors from 6pm - 7pmðŸ”¥ (Helpers needed to pad juniors please guys... https://t.co/mIqt6GAOwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than a week to the Sandee Super Show 3 down at the Barnsley Metrodome! Ayden, Lewis &amp; Zain will be putting... https://t.co/ULmgmO7fWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainings on tonight guys as normal 7.00-8.30 see you all there troops ðŸ–’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always great helping out in our local community! These three lads have done very well so far &amp; only their second... https://t.co/SFlFibWWtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another TOP session tonight with these gems! For those of you that missed out - you'll never realise your true... https://t.co/kMjwox2ih4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP effort tonight guys! Everybody giving 100% throughout the session! The gym was properly buzzing tonight!... https://t.co/1d3Jknvkg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai from 19.30 - 21.00 tonight! 

Beginners &amp; new starts welcome - male &amp; female! ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant having Liam (4th right) back! Really talented lad - as are all of the young squad in this picture! Ace... https://t.co/W0IPVQc2bZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day back at Active Schools! Hopefully unearth a wee diamond or two! The gym seems to be lowering in age... https://t.co/AaG8oL2DU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to having Liam join us in April for a few days! There's nothing this guy doesn't know... https://t.co/DlAKSlU47j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wanna say a HUGE thanks to Vikki for helping out tonight... It ain't easy trying to juggle training fighters... https://t.co/D58BJ5CMdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai from 19.30 - 21.00 tonight! We'll be working on attacking with the push kick (teep) &amp; also... https://t.co/Ig0efMdHJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Black Diamond! 3 years running &amp; getting bigger, better &amp; stronger! People come - people go, but... https://t.co/XTXtZFD19a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great afternoon of sparring through at the Every Day Athlete Gym in Glasgow with our junior team! Loads of future... https://t.co/IZassAZOo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day ahead of ourselves tomorrow with taking our juniors through to the Every Day Athlete Gym in Glasgow...... https://t.co/mQMYDWVbuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sparring practice from 1.30pm! I'll be in the gym from 1pm... Bring your A-game! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training on tonight 7.00-8.30 come and get fighting fit....little tech class tonight as well and learn to make... https://t.co/e5z64xe1hh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/8626d1v7Aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/oCt4lxhToT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Muay Thai from 18.00 - 19.00! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼

Junior fighters from 19.00 - 19.30! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼

Seniors from 19.30 - 21.00! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼... https://t.co/4O57N33VXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai from 19.30 - 21.30 tonight guys! Come &amp; learn one of the worlds finest &amp; coolest martial arts!... https://t.co/bNf1XmCk1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai from 19.30 - 21.30 tonight guys! Come &amp; learn one of the worlds finest &amp; coolest martial arts!... https://t.co/OpZAAjWBDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 days! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼ðŸ’Ž #blackdiamond #muaythai #thaiboxing #sandeesupershow3 #building4thefuture #thepeoplesgym... https://t.co/InvoYgbr9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesdays at Black Diamond! 

Juniors class: 6pm - 7pm ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼

Junior fighters: 7pm - 7.30pm ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼

Seniors class: 7.30pm... https://t.co/2M96ckjkut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yokkao training shinnies for sale for Â£45 - Â£50... Only worn a handful of times.

Adult medium in size.

PM if... https://t.co/FDpkAIzRqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai tonight from 19.30 - 21.00 guys! Be first &amp; start getting in shape for the summer now! All new... https://t.co/LFGCbsGVit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP session this afternoon with everybody working hard in sparring! 2017 is destined to be a great year for us!... https://t.co/1kO3EivqsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open mat/sparring practice this afternoon from 13.30 - 14.30... Don't miss out guys! Start the year strong! ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Smoking blunts - swooping cunts"... ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/8zsOQ1tonZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being self employed in January sucks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right guys/girls dont forget its the first Friday session of 2017 and i am feeling mean! Get yourself along to... https://t.co/6kCqawrp1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long before three of our diamonds go to battle on the Sandee Super Show 3 down in Barnsley! Ayden, Lewis &amp;... https://t.co/Z87pGjra9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The junior fight crew of 2016/17! You'll be seeing a lot more of this lot over the coming years! ðŸ’Ž #blackdiamond... https://t.co/kN5REYAiBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Andy &amp; co over at Rewind Media for the first episode of the series regarding Black Diamond Thai Boxing... https://t.co/Ig6cbgrAPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember guys, our first night back of 2017 is tonight! A busy year lies ahead with folk competing &amp; also making... https://t.co/3TKIU18vrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minor change guys - we'll be starting back on THURSDAY the 5th of January 2017! So tomorrow &amp; I can't wait!

Our... https://t.co/mgkkuStlmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First session of 2017 in the back pocket! We've got a busy year ahead of ourselves &amp; I'm sure it'll be every bit... https://t.co/3a8peDBVy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of being a cabby! Actually miss being around my loved ones at times like this...

Happy New Year &amp; all... https://t.co/SjG8mwSDys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F*@ks aw this hogmanay pish...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 is sure to bring more success our way - be part of it &amp; join our little family of diamonds by ditching the... https://t.co/wMFbHLCJ9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last training session of 2016 done &amp; dusted! Lewis, Ayden &amp; Zain all gearing up with extra training throughout... https://t.co/tbOaz1DrAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing a bus stop in Whitecraig when I say to the other half - "this isn't half a shitehole eh"... (Apologies... https://t.co/OrpkLXVSYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think some people realise how important bag work is. Some folk see it as "boring"... I don't - it's an... https://t.co/7qNFk2ehFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking to match the following fighters throughout 2017... Happy to travel around the UK if the dates &amp; terms... https://t.co/bsKWmgnpV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh FFS man... Princes Leia tae?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five days off for the festive break &amp; now back to the grind with these two in preparation for the Sandee Super... https://t.co/2MhN0mcbUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What great evening with the family! A second Christmas in the space of 24 hours - very lucky! Thank you to my Mum... https://t.co/Egd2vdbMdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If these stories are true - what a guy... â¤ï¸ https://t.co/dpMXDFhVoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael gone now?! FFS 2016!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just like to say a MASSIVE Merry Christmas to all of my family &amp; friends - new &amp; old! Also a HUGE thank you... https://t.co/Dnf0MnHrjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Easter... ðŸ£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I likely won't get the chance to say it tomorrow, but a SPECIAL Merry Christmas to our students &amp; fighters at... https://t.co/Pbeg9viOMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great way to end 2016 in our end of year - Christmas Smackdown! I'm both humbled &amp; very fortunate to be... https://t.co/uoUYdDD6mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember guys - it's our end of year CHRISTMAS SMACKDOWN!!! ðŸŽ…ðŸ¼ðŸ’¥ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼

Be at the gym anytime 6pm - 8pm to join in the... https://t.co/QWIqImNP8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vitalite, a french baguette, cuppa tea &amp; some N64... Yep - that was my school lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ PLEASE READ - PLEASE READðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

Today's junior class from 6pm - 7.30pm will be CANCELLED.

Seniors class as... https://t.co/zMs79bWLvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember guys, training tonight from 7.30pm - 9pm!  ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ALL WELCOME!ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

We'll also be doing our Christmas raffle... https://t.co/kZWY92kKQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥BIG ANNOUNCEMENT!ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

Bringing YOU the BEST in the business! UK Muay Thai legend, Liam Harrison of Richard... https://t.co/7MuiP34oNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥PLEASE READ - PLEASE READðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

The gym will be CLOSED for this afternoons sparring/open mat class as it's getting... https://t.co/q0wm0XuHIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai tonight from 7pm - 8.30pm... I don't want anybody messing around guys - I'VE LEFT ZAIN IN CHARGE... https://t.co/zWTmGcqHeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thursday @ Black Diamond! 

ðŸ”¥Junior Muay Thai: 6pm - 7pmðŸ”¥

ðŸ”¥Junior fighters: 7pm - 7.30pmðŸ”¥

ðŸ”¥Senior... https://t.co/4S151aEmcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right guys, I'm in the middle of moving house so Zain is looking after things tonight! Please show him your... https://t.co/dRTuUZaSz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DW's spot on... Preach! ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼ https://t.co/TJqFsnW1Ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed Muay Thai Monday @ Black Diamond from 19.30 - 21.00... All levels welcome! 

See you soon guys! ðŸ’Ž https://t.co/6ZRkoB9unM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sack that! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Aerit2j2b6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/zCBUt1GdIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/5pRj38mLsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wanna say a HUGE thanks to Ally for taking Zain, Greg &amp; Arriayn through to Wossabama's inter-club this... https://t.co/pOwE9b3b3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/Pge7U3uHvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥PLEASE READ - PLEASE READðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

Guys - I've had to CANCEL arrangements for tomorrow's inter... There's absolutely... https://t.co/QYvBDiR8BP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sparring/open mat as normal today from 1.30pm - 2.30pm guys... I won't be in, but Chaz will be there to open up... https://t.co/GYB9nOwxON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gym CLOSED tonight guys... Chaz can't make it in due to personal issues.

OPEN tomorrow as normal from 1.30pm - 2.30pm ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training timetable for Thursday @ Black Diamond! ðŸ’Ž

ðŸ”¥Mixed junior class: 6pm - 7pmðŸ”¥

ðŸ”¥Junior fighters: 7pm -... https://t.co/4KmTUw9bAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 2 x seats remaining at the clubs silver table on the Sandee Super Show 3 - be quick to claim your seat guys... https://t.co/jxM3r16Rf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this piece of UK Muay Thai GOLD while packing for the move!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right guys, I need a rough idea of who is all coming down to the Sandee Super Show 3 in Barnsley to support Lewis... https://t.co/7L140z8m2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evading the right hook... That roos slick! ðŸ˜‚

https://t.co/0tHB1kDxR1 https://t.co/q6Drwxvt9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the grind guys! We've got a busy 2017 ahead of us! ðŸ’Ž

ðŸ”¥JUNIORS CLASS: 6pm - 7pmðŸ”¥

ðŸ”¥JUNIOR FIGHTERS: 7pm -... https://t.co/GDYaBmsMKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building a great team here at Black Diamond! We'd only opened our doors in Feb 2014 &amp; we'd managed to win our... https://t.co/OKbM0qTDWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember guys, training as normal tonight from 7.30pm! ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis done us extremely proud today! He's only went &amp; won the gyms first title (WTKA Scottish Championship Title)... https://t.co/0SGQcrle0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis done us extremely proud today! He's only went &amp; won the gyms first title (WTKA Scottish Championship Title)... https://t.co/Q534CTDDgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥PLEASE READ - PLEASE READðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥

Details for today's event:

The address for the Sortaksin Muay Thai Gym is as... https://t.co/Qxlhh2bGLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wanna say a HUGE good luck to all of my juniors for tomorrow &amp; to all who helped them prepare for tomorrow's... https://t.co/BvHpiFIt5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right guys, who's all travelling to Markinch tomorrow? I'll be travelling up with Lee-Anne, Ally &amp; Vikki... Zain,... https://t.co/GUQKFSdlJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training today from 1.30pm - 2.30pm guys... Zain will be looking after things again guys so be good! I've given... https://t.co/tuUtK5eXbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some folk genuinely boil my piss... 90% of the time I'm laid back &amp; don't give much of a toss, but it's just that... https://t.co/V83L5mfURQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old guy next to me just stopped &amp; paused for a minute... To fart! ðŸ’¨ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class will be on as normal from 7pm - 8.30pm tonight guys! Both Zain &amp; Arriayn will be taking care of things...... https://t.co/BGSa3zzWG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, Chaz can't make it in tonight... Do I have anybody that can cover the class? 

Let me know asap.

Scott ðŸ’Ž... https://t.co/0ZQXAvop8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good wee meeting at Ross High this afternoon that'll see me take three teens that have behavioural issues down to... https://t.co/FUo2PnmydB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>