<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @nytimes Doctor you don't want to use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally https://t.co/HpiJlQeCw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer you go Senator! Take them DOWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts This stuff is going to instigate the Second Civil War]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS This is bullshit, we need to file for treason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachelheldevans God will do nothing, WE must help us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missy520 that makes sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missy520 it is a shame, especially if it was a first edition 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missy520 what was her reaction supposed to be? If the girl wants to tweet she gets what she gets in response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missy520 it's still a bit much for a "first book" no mater what the story line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why don't you just go away Mr Hate? You foster it then are surprised when it bites you. Fidiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS you retweeted yourself? It's still your fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS where those Benghazi people at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With you. https://t.co/POGtJmZSF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes 45 is literally dumb as goose shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann nailed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel welcome to 45speak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirdieBiser @GovRepublic @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr lol no brain power, shocker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirdieBiser @Kathryn_tornado @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr Treason- the betrayal of a trust. Seems legit, next loser?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirdieBiser @GovRepublic @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr I think you need to stop swallowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4TheTruth2012 @SenSchumer oh look, an asshat for 45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you are so stupid I wonder how you actually breathe all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making excuses for 45 because he is an incompetent moron...just say no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWeasel and his wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Inkydelaware @NatParkUndrgrnd hahahaha...45 be jealous, watch your back Phil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TXStarLake @BryanDawsonUSA actually he didn't. She cost herself the election. First step is asmitting the problem or it will happen again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ButWhatAbout23 @SenateGOP also spelled kerosine, don't prematurely post without your facts checked sweetie. Now go  get on the bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missy520 @Missy520 more stupid then scary, Harry Potter is kind of a big book to start out reading on, I think she's lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr I believe your collective pants are on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts @RepGosar fact is you are being sneaky Gosar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FullFrontalSamB @BetteMidler more importantly, where does he think Fred lives ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryNatlPark what a tool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @ChuckGrassley @senjudiciary Apparently the GOP enjoys that legal weed in DC...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gruber @DISUNC this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empty_gesture @LivingBlueinRed I think now would work, let's do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed side note, original message autocorrected to "he died today" ... if only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed And he doesn't  even try, he just opens his mouth and stupid shit projectile vomits out if it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDataAlex @NatlParkService @conradanker we need to take this government down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint here's a clue, we aren't afraid, we are PISSED! Get out there and REPRESENT US!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr Bull. You lie for a living and we pay for it. Time for you all to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always Watching! Let's keep it going. https://t.co/u8CtQT1PzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders love you Bernie! Keep holding their  feet to the fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed 45 is a gutless coward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjohnlane @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr Breathe. The GOP had spent the last 8 years obstructing and now they cry for peace. No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kathryn_tornado @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr what the GOP did should be considered an act of treason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Walken23 @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr That would be "No", he would roll over and pee...maybe even on the bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovRepublic @SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr Mitch is an Alternate Ztruth pandering jackal #McConnellsThroatPouch #Delete45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @SenateMajLdr If by interpret you mean twist things around to suit his master, you would be right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang @freddogone Honestly people wtf are you thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltYelloNatPark gloves off, got my ax, where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed @tedcruz Teds go read s book, maybe Horton Hears A Fuck Off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chippy524 @minhalbaig @BethBehrs no she does not have the appropriate qualifications, $$$$ doesn't count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretJay7 @09072021 45 has no soul and less brains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec Do you realize what a colossal Bozo you are?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dagraffman @AltUSFWS Spicer needs a ball gag STAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanDawsonUSA I wish 45 was a cockroach so I could smack him flat with a slipper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics 45 is a creep #DeleteDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed @LOLGOP let's hope a couple bounced...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenDuBreuil @joshuawoodz @thehill I think we were played by two crafty parties, ultimately we suffer. We need to break the system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenDuBreuil @joshuawoodz @thehill I agree Jen, he is the puppet master]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ButWhatAbout23 @SenateGOP  oh goodie, middle school has let out for the day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask yourself why 45 has picked such unsuitable candidates? Because $$$$$$$$$$$$ https://t.co/WLaV5KG6gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill that would be because they are wrong. The EPA serves an important role. He serves himself. Dictator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill The PEOPLE do not support hate and lies. Regardless of Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill don't try to generalize. If you nothing wrong with any of Trumps executive orders than you aren't paying attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS @Zac_Petkanas This, 45 is just a big ugly bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill no he isn't, he is supposed to represent the people, he is not. He is doing as he pleases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill what good has he done? Other than to further enrich himself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill then open your eyes tobit and see the damage he is trying to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @JenDuBreuil @thehill shoving your friends and people the have paid you $$$$$$ into positions of power as yes men is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @AltUSFWS how do I file a lawsuit against the GOP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenDuBreuil @joshuawoodz @thehill no they just keep towing the line of lies they are fed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill again, more a matter of actual truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill @marklevinshow keep swallowing, did he show up for your guns too in this fantasy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @JenDuBreuil @thehill the founders would be disgusted by your Toddler-in -Chief and his blatant disregard for the people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @JenDuBreuil @thehill I se 45 and his party as trying to make us a dictatorship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill @marklevinshow Trump wouldn't know the Constitution if you slapped him in the head with it. No points for dumb luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill that would be because you are so used to swallowing lies that you no longer recognize the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill then you do not do not believe what you say you believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP @AltHotSprings FYI Pence, petty much everyone but morons and the puppet wranglers think 45 is a mentally unstable buffoon. #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill if that is what you believe in than this clown car administration must get you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill no, there is actual truth, actual Justice and a true American way and then there are Alternate Facts a/k/a lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuawoodz @thehill Truth Justice and the American Way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words we don't need another Donnie Dicksucker on our payroll. https://t.co/llQEjY91Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollandTaylor @DISUNC they have been banned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews @RudyGiuliani @Newsweek_INT Rudy doesn't have the slightest grasp of realty either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory @DISUNC This is where we are now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you are sickening. #1 on the full of shit meter. Sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Impeach_D_Trump @mickmcmickster what too much alcohol does to your soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP perhaps you could stfu and blow away?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @LivingBlueinRed @realDonaldTrump @seanspicer @KellyannePolls beyond disgusting. I vote that they spontaneously  combust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed kind of a big deal...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS @GOP because "pro-life" until the baby is born then "no room for slackers"...embarrassed of yourselves yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickCohen4 @jk_rowling @YouTube 45 effects the world with his stupidity, it has a far greater reach than yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @washingtonpost Guess you should have taken that stance on the last one. Hypocrites. Start doing your job you slackers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @AltUSFWS Boom Baby ! Respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP @SenateGOP  So you guys are just going to continue to lie and make stuff up ? This is theft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenMikeLee @SenateGOP so after you have completely ruined the country, where you moving to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnThune @SenateGOP  smoke another blunt buddy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>