<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRobinsonnx happy bday Amy hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton fuck off ya doss cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#T2trainspotting fuckin brilliant ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzzing for T2 tonight ðŸ’€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicooleBurgess thanks Nicole ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@braddonaldson cheers bro ðŸ’š hope to see you Saturday x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRobinsonnx cheers Amy Rab xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daisyforbess thanks Daisy x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlingX thanks Caity G ðŸ˜Ž x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexkeddie thanks Alex x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollysamuel2 thanks HollyðŸ˜Š xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossHeeps thanks mate x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simoneconnolly thanks SimoneðŸ˜Šxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywebsterr thanks webtaes ðŸ’™ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadeadamsxo cheers Jade, and thanks for the card too ðŸ˜Šx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sean_Nicol thank chief ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixnoble9 thanks Alix! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luisapetretti thanks Lu ðŸ˜„ she hasðŸ‘ðŸ¼ xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenAtkinson97 @bertoise @AHaggon surprised you didny pull that axe of yours out ben....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Medio96 happy bday mate hope it's a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixnoble9 happy bday Alix hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most importantly, couldn't ask for a better bird after all the effort she went to and being able to keep it from me for weeksâ™¥ï¸@beckynicolx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to all who came last night and sorry to my pals for the verbal abuse they suffered after I thought they were all on the patchðŸ˜‚ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic the night man get to fuckðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMalcolm18 mind = blown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenhandX happy bday Lauren hope it's a good one ðŸŽˆ X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst thing about this weather is getting into a freezing cold car and waiting about 2456 minutes for it to warm up ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenH9 is he fuck tho no even scoring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooney to get 250 against Liverpool on Sunday ðŸ”´âš«ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive happy birthday to this angel @beckynicolx on her 21st ðŸ˜šðŸ’š https://t.co/0Xf0dkyyas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever met the famous CCS? You have now https://t.co/7urwMuXcQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 spot on Cummings 3-0 at 33s keeeman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loviee97 @BenAtkinson97 @jjjjj_rfc @spfl @HibsOfficial stilll got at least another 5 year of it as well Lololol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Snapchat is a game changer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another horrible decision from Mike Dean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Becky on saving money in 2017: "save a penny a day and at the end of the year you'll have Â£365"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoogsTweets dae ye love the darts aye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenAtkinson97 @donovan3__ aye that sounds more like it, he's gone soft as well nae reply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give it a week before you see @donovan3__ kicking about wi one of these on #styleicon https://t.co/BXGoM29JMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donovan3__ sound martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's definitely Sunday the day no bothered what anyone else says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlyCarlya1993 happy bday Carly hope it's a belter ðŸŽˆ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet are you putting the snodgrass and city win up or no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet what about snodgrass anytime and a city win??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet snodgrass anytime, iheanacho anytime, Davis and otamendi to get booked, over 10 corners and city to win. #requestabet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenH9 gutted... am no gone out the morn fuck that. No after that news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenH9 @JakeWelsh10 what you on about Daz.... ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeWelsh10 Av heard word directly from The Rangers board n they've confirmed Davie will be there along with Scotland's own, Gordon Greer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeWelsh10 @reececollins10 reece mate he's got a point.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeWelsh10 it's going to be unbeilable Jeff ðŸš€ðŸš€ðŸš€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 now that's too early, you're a madmin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 Half 10 mate. Fuck going out then, that's too late ya raj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all about the sesh the morn â˜ðŸ¼ï¸ #BoxingDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas ðŸŽ…ðŸ¿ðŸŽ„ https://t.co/IeMbbYANcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas fuckers ðŸŽ…ðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donovan3__ your brains snussed lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donovan3__ what you slavering about Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a waste of 12 grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work this week is as slow as a week in the jail ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joestevens_ am terrified for next year ðŸ˜¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckynicolx how times have changed... ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexJohanson3 happy bday mate hope it's a good one ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadeas93 happy bday jadeo hope it's a belter ðŸŽˆ X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy bday to my main man Reggie Kray ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ have a good one sen @callumhope16 x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertoise @_ap88 @DanRodenby so if he knocks him down and doesn't beat the 10 count he wins by a slamdunk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertoise @_ap88 @DanRodenby since you put it that way that makes total sense. Great point there Dan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRodenby @bertoise you don't know shit about boxing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertoise @DanRodenby is it no double points if u get knocked down and bk up before the count of 10? Cos if he counts to 20 the fights over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertoise @DanRodenby what fight were you watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertoise had blackledge up 3 rounds as well. Smith is lucky this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollysamuel2 happy bday holly hope it's a good one ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scougall10 happy bday mate hope it's a belter ðŸ‘ðŸ¼x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadeas93 up in the big leagues wi yersell ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamnoble123 meet and greet the morn Asda at the Jewell if your ma wants her tits signed bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sean_Nicol apologies, there will be no further questions at this time. #nopaparazzi ðŸ“¸ðŸ–ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackrobbo_music happy bday jacko mate hope it's a good one ðŸŽˆx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamnoble123 @reececollins10 @callumhope16 @Footy_Jokes they think it's all over.... IT IS NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamnoble123 @reececollins10 @callumhope16 @Footy_Jokes ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ willy my man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 @callumhope16 @Footy_Jokes nae need to change the subject]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 @callumhope16 @Sporf aw aye mate mind that time Arsenal won the World Cup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumhope16 @Footy_Fooligans hats off to you mate that is some brilliant patter. How'd you think of that? Only you could mate. Fantastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhiSimpss22 happy bday hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@14aimeedalton happy bday Aimee hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joannavicx happy bday, have a belter X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 @donovan3__ there's breezy documentaries for you to chug over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donovan3__ @reececollins10 30 days free then need to pay for it mate #bumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 watched the grand tour yet on Amazon???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighMaltman happy bday hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawriec42 check the bookies mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Housebreakers are the genuine scum of the earth. Nout worse ðŸ”ªðŸ”ªðŸ”ªðŸ”ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday's drag like a motherfucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenAtkinson97 must've been doing that wi Berty cos that is a horrendous tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeWelsh10 happy bday ma Sen have a good one ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amiephilips happy bday hope it's a good one X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daisyforbess happy bday daisy hope it's a good one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawriec42 @Aldorobb old one is the exact same mate, different gravy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawriec42 aye mate. Home for 6pm so should be on for about 6:01pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 to 10 on a Monday morning and all I can think about is cod4 ðŸ¤“ðŸŽ®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenH9 class eh pulls on dem heart strings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reececollins10 the daddy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>