<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally everyone in He-Man and She-Ra is ripped but there aren't any gyms on Eternia or Etheria. I find the whole… https://t.co/2fdVFB8pkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have made an error during my last vinyl shop... https://t.co/u40pZq1oxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner @bloodandmud @Thesuperpig7 let's be honest, it wasn't hard finding candidates for the front row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#61minuteman #Greatestofalltime 
Jericho was robbed last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorTBDM Awesome recommendation mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is actually the most insane album I've ever heard. Incomprehensible https://t.co/JVx5CaIx0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud @joshgardner K Wood got in as even though there are fattier hookers, he cares too deeply about the Pieons. No matter the result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I avoided spoilers all day for the #WweRoyalRumble2017. Crap.
#PeterCapaldi no longer the Doctor. Crap.
TRUMP IS STILL PRESIDENT. Crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next 19 hours are 'Avoid #RoyalRumble Spoilers Time']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I'm hyped for the #RoyalRumble but tonight is all about #NXTTakeOver and one glorious man https://t.co/4jd6S3jvIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepaulwilliams @JiffyRugby Not read the book but that try was my introduction to league]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eleanorgoodman the best day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke_morton this is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to see a fight between soldiers wielding black and Yorkshire puddings. Delicious. Great reconstruction @Lucy_Worsley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MachoGrandePod Love that If These Trees Could Talk album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #WALvENG RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too
https://t.co/dd9x2nP1AW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ceritaylor @GreenManFest i'm going #whoop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephen_hill_UK Seeing them on Monday was totally bittersweet. So incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fat Tony from #TheSimpsons and Connie from #FamilyGuy (the popular girl) have the same surname. Incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KulaBeth Imagine inviting him in for tea and cake, and having him read the ingredients in a dramatic voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian McKellen on discovering he was baptised: "Am I going to heaven? Oh that's fine..."
#WhoDoYouThinkYouAre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still trying to calm down after The Dillinger Escape Plan. Jeezus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to watch The Dillinger Escape Plan for almost certainly the last time. https://t.co/kyzBfc6O36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penblwydd hapus to Andrei, my favourite football player ever. https://t.co/eRXBHGtBmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Repka @bloodandmud @joshgardner and why the three year residency rule made him bite Rory Best with the force of a geriatric trout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud @joshgardner #Shit: the Premiership. Only two teams in the quarters. A sad, bloated, diabetic, poor man's Pro12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Repka @bloodandmud @joshgardner haha yeah, coz it's his technique that's the problem, not the fact he's a bellend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner he knows and still did the whole 'no hard feelings pal' to Big Will. Shameless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner Ridiculous. Saw Cubby in Cardiff last night, was gonna give him a proper admonishing... but he is WAAAY bigger than me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some horrendous diving by the #Falcons no 23. Does this happen much in #NFL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$1.5 billion for a new stadium in Atlanta. It looks like Kryten's head https://t.co/aZAlOb4WIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's definitely bonkers enough, but I wonder if Mourad Boudjellal has the millions needed to bring Julio Jones from the #falcons to Toulon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud proof as always that Will talks out of his arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepaulwilliams still a liability in defence but his broken play running is outstanding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about @SodabarOfficial in the wizz quiz in the toilets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well Trump may be President, but @SuperRugby starts in 33 days, @NRL in 41, @lionsofficial tour in less than five months. Priorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I...? I couldn't have! She was alive... I felt it...." https://t.co/ZRnRjFsIDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh well, most post-acopalyptic stories are pretty cool #inaguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BERNIE2020 is my new favourite for the #RoyalRumble https://t.co/9WPhyykCYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Avenged Sevenfold brought out their inflatable astronaut in Cardiff tonight https://t.co/F3z59QZD2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cue us reciting the entire Spinal Tap scene from The Simpsons https://t.co/3hJyn6xxNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great that Wales have rewarded form with new caps, but seriously are the wing and loosehead situations that desperate? #sixnations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're tiring on the long drive home from #WWEUKCT and @matthew_ogrady puts @hatebreed on the stereo https://t.co/qgMZBmn46L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for @SplitsMcpins and @sppurser to Duke it out in the final of the #WWEUKChampionship next year 
#savebowlarama @ATTACKWrestling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Da iawn @Tyler_Bate! Was great to see @ATTACKWrestling taking @WWEUKCT by storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to Tyler, but come on @PeteDunneYxB #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I'm the only person here not going nuts about Fin Baler. Soz #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing match and great atmosphere here. I was supporting @MandrewsJunior but great to see @PeteDunneYxB in the final #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look Ma, I'm on the telly #WWEUKCT https://t.co/mcgCdUHPCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic Pete #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Merl_Hammer no I forgot my kneepads so they won't let me compete. Corporate bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reesy The Reaper Rees has entered as a late wildcard in the #WWEUKCT https://t.co/1i5OobqFaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reesy The Reaper Rees has entered as a late wildcard in the #WWEUKCT https://t.co/q45Pdg9DTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Welcome to the North' https://t.co/eojfzfKTPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Blackpool with @matthew_ogrady for the #WWEUKCT finals 
Hopefully @PeteDunneYxB continues to misbehave @WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play the #wrestlekingdom11 Okada and Omega match is amazing. But how one of them didn't die is beyond me. Some of those bumps... Jeez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic Pete #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm from a bad place, I've seen things... I'm from Birmingham" 
#WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Racing 92 decide to take Europe seriously in round 5? Baffling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird to see Pete Dunne fighting against someone with a top knot #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SplitsMcpins @ATTACKWrestling anything for you Splits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of making a #SaveBowlarama sign to take up to #WWEUKCT tomorrow @ATTACKWrestling @SplitsMcpins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sppurser surprised you ain't there, you filthy heel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there tomorrow but stoked to be watching #WWEUKCT tonight. Let's go @PeteDunneYxB and @MandrewsJunior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howay the lads! https://t.co/jsNTCTFagW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can confirm this is EXACTLY what it's like to work from home https://t.co/Fp6ldG1KGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner didn't Bismark du Plessis get red carded for doing it against NZ a few years back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud #99problems when the physio and waterboys try to convince the linesman that the ball kicked out on the full was outside the 22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Last Kingdom is a tremendous series and so faithful to the books. David Dawson, Charlie Murphy &amp; Rune Temte are particularly awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Leaf Clover being belted out by @MetReloadedTrib 
Would love to see @Metallica play it next time they're in the UK. Hint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a testament to Metallica's songwriting that even their cover acts are far better live than so many bands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner @bloodandmud @Sourdust Andy's decisions are between him and the runes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner He's on a cryptic, intellectual space beyond my comprehension]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner He seems to have gone from 5 to 7 as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After @meshuggah in Bristol a guy said to me "Great show Jens!"
All us baldies look alike https://t.co/eKnihLM8n2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameyjasta At the Meshuggah show tonight dudes were shouting for 'The Alarm Clock riff!' 
You've started something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People on MDMA, when you take MDMA why do you go up to people who aren't on MDMA, tell them you're on MDMA and how much MDMA you've taken?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is basically my life. Every. Day. https://t.co/WouIJr9AUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm of the opinion that Bleed by Meshuggah may be the finest song ever recorded https://t.co/6YsYg3Yuc1 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Zeus is my witness I am NEVER cooking fish in the flat again.

The smell has been here for THREE DAYS!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eugehop10 you will love it mate. Enjoy it. And enjoy this day x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to everyone waking up to see their reactions to #watersportsgate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never have I wanted to attend a wrestling event more than this https://t.co/GZy8A2Cq42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nowplaying Kreator – Gods Of Violence. Four albums in a row of awesome thrash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephen_hill_UK Nothing will ever beat that wondrous satisfaction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephen_hill_UK I like S&amp;M, because it means I can say 'I like S&amp;M'.

Also Iced Earth – Alive In Athens &amp; Emperor – Emperial Live Ceremony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're struggling at the gym and @BehemothBand comes on shuffle https://t.co/YQP9MpwVn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Surfingsunshine I shall watch it with you :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Surfingsunshine Opinions? https://t.co/op4ONPDrr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently watching a #lakeside2017 darts match between David Cameron and Jimmy Hendicks. The crowd are cheering for Cameron. 

Life is weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud @joshgardner SHIT: Matthew Morgan at full back. Was really mean of Glasgow to keep kicking high balls at him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday my mum told me a joke she'd heard from Cardiff RFC legend Steve Ford about 20 years ago. Still funny.
Great wing, lovely bloke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammymaine I do lots of stretches/yoga to fall asleep. By the time I'm done my muscles are calming down and I tend to drop off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine not liking Phil Collins!
Who are these content, well-adjusted people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love when someone bombs a two on one overlap and drops the ball on the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Repka Depravity Favours The Bold by Anaal Nathrakh actually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess what I'm listening to... https://t.co/OSReBvQgTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgardner I love how your negativity gets disproved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloodandmud I think it was his insistence on wearing a long sleeve base layer and scrum cap that did him in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Merl_Hammer haha I have just been on a very mediocre date and she said EXACTLY the same thing]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>