<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Prime Minister confirms the election date will be announced later today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What on earth is with Wellington's weather. Yet again, I thought the wind was going to lift my house up overnight, wizard of oz style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fig farmers capitalising on Hawke's Bay's drought
https://t.co/Ynz7VRnPs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At HN water inquiry, Hastings DC water services manager Brett Chapman reveals there was campylobacter found in the Brookvale bores on Jan 19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnmck419 you cover politics, I'll do the sports? I think staying here in the hot sun for the ODI is a good idea https://t.co/3RTbQVkeci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnmck419 I'm really good at sports pickups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tfw the Aussie cricket team rock up to your hotel with a truck full of gear. @Johnmck419 do you need a sports picku… https://t.co/0ul7pTCTpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Havelock North's had more problems with water than any other region
https://t.co/AErVjwGWFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @rarahsobson @CTrevettNZH but junior j j j you look like you're laughing. You're secretly one of us now, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So wrong. We all know it's a potato fritter. https://t.co/LaudO2Fq3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hastings DC has had more "transgressions" with its water supply than any other area, the Havelock North inquiry has heard today @1NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheep probable cause of gastro outbreak in Havelock North
https://t.co/FMRo9GtfMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr @SparkNZ they said all day yesterday that it was fixed for most people. I had no working phone from 9.45am to 6.30pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little says his Chinese horoscope says he should expect favourable fortune in 2017. Says English's is his luck will decline from Sep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Little jokes we've had a terrible summer - and points out the sun finally comes out on a long weekend when Lab/Greens come together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metiria Turei using her SON speech to pay tribute to women, in particular Helen Kelly &amp; Jeanette Fitzsimons. Urging women to keep fighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedian Guy Williams introducing the Labour &amp; Greens leaders as leaders of the next Government https://t.co/l7yHyXZTTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spark outage has made things slightly difficult at the state of the nation. People scrambling to use hotspots of those who have signal etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @SamSachdevaNZ You better not take my mantle as the hottest date in town Diva 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy Williams on stage warming the crowd up ahead of Labour/Greens state of the nation. Standing room only, people o… https://t.co/4kB3cfbEWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @JoKiwi55 @coltheman1 @pukeko65 agreed. Trolls might need to think about mental health a bit more as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil @CTrevettNZH a little like the gallery party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 @coltheman1 @pukeko65 @philquin am I being attacked for doing a story on mental health? So much irony there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddBarclayMP I count 8 young professionals in Gore!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overhaul at Wellington mental health services - but it's just the tip of the iceberg https://t.co/xBeVwjJEcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamSachdevaNZ @jo_moir we all know what telling a girl she looks tired means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamSachdevaNZ it's because you told me I looked terrible cc @jo_moir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShayneCurrieNZH I watched this twice and I still can't even believe that it's not a parody. It's worse than awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook i just can't imagine what he was possibly thinking in even asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook I assume this was more of "you want chips with your burger, right?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigmcculloch I think this is great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @rarahsobson That's what they all say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rarahsobson @jmodoh I know it's hard to believe JJJ-Junior, but the world doesn't revolve around Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh All three of you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh Also, blows my mind you actually thought NZers celebrated Australia Day in any way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh What pub?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pineyzb Now THAT is one of the best ideas I've ever heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dunne has officially launched a petition to get our summer holidays moved to Feb. Says we did it with daylight saving, why not this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook I'm pretty sure this is the first and only time anyone has ever said that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending on pokie machines up, despite number of machines going down - so the Government is demanding answers https://t.co/c1qAeNp1YC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyFoodBagNZ @onewilliamsj it's pretty good. And was always close to 3 meals for me. So maybe half a meal for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH and @alexTarrant is wearing his best dress shorts for HIS first post cab back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No election date today but "fairly shortly" English says, once he's told his caucus colleagues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good afternoon and happy new year" - Bill English kicks off his first post-cabinet press conference https://t.co/Oh8PiDcBib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the newest member of the press gallery @giaisonline. A few technical difficulties earlier in the day but we'll make her welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dkinita See my next tweet - typo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minimum wage to increase to $15.75 from April 1 (correcting typo in last tweet). The starting out wage will go from $12.20 to $12.60.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 @kimbakerwilson And that's why we love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 It's called your iphone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana @jo_moir @kelly_armitage1 Jo, ignore those two, they're trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell that's what happens when all of Wellington's best cafes are closed 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir I'm glad you're home safe then!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels a bit like winter but let's hope it warms up a bit for Wellington Cup Day. Pretty good date too @jo_moir https://t.co/TKbRM9ugJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz Who even are you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last interview with @ambmarkgilbert before he leaves for the US tonight will be on @1NewsNZ. And one last selfie… https://t.co/hnb6jCGDWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz woohoo 30! This seems appropriate considering your eating habits. Have the best 2 day birthday xx https://t.co/rPel1xUIsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinHague @wimon_song @maggiebarrynz @kimberleysavage wow. Really wish we had known that - and found it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinHague @wimon_song @maggiebarrynz what IS it though? @kimberleysavage and I walked around trying to find it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wimon_song got so lost trying to find what the actual circle of friends is the other day. I'm sure there's symbolism in that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir You think the attic is bad. You should try the windowless bunker. The attic is glam compared to this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh regretting making fun of the weather warnings now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm well used to Wellington's wind, but can't say I've ever felt like it was ripping through the inside of my house like it was all night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil you mean places with more than one vowel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristinhallNZ oh so it was God that nearly killed me, not a drunk driver? Makes sense 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aehodgkinson trains. Cars. Food. Repeat endlessly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rarahsobson @jo_moir maybe that explains things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @rarahsobson wish we could blame the apple shortage for a lack of this https://t.co/ZAGfjgafq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @rarahsobson @francescook and I were having a lovely lie on the beach this arvo, until we got slammed by flying sand/stones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aehodgkinson this is what Snapchat is for! I'm always sending outfit choices via snaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelly_armitage1 tbh it's probably a good thing for everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelly_armitage1 so no more playsuit wearing for me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LachlanForsyth got my clean, unworn hoodie in my bag for just this purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope good, just in time for my arrival. I've barely worn a jersey for 3 weeks, so I'm really looking forward to this 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson I KNOW! I'll be back up soon. Or come to Wellington, I hear the weather is spectacular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellingtonians, on a scale of 1 to i-really-really-hate-this, how bad is the weather today for my return?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir at least you'll be able to afford a house now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelly_armitage1 so proud of him right now 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 thanks so much to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 welcome home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauliolo @emmawehipeihana @kelly_armitage1 if only Emma had any sway over any of the hosts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell is now the right time to tell you i plan to spend the day at the beach?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kerry_McBride if I don't check for a couple of hours I come back on &amp; @mcquillanatorz @rarahsobson have so many news updates for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello from the @ASB_Classic. Great day back at the tennis. https://t.co/RyjwLzhkeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnmck419 My parents reaction upon discovering it was worth the 3 minutes I saw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnmck419 it's an entire show about making &amp; delivering pizzas. For the sake of your brain cells, please stop watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnmck419 I thought this was some "sporting" thing. My parents were channel flicking &amp; have screamed with horror on realising it's real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick I know I keep ranting but I REALLY REALLY want to know how much time any of these people have spent at Waitangi on the 4/5/6th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir was it Ash? 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going through decades of family photos. Found this treasure of myself &amp; my now deceased older brother. Always about… https://t.co/MbRjjrYg1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LachlanForsyth I usually am. Unsure this year. Definitely go if you can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Head_Weasel @LachlanForsyth Feb 5 is the day of big (aka more eventful) protests. Feb 6 there's a hikoi but it's peaceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @SamSachdevaNZ oh and brunch. But that's usually tied in with either post-gym or post-wine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @SamSachdevaNZ no more texts for you. We shall communicate about gym and wine via telepathy only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @SamSachdevaNZ but now we get to send the fun texts! You know how 'tis one of my life highlights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdee155 @MikeThorpeTVNZ @jo_moir not at all. Read my tweets. I'm saying the 6th at Waitangi is a true celebration of our national day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdee155 @MikeThorpeTVNZ @jo_moir We are talking about the 6th mate. Those things happened on the 5th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @grantrobertson1 I am very jealous of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Most politicians leave after the dawn ceremony. Perhaps more should stay. https://t.co/xt519u6TCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 agree. That's my point about the 6th. It enhances prejudices to make it sound like there are problems on the 6th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 yes. It's simplifying it but the 5th is for talking (and listening) and the 6th is commemoration &amp; celebration.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>