<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasha1880 @DailyCaller I know I saw something. I look for it. He also could have called their PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasha1880 @DailyCaller I believe Pres Trump offer support to Canada for that attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ @POTUS These 2 r ridiculous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Media should've more upset about the horrible rioting last night at UC Berkeley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harlan This is crazy!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @FoxNews Instead of what it's about / national security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @FoxNews Govt officials (mostly DEMs) sld be ashamed of themselves making this politics....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @FoxNews The problem is our im laws weren't enforced the past 8 yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CNNPolitics @realDonaldTrump WOW! Not sure what the rest of the interview was like but interesting its not negative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RodgerDodger4 @Harlan DEMs already have.2 of dems r introducing a bill 2 take this away from the president and give to congress.Stupid ppl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @BernieSanders Typical DEM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me and 8 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsoutrage @DailyCaller Sorry but the DailyBeast msg she refers to is wrong.She sld understand that she wld be doing this for the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart @rushlimbaugh Thank U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart @rushlimbaugh what is 4chan mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manofhonour1990 @AwakenOne16 @Ike_Saul @KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump Then don't engage in conversation. No need to be so mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwakenOne16 @manofhonour1990 @Ike_Saul @KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump Why is Ned Stark so mean?  Is that really necessary? Seriously why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwakenOne16 @robinhardage @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls @Ike_Saul OMG - everything w/ the DEMs to racism. What is up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzybtzgoliath @young_maymay @MeghanMcCain Why does everything with liberals end up being racist? Enough already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouverboomer I have a job and have had my job for over 22 years. U have no idea what ur saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@speechcoachjody @young_maymay @MeghanMcCain with HRC/Dems it's always the same.Every1 is racist on the opposite side. A new line is needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mememoreme Macy's jobs on BO watch like all the other jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump Their ALL so predictable! They think there sooo important but their not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle This why I have no intention on watching. Sore losers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @MSNBC @NAACP @SenatorSessions Voter should be checked wagainst the voter rolls in ea state when voting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @MSNBC @NAACP @SenatorSessions There is absolutely NO reason not to have ID to vote.It's easy to get an ID.Poorexcuse by Dems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's time for everyone to get on board. Stop the negativity.If DJT succeeds WE ALL succeed.I would think we ALL want that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWorldsFrates @DailyCaller @SpeakerRyan Geez enough already from the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwakenOne16 Email of support sent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Wish I could but will be watching on TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 American is a Constitutional Republic unique &amp; needs to stay that way. NO to BIG Government,NO to Socialism,NO to Globalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KassyDillon @KalasiaRicher Love your banner. 2017 is going to great and entertaining too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Have a little humor ppl. This is pointed at the media. The media was soooo bias. Stop over thinking ever tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Most ridiculous thing I've heard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calypso1000 @danabradford7 @AwakenOne16 Trump is not racist. This is all liberal media propaganda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwakenOne16 @mimimpls That includes other politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwakenOne16 @mimimpls Exactly- Words. Ppl are delusional if they think other men or women in some cases haven't said horrible things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs Get back control of the internet that BO give them in October!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GilesBgiles1974 @jackieevancho It's time for the liberals to start acting like adults.Be supportive.Stop picking on ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller WOW hold the presses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ @ShepNewsTeam @FoxNews @realDonaldTrump That's Why I only watch Fox&amp;friends then switch to Fox Business until Hannity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlphaRomeo223 @WalshFreedom Don't think so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Why are you reacting to anything this rag reports? Wait to hear from @realDonaldTrump himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HankFontenot @Harlan God bless u Harlan. U should receive battle pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @BuzzFeedNews It was obvious right from the beginning that this was fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ Why didn't BO do this investigation before now? Ridiculous! This is all a/b discrediting Trumps pres. Bunch of lib cry babies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ Extra - it was only reported on Fox which is majority of Trump supporters anyway. Impact seems minimal on the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ 3/3 foreign actor. Plus this had nothing to do w/ the election.It was the emails.If think a/b it MSM didn't report on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ 2/3 - Lets get that straight. Also- who's the so called source? Until it's official I wld hold ur judgement.Could be any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddHeadleeAZ 1/3 - It's not 17 agencies it's two (CIA &amp; NSA) that are at the investigation level. The other 15 just review their outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart How about the women that r not shopping today. Apparently they want to prove women have power to impact the economy.STUPID!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart Libs are behaving patheticly. GOP would not be carrying on like this, especialy this long. Get over it already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp Not denying reality-I listen &amp; invest. all avenues.Also take some news with a grain of salt depending on the source.U sld too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom They haven't confirmed this......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp U may want to read this article as well. https://t.co/X0N4gPkelq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp I get it u don't like Trump. So basically anything he says ur not going like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp He's saying they need to investigate ALL foreign actors. U don't want to rule out others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp @TheChrisSuprunExcept FBI says something different than the CIA.Let's wait and see what the end result is. Every1 loves 2 judge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip So that's a misleading statement for sure. Way to take that out of context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Another area that needs to be cleaned up is the voter rolls &amp; everyone should have to show ID to vote. Enough w/ that nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattiestepp @TheChrisSuprun Talk about FAKE news. Typical Liberal bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Joe- U &amp; Everyone else should stop the drama. It's not the election. It's the DNC and podestas emails their referring to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 7 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity #Hannity No!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews she's ridiculous! These ladies on the view think ppl care what they have to say. We don't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PastorCRBoston @brianstelter @realDonaldTrump Let's talk truths here - fake news comes out of CNN frequently. Their bias gets in their way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcgreenx @PastorCRBoston @brianstelter She's been unprofessional on many occasions- she debated Trump during a debate - not her role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcgreenx @PastorCRBoston @brianstelter it was in the news. Look it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcgreenx @PastorCRBoston @brianstelter Are u kidding- she was crying on air, ridiculous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec What is the background on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller When will ppl start acting like grown ups?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller DC no one cares about your opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart not sure what u mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller So glad their thinking of the American ppl!These senators are there to work for the ppl.They've lost sight of that.Time he goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has to STOP https://t.co/idBZA1rhgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce @chippergaines @joannagaines @hgtv @CBNNews Love watching Chip and Joanna on fixer upper!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii What a whack Jill Stein is! This is such a waste of time. MOVE IN already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom @FoxNews It's like the person who gets evicted &amp; trashes the place on the way out. What a/b our So. border? OB doing nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke can't the state say NO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/Xt2rJFR8ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom It's time for all the whiners to grow up and get on board with the rest of the country and support our new president.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>