<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@McDermottQC I was thinking the same - apparently resiling from the Paris Agreement is imminent. Extraordinary times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit: MPs debate article 50 bill - Politics live | Politics | The Guardian https://t.co/Ut3vJdlWWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DermotTcd @lorcansirr @doccer oh, I think that's just *one* of the worries of what's being overlooked in the rush to build #housingquality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C as we all know down here in the Free State, he's the Holy Spirit in human form.  So probably...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C oh, I think I'd only get into trouble for loving the law too much...but maybe you could do it..!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Sessions, pressing #SallyYates on whether she could say no to the President; she stands up for the Constitutio… https://t.co/DCFmLiHAGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting attorney general who said travel ban was not lawful – live | US news | The Guardian https://t.co/BH1zyMVcsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems the right time for a shout-out to Gilberto Bosques Saldivar.

'Mexican Schindler' honored - latimes https://t.co/S4XO5Pl3n2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C @CyprusAvenue228 ...and fantastic company...remember?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[while you are not safe I am not safe...

#Resistance

Howl by Allen Ginsberg | Poetry Foundation https://t.co/XeiN8aBPTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting #HomeSweetHome

 Squatters turn oligarch's empty London property into homeless shelter | The Guardian https://t.co/0yFHPb2pbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make America Hate Again:

Orwell’s “1984” and Trump’s America - The New Yorker https://t.co/8uFUcgLWJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifying - people's lives will be devastated by this, and families and communities torn apart. https://t.co/2nMhHWw8Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and perhaps his parting gift to us: 

1984 (John Hurt) - Official Trailer - YouTube https://t.co/1xAMFDZRDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and how I will remember him:

John Hurt in 'Krapp's Last Tape' - Video - https://t.co/z1woMOKbHj https://t.co/gnhLjkN1ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How my children remember the great John Hurt:

Harry Potter &amp; the Sorcerer's Stone | Harry's Wand - YouTube https://t.co/0AgqvZ7ms5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, John Hurt. I had the pleasure of seeing him twice in Krapp's last tape.  Such a loss.  https://t.co/P9V5PF8YC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd add - check building control records...

Buying a new house off plans? Here’s what you need to know https://t.co/BoH94zHSoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families unable to sue but Stardust owners took £3m claim https://t.co/GEYru2ylVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A child under the age of 10 dying every 10 minutes' - Threat of famine in Yemen https://t.co/0EcQ3paNX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Party leaders join Article 50 application https://t.co/xlvhag61uO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On way to TV3 to speak about the legacy of housing defects and what can be done, with @MaoiliosaRey &amp; @Mickcliff  https://t.co/7eTAiFo3Ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US State department's entire senior management team quits as Secretary Rex Tillerson takes up post | The Independent https://t.co/1UnG6AMw7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Trump, the Doomsday Clock Advances Toward Midnight - The New York Times https://t.co/KQ8W9SYtz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the #Brexit Bill.  The title is nearly as long as the operative section. https://t.co/WqaIUMlbg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New hate crime package to target groups at need - Press releases - GOV.UK https://t.co/N2YuQ7xX8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @cathmartingreen - Developers with poor compliance records allowed to keep building - regulator needed

https://t.co/ohgrm4C9DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong words, but no action:

Rogue developers ‘should never be allowed to build again’, says Taoiseach https://t.co/wzZusGjySF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmckibben Very tough times; it would be easy to feel overwhelmed and helpless, which you clearly don't. Thank you from Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..and why there was still no regulatory body for builders and underfunded local authority building control @BRegsBlog @cathmartingreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRegsBlog Yes. @cathmartingreen called for review of housing defects and asked why no law reform to provide dispute resolution &amp; remedies..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@navi226 oh, I'll bore you about the liability problems post-gig at some point.  And I have a paper on the topic if you'd like a copy ?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@navi226 builders can appoint their own employees to inspect, and good luck with working out who's liable under the 'super duper' Regs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @cathmartingreen, calling for review into housing defects and law reform:  

"Rebuilding Ireland - let's get it right this time"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but disappointing that Government won't commit to review of causes of housing defects and law reform needed to provide remedies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear support from Taoiseach for independent oversight of building &amp; enforcement of building control

@BRegsBlog @cathmartingreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taoiseach:  Rogue builders should not be allowed to build again: independent supervision required on construction sites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy @cathmartingreen calls for review into housing failures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remedies for housing defects raised by @cathmartingreen in Dáil

Watch Oireachtas TV , Houses of the Oireachtas https://t.co/bZ0GC0qGju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C @SpinningHugo Welcome to supremacy, EU law's equivalent of God making a rock that's too heavy for God to lift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C @rtenews It would hardly be the time to cosy up to our Parliament while ignoring her own (and yours).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fdelond well done Fiona - really clear explanation and context for today's judgment.  I liked 'this is where politics takes over..']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect to Gina Miller for standing up for democracy and the rule of law; it's appalling that she was vilified &amp; threatened for doing so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 2016 post on the legal context for the #Beacon South Quarter apartment defects: 

February | 2016 | Constituo https://t.co/498zwwTcGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['What's the solution?' @todaysor. No commitment by Government to law reform to provide remedies for homeowners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['For future developments homeowners have accountability throughout the process' due to BCAR: I don't agree, @josephamadigan on @todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surveyor on @todaysor suggests going after professionals - despite suggestion that problem is fire safety rather than design]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussion now on @todaysor re . #Beacon South Quarter apartment defects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Neuberger: No obligation to consult the devolved legislatures of Northern Ireland, Scotland and Wales #Article50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Neuberger: The 2016 referendum is of great political significance, but an authorising Act of Parliament is needed to trigger #Article50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Supreme Court: Gov can't trigger Art 50 without Parliamentary approval]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Issue in these proceedings have 'nothing to do' with whether UK should leave EU, or the terms on which it should do so #Article50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the Article 50 decision from Court 1 of U.K. Supreme Court : Live https://t.co/V0njlBn9D4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many more lives will be ruined by housing defects before Government &amp; industry solve this?

#Beacon #Millfield #Riverwalk #longboatquay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready to stand up for the UK Supreme Court:

Supreme court poised to deliver article 50 judgment | The Guardian https://t.co/JSDRwVcUoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for an enquiry &amp; solutions for housing defects:

South Dublin apartment owners face €10m bill to fix defects https://t.co/4pjpotWdHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May knew about Trident failure before renewal vote | UK news | The Guardian https://t.co/qRoaET9Umu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Climate Change Risk Assessment 2017 | Committee on Climate Change https://t.co/hceTvhyvqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awful news - very distressing for the children and teachers of Scoil Naithí  https://t.co/DDUB5ieCXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government 'tried to bury' its own alarming report on climate change | The Independent https://t.co/DZL0RXBX2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative facts... https://t.co/Av6KE7k6ZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lorcansirr well spotted! I'll finish that piece...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edepaor @Steven__C @Doctor_J_ great share E: "I can’t think of a better time in history to hear a woman scream-sing her head off."- quite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump protest - marches going on worldwide | The Irish Times https://t.co/MYExMy1grm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers as we turn the corner and see thousands ahead of us #womensmarchdublin https://t.co/exfATcUu9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge crowd here for the #womensmarchDublin https://t.co/s7gVGfVLAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How vulture companies tried to influence Department of Finance https://t.co/1UIxqmSgtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_Regan and of how only the philosophers are fit to rule, as anyone with a trade will necessarily have a conflict. Hmmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oconnola fascinating.  Imagine the impact if everyone stopped turning right and also stopped eating beef...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emmett_Scanlon me neither...I blame
the Americans...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJohnFoyle @felicebrothers well *somebody* nearly went to Black Sabbath
@Doctor_J_ 
but the draw of Friday night BBC4 was too great...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJohnFoyle Am at home watching a Status Quo documentary in lieu of the cancelled @felicebrothers ...!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emmett_Scanlon how many words did you manage to write ?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McDermottQC It really makes Boris Johnson's boasting about being first in line for a trade deal seem hopelessly naive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeRebCelts @OisinOhAlmhain perhaps you missed this earlier in the week?

https://t.co/Qs0kRs8J9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner I started to watch, out of solidarity for Hillary, but I couldn't stomach it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This won't cheer you up - OK Go brilliantly repurpose Morrissey's Interesting Drug: https://t.co/SczloqKTym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Inauguration of Donald Trump: Preserve, Protect, and Defend - The New Yorker https://t.co/4ynx9s5n6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Paisley jnr urges DUP to follow example set by McGuinness https://t.co/RuFTrCHsR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emmett_Scanlon stay away from twitter !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C you'll be in the Hockeyverse.

Stormont to host international hockey tournament https://t.co/qJ83eLOpdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryano Wow.  They really played their part when it came to environmental sustainability...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bentonra anytime now, time machine...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re not out to punish Britain, but you need to shed your illusions | Guy Verhofstadt | Opinion | The Guardian https://t.co/i6Xq1980pZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global warning: live from the climate-change frontline as Trump becomes president | Environment | The Guardian https://t.co/aV54PLu9Kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balanced and insightful piece from Karlin Lillington: We must beware Julian Assange’s opportunism 

@IrishTimes  https://t.co/xhTvOrUb8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkconnolly tweet of the year https://t.co/eKjnLzWn1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkconnolly @Steven__C 

"Harry Truman, Doris Day, Red China, Johnnie Ray..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme court to deliver Brexit ruling on 24 January | Politics | The Guardian https://t.co/NIZChizfU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pyrite scandal: Widowed with two children in a crumbling home https://t.co/lvJouObotD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No EU country has unconditional access to the EU market - it's not a 'punitive deal' to deny that to the UK.
 https://t.co/WWteNqGcfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats off to @BrendanCourtney and family for telling their story of getting care for their Dad. Crazy that Fair Deal doesn't cover home care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanCourtney @RTEOne @SimonHarrisTD Well done to you and all your family for this. Unbelievable that FD doesn't cover home care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C don't think I didn't notice Terence Trent D'Arby in your cassette box, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven__C I was a big fan in the day thanks to Dave Fanning...I have that tape somewhere.
Meanwhile, Henry Kissinger is on telly, cue song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unfortunate that Theresa May is following Trump's lead by referring to reciprocal, collaborative international relationships as 'deals']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccferrie @LovinDublin @AlanaLav great news !! I'll be there on opening night .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliamentary consideration of Brexit 'deal' is looking like an optics exercise, as No10 is prepared to ignore it: https://t.co/irROOV3cK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of seeking Parliamentary approval only for the 'final' Brexit deal is that Parliament will have little scope to change it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantDCostello I think that she also suggested that they'd be traitors if they asked any questions about the negotiations. Fun times ahead.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>