<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[NO WIND at the top of Mt Kau Kau ! #whywellington https://t.co/ztdSpSaQSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Davies: 'There’s nowhere more beautiful than Wellington' https://t.co/18HeYMjwF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell Whangamata, thanks for a special holiday with all my boys https://t.co/tpilTPmnOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reading @AWDTNZ Hawke's Bay woman juggles running a farm as well as family https://t.co/SZ4lRwOV6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From the Ritz to a Padded Cell: A Workaholic’s Lesson on Love and Loss"" https://t.co/nZI7eOig6P by @lindseyboggs on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michey620 @HiddlestonMark I was planning to do some IOD study but far too nice a day in the Capital. https://t.co/Ai7s4dSstL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMHorgan @mjbulloc so I missed the opportunity to taste and judge. #disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for you @michey620 https://t.co/SKcyBvLE5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Athlete mentality lessons &amp; limitations for business leaders | London Business School https://t.co/RrFZgIaTgQ via @LBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a morning to walk to work.#WhyWellington https://t.co/UDZhviXmG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s stalling progress for women at work? @mckinsey https://t.co/qf5mXq7Be6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANZ HR helping out at Wellington City Mission #christmas spirit https://t.co/OwM9Mlsm93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaquie Brown: Pondering the "why" of Christmas  https://t.co/0KDXLcmW78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special day decorating our tree #familytradition https://t.co/PsEY03pa8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jake Millar: How John Key changed my life https://t.co/ahaa4xXXv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban children learn about maths on dairy farms https://t.co/dfbDL7GH6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mahe Drysdale shares his stories for International Men's Day  @ANZ_NZ . What an inspiration. https://t.co/O5WjAmfdPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMHorgan thanks for MCing International Men's Day, love the talk re male role models https://t.co/lKUnaYYgpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Evan Williams , fantastic work onboarding employees with disabilities at ANZ @ANZ_NZ STAR awards https://t.co/rTSr2D5whd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using finance and psychology to fight fat https://t.co/dIh6xAOfWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic initative from ANZ  Wellington ICT Graduate School partners with ANZ | https://t.co/Nio06zodav https://t.co/BDri9v7lbX via @voxynz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspirational from an 11 year old https://t.co/M2pUrXSxNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud that ANZ is supporting Transgender awareness week @LaQuishaStR @ANZ_NZ https://t.co/zC8LyW3Zw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larissa_beeson and we loved having you back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food for thought....@GeorgiaDry LinkedIn thinks campus recruiting hurts diversity https://t.co/MiFxsMbiRT via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up with his view this morning the Navy has arrived! #WhyWellington https://t.co/nT4vz9dDjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is up to all of us to shape the world we live in https://t.co/RZG7Un9k7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know the policy positions of Clinton and Trump Take our test to find out! https://t.co/uoallBHMce via @nzstuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for you @lorenmckean Why the modern PA is invaluable  | ANZ BlueNotes https://t.co/s0OGi12wUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More men named Peter heading up ASX companies than the total number of women?https://t.co/5wOBX4Cxnm via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant morning up Mount Kau Kau #WhyWellington https://t.co/kIpm4LxOam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching grads to be flexible is more important than worrying about jobs that don't yet exist https://t.co/ARTC6kNA5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first Apple Pay purchase! Instant coffee #applepay https://t.co/2f0iOUjUHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @justin_lester look forward to seeing Wellington develop and work together under your leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to share ANZ gender diversity stories at NZ Law Conference for Practice Managers https://t.co/bkt36jO0Z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why men don’t go home to look after the baby | ANZ BlueNotes https://t.co/ZTMWvMS8f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half a world away: how the All Blacks fathers miss their children https://t.co/fSjUICcs8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Wellington! #Whywellington https://t.co/2d6NzoKAA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exercise for Happiness! Why I'm addicted to exercise but don't care about my abs https://t.co/8ETc3JlGrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMHorgan @FelicityJEvans @lorenmckean happy to judge, Agria are my favourite though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great sponsorship by @ANZ_NZ @JBennettNZ https://t.co/lHprHSvRWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you think @TMHorgan The worst things people do at the gym  https://t.co/Wun1odUc4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaMMCL thank you for sharing your inspirational story about goal setting and your adventures on Te Araroa trail https://t.co/rUpgMvddIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whywellington Huffington Post lauds Wellington's 'remarkable' creative resurgence https://t.co/WtFyArTuvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How cool is that! Kiwi Paralympics swimmer Mary Fisher can hear her gold medal https://t.co/sbnsqnPFoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AWDTNZ it was a pleasure to speak at the Elevator session last night and what an amazing group of Rural women! https://t.co/MvTgQUzVmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMHorgan hope you had all your safety gear on.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 things about New Zealand that shocked me https://t.co/w0QfRxMyci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andsal_andrew sorry just chocolate for a 50 year old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an awesome day working together as an ANZ team whilst supporting child cancer.  https://t.co/uS3p58lxyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FennCarl You missed my first message. Happy birthday! https://t.co/7vLGoP8s2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 50th Carl Fenn!! https://t.co/kxyvZCIHf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all you Wellingtonians I have to share this  "You're the bucket to my fountain". Love it #whywellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise words from Richard Branson Life is not a journey to retirement https://t.co/9yXJ8Cgnga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why Finland has the best schools https://t.co/Tv4AU7ZbeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has worked for our family too! https://t.co/c9EZwAcNQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hannah_A_McD keep an eye out for my son Angus, he's having midterm break with 4 mates there....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SilverFerns have done their job, now it's the turn of the All Blacks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable... Kiwi rower Eric Murray claims he was told having a child would ruin his career in 2011 https://t.co/i08EIvhnUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All set with my baking for the annual Bake Sale for Daffodil Day @ANZ_NZ #daffodil day @NZCancerSo https://t.co/uCidnuejbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One weird trick for winning lots of Olympic medals: funding female athletes https://t.co/6TAVXl3KHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like Spring at Lyall Bay today #whywellington https://t.co/jwaQlAasgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Inspiring Sports Mantras from Olympic Athletes https://t.co/luyBsjdKmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to save experience from the scrap heap | ANZ BlueNotes https://t.co/hw4bfAX2BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pink ghetto?! Human Resources Institute survey results show $10K gender pay gap  https://t.co/hGOHkEqLEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ leads the way.... https://t.co/izHLiFuts7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warninternation thank you for sharing your story with NZ on Sunday TV Lance. Your honesty and humility is appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the Canes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captivating read: I walked from Liverpool to London. Brexit was no surprise | Mike Carter https://t.co/E26nbZunpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Aussies are flocking to the capital https://t.co/r0zH0mwj36 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoeverry interesting Governance session with Director panel at @AWDTNZ escalator evening https://t.co/p0oln3SULK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help her confidence! I will keep playing #LikeAGirl. Watch and join @Always to encourage all girls to keep playing! https://t.co/jIIy1UVx9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents under financial strain propping up adult offspring https://t.co/d4ORUELBtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Times have changed 'We weren't allowed to drive police cars' says woman who joined police in 1957 https://t.co/ELVVmqQRMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for ANZ and well quoted @SarahBerryNZ ANZ wins battle of the mortgages  https://t.co/57KbtjerHh via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help!!! Millennials consider 50 to be old age https://t.co/FWsWtkNx8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ones for you @SarahCourtNZ  https://t.co/pkQSXE2JrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the 80s I thought I was equal to men. Now I have teen daughters I know we're not | Alison Orme https://t.co/exGx07m7l1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that surprised me as a stay-at-home dad https://t.co/eaJyXSJlCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take note fathers....Dads who yell have more aggressive, less cooperative teenagers https://t.co/NJ8PmnOoAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FelicityJEvans listening to @ginamcjorrow sharing ANZs  progress on gender equality. @WEPrinciples #WEPs https://t.co/38oRsqt2kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear launch of Gender Equality Workplace Strategy #WEPs https://t.co/C2QGi9QRtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My top 10 quotes on family https://t.co/x3ZwBUyU1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All warmed up to watch the Pulse! @FelicityJEvans https://t.co/DhVnfpTSHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMHorgan @CraigBunyanNZ good luck to the ANZ team! Do us proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ardent cricket fans, watch this lengthy but humbling, inspirational speech.2016: Brendon Mccullum https://t.co/rSZbjzPOMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great move @WgtnCC Wellington city council announces new smokefree action plan  https://t.co/yBaoSIHFJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for you to read @AngusLC  https://t.co/hd1lCjsVPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth a read :Unlocking the Hearts and Minds of Millennials on Procurious https://t.co/rzY4pehzge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't agree more  https://t.co/OrQG4WH8ZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Make A Ms. Stake With A Person's Preferred Title https://t.co/5dsQUxM2bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good article @AWDTNZ Finding economic strength and diversity in New Zealand’s businesses https://t.co/q1k8zJD16m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Is it legal to force women to wear high heels at work? https://t.co/sAGGf3517L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic lyrics and music from six60 to all mothers https://t.co/NfsTqTlrAd via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mothers: Respect the strong, selfless women in your life https://t.co/LPvtTwXEnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weekend in Wellington, the world's coolest little capital https://t.co/uORXGvw7i2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaMMCL what a humbling experience to follow your adventure and personal growth. I have loved reading your blog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifteen things your kids will thank you for when they're older https://t.co/NBuVwLSClI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMBell @northernmystics @PulseNetball just wait for our comeback this quarter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FelicityJEvans  speed of the game defeated me! https://t.co/HiltD04NVs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>