<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Moonlight is quite possibly the most powerful film I've seen in some time. Fully deserves the award nominations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that in 2017 we're still categorising people by religion is just baffling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julio Arca would still walk into the Sunderland team. #safc https://t.co/B5pXKwYiSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @SwordsThunder. Doing the Fingal area proud. Well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your only job in life is to play football for ridiculous money then you have to beat the first man from a corner. No excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorPacKelly Some men just want to watch the world burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Human Traffic sequel is in the works.. https://t.co/wWMtizNTMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieGuildea The majority of 9/11 terrorists were from Saudi Arabia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's deplorable to ban people for the crimes of others but interesting to note that Saudi Arabia doesn't feature on… https://t.co/aaK5jotJyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chancing my arm here but looking for 2/3 tickets for @LoyleCarner at the Workman's. Can meet in Town. #TicketFairy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirJordann A true prophet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently spoke to @richardwade about the relocation of the Chargers from San Diego to LA. #nfl #chargers https://t.co/yvbsdLFULq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidAmoyal Spurs are the only other team who appear to have a solid structure in place. Whether they can catch Chelsea or not...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People sheltering from the rain seems rather fitting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sixers (2) have now lost less games in the new year than the Cavs (3). Something is brewing in Philly. #Sixers https://t.co/ni4nt8A9CM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Featured in Sports Illustrated - September 2015. #raptors https://t.co/MaNLLSIMEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland firmly on track to becoming Europe's leading nanny state. https://t.co/sKcrluyuFO
#ForcaBrasil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous that they seem so opposed to relegation/two divisions in American sports but relocating clubs is the nor… https://t.co/LDXaWjuMbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kavanagh on Meryl Streep's speech at the Golden Globes. https://t.co/p7otDzwXpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..but editorially the Irish Times let themselves down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I disagree with the views of the alt-right,to say they shouldn't be allowed publish their views in a democratic state is absurd..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely ridiculous numbers. https://t.co/VEFOrymT1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkable to think Ronda Rousey has spent little over 29 minutes inside the cage in her professional career. (14 fights)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany Grapples With Its African Genocide https://t.co/q9sMpXgwZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like the Warriors to blow a lead #NBAXmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke to James Gallagher earlier in the week about his fight with Anthony Taylor and what the future holds for him.… https://t.co/Vfig9HCo4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Mark Farren remembered at the #bbcspoty ceremony. https://t.co/YNy96dTns9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antonio Conte only lost four league games out of 63 between Jan and May while manager of Juventus. Make of that what you will. #CFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G9FDXODdnN Potentially three teams are set to be relegated from the League of Ireland next year. Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duquesnoy may be the best thing to come out of France since Claude Makelele. Excited to see him in action. #Bamma27 https://t.co/i2LN3fmOj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan Hartley served with a six week ban but returns the week before the Six Nations. Coincidental, surely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie Hopkins on the Late Late. Ian O'Doherty on #CBLive. Next thing we'll have Donald Trump presenting the Rose of Tralee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["58-35 Philadelphia. That is correct, 58-35 Philadelphia". Sums up the level of performance by the Sixers so far. #nba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who becomes interim featherweight champion if Holloway loses this weekend? God knows the division won't function without one #UFC206]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ecT9ijICaV Unbelievable from Klay Thompson. Moral of the story; draw on a goatee and you can achieve greatness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Ham club statement: "This behaviour has no place in football and West Ham United will work tirelessly to eradi… https://t.co/owWkZkkVgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/prOPj7SeKe Can't say I'm a huge gaming fan anymore but this has me very excited. First one was a masterpiece. #TheLastOfUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UC3xncLmo8 The best piece of sports journalism you're going to read all week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always, looking forward to a bit of Primal Scream later on.
https://t.co/XP7dQpcku7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Die like Irish warrior, don't run like chicken" - @TeamKhabib undoubtedly with the best call out of recent times.… https://t.co/xhdgao2tqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidlowe Sid, from an Irish point of view, can we expect to see him in a Welsh shirt in four months time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ajyhu48alp This is a great read from @BleacherReport on their hunt for the truth about Ali Dia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take it easy, Craig Gill. 
https://t.co/uJi1qKNrqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidlowe Ctrl+Alt-right+Del, then click 'end task'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From persona to talent, Joel Embiid seems to have it all. #BBQChicken https://t.co/0wNWBfTy2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Dyer, naughty geezer and certified historian. https://t.co/pMxAriHhSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone had the exact same thought until a few minutes ago. https://t.co/Ml2nSpVGsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I'd give to be back in the San Siro for the derby. It really is a special fixture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ. My eyes are yet to adjust to the kit clash, 20 minutes in. #MilanDerby https://t.co/mb7c9zNGh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fenno21 As a Sunderland fan, I agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fights cancelled on Irish soil in past 13 months:

Poirier v Duffy
Stipe Miocic v Ben Rothwell
Dong Hyum Kim v Gunni Nelson
McCall v Seery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian McCall is just not meant to ever fight again. Big loss for the card which is now wafer thin. #UFCBelfast https://t.co/9Oi15xsvV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baffling listening to Jonathan Irwin defending Pat Hickey on radio. Makes you wonder where some of the donations to J&amp;J foundation are going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drama and/or chaos seem to go part and parcel with the #BrazilGP. None more so than the 2003 GP https://t.co/4cA8GohT7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best lightweight in the game. Makes for an interesting interview. https://t.co/e06G6az4zG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCsixtyseven Of course, it should read; 'football impersonator attacks Elvis Presley impersonator']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's now understood as to why Conor McGregor was late to the press conference...#ufc205 https://t.co/EfEtwaP0vf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Red Bull's takeover of Swindon Town is imminent. For fans of Leeds United, you can rest easy knowing it's not your club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanSheehanBA @arielhelwani We very nearly made it, Seán. https://t.co/c0M28ej7r5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't say I'm surprised. If life has taught me anything, it's to never underestimate the stupidity of the human race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People of America, you know what to do. #ElectionDay 

https://t.co/12Cq8MyZuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life on earth - both fascinating and depressing in equal measure https://t.co/3NPWiO7jEx via @BBCEarth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TowerDublin @xdannyxbrownx @academydublin Atrocity Exhibition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The snake/iguana scene is by far the most pulsating television I've viewed in some time. Excellent, as per usual, @BBCEarth. #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a long time coming. Fair play, Cork City! #FAICupFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's exactly how football should be played. Shels are cruising. #WFAICup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clock out of work this evening and I'm on the first flight to Amsterdam tomorrow. The countdown is well and truly o… https://t.co/NaDAYXvc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely incredible. Football is nothing without fans. https://t.co/rOfLyhgnJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stranded at the bottom of both the country and Premier League table. #SAFC https://t.co/upKrU8P3ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pulp - The Day After the Revolution. What a way to go out @TXFMDublin #txfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing Dolberg in action this weekend. Very exciting prospect. #Ajax https://t.co/ShRWnfsou6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btsportrugby Quick question, will you be showing Ireland vs New Zealand match on Nov 5th in the UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a shame that Irish radio is set to lose its best radio station this evening. Thanks for the tunes @TXFMDublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eircare Followed. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who's going to become the next member of Dundalks back four to score?" @RTEsoccer fully aboard the bandwagon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's going to top this today. Gas. https://t.co/R5zNCPy7i7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firhouse is a circus, berserk as fuck...#makeasongdublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very convincing performance from @CastleknockGAA but all eyes are back on Parnell Park tonight. https://t.co/q8HsNZs1eO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenaMullins @LMFMRADIO Hey Helena, which show did this go out on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiohead to headline Glastonbury. Don't suppose there's any chance of an Irish gig next Summer? https://t.co/CdHe4GxuvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FIFA world rankings can confirm that Scotland are still shit at football. https://t.co/DtZLZLDB7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a child, I fondly remember scoring our only goal in a 5-1 defeat at Huntstown Villa to a very similar reaction f… https://t.co/kHCeYMcX4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not too hopeful for the future of this world after realising how many people are willing to pay €85 for Drake tickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big happy birthday to the big man, @NiallQuinn22 . Put the ball in the Arsenal net at my first ever Sunderland game many moons ago. #SAFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a Bohs fan, I've some fond memories of Tolka Park from over the years. Sad to see it go but best for both clubs in the long run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing gave me more enjoyment as a child than watching Schumacher do his thing on the track. The greatest ever. https://t.co/Ut6YIOHZHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first time Milan have displayed true character in a very long time. Great to see Locatelli get his name on the scoresheet. #ForzaMilan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracle at Medinah is in the past. Long live the horror at Hazeltine. #RyderCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SAFC Things can only get better. https://t.co/xR8ydcQqMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable achievement. Delighted for Stephen Kenny, one of the genuinely good guys in football. Fair play, @dundalkfc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UFC205 is getting ridiculous at this stage. Those lucky Yanks. https://t.co/8CyyvR3pUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gibney_A On somewhat of a side note, 34,000+ attended the ladies GAA final in Croke Park, Dublin the past weekend. Interest is on the rise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmcgahon_ @TheNotoriousMMA 9/4? Absolutely dreadful odds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Sam should have remained in Sunderland freezing his balls off rather than having the flame lit under his arse in London. Lesson learned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yeah, but does it have a five screen cinema? Forever in Balbriggan's shadow... https://t.co/mbzXFPUsrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an absolute gem Hidetoshi Nakata was. Cracking player. https://t.co/Kcay3WJRL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that Kevin Doyle and Aiden McGeady are in the squad is laughable really. #COYBIG https://t.co/pcbnLcURhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally finished Narcos but the whole Jim Morrisson working on a farm confused me I must admit. #Narcos https://t.co/ZSrIHqvh6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don King and Donald Trump together in one room. Much like dropping a live electrical wire into a bath, it guarantee… https://t.co/70E35VOB2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got word that #Brangelina is no more... https://t.co/PBC66pZ8et]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>