<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want a list? https://t.co/yAaoyRYYOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver @RoryDryden Glad to hear it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver I will miss the Smart cars. So easy to park!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an alarm near 38 1st ave west (The One) been sounding all night and still sounding. Are we going to have to listen to it all w/e?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farcical! Uneducated obviously! https://t.co/CCUnoc6JsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They could take a leaf out of Vancouver's Transit book. https://t.co/4iLVTY6OCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to see more of these. https://t.co/cnevaDISnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with a broken boat! https://t.co/MX1l4TXH9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will check this out. It's almost next door. https://t.co/wzyfqj2NYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is so difficult for older people to interact with others when they are going deaf or blind cos of ageing. https://t.co/ixxLYo1fTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a man of colour then? https://t.co/PuK04TnZNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money? https://t.co/o6kTsVL9mY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even bother 'mighting' anymore. https://t.co/3n0K0ClX2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Australian Navy didn't 'come across' him, they went to find him and did so. https://t.co/MzIiTjG4Bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the body in order is the tough part! https://t.co/zspUvXvhlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps they are giving him some more rope. https://t.co/tnNKjNxXg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sort of like streaming, right? https://t.co/4VabAbHA8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stop complaining people. Nature will not be tamed! https://t.co/2uAEmCausT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done the VVC! https://t.co/i0vz5pqV8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was as a result of the tower worker's strike. https://t.co/6ir4RUN8if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might as well ban all traffic then! https://t.co/pV4SxLxm0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He obviously doesn't know why he got it. https://t.co/tLwjOm0jy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out for crackpot therapies following this. https://t.co/um8kSCpIeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp re earlier problem:- sorted by phone. Thanks anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp no, didn't remove coax. Not there now. Will get back to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp having trouble connecting to the internet in Coal Harbour. Switched off and on. No change. Problems in that area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's moving house. https://t.co/M4vOWXSXoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SashaDryden @CinemaInFrames Gemini's areMay 20th to June 20th. You should know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark money looks apposite. https://t.co/Pxp07ZkvsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear! https://t.co/cbeJN6rylF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's life! And sailing. https://t.co/QFTCGEsAKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD? San Diego? Forget the record Jeanne. Just enjoy the journey! https://t.co/nN1nAaF7aI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's because you lack docking skills in a rib? https://t.co/ZQeDvPdxNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Book of Mormon? https://t.co/H4zdLTH9Fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope this doesn't give Trump ideas! https://t.co/fXTtVvWJF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_b_o so once your weight is taken by bosuns chair you draw your feet up pulling the board and slug up with them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble is, the law gives right of way to pedestrians at intersections so they don't feel it's necessary to loo… https://t.co/0VXjVwv96K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, great. I once had my ear nicked by a drunken barber. In California, I hasten to add. https://t.co/42ul3HZJ5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine but are they going to pay tax!? https://t.co/UpiZVvy3oZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless her! https://t.co/MM4hVmkO1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody cold it was! https://t.co/fepvOU6CZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God Bless America! May the best candidate win today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary thought. https://t.co/RP8xkwRNqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low frequency motor noise in the building keeping me awake. Thinking of going to the marina to sleep on the boat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't he holding the 'brolly over the lady's head? https://t.co/Mn2BjYZKQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DMReporter  will everybody please remain calm! Listen to yourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meat grinder at the local butcher evokes images of season 2. Recommend bacon not sausage for your breakfast tomorro… https://t.co/dJv8h2mGin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver can I take a car from Vancouver and finish the trip in the US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver @RoryDryden sorry i was trying to reply to the tweet about using a car across the US border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver can you leave the car there or do you have to bring it back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to charge your phone before using as no means of charging in the new cars. https://t.co/3AazrtR5pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure your phone is charged. No way to charge in the new cars. https://t.co/0FCGbABnXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great meal Slish! https://t.co/EJZBMyNT6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Bottled Sartori! https://t.co/sC61mRZDCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancityBuzz no Canadian airports on that map!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Canadian airports though! https://t.co/GrF1wyzHNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? https://t.co/yjE8511EQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too except I'm busy drinking coffee and checking my boat is afloat. https://t.co/TCD4HVXypv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bad weather forecast for tomorrow. @ Heather Civic Marina https://t.co/zdidboUsR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TELUSsupport No I am a user at the marina. Getting fed up with the random intermittent service. Nothing seems to be being done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TELUSsupport when are you going to get the wifi at Heather Civic Marina working properly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@car2goVancouver not one fourtwonew is showing up in my app so have not been able to try one out yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None available on my app! No B-types either. https://t.co/6bK46UWU9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out how they do it in the UK. They've been using them for years. https://t.co/O48N58c62I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pfbvan the alphabet. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time this was recognized! https://t.co/hPq2534s5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not just a matter of comfort but also of safety! https://t.co/0izShNhJ5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - F1 engineer makes 'first flat-pack truck' https://t.co/wQWzH7Gix6 what a good idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will make a change from having Starbucks on every corner. https://t.co/mEQ9Psw6VH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad these guys are on our side! https://t.co/Vy2Zw3X8uE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_UK you put your feet up dear and watch Coronation Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought that but then the pics from space would show that wouldn't they? https://t.co/Xi1gWS2x8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orca pod in Howe sound on Monday. https://t.co/PbwwLpvLAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing it didn't land on someone's head! https://t.co/KflyfmzXum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safer not to take anything.  https://t.co/ey0bEQXtUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What!?!? https://t.co/IFgefIsYbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmm........tough one! https://t.co/JxGkyvJ8oS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thanks to the kind people and first responders who came to my assistance when I tripped and headbutted the sidewalk this afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTCanoe what's a PTCJ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying ants!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImpracticalBoat how's it going Dave? Following tou in Vancouver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't bother! It will grow back. https://t.co/Q7kDjmVy50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must keep a statue on the boat. https://t.co/1eyoALKN6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can do it so can they! https://t.co/OTQ5Cs1f1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD car alarm sounding every 3:39 mins for the last hour somewhere around Olympic Village/Mount Pleasant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't feel well. Stay away from me. I'll be better soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can never get my head around this logic. I just sit. https://t.co/tQju3dPJDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_UK good idea maam. Couldn't be worse than the absolute shower in power now While you're at it take over Europe as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_UK What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's gone mad! https://t.co/isRLLIylUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do this all the time! https://t.co/oXJZazbBwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who indeed? https://t.co/haNywVlKUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. This can be positive or negative. https://t.co/InWxWAiyDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened? Did you fall off? https://t.co/zDhJ072Oy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is it about Richmond? Their proximity to the USA? https://t.co/0LwKDCAsl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you do the third floor? https://t.co/GLQdxrplRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Tsege's life is in danger but @PHammondMP you can save him. Ask the Ethiopian government for his release during your stay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in our building! https://t.co/EmMWt0hoHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport I am trying to write a review in the app store for an app I downloaded months ago but you keep telling me to download it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoRails I am trying to write a review in the app store and Apple keeps telling me I should download it. I already did months ago.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>