<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientist and a gentleman: https://t.co/B2M5EUjBRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newest paper from the Marigold lab with @rodrigo_maeda and SDSU's Shawn O'Connor as first authors. A great experime… https://t.co/NOA9UDE5U5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great A.I. Awakening https://t.co/GgM0edebvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Smartphones Ruining Distance Running? - The New Yorker https://t.co/exiIs7nzh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Math Make a Better Marathon? - The New Yorker https://t.co/7F2JHsgC2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practice Doesn’t Make Perfect - The New Yorker https://t.co/71OZDUtdSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: ‘Blindfolded’ ants reveal clues to insect navigation https://t.co/v3QAE9Rcsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weighty Matters Involving Electrons | Tesla Motors https://t.co/Tx4OUraZYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First-Person: The Benefits of "Strange" Science | Duke magazine https://t.co/O7rFT6Adiw via @dukealumni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The classroom is a lab": A researcher discovers teaching | Science https://t.co/YngOhgrSwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford study finds walking improves creativity https://t.co/m9DiASomkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young health researchers consider leaving the country due to funding drought | Ottawa Citizen https://t.co/wc3SrmjmpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manifold Destiny https://t.co/ZHPJoAqNGJ via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget crunch could dissolve Berkeley’s College of Chemistry | Science | AAAS https://t.co/atYpu48NVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scientists harvesting energy from humans to power our wearables | Guardian Sustainable Business | The Guardian https://t.co/6j2Dh7hHYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the soft, cuddly robots of the future : Nature News &amp; Comment https://t.co/sy6uTSNBQK via NatureNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researcher on CIHR funding drought: 'It is called eating your young' https://t.co/soBk2ligZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science made me a better parent | From AAAS https://t.co/uglb03LV5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science | From AAAS https://t.co/uglb03LV5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada creates science-minister post : Nature News &amp; Comment https://t.co/OCM4JNUZ6E via @NatureNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clear, correct, and compelling piece by Alex Hutchinson from @sweatscience "@globeandmail: http://t.co/JKydND2I8Z From @Globe_Health”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[featuring Jessica Selinger, lead author of Current Biology paper:  https://t.co/SBcym06wmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New SFU Locomotion Lab research published in @CurrentBiology and covered by the BBC: https://t.co/77tfapMmPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extreme Bias: How Rejection Clouds The Eyes of Researchers: http://t.co/vb79nwXQvT via @scholarlykitchn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A collaboration from RadioLab's Krulwich and Princeton's John Bonner @NPR: Here's Something You Don't Want To Know http://t.co/47pFBQXlsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the people helping generate renewable energy in the most weird ways http://t.co/NNHdpvzcgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neuromyths and the disconnect between science and the public — Neuroscientifically Challenged http://t.co/RqNZZmm7hN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoring a Master’s Voice , via @nytimes http://t.co/91EbSdvI6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poetic piece about @SFU LocoLab's research:  “@nytimesscience: Our understanding of giraffes does not measure up http://t.co/kqxYouGpEk”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, Darwin and My College Biology Class, via @nytimes http://t.co/xmVAY9Ed7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science deniers know the facts, but facts are trumped by ideals. "When Beliefs and Facts Collide, via @nytimes" http://t.co/BcrPFQp8k6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx John! Position ad is here: http://t.co/ERCmusCXCG “@JohnRHutchinson: PhD and postdoc in neuromechanics available with @maxdonelan”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woutersinas @johnrhutchinson Excellent! The position advertisement is here: http://t.co/ERCmusCXCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Welcome to your child's brain". Finally, some evidence-based insight into parenting. Thx @SamWangPhD &amp; @sandra_aamodt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished The Signal and the Noise. My prior was that it would be good, but my posterior is that @fivethirtyeight's next book will be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks is a gift shop that happens to sell coffee. How about local like @JJBeanCoffee? MT “@SFU: plans for a @starbucks location on #SFU”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["energy-harvesting tiles...produces 4.7 kWh of energy during the Paris marathon" Great, $0.28 "saved". Sigh.  http://t.co/J2gJldZLvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tisk @sciam You interviewed me for an hour about limits to human energy harvesting yet you publish this promo fluff.  http://t.co/J2gJldZLvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Big Data is “a fickle, coy mistress,” inviting, yet not without risk.' from @GaryMarcus in @NewYorker  http://t.co/nnjr1BwUWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Good innovators typically think very big and they think very small" from Nate Silver's "The signal and the noise"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bees Buzz Each Other, but Not the Way You Think - ScienceNOW http://t.co/GZYTwT2UOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Open access: The true cost of science publishing" from @NatureMagazine  http://t.co/lHAS3a6FVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meaningless but, SFU #30! RT "@THEWorldUniRank: Top 100 universities under 50 years old: http://t.co/4pCiE2JX4n”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also "...create in a childlike and openhearted manner, but to be un-wistful and cruel when judging one’s creation." http://t.co/b1dkklVrbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Simplicity is not about making something without ornament, but rather..." from The Story of My App @NewYorker: http://t.co/b1dkklVrbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFU Loco Lab @hlmore trip MT“@sfunews: research with giraffes - SFU student has research trip of a lifetime. http://t.co/b1MS0WNfPm ^dl”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating story about overcoming blindness: "but I want to be famous for the right reasons, for the work I’ve done" http://t.co/XOB67zjo35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 My fav quote: "…the way you use human power is not by having people produce electricity, but to use their own power to use less of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 @emmaroller interviewed me for her excellent article "The Body Electric" for @slate magazine: http://t.co/SGE8anfDW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome @discovery video of lizard chasing small mammal. Shot like a high intensity car chase. I have no idea how they did this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatGeo does Muybridge proud. Sprinting cheetahs are both mesmerizing and beautiful.   http://t.co/chVGD0Hkun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planet of the Mice? RT “@TelegraphSci: Human brain cells 'make mice more intelligent' http://t.co/m0u00ssWJ9”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? Time for an even better mousetrap. RT “@TelegraphSci: Human brain cells 'make mice more intelligent' http://t.co/m0u00ssWJ9”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRHutchinson Totally. Superimposing paint video and XROMM video might convincingly illustrate the amount of relative motion. Not horses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRHutchinson RE horse skeleton jumping. Cool as art or static anatomy lesson but skin motion relative to bones makes dynamics unlikely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alas, Tom Conners has stopped stompin': http://t.co/7P4GrhJZwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeermanCor @MarkSnaterse Ferry Man: Thanks for the killer Cruise Ctrl jacket! Your son just delivered it. Love it and will wear it proudly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learned about Harold Cohen's AARON - a computer artist capable of incredible works of art: http://t.co/RLdxkXSOGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“When there’s something we think could be better, we must make an effort to try and make it better.”– John Coltrane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From this month's JEB: Blinded tadpoles learn to use eyes implanted on spinal cord to "see". Wild. http://t.co/OknIqZPtW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Dynamics tackle hard task of coordination during throwing. But with cinder blocks and a robot. MT “@wired: http://t.co/eKM8Vi5Svq”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some press for recent SFU Locomotion Lab paper: RT “@DiscoverMag: Giraffes' long nerves make them slow to respond http://t.co/lzj6SkMSSE”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the press release from JEB for @hlmore and Shawn's paper. Funny, if not pinpoint accurate, cartoon within.  http://t.co/0V9Vk8bpAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hlmore and Shawn O'Connor's study on giraffe reaction times just published in JEB. Summary: long, long delays! http://t.co/sTJ0HytOir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amplifying small changes in videos leads to incredibly cool applications including non contact pulse measurements.  http://t.co/QUkuss2YIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing example of passive dynamic rhythm generation and stability. Epic - Slinky on a Treadmill:  http://t.co/JOLhwrBBpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally some hoppy rain is falling on the IPA desert that starts at the Canadian border.  http://t.co/4Tp3xxIUJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quadcopter inverted pendulum throwing, catching and balancing. Super sweet! http://t.co/Ann6xzT6tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFU Locomotion Lab PhD student, Mark Snaterse, interviewed about Cruise Control app by SFU's student newspaper: http://t.co/e8f1CxE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFU prof done good: Gender equality eludes groundbreaking scientist http://t.co/6SyL1Kp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond quantification to control: The Nest thermostat and its control freak founders.  http://t.co/0EdPsXcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFU Locomotion Lab research featured in NYT: “@nytimes: How your playlist can impact your running habits: http://t.co/oQCIiOO0”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweatscience Yikes! I should have written OUR work! No one played a more important role than @MarkSnaterse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweatscience Just read your latest. There are few who can write about science with such clarity and interest. Thanks for covering my work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arduinos, RepRaps and the Thingiverse -  "Building Research Equipmentwith Free, Open-Source Hardware" http://t.co/2RrubsJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One serving only, please! MT “@NatureNews: scientists double dipping for funding. http://t.co/F0dVwyVm”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize this piece by @carlzimmer to write good. Literally.  http://t.co/kgxML4E4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From my PhD student @hlmore because "it combines two things I think a lot about". Pretty sure she means diapers/walking http://t.co/8ySXba7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new symbolic language to overcome deceit-prone words helps CP kids find their "voice". Sad ending. From @Radiolab  http://t.co/j66IVTmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catapulting Canine! RT “@JohnRHutchinson: This amazing dog leap is my favourtite GIF of the day. http://t.co/sZtUaMVS”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here I was thinking my struggles meant I was part robot - Ticketmaster dumps 'hated' Captcha http://t.co/p7zDx9c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryMarcus Related: motors are better than muscle in many ways. Clutches are hard but real dif is that animal control evolved for movement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryMarcus Tried to read Cleaning Up Sci but got distracted by Making Robots is Hard: http://t.co/l4ABIin5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The onslaught continues - pop neuroscience, shoddy neurojournalism, and the neuroexplanation of everything:  https://t.co/B5cQGJs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Neuromania" and "Brain Porn" - our over fascination with brain imaging:  http://t.co/08lENMSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marcus and Davis contrast Fisher and Bayes' stat approaches clearly and concisely even if Silver critique a bit unfair  http://t.co/VPqvb6iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To ask if modelling is useful in physiology is to ask if hypotheses are useful in science. It is an absurd question" DA Robinson (1977)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transparent skulls, fluorescent dyes, and virtual worlds - The neuroscience of larval zebra fish.  http://t.co/9Mj6Xlrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vonnegut's keys to the written word - writing wisdom for us scientists too.  http://t.co/hghSv0Fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruiseCtrlRun "When I Was A Young Girl" by Feist is a sweet #CruiseCtrlSongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruiseCtrlRun "Don't Make Me A Target" by Spoon is a killer #CruiseCtrlSongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more bribing? Train a Parent, Spare a Child http://t.co/3BEy4j7g http://t.co/ZQbuTBlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Nature and @edyong209 Bob Paine, ecology and, most importantly, mentorship.  http://t.co/ZBXqD0i1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bengoldacre Are skeptics less healthy, on average, due to reduced placebo effect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Canadian moment on Main St in North Vancouver. http://t.co/vJEsAhMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruiseCtrlRun "The Joker" by The Steve Miller Band is a great #CruiseCtrlSongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruiseCtrlRun "Creator" by Santogold is a complex but pretty killer #CruiseCtrlSongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruiseCtrlRun "Surface to Air" by The Chemical Brothers is a great #CruiseCtrlSongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot reason people out of positions they didn't reason themselves into" Truth in preface of Bad Science @bengoldacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice article on Bionic Power in the Ottawa Citizen today.  http://t.co/EKqHmyCy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>