<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharksfan08 @MTVASHLEYBROOKE Ashley sounds fun! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also.... my boy @TheOfficial_CT is an absolute beast....... the best of the best....... still think @MTVBananas is close second! #ruthless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The challenge- Rivals" marathon is starting now......... Dammit,
Gonna be a long one. #challenge #mykindashow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jorgebdamian @morgan_willett @alexshay1 @realityrally I can't wait to GET a pic with these two stunners!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERIKA!!!!!!! So much love!!!! Thanks for your donation to @realityrally !!! Who's up!! Show this organization some… https://t.co/TapGZKxl42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meh! Only minor. These guys are skilled enough to remove it one way or another haha https://t.co/aLXX3MyX9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha fingers crosssseeddddd it isn't????? Haha much love tho man. #respect https://t.co/j61CgIuQo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamsheajenkins @iam_erika alwaysssss refrigerate that shit!!! I love the cold ketchup on warm fries!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesssss!!! All going to the same fund!!! Respect!!! https://t.co/R3wtgDf60N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO much respect for my man @jorgebdamian for his donation to @realityrally !! WHOS NEXT!! Amazing cause guys, every cent counts!! (Link bio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 days to help raise money for @realityrally ! An amazing cause that helps women/ families dealing with breast cancer! (Link in bio) thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElGreco21 @SpencerBClawson @realityrally check the link! Thanks in advance for the donation!!! Every cent counts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's get the @realityrally donation train going again today!! ONE WEEK LEFT to reach my goal of $500!! Every cent counts! (Link bio) #RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kickass_koala @jordanparhar hahaha I noticed! And laughed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also pretty sure someone just messed up the spelling of "February" years ago and just no one questioned him so he left it like that. So dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But like this "dry February" thing doesn't count in Super Bowl Sunday right?........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kickass_koala @jordanparhar great...... but you forgot to ask a question......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Is. Amazing......... Big JP aka Dr. love aka Hitch aka Cupids Cupid aka the loveboat special aka Mr. Right wi… https://t.co/Vpi6yDkvLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha little Newfie humour...... https://t.co/Kiaby3Chsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the donation train for @realityrally is ROLLING! $210/$500 raised!! Can we get to $250 before we hit the hay!? THANK YOU! (Link in bio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANOTHER donation!!!! Massive thanks to Patrick Monchamp for the donation!!! Let's get a few more in before the days over!! (Link in Bio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting there!!! Thanks SO MUCH to @brnnhllck for her donation!!! Means so much!! Let's keep the train going!!! (Link in bio) @realityrally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! 8 days to go, and only $375 away from my goal of $500 raised for breast cancer! Any cent counts, and is SUPER appreciated! (Link bio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brunogmanuel @MakeupArtistMeg hahaha promise we will do it next week!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUGE shoutout to @MakeupArtistMeg for her donation to @realityrally !!! Much love!! Who's next to step up??? #goodcause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First $25 donation of the day for @realityrally !!!! Who's next!? Let's get a donation train going!! (Link in bio) LETS DO THIS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! 8 days to go, and only $400 away from my goal of $500 raised for breast cancer! Lend a hand, every cent counts https://t.co/11uZ6XRdaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Big_Johng how long was the recovery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has it been since reconstruction?? That's the next step for me https://t.co/s6awznXlK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainboomonster meeting with specialist Tuesday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpencerBClawson what can I do for you???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I REALLY love my jack Astors family..... what an amazing group of people..... #blessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Also heard about the mosque shooting? We should ban all Caucasians now as well. Let's just have it so no one l… https://t.co/1YnDTCd0z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaks my heart...... we are better than this.... as a country... as a planet..... thoughts and prayers are not eno… https://t.co/4SK3i3YFQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluejoni not what I'd like to see in a pres!!!! Wish the world had a vote : P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and Neda is great! Living in Van, doing well! she's a great woman!!! https://t.co/7Cq9mwYmM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect man! Just like keeping human rights at the top of priority list! all equal. thanks for engaging in a mature… https://t.co/dszprfKO0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rhianno04361477 @davemackey4 haven't seen ANYTHING he has done for the boost of the economy. been ALL hate and fear thats his priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And THAT i understnad.... but he has gone far beyond "job issues" and has is funning the country on fear and bigotr… https://t.co/W0JytLW0ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katrina_Srour its on youtube..... hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait...... I wasn't on canadian idol???? why the EFF have i been at all these singing auditions????? https://t.co/J8BUAeJnan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRiotmaker To run a country. To be economically agressive yet socially in tune. To make changes that are needed without using Fear/bigotry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAY be super out of context..... but as @kevinolearytv says " THERE MUST BE A BETTER WAY" ( and no this tweet does not support for PM)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemackey4 and no disrespect at all david. To each their own. I just consider myself an advocate for more PRO human rights verses opposite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mucciamatt @davemackey4 better safe than sorry right??? Fuck human rights and equality!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfdan see other account ya nut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man!! How are you? https://t.co/E7bNfONWDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True!!! You're so right!!! So terrible an ENTIRE RACE AND RELIGION is to blame for 9/11. You got me. https://t.co/RIpM85RiD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human rights=right . End of story imo https://t.co/KeOXXtOxmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past week of trumps doings. If you agree with that then i personally feel bad to how you were raised yes.... https://t.co/eOsgVdXhs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mannnnn Trump supporters must have had some whack parents...... HOW does one justify openly supporting his actions? I can't comprehend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy belated @Catvanzyl !!! Hope you had an amazing day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one got you wrong..... you're the same insensitive, ass hole, bigot, that we thought you were. https://t.co/GQq8P968wj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katrinalegare hopefully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neon_orange15 @YouTube Ive watched!!! Still nothing that is on trumps level imo!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GustavoPatriz mehhhhhh.  Nothing there that warrants him being the Canadian trump. Next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau is definitely a great face for Canada. Semes@to@have great morals and want beat for the country. (I'm Not t… https://t.co/2IxAPJBgz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotcha!!! So seems like some similarities?! I'll def look into it more. Was just curious https://t.co/fBgIz6G2vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That makes sense!!! That's for not being 12 and coming back with snarky remarks like some..... lol https://t.co/QfhQLuKQYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the only connection is that they are business men? https://t.co/qNHBSSFX0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must have missed the "if so" part of my tweet. Wanna link me to his Bigot and racist remarks??? Thanks https://t.co/B8nKsq7Ejr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's not the nicest guy..... but I haven't heard him be a racist or a bigot or anything CLOSE to trump.... https://t.co/J3c5YvDSCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause if so that's dumb........ and unfair imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't done much research on @kevinolearytv , but is he automatically "the Canadian Trump" cause he's a business man and was on TV?(cont'd)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IS THIS 2015????? https://t.co/19y80LAvpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not fun, but it's worth it" -me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks man! Just doing what I love. A smile on a face is a pie in the face to another!!! Much love https://t.co/wlAkj12Jed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gimme #BBCAN5 please. https://t.co/tulEU1jM4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even after yesterday's #BellLetsTalk , remind yourself today that people are STILL here for you. Always someone in your corner #muchlove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Deeds is such a great flick #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/11uZ6XRdaZ every cent counts! Please find time to donate for this great cause!! @realityrally #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry for your loss!! Cc:@JonPardi #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/l0UU1VUnUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So powerful #BellLetsTalk respect @TheoFleury14 https://t.co/4FO9SwROhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my co-workers / family!!! #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/rwsbqg2sA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_reddamage always here if ya need to chat!! Much love!! #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They need to hear people's stories, need to be educated, need to feel like they can talk openly about their struggl… https://t.co/AIcOr28K7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree with you!But I think it all stars with talk before you walk the walk! People need to see timelines filled w… https://t.co/2z0qKgTboz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the point we are trying to get too!!! Hope you have an amazing day brother, and let's mix in a #BellLetsTalk… https://t.co/b9uM4a3HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100%!!! That's why we talking!! And all over that simple hashtag #BellLetsTalk ;) https://t.co/RlrZwtGVUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So just the hashtag #BellLetsTalk is doing what it's suppose to do....raise awareness and donates money to research… https://t.co/3YuvVX7pg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without a doubt. That's why I LOVE IT!! Simply adding a hashtag raises money AND AWARENESS (imo probably more impor… https://t.co/6QRJxOeey7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Looney bin" I think is outdated word!! you need o be admitted to understand? You'd like people to STOP trying to h… https://t.co/xJvZNxNE3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't take it out on people trying to help the cause. ALSO one way you can let out some frustration and help is use… https://t.co/Ec067uZH9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally on a daily basis......so you are excused from trolling, and the fact you asked this question makes YOU t… https://t.co/Wu43LXju1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just used #BellLetsTalk . (Unlike you) I've always been there for friends and family who need ears, and have dealt… https://t.co/fCPX9ymgFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is one of my favourite days of he year......such an amazing, underrated cause. I'm always here for you! ❤ #BellLetsTalk #endthestigma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha work late hours!!! Kid needs some sleeeeep! But believe me, IMessage is off, I'm ready to roll!!!!… https://t.co/JwUYcvYoJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@604MachoMan hundo!! Sometimes they just have aces!!! Again possibly poor shove. I DUNNO haha #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@604MachoMan lucky!!! Haha poor move overall. Needed it tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone's got a story... everyone's got a struggle.... be generous, be kind, and don't be afraid to love #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No way! Where did you go to highschool? #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/mdYRJQuaRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I could RT all day love!!! #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/zzdzju7IJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ja445 just chillin!!! Watching some tv!! School tomorrow? #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much respect @jendeclinesyou #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/wvE7yjD6RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man Jamal!!!! What's up pal?? #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/8UHOnAXPuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@604MachoMan could always use a rail haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got it!!! Always in for this cause!! #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/Ps87HedBYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my timeline filled with #BellLetsTalk !!! Check out my boy @KevinRobMartin , running strong on twitch right now!! #kmart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No excuse to not add #BellLetsTalk to EVERY tweet/text/snap you send in the next 24 hours!! Such an amazing, needed cause!!! You go @Bell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only every protest was this peaceful. Respect to the officers and especially the people protesting. https://t.co/8jv2lVEJ6S]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>