<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[For Christ sake man, why have you people started colouring fake freckles on ya face? ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiaRose_1998 the fact that this gif is Ariana Grande makes it 10x better too ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people can't help but throw shade everyday, it's just in their soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaydePierce apparently if u keep taking the pregnancy vitamins it helps as your hormones are low or something after giving birth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arouens thank you ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsKOOsh relax you'll see me tomoz ðŸ’ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arouens where from please ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol who are you people to be demanding apologies please, your taking it far now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol no sauce whatsoever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry i went through some of my old tweets this morning, half got deleted i was mortified lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry nope don't try it you're just an ass lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry look at your life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intimidating face? ðŸ¤” you think you're Phil Mitchell init ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/HiHeKCbayq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victoriatandu yes u have traitor, where are you ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry lol told u he's an idiot ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or saying slick stuff on the sly but it's cool though, whatever can't even be asked ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will be telling you shit about yourself that u already know, I didn't need a reminder thanks ðŸ‘‹ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like if you have convos about me behind my back, great ðŸ‘ðŸ¾ðŸ‘ðŸ¾ðŸ‘ðŸ¾ good for you but just don't say it to me don't want to hear that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather stay at home than be subjected to hurtful comments all the time, like leave me alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want friends or family that are gonna make me feel bad about myself, I don't care who you are or how long we've known each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wish people could understand the things they say and their actions towards people can have a deeper effect on others ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly wish I could just stay at home all day and watch telly ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly why I don't like going out everything and everyone upsets me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can everyone go to bed I'm in a emo rant mood ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am just exhausted in every aspect of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I acc need a serious break from life ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an exaggeration but thats how silly u sound tryna be poetic with your shade ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully those that were lost in the sauce 2016 finally drown and die in 2017 â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Connor is so weird man I can't deal ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your fave makeup brands test on animals but you're a vegan ðŸ¤”... Okay ðŸ™ŽðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate when people use spirituality to throw shade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't like the way Azryah was spoken to in this episode, by Lucus first of all but Esther topped it off, it was disgusting #BKChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling so conflicted at the moment ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh really... Tell me more ðŸ¤” https://t.co/etdGKJIbnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry sknnnn they have to wait lemme lee small small weight ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccatembo_ Oo tbh I don't know bloggers who've been at it for 10 years ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose why are you baiting out the government ting please ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccatembo_ only if you get proper popular and do a variety of things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jrange I think a lot including myself will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’€ https://t.co/NAysz9U4Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[story of both our lives lol https://t.co/SKtAFVgozc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kranium shoulda won that award but hey ho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She killed it ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/nwykQyGSkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ugandan babe shocked me and made the best fried riceðŸ˜³ðŸ˜ðŸ‘ @tameramelrose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose crying ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChlovaLx happy birthday Chloe ðŸŽ‰ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry @_RoyalNova @tameramelrose @FideliaAshanti lol yes you were willing to lock the whole ting off ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose @Leeshartry @_RoyalNova @FideliaAshanti at least you know ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry @_RoyalNova @tameramelrose @FideliaAshanti yes I will never forget u spazzing on my birthday for your phone ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dressing up at work today ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@popseyyy happy birthday Mary Pearl ðŸŽ‰ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway I'm going back on what seems to be a never ending social detox lol, I need to step back âœŒðŸ¾ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've come to realise you can't be surrounded by nothing but negative energy and expect that not to affect you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only wanna focus on positivity and things that make me happy for the rest of my life ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry @tameramelrose but did he have to kick him in the chest ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry please I'm not into your hanky panky business, I don't want you to "finish me off" u creep ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry is this not what you do in your front room in Kent I've heard all the stories ðŸ‘€ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose What the actual fuck ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ is this a real lesson? ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜© yh came out last year, look at the way he was slapping her bum pls, no love ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are you even? ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what I don't understand are the people that bang fraud consistently and yet there is still mildew growing on their walls ðŸ¤”ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She must've snitched hard to get off, I'm not even mad at her ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we don't talk why do you think you can still be using my Netflix, please respect yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is @tameramelrose telling me she will never go carnivore ðŸ¤”ðŸ™ƒ I should hope not wtf ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose I don't play about with mulla ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseOfCB hi, I got gifted a dress from your store but the stitching on the side and under the arm came undone, can I get an exchange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol not really anything to do I hardly wear any, so that's their problem https://t.co/cXRqxMePQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBHelpTeam hi, I was gifted a dress from your store but the stitching ripped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing Pinocchio but you still got dumped, life comes at you fast bro ðŸ™ŽðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a strong believer of karma, what you put out in this world is what you will receive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol after all is said and done was it worth it ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad petty Betty is back in her cage where she belongs, hate having to let her out ðŸ’†ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom, Dick and Harry https://t.co/TQ3zapL7np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teminism that's all u know ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do u people keep saying Blac Chyna is abusive towards Rob, are we all watching the same show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't care less what men actually little boys think or say about me I just keep it noted and move along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually black girl slander or any form of shaming women only angers me when it comes from women themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never taken black girl slander seriously, not that I support it but nothing that's ever said relates to me in the slightest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrie the mandem candy ðŸ‘ðŸ¾ðŸ”¥ðŸ˜ https://t.co/qoasiZMUBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine wasting all the lies in the world and yet you still didnt get your bitch back, what a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same guy that will be ripping into people for being liars and yet come and see him ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thought we were friends and built a relationship" but you're lying on my name, where do they do that at ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely one would question the validity of such false statements considering the liar has done this exact same thing before but hey ho ðŸ™ŽðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't wanna hear about you ever again not even when she tells you that you're better as friends ðŸŽµâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victoriatandu you know I'm petty Betty â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tara said this, Tara said that, but it's actually big man himself that loves to run and chat â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please if anyone has seen @Leeshartry or @FideliaAshanti contact me asap they are currently missing ðŸ™ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leeshartry and @FideliaAshanti what are yous playing at ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialPLT WHERE ON EARTH IS MY PACKAGE? I need for tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever think of me when you lie? Lie down in your bed, your bed of lies ðŸŽµðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also pray the Lord reminds certain people that I don't care enough to entertain their antics, double amen ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pray the Lord exposes the lies certain people are telling on me, amen ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to @realmostack that Liar liar tune is straight fire ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teminism I'm 99% sure you're trolling because you use to live and breathe Tupac ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_RoyalNova ðŸ˜«ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜­ this is for you babe  https://t.co/rZVwgAeJp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnotherJamal it's a *irresponsible thing, fixed it your welcome â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tameramelrose no mins anymore but I got the cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are you tho? ðŸ¤” https://t.co/DDUbtXtOek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the fact that some of you listened to that psychopaths 2010 freestyle and weren't moved by those lyrics is deeply concerning ðŸ¤”]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>