<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh stick you, you mamma too and you daddyyyyy @RadioX #daphneandceleste #throwbackthursday ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»ðŸŽ§ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waaaahhhhh stupid work making me miss that match! ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not very often I spend 10 hours at the yard, might be ill but was v awesome to have a proper horsey day ðŸ˜Šâ¤ï¸ðŸ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My abs are sore from coughing ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is class ðŸ˜‚ hat trick in the Derby pleeeeaaaasssseeee ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»âš½ï¸ðŸ† https://t.co/ufJ5aIme5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhhhh dunno if I want a derby the now or no ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ âš½ï¸ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js @Scullion1996 thought u would already know this being in the same league as them.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kercus123 @backstreetboys uncle Chris must've been singing her lullabys ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping @Bonnyriggrose81 can cause a cup upset today âš½ï¸ðŸ†#Goodluck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Susy412 still tesco but back in community development :) X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New job that is actually relevant to my qualifications and career face on ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #finally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great that @TheSSEHydro has a bar selling unchilled drinks and the staff think it's funny when you ask for a cold one....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js this was last year lol. Still funny tho X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to @scuj1 who is 34 today. Older and grumpier than he was yesterday! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js @nat4sha_ @Brizo0505 haha if he was 10 years younger aye! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shhhh be quiet you might piss somebody off, like me motherfucker you've been at it for too long! ðŸŽ§ðŸŽ¸ðŸ‘ŒðŸ» #3sleeps #a7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! #thevoiceuk ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»ðŸŽ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Jones voice ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #thevoiceuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double @BiffyClyro followed by @stereophonics on the way to work, cheers @RadioX ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss these two being at Tynie so much, memories will always live on tho â™¥ï¸ https://t.co/jn1Ge9e8Mu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js don't think we're northern tho? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just woke up and can't move from my bed ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not even 7.30 and @LeanneLowe11 has me drinking a mixture of prosecco and gin ðŸ™ˆ might no see the bells! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muppet movie is on and I really don't want to go to work ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work, ponies, pizza and napping. Quietest Boxing Day ever!! ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´ #oldandboring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My family must be the only one in Scotland not playing speak out the past 2 days....ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very spoiled this Xmas...thank you so much to @onechord_js for my @EstherThePig stuff, my fave pressie ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ…ðŸ»ðŸ˜ðŸ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooooo happy to have a drink in my hand, hard week! ðŸ¾ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸŽ…ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 hour shift....here we go ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5am start tomorrow ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaFerguson18 we are going to the seaside!!! https://t.co/Wdnx44gxC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just bought a pie and a tea at the football and poured my milk over the pie instead of in the tea ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ I need a holiday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 not drinking for various reasons X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 yard night out X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't be assed going out tonight ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js @scuj1  busted at subway ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ https://t.co/hPaO7idh92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 @onechord_js Jamie is meant to be boycotting McDonald's and subway so hoping he hasn't broke that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely have a high pain threshold but there have been so many times my wisdom teeth have nearly had me in tears #ow ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 not through choice tho. Still probs worked more than Wendy all year including my 5 months unemployment ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still gonna be super busy tho ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a day off work tomorrow ðŸ˜®ðŸ˜®ðŸ˜®ðŸ˜®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js just want to be back there ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js you are an awesome husband tho â™¥ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public transport today will not be fun ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biffy on, cider open ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ðŸ»ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been so busy working barely had time to realise it's one sleep until @BiffyClyro tomorrow ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ fourth time this year seeing them ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸŽ¸ðŸŽ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did someone just try and smash honey g?! #xfactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js  me and Sal are soul mates https://t.co/kIgARkcL94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 more than usual! Also got up for a pee every half hour all night and fell on top of me every time on the way back! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 Long story, Jamie can explain to you X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[â¤ï¸ so glad he's not going to Celtic would actually break me ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/1CwcNCqYck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would do nearly anything to be going here again this year ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜” https://t.co/do2Ga8GmBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not a good morning ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good day away jumping with the lovely boy Vinny ðŸ´â¤ï¸â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js I want this guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 @onechord_js not sure which one is the more obedient of the 2 ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are people managing the #MannequinChallenge with their dogs! Mine would last 0.2 seconds at most ðŸ™ˆðŸ¶â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do today is stalk @LeoDiCaprio around Edinburgh...why did my new job have to start this week ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ’”ðŸ’”ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That bear ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ» #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will not cope of a baby goat gets eaten ðŸ˜­ #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to watch after that shambles ðŸ˜³ #EnglandvScotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I didn't win the lunch date with @LeoDiCaprio next week then ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of those nights you don't wanna go to sleep cos you don't want tomorrow to come ðŸ˜¢ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Melissa and Clark stay together #MarriedAtFirstSight â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulaHMFC I didn't even notice that till u pointed it out ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Susy412 thanks Hun. Gonna be at the Dalkeith store so might see you about! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 didn't even think of that! ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 at Tesco, I'm on the dairy counter. Mmmmm cheese ðŸ˜ðŸ§€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 just stuff, one being I got a seasonal job ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a good couple of bits of news today ðŸ˜Š #yay #needed #cheeredup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFratellis @onechord_js get them a spice of life!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 @onechord_js it probably will be but it's pretty important we get there on time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched @LeoDiCaprio Before the Flood doc...wow â¤ï¸ðŸŒŽ amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beck1sm @scuj1 pretty sure you've come close to this.. The day you said you weren't comin in cos u felt 'meh' ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 buy ur mummy something nice for dealing with your pish...and the nice colleagues you have left a @krispykremeUK X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 you could spend ur winnings on it! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planet Earth ðŸŒŽ been buzzing for this ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ears will not thaw out and that's with ear muffs on ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 fuck off! When u taking me out? We've no had a date in a while ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Susy412 might have to sneak it into the tree when my Jamie isn't looking tho ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long, hard couple of days ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜¢ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js aye apart from on a road trip..... X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onechord_js @JeremyClarkson not with those idiots! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish folk on @itvjeremykyle this morning.....oh my gawwwwddd ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg the stuff @onechord_js watches on you tube before bed ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneLowe11 @onechord_js why were we talking about him lol?! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just told a wee boy at @bighearts kinship care day the players had arrived....he asked me where @Cristiano was ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese has sorted my hangover right out ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneLowe11 @onechord_js what was this about lol?! ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 I would stab myself trying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 wtf is that?! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that @BiffyClyro have snapchat now ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 all the time now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 you're not stealing my crown ðŸ‘‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the circus ðŸ˜ðŸŽª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for Crystal Maze tonight and also just seen there's a child genius vs celebs before too! #SU2C ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 terrible! Didn't miss much tho ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneLowe11  why you no here ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/5GfGgozdrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got on the bus and realised I've put no hairspray in my hair ðŸ™ˆ. Least it's raining and can blame it on that â˜”ï¸â˜”ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National egg day. Nothing makes me feel more sick than this ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>