<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kittykatstargal oh i thought you were asexual not gamesexual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ So this is what it looks like when a TV station goes through a midlife crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuedeBlade https://t.co/yauO8ZWR0N we're on the same wavelength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vOtZwWEpOX photograph.amv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily reminder: Don't forget to wear a skirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhantomRoxas Pfft. That's great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhantomRoxas @KezzupReviews Huh, really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4UgRGQfMQM current aesthetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the VA's in the Mobius FF x FFVIIR collab sound sooo bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs Ooh, looks like they managed to get Cloud's voice actor for this collab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I got Cloud on the first 3*/4* greater summon! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaylinEvergreen I just pulled the really really rare event job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaylinEvergreen it's the hero from FF mobius in Cloud's outfit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT FIRST PULL #ffmobius https://t.co/PzgUOSwPR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KezzupReviews "Just ice? Shouldn't there be some kind of drink as well?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaylinEvergreen @Capt_Wolf_Kick @jasonhall230 What?! I just die a lot, I assumed! I *assumed*!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaylinEvergreen @jasonhall230 And not a fox. Jason has a thing for maiming foxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lineart is always the most annoying part of art for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: do i have to draw the hand
also me: draw the hand
me: but i could like change her design and do gloves
also me: draw the fucking hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadScientist212 and it's not even sisterly incest!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's episode of @theparapod was... *special*. Link here if you want it. https://t.co/zOE6X3jyfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Firefaerie81 @PhantomRoxas Well... Okay. A cartoon of the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Firefaerie81 @PhantomRoxas And in return we got a series that acts like it has an extremely one-sided crush with the country. :'D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theparapod "Everyone's seen porn from the 70s" Oh god Barry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonhall230 I'd need to start a gofundme for the funds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonhall230 Me! I want bacon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelToole How is the subtitle for this movie not "Wick is Whack"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hbomberguy hey now let's not go that far

sonic 06 at least tried to be a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I still have like 100 mystic tablets to blow in Mobius FF so I've been grinding Gigantaurs in the background x_x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also me: *has like, 30 pages left to do lineart for*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me, in the middle of doing lineart of the first chapter of a webcomic: "I should storyboard out some of the second chapter as I go"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhantomRoxas It's almost like he's an unqualified man who conned himself into power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhantomRoxas which is hilarious because your state sends more in federal funds than they get back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UNDERSHORTS: all the thrill of panty shots with the added bonus of everyone involved keeping their dignity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tbh I think having undershorts is sexier because panty shots are just creepy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me, a responsible adult: *sees opportunity for panty shot in drawing* 
"but she'd know, right? so she'd be wearing like, shorts underneath"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonhall230 @NightoftheLark STAY UP UNTIL 5 IN THE MORNING AND EAT BREAKFAST BEFORE GOING TO BED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*republicans and right-wingers do something really bad*
THE INTERNET: hey let's look for ways that this is the democratic left's fault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonhall230 @NightoftheLark Be the ice cream breakfast-eating adult you have denied yourself for so long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sudden thought: if snl pisses trump off enough to get him to make laws to cancel them and they pass, they could move production to mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ice cream for breakfast is what adults do right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like every song would be better if it had interjections by people shouting "Kame-ha-me-ha!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shuggoth @Cazboab So going to bed at 12 and waking up at 8:30 is "Normal" right? help me i don't know what normal is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlmightyStross @Cazboab No no no, I'm normal, that makes me weird!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is it with me and going to bed at decent times and waking up at decent times lately?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs That's also different. I'm looking for the .ini file, though presuming that it exists for this game might be a mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs (And I already kinda looked there for it... ^^;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs Where the app is stored isn't usually where the settings are stored, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Wolf_Kick I've seen the first episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs not quite what I was looking for but thanks I guess? ^^;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Wolf_Kick @Firefaerie81 Here's hoping that she isn't pushed to the side &amp; is written well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz Okay, but at any point do you call it Breasteria?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYTHING is better when it's a pun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can draw a mean plate of bacon, eggs, and waffles https://t.co/LFFvmERtid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlrolson ...definitely not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[let me fix this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aw shit i missed an opportunity for a visual pun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can draw a mean plate of bacon, eggs and waffles https://t.co/OC934aa2AZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMakuzawa Someone should let him know it's not a surprise if we know it's coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myanimewaifu hey i found a song for your next stream https://t.co/xLwXdUL0qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 9 at night, how is there still light outside?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bagelrin (These are the best I can make my own eyes.) https://t.co/DfKEslh6gC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bagelrin But I'm by no means an expert, so feel free to dismiss my opinion. ^^;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bagelrin They're a little too glossy. I've found that harder shading on the light gives them a the more glassier look that helps them--]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMakuzawa There's nothing that frustrates me more viscerally than a bad internet connection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMakuzawa Must be your connection, I got mine pretty quick after I went through my files to fix what was causing me to be unable to link.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bagelrin The hair's good, the eyes need work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liuwdere take a shower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GIGABEETLE Look just tweet "It's been..." without any followup, that'll do the job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing FF mobius on a stable platform that doesn't lock that platform down when you play it improves the game *so much* for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the moral of any game with "break" mechanics: Beat your enemy while they're down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DejiNyucu Because it's only 6 PM in New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I have a 1080p monitor but I want to run it at a sub-1080p resolution but not 720p because that's too small...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs You wouldn't happen to know where the settings file for FF Mobius PC is located so I can set a custom res?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FF Mobius is the perfect game to leave running in auto battle mode on the opposite monitor while you're doing actual work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oceanicbreak What game be this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, this game runs so smooth on PC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelindsayellis SAME. except, you know, without people telling me I'm valuable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whee, I finally got into the PC version of FF Mobius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sailorbee Does she also have an "I'M GAY" tattoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My terrible meme is still getting retweets fyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dMOmpsynxn So this guide helped me connect my FF Mobius stuff to the PC version in a roundabout way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw story elements you want to include solidify themselves in your mind in a way that's incredibly satisfactory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NightoftheLark I feel bad because by the time I finish FE fates and decide to start Heroes, everyone will be done with it. :'D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Saberleo_ @myanimewaifu It's always good to be informed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't login to the Mobius FF PC servers. &gt;_&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aquadraca So I did two pulls in the current event and noooow... https://t.co/IYQCQEPWIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMakuzawa I can't even get my account to connect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs Yeah I wasn't kidding when I said the game launch was borked. :'D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonhall230 @Zucchinipuffs @PhantomRoxas Is it really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zucchinipuffs @jasonhall230 @PhantomRoxas Do people often confuse you for a woman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs Because this is the error that I and hundreds of others are getting when they try to link accounts. https://t.co/jBK9CdNMd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs Did they manage to link their accounts from their mobile or did they start a whole new save?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I just tried again and it's still not working. x_x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I figured they'd have this fixed up by now but it's been "live" on steam for like 12 hours &gt;_&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs It doesn't work. Like at all. Connection errors, can't link accounts, tries to connect to HK servers instead of global...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koukoupuffs I'm waiting for the PC version to be unborked. &gt;_&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(also they aren't fixed yet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[started typing code to see if servers were up yet in FF Mobius and noticed something about the first five letters o… https://t.co/nCSJAr1zNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was an interesting chapter. Pacing has been pretty on point lately.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>