<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking pissflaps #scovire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_sheridan the EU parliament is in Brussels (sprouts) #humour #politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DirkVanBryn @Crap90sFootball @A_W_Gordon @PrescottRossi I look forward to spending many hours on this page. Excellent find!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgriffin91 @nick_sheridan He's the guy who ran away and left his wife for a young one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanglynn86 that is a very interesting point Ryan, food for thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would like to welcome my good friend @nick_sheridan back to twitter. Happy debating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling today will make or break us. Barnsley away, Mike Dean. #LUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely Murray should've went off for a Head Assessment? Didn't look at the races there at all! #GLAvMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FA Cup draw "banter" is the shittest banter ever. Get on with the draw and stop talking shite. #HeresTheLads #FuckOff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanglynn86 great interview, but that was painful to watch..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy do another show in Dublin please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaranoconnor photoshop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa Nothing will top the greatness of the CoD4 sessions of yesteryear. #TeamTactical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgriffin91 @Channel4 @jonsnowC4 just when I thought I couldn't think any more highly of him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck, what a match, what a kick @JackCarty1 #5050]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe that Jerome Garcès gets paid actual money to referee professional rugby union matches. #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Blindboy Boatclub actually @AlanFarrell? Something you're not telling us @Rubberbandits? #InsideJab https://t.co/Gk1riVBDkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Atlantic is well worth a watch. I'd go as far as saying Ray Burke is worse than Cromwell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE just as well, I was running out of candles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Bertie Ahern is coming back, apparently... Is that when we're supposed to take those iodine tablets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrflava123 @bisping @ufc McGregor isn't British though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @AwayDays_ and keep going to the 21st of January]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwayDays_ @OMearaaa "I've been dreaming of a shite Christmas..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is the most Rob Green thing to ever happen. #LEENEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up genuinely excited for a @LUFC match for the first time in about 12 years. Hon the lads! #MOT #LeedsLeedsLeeds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stacksey @ditofficial I did tell the man, he said all the computers were running slow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging from my FB timeline, people seem to care more of what goes on in Washington DC than on Kildare Street. #ArmchairExpertsEverywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been in the library for 40 minutes now, tried to log into 3 different computers and no luck. @ditofficial is some kip....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland beat the All Blacks and Leeds are in the playoffs, a truly great day. #Pints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst Ireland's call ever #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hon the Leeds! In the playoffs, mighty stuff. #MOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa now that I would like to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa Pontus Jansson will break Coutinho's legs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoying the demise of Manchester United Football Corporation these days. #CHEMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBrundleF1 @LewisHamilton any chance of him getting a go on a MotoGP bike? seen as Lorenzo had a spin in his merc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaayDolan sure there's no WiFi in DIT Jimmy, and we aren't getting €200k a week!😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa They should have just called it "An Audience With Jurgen Klopp (Followed by Burnley-Watford)"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa at least it's sunshine and scattered showers here as opposed to  sunshine and a scatter of racial violence....  #Murica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tis a day for a Choc Ice on the way home, maybe 6 pints as well... #Scorcher #FewPintsAreGrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich people with columns in the Indo all saying that the govt should appeal the #AppleTax decision... In other news water is wet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackCarty1 @connachtrugby are you still afraid of 50/50's?😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgriffin91 excellent stuff, how you manage that?😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive respect for #twowomentravel  #repealthe8th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @KevDowling @DeathToAllMarks except the bottles would be filled with piss...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews some of us have to go to work shortly....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews why did the 33 just disappear from the timing screen at stop 1172?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lad beside me on the bus playing Garth Brooks' "Friends in Low Places" on a speaker.. Someone call the guards quick @dublinbusnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally welling up for that Johnny Giles montage, what a man. #There]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanrea "good craic" has a different meaning over there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickey Joe Harte would've saved that shot. #SoftHairSoftHands #ENGICE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help me please #IRLFRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Brit who voted in feeling like a mediocre English footballer now... "Do I have an Irish Granny?" #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could well be Trump and Johnson in power by the end of the year... And think what Bush and Blair did! 😳 #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I'm thinking at the moment is " Jaysus, ASDA in Enniskillen will be hopping!" #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see the @iom_tt  being covered live on Snapchat and how about Micky Dunlop!😱😱 #Ballsy #iomtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @EamoV1 giant cheques haven't been seen in Elland Road since 2003...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buseireann oh wait hold on, after pulling out of the station the driver parks it on the road and vows to catch up with another bus...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the @Buseireann X20 to Dublin, 7 people standing. Driver hasn't a clue or doesn't care. Hardly safe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews why am I not even surprised? #Joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews Why did the 41B drive by stop 3689 but with "Out of Service" on the front?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamOfUs Has to be hammering England in Croker, 2007 with Shane Horgans GAA catch for the try!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual rugby from Connacht... #Pro12Final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope someone throws a snackbox at this refs head in Galway tonight. #CONvGLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do referees keep on fucking Connacht? #CONvGLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa Irish oral is it??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting that this documentary comes out around the same time as a publicity crisis. #TheGuards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Denis O'Brien.... That would be true gas cuntism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBoland2 that would be a good course of action... #FewPintsAreGrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad day when Australia and Israel beat us to the final... Hard luck @JayBoland2  #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBoland2 pints tonight is itt?? #BittaKipperToo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By far the most depressing thing I have ever watched in a long time. Sickening. #Hillsborough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask for a pair in size 10, and after a committee meeting between the shop assistant and the manager, they bring me back a pair in 12...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In JD sports purchasing some new runners, talk about an ordeal and a half... #HaveYaGotThoseInTenDyaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballerWikis @ConorGreene91 don't go near the stuff...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MotoGP.... @ValeYellow46 @eugenelaverty yesss lads!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boojum_Dublin what time ye open till? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matoxley @hotsauce69x @MotoGP How can it be deemed too dangerous for MotoGP and not for WSBK??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ray_Mears @SpydercoKnives @ConorGreene91 ya'd cut a few lamb shanks with that yoke...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness Jordan Spieth seems like great craic... #SaidNoOneEver #Gurnick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Boojum opening a stones throw from the gaff and off to Elland Road next week. What a time to be alive...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boojum_Dublin When are ye opening lads? I'm shtarvin hai!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dublinbusnews Do your drivers know that the accelerator and brake pedals are more than just simply on/off switches? #WhiplashCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the #MichaelaMcCollum interview.... Moral of the story kids is don't buy gear on tic! #BadSkag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still trying to fathom what happened in the @MotoGP today other than GET THE FUCK IN YEOWW!! @eugenelaverty #EL50 #GreatDayForTheParish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin Bus would put even the jolliest of folk in terrible form. #IMightGetHomeTomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GerryAdamsSF Howya Gerry! Heard it was agecards only at the White House, same craic in coppers, they wouldn't take my "provisional".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the most depressing day in Irish history? #IREvENG #GE16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hendo_Gooner sad times we live in...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hendo_Gooner "Me father voted Fine Gael so I'll vote Fine Gael" and "He fixed the road" is their only political rationale...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @FrTedQOTD this is the greatest thing to ever happen on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RTE2ElectionSpecial Is kind of like the @vincentbrowne debate, but for real people...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@joanburton Wow they've got an Opel van! Criminals are shitting themselves now. You are a hero Joan...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViperHiggins The Regency shooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claire Byrne couldn't ask a question about #repealthe8th because Lucinda Creighton's head would've imploded... #LeadersDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucinda Creighton is Ireland's best Margaret Thatcher tribute band. #LeadersDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barry Cowen looks like a Hurling Manager about to rip into a Junior B team who were just beaten by 27 points...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flicked over from the Champions League on RTE to the Intertoto cup on TV3. Shite Enough... #LeadersDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joan Burton is like a fish up a tree. Clueless. #LeadersDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blueshirts knocking on the door ruining my lovely Sunday. #FuckOff #Die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMearaaa @DanielSturridge @LFC @Phil_Coutinho Alan Hutton's barred from Centra for robbing Wham Bars...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>