<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember this, Mike? https://t.co/iA88f8uQVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes  They'll blame Obama and/or his policies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until Trump releases tax returns and there has been a full investigation into Russian hacking, he should not be allowed to nominate SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rule Number 4:  Never, ever admit the actual truth, .... especially if it hurts the party.   #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump appears to be a man who couldn't pour water out of a pail without instructions.    #ComradeTrump… https://t.co/rR6UMc8sio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Comrade Trump:  Your mother was an immigrant.  I'm sure she'd be very proud of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't help but worry about a politician who thinks that plutonium is something named after a Disney character.… https://t.co/aBH42gnmg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mnny6223 @Naijai3 @mike_pence  Too late to take it back Mr. Pence. It's out there. Just another example of your stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is a terrorist's wet dream. He inflames radical hatred against America and then crows about "protectin… https://t.co/K4AAmxqyUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some guys think women are ruled by their hormones. As opposed to what a Congressman SHOULD be ruled by ........ the oil and gun lobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people in the GOP feel that women are too emotional and unstable to be President; ....... and yet, look who th… https://t.co/wGbzJnj2gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Patriotism is supporting your country all the time, ... and your government when it deserves it."    -  Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More and more shrinks say Trump displays mental illness  @mcspocky   #TrumpsAmerica     https://t.co/mSNAgy1mum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump isn't pandering to the most prejudiced people in America. ......... He's hustling them.        #DipShits… https://t.co/I5a6LuewMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember this Mike? https://t.co/W8bIIxYwjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad we can't find more politicians who are willing to live for the public ..... rather than live off the public.            #Bobby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Kellyanne Conway:   FYI .....  Genitalia is not an Italian airline https://t.co/VXEr4gnMRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If our forefathers had tried to be "patriotic" by NOT questioning their leaders' actions, this country might very w… https://t.co/tWQ92gJYfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The purpose of the United States Constitution is to limit the power of the Federal Government, not the American people"   - Teddy Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, people sometimes want to be stupid and prefer not to know the truth. The GOP depends on it.   #FoxNews  #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The people that elect corrupt politicians, imposters, thieves and traitors are not victims, .... they are accomplices"    - George Orwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen. the poster child for instability and stupidity ...... https://t.co/6TiIEThcll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorists use religion to explain their irrational behavior, ..... what's Donald Trump's excuse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are about to enter another dimension, a dimension not only of sight and sound but of mindlessness.  Next stop,… https://t.co/cdKp68lne7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Donald Dipshit:  You promised your supporters that Mexico would pay for your wall.  YOU LIED.      #BrokenPromise      #JustTheStart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear White House:  If you're compiling an enemies list of Twitter users for Donald Trump, don't forget to include m… https://t.co/T98Anyk6oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Trump Supporters:  Wake up!!!  Mexico is NEVER going to pay for Donald's fucking wall.  America is.       Yeah, us!!!!!       #DipShits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump bankrupted his own casino.  A casino!  Where the house always wins!  ...... Are you fucking kidding me?        #Idiot_in_Charge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is honest in his own way.  He honestly is an egomaniacal narcissistic pervert.     #ComradeTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's immigration ban doesn't include countries where he has businesses.  Of course, I'm sure that's just a coincidence.    #ComradeTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump and his people continue with their blatant lies, a free press must continue to report the truth to the people.        #1stAmendment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't need a wall, or a refugee ban.  We need better healthcare. We need improved infrastructure.  But above all… https://t.co/qNZBwx6pnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DianneWing2 @jodotcom  .... And how can you be "pro-life", yet favor the death penalty???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia arrests top cyber-intelligence official and top FSB agent after information was leaked.  Coincidence?      https://t.co/Ih0GQKE02v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump appears to be turning Voice of America radio into Voice of Alternative Facts radio.     #PropagandaRadio     https://t.co/i2g84XfJ13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWeasel  They're not pro-life. They're pro-birth. Once you're born, you're on your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lavenderblue27  He who shall not be named.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USRealityCheck  Trump won't release his tax returns because he knows he'd be impeached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget voter ID laws.  What this country needs is a voter IQ law !!!!    #MakeAmericaGrateAgain    @RWNJs https://t.co/1Oy6n3BDKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The secret of Freedom lies in educating people; ... whereas the secret of Tyranny is in keeping them ignorant."    - Maximilien Robespierre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear members of the Press:  We will be depending on you more than ever to supply us with the truth.     #AlternativeFacts      #ComradeTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  Dear Kellyanne Conway; There is no such thing as "alternative facts". There are facts and there are lies. PERIOD.  #ComradeTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rocky1542 @KellyannePolls  Lay off Kellyanne. I think she dressed appropriately for a circus performer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Politics_PR  New York Times admits it held back a Trump-Russia story that the FBI asked it not to publish   https://t.co/1Cwfsduv1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On his reality show, Trump starred as a total asshole torturing people who were stupid enough to work with him; ...… https://t.co/rvQQlDvSyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Comrade Trump;  My great-great grandparents were immigrants, ..... as were your parents, if you recall.               #RacistIdiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republicans wouldn't allow Obama to pick a Supreme Court justice, but are okay with Putin picking our new presi… https://t.co/DJ4L22KRC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rocky1542  Yes, ... but this narcissistic idiot doesn't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the over / under on how many days Trump will last in office before he gets impeached?   300 days?   400? https://t.co/ZGfA5sL3Zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Comrade Trump: From one unstable person to another, I hope everyone is happy in your head   -- Vladimir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump really wants Planned Parenthood to be shut down, he should turn it into a Trump property. https://t.co/thRQV5oKm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The upside down U.S. flag:  an official signal of distress.             #ComradeTrump https://t.co/SvaTEO9zM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spy agencies around the world are looking into Trump’s Russian ties
https://t.co/jPiGOAgpMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Trump Supporters:  You haven't made America great, ..... you made us weaker.            #PutinsPuppet          #ComradeTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Donald Trump never apologizes; he's never wrong no matter what crazy thing he says. ..... He's the white Kanye."    ― Bill Maher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In politics, age and experience don't always bring wisdom; ..... clearly, Mitch McConnell is proof of that. https://t.co/gnwdfjjtdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our lives begin to end the day we become silent about things that matter"    -- Rev. Martin Luther King https://t.co/ZZv3J56fWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Comrade Trump:  I need you to fuck up the American intelligence community  -- Vladimir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the situation were reversed and a Democrat won POTUS, with RNC emails being hacked, Republicans would be screaming for investigation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanLeeGee  There's a difference between being "pro-life" and simply "pro-birth".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilQuentin  Will that work with Donald Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @realDonaldTrump  No, they won't "pay us back". Another statement that shows how stupid Trump is!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder Trump wants to gut U.S. Intelligence.  Orders from Putin?  https://t.co/bPdbagN0O1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind @brontyman  Dear Kellyanne:  Strap yourself in. It's gonna be a bumpy ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann   Trump's insane Russian tweets today confirm his imminent psychological crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are racist, sexist, homophobic, xenophobic and speak fluent bullshit, ... you may have a place in the Trump… https://t.co/3BlOxeZMQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Fox News to learn about the facts is kinda like watching the corner hooker in order to gain good fashion sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Donald Dipshit:  We would prefer that our bridges and roads be upgraded before you build your fucking wall.… https://t.co/U9quTIAP2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoWithHer @MadYellowDog @MSNBC @JoeNBC  Can't understand why Morning Joe is on MSNBC. Stopped watching them long ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WVFDW @SheriBentsen   He has a reason. It's called Alzheimer's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOP:  Now that you have Donald "grab 'em by the pussy" Trump in the White House, ...... let's talk about famil… https://t.co/CEvXGkaQUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who criticize Trump should expect to face consequences"  - Kellyanne Conway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump went through three deferments to avoid serving in the military.     #RealAmericanHero       #ComradeDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citizens United may be doing more to circumvent the Constitution and destroy democracy than anyone ever thought possible.    #ComradeDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DonaldDipshit seems to have a very serious problem dealing with reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, Pence:   the Beavis and Butthead of American politics. https://t.co/RCJEaeZ1ZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is the admittance of a foreign dictator interfering with an American election through hacking, NOT a reason to investigate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admit that Trump's ego scares the shit out of me. Face it, the man has all the impulse control of a five year-old on meth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump:  The poster child for instability and stupidity. https://t.co/Z8t1H1onX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald's right, he doesn't need a daily intel briefing; ........ what he needs is intelligence of a much longer dur… https://t.co/WfQnqbHpB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Colin Kaepernick:  It's not a matter of what you stand for, but what you'll sit still for.      #YouShouldHaveVotedAsshole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has more skeletons in their closet than Donald Dipshit. Investigative reporters must be licking their chops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are Tourette's patients who have more control over what comes out of their mouths than Donald Trump does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's rallies look like a virtual Woodstock for the mentally impaired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, those who stand for nothing will often sit still for just about anything.                        #Vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to the GOP to come up with a solution to a problem that doesn't even exist.     #VoterFraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Donald Trump meets an autistic teenager, they should wear name tags so we can tell them apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOP:   Stem cell research shows great promise in restoring spinal cord tissue, .... which could help Republicans in Congress.   #Ironic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong. I love idiots. .....  I just don't think they should be in charge of the country.             #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Donald Trump:  Don't do anything stupid.  ..... Well, just try not to do anything          #Gettysburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It appears that our election process has turned into an episode of "Survivor."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching a Donald Trump rally is like watching a bad skit on Saturday Night Live, .... nothing can save those poor bastards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Ted Cruz will stay home on election night and burn a good book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wikipedia is the place I go to when I'm looking for knowledge. I go to Donald Trump's Twitter page for political comedy and general bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Dipshit continues his campaign of stupid, this time in Gettysburg, PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Donald:  Yes, there is a movement; ....... and it's in my bowels everytime I hear you speak. https://t.co/ANHaBnCwat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear GOP Congress:  Just a warning, there is no version of this scenario that doesn't end badly for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Donald:  A politician who is morally abhorrent and intellectually challanged is not the leader we're looking f… https://t.co/u2cVThPBCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between 2002 and 2006, Donald Trump donated $6,200 to Hillary Clinton's campaign for Senate re-election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I question politicians who R more interested in telling you why you shouldn't vote for the other candidate, than Y you should vote for them]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>