<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Architect, South Dublin, Permanent https://t.co/JH20sJ9bzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Project Manager - Sandyford, South Dublin, Permanent https://t.co/hnDtXzLclv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer, Permanent, NW Ireland, Fortune 500 co. Excellent package/bens/bonus david@methodius.com https://t.co/HVvyBdtZeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer, Dublin City Centre, €50-€60k. Permanent - Must be Eligible to Work in Ireland/EU https://t.co/zTTRN0PkWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Support Specialist, Dublin South, Permanent https://t.co/QsdDCFzstD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer - 6 Months contract. Dublin City Centre, https://t.co/uPiuphi9hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer (4 Roles), Cavan, Ireland, Permanent - Salary €55 to €65k, https://t.co/5iZ8HXSbSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Lead Developer, Dublin, Permanent - Excellent salary/package https://t.co/LIBZF3wKk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Developers, Permanent, Cutting edge new software, Fortune 500 Co, Permanent https://t.co/rHXOgGHNTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Lead (Software), Permanent, Multinational setting up Worldwide Hub in South Dublin, permanent https://t.co/mNj3w0nNVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Managers (4 Roles), Multinational Setting up in South Dublin, Permanent, €60 to €70k https://t.co/JdTptA8f8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architects (4 Roles), South Dublin, Permanent, Excellent Salary/Package https://t.co/UTTR0dmV4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Developer Roles, New team working on industry changing technology, Fortune 500 Co, permanent, Ireland https://t.co/bBKJ9cbkv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Lead Developer, Dublin, Ireland https://t.co/icYJFI4tLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer (4 Roles), Limerick, Ireland, Perm, - Fortune 500 Co. https://t.co/EiLhTpBotr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Software Quality Assurance, Antwerp Area, Belgium https://t.co/LR6DDozaC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Lead Developer, Dublin City Centre - with an exciting growing company changing their industry, Great salary…https://t.co/7yO1ImoWM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Developer, Dublin, Ireland, Permanent, Exciting compnay, Excellent salary https://t.co/Uaty04OKYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immediate need for a Java Developer Contractor for 12 months, based in Waterford City, The specific need is someone…https://t.co/ES38jwMG8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Actuarial Associate (Two Roles), Perm, Fortune 500 Co, NW Ireland email me at david@methodius.com for the ful…https://t.co/Zq2J7HZVeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archer Enterprise Architect/ Lead Specialist, NW Ireland, Permanent, Fortune 500 Co. https://t.co/4y7vFFDj20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Engineer, Dublin City Centre, with an exciting and growing young company https://t.co/72TeOqSdA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Developer (Two Roles) 5+ yrs experience, Fortune 500 Co, Permanent, Ireland https://t.co/7oWQOGyuUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA DEVELOPER ROLES, with a Growing Irish Start up, NW Ireland, Permanent, Excellent salary https://t.co/JmbbgsR5Wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archer Product Manager, Permanent, NW Ireland, Fortune 500 Co. https://t.co/bWmRN2JopK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer, 5 years+ experience delivering Enterprise solutions in Java or MS .Net •  2 years+ experience…https://t.co/H5eO06HmDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer, Permanent, Ireland, Fortune 500 Co. https://t.co/H5eO06HmDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Developer with Zend 2 &amp; Team Lead Experience, Dublin City Centre, Permanent https://t.co/zaWvnNjZI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Developer with Zend 2 &amp; Team Lead Experience, Dublin City Centre, Permanent, https://t.co/zaWvnNjZI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER 
Our client, a successful software company are looking to hire a senior Java developer to bec…https://t.co/uiHcVHIELc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT PROJECT MANAGER (Two Roles), Permanent, Fortune 500 Co, Ireland, Excellent Salary/Package - to see the full spec…https://t.co/GuJp1cHMJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Manager https://t.co/v9MuPN6ZvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Developers with Zend 2, Dublin City Centre, Permanent https://t.co/XB4gu2PtFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware Java Systems Architect – Data Integration, Permanent, Fortune 500 Co, Limerick https://t.co/5OuXhRE5e1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Sales Manager – Gardencare Business, Oranmore, Co. Galway  https://t.co/WpwArloNBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Java J2EE Developers, Permanent, NW Ireland, Fortune 500, 5 yrs exp, architecture, system design &amp; dev of Securi…http://t.co/h2Q72IMfvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator (10 – 12 Week Contact) - Dublin City Centre  https://t.co/mtiiQinRAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT System Administrator, Wicklow, €60k   Bens, Perm  https://t.co/RpSl2lDf3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Fortune 500 co. well established in Dublin, to join an expanding Team working on cutting edge proj…https://t.co/7QYgZVpQVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist - Senior Analyst, Perm, Ireland, Fortune 500 Co, with expertise in statistical modeling techni…http://t.co/h2Q72J3QUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UNIX System Administrator (2 Roles), Permanent, Fortune 500 Co, Limerick, Ireland https://t.co/g21d0ubWTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr PHP Developer Team Lead, Dublin city Centre, Permanent, Excellent Salary/Package https://t.co/D77BTJTTmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Salesforce Programmers, to design &amp; delivery of http://t.co/X1Qzeq7tPG based solutions, 5 yrs  exp  Enterprise solutions in Java or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr http://t.co/X1Qzeq7tPG  Lead Developer/Product Owner, to be the  lead tech reqs, architect &amp; document tech solutions &amp; develop on the …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RSA Archer Developer https://t.co/fg99MrjV6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer role in Letterkenny, Permanent, with a growing start up company, providing cloud-based software, Cand…http://t.co/fZhwMrBw9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst/ Snr Data Analyst, Performing in-depth analysis on existing data to provide summary and interpretation of results, Provide str…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager - Senior Project Manager - Software, strong PM exp,  strong communication skills, leadership ability,  track record of Proj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Mainframe Programmer, Permanent, 7 yrs exp, strong in COBOL, DB2/SPUF,  MVS JCL, Fortune 500 Co, NW Ireland, Must be eligible to work i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[looking for RSA Archer Developer, Permanent, Ireland, with a Fortune 500 Co, I'll forward on the full spec if you're interested,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr .Net Developer, 7   yrs exp,with PM or project lead exp &amp;  C# 4.0 , PL\SQL exp, &amp; Oracle &amp; Sql Server, Design &amp; …http://t.co/FNLcn4SwqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM WebSphere Portal Administrators with Jenkins (2 Roles), Permanent, Ireland, Fortune 500 Co - email david@methodius.com for th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM WCM Admin/ IBM WebSphere Portal Administrators (2 Roles), Perm, Fortune 500, Ireland -email me for the full spec…http://t.co/FNLcn4SwqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 50 jobs of the future in Ireland! http://t.co/lbjxwDq9BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you ready? Here are the top 50 jobs of the future - Independent.ie http://t.co/lbjxwDq9BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi All, Any Irish based SW devs, PMs, BAs, Support etc, a friend who works in The Independant, is doing a piece next week re pay scales in …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IBM WebSphere Portal Developers, Ireland, Permanent, 5 yrs   hands on WebSphere Portal exp, and web content management, with exp in …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer, Dublin City, Permanent, Fortune 500 Co,  5 yrs SW design &amp; Dev exp in Enterprise Java, JEE. You will be building high quali…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi All, I'm looking Data Scientist / Lead Data Scientist, Permanent, Ireland, ideally a PhD, Visa can be organised, …http://t.co/h2Q72IMNSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr C#.NET Developer, Ireland, Permanent, 7  yrs exp, C#, .NET 4.0 , Knowledge of Oracle &amp; Sql Server, software dev,…http://t.co/h2Q72IMNSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gidgerby 5 yrs Xpages for a tool from 2007 a bit ambitious allright, some decent hands on Xpages exp would suffice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattwhite Just forwarded the HR Manager the link to Xpages origins, 2007, he's considering 5 yrs exp a bit ambitious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perlausten This would go some way to explaining why I'm not finding people for this, thanks for the heads up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi All, I have urgent need for Lotus Notes Developer with 5 years XPages experience. Contract 3 to 6 months, Ireland, I will review all app…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Architecht,  Perm, NW Ireland, Fortune 500 Co, 7  yrs exp, Knowledge of one or more Java, .NET, J2EE, SOA, Messaging, Clou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/ Websphere Portal Developers Mid &amp; Snr roles, Ireland, Fortune 500 Co, Exp in Java/J2EE/JSP with web design exp using JavaScript, AJAX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer / Senior Systems Engineer, 4 yrs   exp, proficiency in understanding printing concepts &amp; technologies, NW Ireland, Permane…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone knows a Web Developer ready for a 2 Week contract in Dublin City Centre, starting next week, excellent daily rates, Please get in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Cm5oIKwzdG Great, Ill forward on the full spec - can you pop me an email to david@methodius.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Managers (2 Roles), NW Ireland, Permanent, Fortune 500 Co, Manage project development from initiation to closure, Candidat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Websphere Portal Developers - Mid to Snr Jobs.: http://t.co/bT9JSNd2En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Websphere Portal Developers - Mid to Snr Jobs. Java Portal Eng (4 positions) with web design exp in JavaScript, AJAX, JSON. You will be inv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Project Manager (Software) with proven record of taking initiative and leading strategic requirements to successful completion.  Stron…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jLX0f8fcMD Ill follow up on this now, thanks for the update]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#. NET Developers, Ireland, Permanent, with a fortune 500 Co, 7   year hands exp, C#, .NET 4.0 , PL\SQL ,phases of SW development from ana…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr C#.NET Developer with Oracle/PL/SQL,: http://t.co/8xuJxAv3c7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Management Specialist, NW Ireland: http://t.co/KQFPKj2jgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/cLbm1kn1dS Thanks for the message - but there is a criteria above "Must be eligible to work in EU" - is this the case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Qr3EYrwB8G This role is still open if anyone is interested,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Oracle PL SQL Developer, Dublin, 5 yrs + exp Oracle 10g or 11g SQL, PL/SQL, Perm, €65k + bens/bonus Must be eligable to work in EU, Flu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Oracle PL SQL Developer, Dublin, 5 yrs + exp Oracle 10g or 11g SQL, PL/SQL, Perm, €65k + bens/bonus: http://t.co/J8NI2ITrwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, 3 + yrs exp in a Business Process Improvement/ Business Analyst role, Strong documentation, writing Functional  Specs doc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Oracle PL SQL Dev, 5 yrs+ exp Oracle 10g or 11g SQL, PL/SQL dev, writing Oracle Store Procedures, Java dev, Fortune 500 co, Dublin city…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/JL9dZASQi4 Great, thanks for that,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr J2EE/Java developers, Web dev, strong XML/JavaScript exp, cyberfusion/scheduler processes &amp; deployment exp essential, perm, Ireland, Fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developers, 4 yrs + J2EE, exp, architecture &amp; system design of J2EE web applications, Fortune 500 Co, Perm,...: http://t.co/LgiTtOLJC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Support Developer with Oracle Forms, 5 yrs+ exp, Dublin City, Fortune 500 Co, Perm. Must be eligable to work in EU. Salary up…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[looking to fill a Snr Platform Engineer,Lead/Specialist Platform Engineer Linux
 for a Permanent role in Ireland with a Fortune 500 Co,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Voice Recognition Developer, VXML, Speech Recognition, Text to Speech  
IBM Websphere, Genesys or Avaya IVR, Fortune 500, Perm, Irela…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr C#.NET Developer with Oracle/PL/SQL, 7 yrs exp, all phases SW dev, analysis &amp; design - coding, testing, doc, implementation/, Ireland, …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr .NET &amp; a .NET Tech architect roles, Galway, Must be eligable to work in Ireland/EU, Fluent English, Permanent, Fortune 500 Co, I'll ema…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J2EE Java Developers (8 Roles) differeing levels of exp, 3 to 10 yrs exp, With Fortune 500 Co in Ireland, Permanent , eligable to work in E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotus Notes/Domino Senior Systems Eng Jobs (2 Roles), with good Admin exp, Sametime Quickr,Permanent, Ireland, Fortune 500 Co, Excellent pa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J2EE Developers (3 Roles), 5+ yrs exp, dev enterprise level J2EE appl, South Leinster, 12 Month Contract, eligable to work in Ireland, flue…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Message Broker Developer role in Ireland, with good experience in Java and in J2EE web applications development, Fortune 500 Co, perma…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Developer/ PL/SQL Roles with 5+ yrs exp, Ireland, Permanent, in a Fortune 500 co,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Release Manager, with Release Management and Code Deployment experience, permanent, Fortune 500 Co, Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SQL developer,developing data structures using Oracle 11g server +, Perm, Fortune 500Co,  Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Project Manager/Tech Lead, J2EE 10+ yrs exp, with web applications, Websphere, Fortune 500 Co, Perm,  N W...: http://t.co/PXenE7h2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/J2EE with SQL Developers(4 roles), 3+ yrs exp, Fortune 500 Financial Co, Munster, Ireland, Must be eligable to...: http://t.co/mjGipP15]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>