<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#laceupthegloves 
#getinthering 
#resist https://t.co/4pGrpRvGgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friendship IS magical.
@Marvel #besties https://t.co/SYe0OyUzpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cazzy Not surprised. That stuff's the high-grade shit. Uncut dope for film junkies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cazzy I give it a week or so. Once the good stuff clears out, things will start dropping. Hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cazzy It was minimal - 10% off - but coupled with the bulk deals and door crasher price on RIDDICK, it was a sweet deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently acquired at HMV's clearance sale. Bittersweet, as it is one of the last of my favourite places left for ha… https://t.co/Fach3ggBsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's all trendy and shit to bash it now, but man, screw that noise.
So excited for Season 2.  https://t.co/UEbeBHYrRm via @ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 yr-old piece I did in homage to THE PRIVATE EYES &amp; Marvel Monsters of yore.Seems like a good time to drag it out… https://t.co/KbdnNJZoAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Not to sound too fan-ish, but holy moley, "The Bacon Man" sounds like a character from one of your books. #HePutsTheMeatToYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man needs not reason nor excuse to be cruel.

No, all they need is permission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vigalondo 's COLOSSAL: love the premise.
Love Jason Sudeikis &amp; Anne Hathaway. 
Love this gorgeous brute. 
Top of t… https://t.co/uTxlQjqtfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AfterShockComix continues to put out some of the best comics for grown-ups, adding BLOOD BLISTER to the line-up. https://t.co/KHPD4VueFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three guesses who made the upgrade to next-gen today.
Seems like the best choice to get things started.
 
#ps4… https://t.co/jfzSAiKYm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came upon this in tonight's research: the recurring theme in @realgdt 's films. An insightful read.

https://t.co/0RhY1gl6MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT On behalf of Toronto: 
Can. Not. Wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4)... for whatever's coming down the pike. Be kind to each other out there. Shit's gone dark, and we're gonna need all the light we can get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) ...has left me spent. And I'm no good to my family if I can't be good to myself. I hope to come back stronger, sharper &amp; ready...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) ...it's time to step away and unplug. There's enough pain in our house that needs tending to, and the steady stream of panic and fear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Suffering from "online misery overload". Coupled with the grief of our recent loss &amp; the heavy weight it's placed on our home &amp; family...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America: This is the enemy.
This is the mission.
Apply pressure. 
Call your elected rep. 
Remove Bannon from The Wh… https://t.co/fnwmVGdkmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIMIC ( 1997):Cinematographer: Dan Laustsen | Director: Guillermo Del Toro 

#OnePerfectShot @realgdt @Miramax https://t.co/KH3PZT6HVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought it a year ago today. Now swollen w/art &amp; notes. Even got a look-see from the man himself.

Thank you,… https://t.co/YyIMw5W9kI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans/Trump apologists: your boy just gave carte blanche access to a known white supremacist agitator.

So... you're okay with this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lilyinapad Saw that, had to give my head a little shake to be sure I read it right. A brief blip of joy on the radar. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People shouldn't be afraid of their government. Governments should be afraid of their people."

Alan Moore, V for… https://t.co/yAUmm4ETk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What he said: keep those gloves laced up, America. This is only round one. #RESISTANCE https://t.co/R98y3GT7q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickBaker made this #Nosferatu out of #PaperMache . 
Dr. Frankenstein is real. 
And you're looking at him.
*bow… https://t.co/Hhso4wh8xs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Rebellions are built on hope."
This gives me hope. #Resist #Rebel https://t.co/KrvpSSk13s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovered on Saturday walkabout. Added it to the collection. Obviously.
#hellboy #guillermodeltoro #anungunrama… https://t.co/CzkStRmMvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed.
Your legacy will be one of shame. https://t.co/UTBH8JRW5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben_Meares A couple of days of radio silence isn't going to hurt, Ben. Switch off, recalibrate, come back fresh. No judgement here, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#crushed 😞 https://t.co/UZJLuwyGIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE AUTOPSY OF JANE DOE, a tight, creepy and clever mystery. For the first time in a long time, I  get the hype.… https://t.co/BmgWDaFknC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kane. John Merrick. Professor Broome. So many great performances, by this legend among actors. RIP John Hurt. https://t.co/evvxHFGyvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fbf to early days - over a year ago - with this little knucklehead. https://t.co/nOtA1aTbge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT 's @trollhunters : The Goblins were a "love at first sight" deal for me. The Sharpee gag never gets tired.… https://t.co/RChjWNh6gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianWCollins Just my two cents' worth: RAZORBACK's the best thing in his filmography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joss @HuffingtonPost Welcome back to Twitter, Joss. As you can see, standards have fallen very low since your last stint here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To celebrate the arrival of #MonstersUnleashed , a reshare: Fin Fang Foom.
King of The Marvel Monsters. https://t.co/iz67gcgZJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Fancy Moses! https://t.co/vRZ7aLHMIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work in Progress:
The few.
The proud.
The wakka-chakka.
@trollhunters https://t.co/zlf3j8lZ7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More monsters than common sense. Right here. #hellboy #pacificrim #guillermodeltoro #monsters #creatures https://t.co/KkJO8pyFaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's office mail: @RealGDT 's Angel of Death ! And it is a thing of infernal beauty.
#hellboyiithegoldenarmy https://t.co/GDmfhZYpOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the road soon.
No phone, no laptop, no plug-in to The Matrix whatsoever.

So be kind to each other.
See you in a few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alwayscoffee @filmthrills @prttybadtweeter ... and I told myself I wouldn't cry... seriously, fuck Nazis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seconded. https://t.co/hUEOlCDAdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ImWithLeVar https://t.co/2LE1Q64Qcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely service.
A lot of tears.
Now time for reminiscing &amp;  healing with all gathered.
R.I.P., my second mother. We all miss and love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Godspeed, America.
And good luck. https://t.co/P6bYLtv6io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have so many reasons why I want this day to just end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cynthialoyst Avoiding it like the plague. Between that and today's memorial, way too much to absorb. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my American friends:
#staystrong https://t.co/yq8x16VRgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broke out pencil crayons for this one. A little rusty, but picking up the flow slowly. #monsters https://t.co/hU7AK7Kjdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my gawd... it's beautiful. AND monthly? *deep breaths, McKenzie, deep breaths* #MonstersUnleashed https://t.co/PoyVq5L6dP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to the point of near-stupidity... https://t.co/cFhHbjN7ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow: memorial for Joanne.
After that? Off the grid &amp; out-of-town with the family for rest &amp; healing.
See you when we get back. Honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A level of disconnect that can best be described as "clinically apocalyptic". Remarkable. https://t.co/MPaYqcZIaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT 76 years in &amp; still dancing circles around the rest of the crowd. Really digging his SHADOWS ON THE GRAVE series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conference-call doodles.
No clue what it's supposed to be.
Not a one. https://t.co/cYwFGjX0nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perlmutations , @artofmmignola , if this is what it takes to bring you to the table for the HELLBOY III summit, th… https://t.co/ntIV3CfLNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisted_twins : just going to leave this here. 
They had me at "Moogle". https://t.co/VC1Ee1jEbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liking what I've seen so far. This seals the deal. https://t.co/9N7io66iEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT PS: if it helps to bring them to the table, I'll bake cookies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT I can't imagine a better collection of words to wake up to this morning. Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So clearly, Gwyneth Paltrow hates vaginas.  
https://t.co/IsvNFpIkPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100K "Yes" votes &amp; @RealGDT promises "a serious sit down w/ Mignola et Perlman!" for HELLBOY III.

I can't make thi… https://t.co/pfQYlbglUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[File under "Obviously ".
Congratulations. 😬 https://t.co/WKXH7sLxn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MonstersUnleashed is off to an awesome start. The last page gave this old-school monster kid a ridiculously huge g… https://t.co/EoXKrUDH3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lexialex Deep breath, recalibrate and return to the ring when ready. You got an army of support here - we got your back, you warrior-queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JovankaVuckovic @RealGDT Right? My goosebumps have goosebumps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT This may be the best thing I've read all day... fingers crossed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisted_twins @GSN @munkmetal1 Crossing fingers, toes and internal organs (better safe than sorry, right?). #hellevatorS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlemissrisk @CBCNews Can't... unsee... must scrub brain with wire brush...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having @TheBeguiling closer to my work now make lunch breaks even better on #NewComicsDay  .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["... they never get the eyes right..." https://t.co/QXf1Qt8UUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cynthialoyst Exactly. I'd go with plaid. A bold choice AND proudly Scottish.
https://t.co/oLFe70NMQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesdays suck. That's just science.
This will more than make up for any f**kery the day decides to throw at me, t… https://t.co/pGZQMxNfa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alwayscoffee Credit goes where it's due, dear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doug_Tilley Agreed. And watching Canada's conservatives drooling with glee at the news is maddening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching The Sun practically slobbering at the prospect of Kevin O'Leary leading the Conservatives is equally hilarious &amp; disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealGDT Watching HBII &amp; BLADE 2 with a flip of the "hero/villain" dynamic is incredibly rewarding. Completely different films. Sadder, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere, in the cinema of my mind, there's a Prince Nuada/Mr. Wink prequel. And it's awesome. A man can dream... https://t.co/AJTT018jxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry isn't easy. @alwayscoffee just makes it *look* like it.
ALL YOUR BEST MONSTERS

https://t.co/w2jhzdRbos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alwayscoffee @nanogeekette This. "Tooth and Nail" is the ONLY way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanogeekette @alwayscoffee Now THAT'S fighting the battle. Good. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanogeekette @alwayscoffee Lace up your gloves and take your positions. Because the revolution AIN'T gonna be won on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nanogeekette @alwayscoffee Irvine Welsh, March 2016. 
Really? It was bound to happen. https://t.co/1kQdOBSGs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katsandcrows @Xtremeplaypen Holy Moley. This is some straight up Frozen/Disney Princess -grade stuff here. Lovely shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed. A nasty bit of work, with  THE best jump scare since EXORCIST III. And that soundtrack... https://t.co/ZdkAwPMNlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moral of this thread:
Talent isn't enough.
Learn the hustle. https://t.co/D20EcLVk2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joseph_OBrien @CBCNews Further proof that anything the Americans can do, Canadians can do as a second-rate pale imitation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lexialex @OldWays1828 Does  the F stand for "Fuck Yourself"? Wow. Guy's a walking shitstain. Oh yeah... and reported.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@job1866 @RealGDT @trollhunters @netflix Thank you! Feedback like this is worth its weight in gold! 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBurnham Ah, Trencher ... WAY ahead of the curve for its time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with that... good night, Twitter. https://t.co/MdpGyxgXsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this.
And I'm also sure as f**K not arguing with Cersei Lannister. https://t.co/wTerLt0BNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garvindale @RealGDT Whoa. Mind? Blown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealCliveBarker 's INFERNAL PARADE: Monsters. Murder. Greasepaint.
Across cities &amp; worlds, the carnival is coming.

https://t.co/czcB4ptg4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megarobotman73 @RealGDT Seconded. Throw in Draal and Angor Rot. 
Not for me. 
No, no...for the kids!
*looks side-to-side nervously*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also known as "buyer's remorse". https://t.co/4U1xHGtdJn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>