<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the book we were reading at #BowlingGreen just before the flying monkeys attacked. https://t.co/qEZzojtUf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the day the Lord has made. Let us rejoice &amp; be glad. Dammit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Winning_Deer @NaomiKritzer @NPR @democracynow Oy. Depressing. I will look into this story. Expecting to be disillusioned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Winning_Deer @NaomiKritzer @NPR Who? Who did they fire? What reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To think of the apparatus of industry &amp; state (military, shipping, etc) necessary to capture, document, transport,… https://t.co/g4rXvVQ8gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bijancbayne @OxonAndrew 2/2 I'm assuming that Africans died in staggering numbers in Haiti &amp; Dominican. Why else the need for resupply?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bijancbayne @OxonAndrew 1/2 When you look at that animation, the number of enslaved africans going to Hispanola is staggering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a #BowlingGreen survivor it pains me to see how the media, both right AND left, is omitting all mention of the flying monkeys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Paul Ryan, @SpeakerRyan, is not looking gleeful. To Paul Ryan, a manly man, destroying the United States of Ame… https://t.co/LuSLIAettE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As @atrios (whom I love despite knowing he'll never acknowledge my existence) would say, "shit is fucked up and bul… https://t.co/buRRXxWJNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7/3 Were I in the Academy, it would get my Best Picture vote. Yes, it would be a political vote. So what? This is an absolutely vital movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6/3 I applaud the creators of Hidden Figures for making an unsublte movie, one that a child -- or even a racist, sexist goon -- can grasp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5/3 I probably won't re-watch Hidden Figures. It is not a subtle movie. But I hope every adolescent in America, nay, the world, sees it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4/3 The story told by Hidden Figures is awe-inspiring, humbling, profoundly important for many reasons. I was crying as end credits rolled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/3 So lots of info was shoe-horned in, &amp; some of the tropes were obvious, &amp; the sound track hits you over the head with a hammer. But. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/3 Script crammed so much info: the personalities &amp; histories of the characters, intensity of the space race, brutal reality of Jim Crow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/3 Just saw Hidden Figures. Liked it lots. Screenplay: cheesy; schematic. Acting: fair to very good. Story: essential, profoundly moving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was in Peace Corps in Senegal my friends in the village named a white chicken after me. https://t.co/7bbFpnRI1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @SenateMajLdr and @SpeakerRyan promised to abolish Obamacare on "Day One". Looks like they're running late. Wonder what's keeping them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the day the Lord has made. Let us rejoice &amp; be glad. &amp; turn off our minds, relax &amp; float downstream. I mean, get up &amp; get going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both. That's my guess. It's like Mafia Wars. https://t.co/bEBRA5D23C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solargroovy Just another case of blind justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish it had not taken her so long to get here, but I'm glad to have her with us. It's Game Over; Beth. You know i… https://t.co/Up3mzEvSUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I like this song, subject of "the most 80's music video ever". I even once paid money to see this band. https://t.co/5c31cbumlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those of us who were actually present at the Bowling Green Massacre will never forget the flying monkeys. Never. Don't even suggest it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want 80's music videos? You CAN NOT top this. It is the distilled essence of the genre. https://t.co/5c31cbumlj https://t.co/3RkwAFgOGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One can dream, can't one? Where is the harm in dreaming? https://t.co/HbT7Fu49y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe me, I am NOT going to mess with her. What's that? She's been dead 100+ years? I don't care. Still afraid. L… https://t.co/xewhK0Rcxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I knew more about betting, bookmaking, etc. It would be diverting to set up bets counting down days until @mike_pence makes his move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God have mercy on the children and other innocents. https://t.co/KX4hePCAs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck the United States of America. Really. Fuck us. If this is what we have become, we deserve whatever we get. Or… https://t.co/X1b3k2OTjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a question that's been worrying me: After @mike_pence mounts his 25th amendment coup, what happens to Bannon, Miller et al?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her brother, Eric Prince, CEO of Blackwater Mercenaries, Inc, is literally the embodiment of every Bond &amp; Batman vi… https://t.co/qEAsh7IddP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S.A.  In 2017.  Jesus wept, as my father used to remind me. https://t.co/oQBX0r8zvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/2 @SpeakerRyan 95+% of people likely to read this thread won't catch allusion to Eddie Haskell. So here's a link: https://t.co/WVKfE8Pgcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 @SpeakerRyan Makes a show of his catholicism. He was an altar boy. As was I. I remember his type, the smarmy Eddie Haskell altar boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2  @SpeakerRyan? A weasel, a coward, a self-loving vain mirror-gazing boy; married money &amp; has spent his entire l… https://t.co/3FF7L1fwLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was freeloading for a while, but I just rejoined @ World View (or whatever it's called) level &amp; also Friends of S… https://t.co/CAIyNHVYo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DAMN IT, @SenateMajLdr, @SpeakerRyan, your mandate &amp; your PROMISE was to dismantle Obamacare! We're watching you! E… https://t.co/XP3lDj2liD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rejoined National Peace Corps Association. Encouraging other RPCVs to do so also. https://t.co/UJxnW6MdBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad my father (U.S. Army 1943-46), friends T. Hale ( liberation of Buchenwald) &amp; T. Goethals (Battle of the Bulge)… https://t.co/oieYn6rYV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a problem that Mr. Grassley solved long, long ago. Once you've sold your soul to Mephisto the image in the m… https://t.co/HHA2PtPbY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest news abt the Peace Corps: https://t.co/uSzMikwtDy // I've finally re-upped my Peace Corps Connect membership. You can thank Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["'Once the rockets go up, who cares where they come down? That's not my department' says Werner von Braun." //… https://t.co/rybVRg01cQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[651 Drill night tonight. We didn't do much, just walked through a few RIT exercises. But every bit of practice help… https://t.co/cirK9mtMBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pepper-spraying thug latter successfully sued for all the harm done to him by the incident. https://t.co/BS5NXQ5eop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EEmersonWhite @owillis Unless they decide they need to relieve him of command to keep us all from getting killed. Scary times indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A writer worth checking out, friends. https://t.co/ZlyEx8XjOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neo-orwellian illustrated #dystopian phantasmagoria -- a story for our times. https://t.co/qEZzojciQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, there are not. https://t.co/a2vfOu0bhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ptwithy Hey Tucker! See DM please. To follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinhendrix no, but I just followed him. @DenisHurley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Still a Scandal! https://t.co/6sheswLE2c via @nybooks  // on Joyce's "Ulysses"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I presented a paper on #biohacking @ #defcon 24. It was fun. More importantly, it amped my hacker cred to infinity.… https://t.co/OCsvNQd74a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread. https://t.co/ageUeV5mVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT. Read now. Call your senators today! https://t.co/3FjtrzpnyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 bullet dodged, amid the fuselage. Stay safe out there! (But keep resisting.) https://t.co/CddnLZi8qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datagoodies Quick, somebody call rewrite! @BCDreyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technopotheosis - my free newsletter abt art, ethics, synthetic biology, firefighting &amp; manual labor. https://t.co/KT3V6IUnRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've read the 1st three at least twice each &amp; loved 'em. The Wake defeated me. It wasn't even a contest. https://t.co/HtZkuwmlgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote this neo-orwellian #dystopian tale in 2008 but it's about today. 12 creepy-cool illustrations by @MFDHemming https://t.co/qEZzojciQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course there is. https://t.co/GO8CFARpbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the day the Lord has made. Let us rejoice &amp; be glad. &amp; do pushups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree with this. But I don't know facts of situation at Berkeley. If it was a police riot, or right-wing riot, it… https://t.co/FecjS1ERt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is coming, yay. I know @mlb is horrible, but baseball isn't. &amp; soon @nfl will be out of our lives for a few months, thank Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EEmersonWhite We have seen a few sparks here and there, but in general, you're right. It's depressing. The people must lead, alas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Park Service &amp; State Department &amp; even inside the White House, providing resistance &amp; intel. At least some o… https://t.co/youTTvHqXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: pic of Navy SEALS flying a Trump flag. I wish they understood patriotism. Cowards. This patriotic Peace Corps Volunteer sez Kiss My Ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the fuck knows. It's crazy salad. @SenateMajLdr &amp; @SpeakerRyan have decided to let President Bannon blow everyt… https://t.co/7C4SXuOwuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But unfortunately it doesn't seem to be working, hence the wig," he added. https://t.co/YPhfApQ7sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technically speaking, is there a difference between punching a Nazi and punching Mitch McConnell? Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military Convoy Flying Trump Flag Belonged to SEAL Unit  https://t.co/2EGOOsEems via @ABC // All involved must be busted or it's bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck this pig. https://t.co/2mvMuT621w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Conservative firebrand". https://t.co/XuBPLCU36r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy SEAL pansies with no respect for military regulations. (When I served my country overseas, under oath &amp; hazard… https://t.co/GStlA2oqkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off on 7 AM boat, 2+ hour drive to Boston, several doctor visits/tests for Dear Wife, 2.5 hour drive to 7:30 boat home to Vineyard. Phew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the day the Lord has made. Let us rejoice &amp; be glad. (Instruction manual available for a modest fee.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phillip K. Dick saw this coming. And so he checked out. https://t.co/QKZSYrj08n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any clickbait that implies Trump "thinks" is going to fail my 1st-level test. Trump "thinks" like a shark or an eel… https://t.co/lqTASxpJmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A war with many fronts. We can, and must, fight on most of them. Support each other. So damn difficult. But we can… https://t.co/RlUunASwlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am retweeting this although I have strong reservations about the use of "mom" as an improper noun. "[m]other" pre… https://t.co/AGOfbSqraA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good. And may God curse any Democrat who wavers. I say that with all sincerity, though I only wish I believ… https://t.co/EgxPslt7SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just getting started, motherfuckers. Game on. https://t.co/2ENwCLk0yL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well now, that seem downright uncharitable. But so long as we don't handcuff the First Lady &amp; send her to a dark si… https://t.co/gS1yqpEwcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck you, "christian". https://t.co/ql44ML4Sbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @sjoakley Firefighting is free therapy for me. Intellectually, physically &amp; socially challenging; useful to others &amp; beneficial to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpentecost No, perhaps I was not clear. I meant the one now married to the president. For his daughter Ivanka I have no sympathy at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodikantor @cfishman Hint: Obama's a kid abandoned by his African father, raised by poor single mother; Gorsuch a child of privilege. Next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similarly, I cried out "Thank you, merciful Jesus, for calling him to your bosom!" https://t.co/L02bAHP6it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjoakley When you're a firefighter you sometimes visit places of obvious disfunction. Our job is to extinguish fire. No further comment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjoakley I agree. And evidently, this same house had had a fire before I came on the department. Astounding irresponsibility. But. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article is fascinating and important, but funny in that it implies that Trump plays any role in decision-makin… https://t.co/F4potJR0d0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelVanderWerf Agree on all counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjoakley The first one was bad; 2nd one could have gotten someone hurt or killed. I believe that Chief issued a citation, but I'm not sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjoakley When I became a firefighter, the very 1st fire I went to was a chimney fire. 1 year later, a fire in the same chimney. Astounding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjoakley You would be astounded to learn how many people don't do that. We see fires where chimneys haven't been cleaned for a decade+.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6/3 @LillyLyle We on roof dropped chains; people inside collected burning debris in buckets from stove &amp; carried it outside, doused w hoses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5/3 @LillyLyle If the chimney had been breached by fire we would have had to use hoses and it would have been very destructive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4/3 @LillyLyle Very little water used; maybe 1 liter. Hoses were there in case it got nasty inside, a precaution. Sometimes you need them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/3 @LillyLyle To minimize damage, we attack fire by dropping chains down chimney from roof; debris falls into wood stove below.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>