<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[His problem with running the meat raffle at Clovelly Bowlo will be, as in politics, no one wants to drink with him https://t.co/VjMnJ9tcGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't knock yourself, Jeff
I thought it was a good laugh and very apt considering how many years I spent around rac… https://t.co/OkVfEm3l7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, Marie, for your support
But I'm sure my wayward godson didn't mean to be spiteful
I never got around to… https://t.co/HfN9CDNzP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That hasn't changed, Jeff
The problem now is that there is no place to get away from gambling
Pubs used to be a ref… https://t.co/IKGjNcJ5ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manly Sea Eagles' deal to rename oval 'Lottoland'
Top effort
Helping Sydney to lead the world in gambling misery
https://t.co/NXjGlRpXgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any chance Trump could grant US citizenship to a fellow shifty con artist?
They took Murdoch off our hands
https://t.co/r48CYQViEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's because they haven't struck any oil, you dopey bastard
And I thought all the dumb bushies were in Parliament… https://t.co/9gG7sa1A6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what immigrants think of The Wall
https://t.co/cqmhFAtoBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's image of our suave, self-assured, smile-beaming Prime Minister
Haemorrhoids can be a bastard https://t.co/5X3bPvaHqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull mob are right
Trump shamelessly copying their best ideas
Like "steady demolition of 50 years’ worth of env… https://t.co/Tz0wxGskde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or for us, hard to imagine it turning out better https://t.co/w3oq0wIdgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 2 PMs have been iInternational laughing stocks
Abbott because he's Abbott
Turnbull for reprising Neville Chamberlain
Pissed on by Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I have a piece of paper in my hand signed by Herr Trump. We will have peace in our time on Manus and Nauru" https://t.co/XbpsSip4xJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm's brain would hopefully be functioning better than his heart, the beat of which is almost indetectable https://t.co/HCfHfPaUF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AFP forced to pay CFMEU's court costs over unlawful Canberra office raid
AFP is LNP lickspittle
Bali 9
Make that 7
https://t.co/qgspVHHfik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked NSW Treasury document
Billions to be made by land title registry operator
Brown Paper Bag Baird's last hurrah
https://t.co/BmC0uFC8y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As a dog returns to his vomit, so a fool repeats his folly"
Regurgitating the same garbage
Blame Labor
Border secu… https://t.co/QvH2vdvoNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vic Premier urged to return trains, trams to public hands
Public transport vital service
Should never be privatised
https://t.co/CKg8I19rhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morrison: Clean energy subsidies could be used to build more coal power plants
Or used to revive buggy whip industry
https://t.co/lhh6SZm7Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Neville Chamberlain “has received assurances [the deal would go ahead] directly from President Trump”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He kicked in one-and-three-quarter million for the election
And he still hasn't got a single friend in the Liberal Party
Bwahahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White and black differences https://t.co/Q5kgYvYLnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little jockey bloke looks like he's having a seizure
Dumb ex-Queensland copper looks like a particularly dumb &amp; dod… https://t.co/eNzEjkw2bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've always been prepared to put my money where my mouth is"
Well his mouth must be in the Caymans https://t.co/wuhV8f0IJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libs &amp; still more Nats have to stay on message with race hate
If they repudiate the deranged demagogue Trump they c… https://t.co/NGFRIILdZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Online Etymology Dictionary dates "welch" back to 1857 as racing slang, "to refuse or avoid payment of money la… https://t.co/4cZbM0EGMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what immigrants think of The Wall
https://t.co/cqmhFAtoBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA Labor candidate set to stand down
Inappropriate behaviour claims
Is there something in the water in WA - and Qld?
https://t.co/mRymHu7p13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Moron candidate and church pastor, 73, wants a Russian bride aged between 20 and 44
"Please explain"
Can they g… https://t.co/2ZiB40x4R4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBN Still On Track For 2016 Completion, Turnbull Says
https://t.co/QginYjM9gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OED recognises both spellings
Refers to alleged dishonesty of the Welsh
As in nursery rhyme, "Taffy was a Welshman" https://t.co/Ume8KbcRZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you'd be aware, Jeff, it was a term much used on racetracks where "to welsh on someone" was regarded as poor form https://t.co/6cs3rKVaKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we've found with our cardboard cutout PM you don't have to be smart to be wealthy
But it helps to be dodgy https://t.co/szBa9iOMjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Prime Minister for Point Piper &amp; Caymans looked crook yesterday imagine how he is now that Trump has welshed on his refugees deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meltdown
Image 1: 1st Question Time as PM
Image 2: Announcing Double Dissolution Election
Image 3: How he looks now https://t.co/FNmAqMy11V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What sort of government is too cowardly to stand up to naked fascism? Ours
https://t.co/UIwHIijc9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would a pub reduce staffing due to existing rate of company tax?
Are many publicans members of Business Council? https://t.co/4m0wCkF55Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you alright, boss
"Should I get Barnaby to take over while you gather your thoughts?" https://t.co/2TDWn7oaoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting parallel between Shorten &amp; Abbott
Losing close election meant 2nd term as Opposition Leader
Time to learn craft of campaigning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word "fascist" was regarded as outdated &amp; offensive
Since the inauguration it's seen as accurate descriptor
Which LNP happy to align with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But most Australians aren't in line to pick up a Brown Paper Bag
Follow the money trail https://t.co/48ZoVK7GpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other Young Libs had forgotten it was going to be a wear your uniform night https://t.co/CPZOXY35Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember how the Double Dissolution was going to get rid of rogue elements in the Senate?
That went well https://t.co/wZMsjq2Bym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given insanity of US leadership &amp; lickspittle Australian leadership
Many tempted to pass themselves off as Canadian https://t.co/QAxlYAKQ2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PublicEthics @blanketcrap @ConversationEDU Foreign aid slashed by LNP
But also compare Whitlam to Hawke/Keating https://t.co/ZTFPwyDne6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian scientists cook up material 200 times stronger than steel out of soybean oil
Turnbull mob gutted CSIRO
https://t.co/SWXeSHzuwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One photo taken pre-Double Dissolution
The other after
MSM were virtually unanimous in declaring it a master stroke https://t.co/WEMNRdMOTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect they might have created a formidable enemy

On the positive side, Linda, you now know what grubs they are https://t.co/EImsBDOsT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A US President implements what are clearly fascist policies
And the reaction of our government
"He's following our lead"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic that the phrase, "gutless wonder", has fallen into disuse at a time when we have a Prime Minister who is the very embodiment of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's ageing by the hour
No bloody wonder when you see the class of boofhead he's got around him https://t.co/Ae8SCcXpr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No prizes for guessing who'll be paying https://t.co/9GCjxoc0Ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understood, but Australians are eternally grateful to the US for making Rupert Murdoch &amp; Greg Norman non-Australians https://t.co/ehkGbAXAKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada to offer temporary residency to travellers stranded by Trump's immigration ban
It's called style
https://t.co/5MYl8TzXmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've caused an international incident with a country that took Rupert Murdoch &amp; Greg Norman off our hands
Apologies https://t.co/ASKxgp5bna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My excuse: generation gap
He doesn't look too switched on, but probably struggling with the enormity of the occasion https://t.co/sxvaD354NW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW Cabinet reshuffle
Factional deals behind Premier's ministerial choices
Libs tearing themselves apart
Life's good
https://t.co/ruhNdIzPj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asbestos almost wetting herself with excitement
Kidman &amp; Travolta with that "Oh gawd" look
Bloke on left nose candy? https://t.co/ewF94SSXBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asbestos &amp; partner having an absolute ball
Don't laugh Australia
You're paying for it
Spending like a drunken sailor https://t.co/5jxpBY4oau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness to Labor they fought hard for an effective Resources Rent Tax
Defeated by Abbott &amp; the miners' millions https://t.co/BTzs50Hgjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortunately the fascist groundswell in Australia is virtually imperceptible https://t.co/IUcC4XzOcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's an Arab?"
Hanson not too proud of her "supposedly 9% Middle Eastern" heritage
Heavy emphasis on "supposedly" https://t.co/xq1KhKVtgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Muslim rally by Reclaim Australia a fizzer
More police &amp; media present than protesters
Bwahahahaha
https://t.co/P8pl8RK9SG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how much she'll claim to have paid for that https://t.co/9KPmenDti5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And lives of the citizens of countries invaded

We should stay out of war unless protecting ourselves from invasion https://t.co/SqRWM3bhW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take it you're not a fan, Sandra https://t.co/holNzanUrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are also massive returns to the US military industrial complex from orchestrating wars https://t.co/uCtQS7nqoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually the Indonesian armed forces only number about 400,000 but your point is well made https://t.co/cREw2rmpw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the leader who made it a Federal issue to leave no urban home unsewered

Gough https://t.co/E4mWu5zKhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US was 3 years late to WW1
US was 2 years late to WW2
Now has President whose stated position is "America First"

Armed neutrality for Aus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guaranteed cure for constipation https://t.co/XQ9V5V0ATt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite well expressed, James
Do you read all of her tweets to Pauline before you post them? https://t.co/mNxRQr6mIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["United States as the most important power to ensure peace"
Ensure peace my arse, Asbestos
They are the warmongers https://t.co/smV3Y1RkUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of business vision
BHP's massive iron ore/coking coal reserves used to create Jap steel industry
Not our own https://t.co/QADD3PoYLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree but Menzies shouldn't get all the credit
Since Federation we've been the land of wasted opportunities https://t.co/v0GtQ6jjtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps the Nats bloke had liquid breakfast at an early opener
His Federal counterpart is often grinning like a loon https://t.co/eYnY7aNzSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacist threatened to shoot up Central Coast shopping centre
Where politicians inflaming race hate leads
https://t.co/KpS4hNaQWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Christofascists hijacked the US political system
We're not there yet but we have our own RWNJs working on it
https://t.co/PAV2g5R6FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump making beginner's error of cosying up to Putin

US determination to provoke China into conflict

We need to shift to armed neutrality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on Brandis's obvious incomprehension of &amp; lack of respect for the law none of his books have ever been opened https://t.co/lmAdzOvc1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piccoli out of step
Genuinely concerned about public education

Interfering with Brown Paper Bags from Lib mates https://t.co/AH9ZtxL5Hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW Libs tearing themselves apart
Out of control factional blood letting
Meanwhile the pissant Nats

How sweet it is https://t.co/txWLANYvcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Menzies, who created the Libs, was their only leader of any substance
Howard was a survivor but truly contemptible https://t.co/tZAQcXC3JR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could you imagine resort to white supremacist race hate being tolerated by the Great Man? https://t.co/Uou9iFSebD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One even leads a Party catering for candidates and voters dumb as dogshit https://t.co/olADUAaa06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're forgiven
A tragedy Whitlam didn't have adequate support from colleagues
Then there was the treachery + CIA https://t.co/kn2KbRdr1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expanded version is even more apposite:
Dumb as dogshit but cunning as a shithouse rat https://t.co/G9bFH5j9eG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You left out Australia's only statesman
Whitlam
Interesting https://t.co/k9fc8sBA2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's beyond any thought of defeating Labor
Focus on destroying Turnbull &amp; vindicating himself
Labor win might assist https://t.co/ep2m4G0dfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSW Labor right has been nothing to be proud of
Hopefully the rats no longer control the ranks https://t.co/0FuN0kXA08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently he was a Minister from 1951! https://t.co/GOG3vpl6Y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was going to use "harbourside" but Billy Big-ears' electorate bordered the Parramatta River
Twitter is constraining https://t.co/dnRJE2uYEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finalists worst ever PM contest
McMahon 21 months
Abbott 24 months
Turnbull 16 months (may have already left office)
All inner-Sydney Libs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We would have turned the child away too
We've always been selfish &amp; unhumanitarian
White Australia attitude endures https://t.co/tSxp0hP8qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right has always dominated Federal ALP
Some counter tendency now
But so much of electorate self-absorbed &amp; uncaring https://t.co/PUVHMcAytr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oz, paper no one buys, is obsessed with it:
"Bill Shorten and the Right must resist Labor Left’s ascendancy" 14 Jan https://t.co/X58eCJTWS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Labor remarkably disciplined since their defeat
Tribute to all concerned
And Left increasingly influential https://t.co/98Yjy1r8Fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usual clutching at straws to try to topple Shorten
Federal Labor has moved from Presidential to collegial leadership https://t.co/pB9l6S7lR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His reputation as a pugilist is way overblown
Only ever had 5 fights, each 3 rounds, all against other uni students https://t.co/YkeHSXTyIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hellenes should not aspire to racist white privilege
A powerful, provocative &amp; challenging message about our society
https://t.co/9DWeRbXfWf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>