<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom is learning fast about Aussies taking the piss!  #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work it Tziporah! You rock #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tegan and Kris... meanwhile Ash has put a bunny on to boil on the  campfire  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#steem !! Love it! #ImACelebrityAU https://t.co/XI0cZ58vEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash is very passive aggressive #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've had a good feed, now they are sitting around a campfire whilst someone sings. What a top evening!! #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash's next tucker challenge... boiled bunny #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Price.. tucker challenge trojan!  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['who's your daddy?' #ImACelebrityAU https://t.co/qksh0jQdU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Kris Smith just Tziporah's pink flamingo who its daddy is? #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no taste buds at the back of your mouth? Then why don't most girls..... never mind :)  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly!! Shut your fucking mouths... Tziporah is awesome https://t.co/MjB7LyPAFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['you're going to have Ostrich anus' Lisa Curry... Great stuff #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomijuric9 was there that night. You were an absolute trojan playing your part in @JTroisi14 goal. Congrats mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['one man with the head job' hehehehehe #BillandBoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far out, how passive aggressive is Ash Pollard #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ash Pollard.. mop and bucket please #snailtrails #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamTziporah Thank you!! #fanboymoment !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am unashamedly on @TeamTziporah  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many on twitter wishing violence or death on Steve Price... charming #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tziporah showing she is not pretentious at all. Great scenes #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a harrowing tale. Congrats Casey on turning it into a positive  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they have Takko Yucky on the spewshi train? #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tonight, we are doing a number on our contestants'
'That's disgusting'
That was, dare I say, piss funny #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aren't we lucky to have the likes of Ashton Kutcher and Julia Louis Dreyfus to lecture common folk on how much better they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Fischer.. picked it!!! #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Fisher for former billionaire lifestyle anyone? #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should have shown Tegan in the shower. Let's be honest, it's what the fans want  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure they'll find Jub Jub in the jungle #ImACelebrityAU https://t.co/PRMauRAfJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant wait to see Casey and Teigan swimming together #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Curry has it sorted. Food, chat and entertainment #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who or what is an 'Ash Pollard'? #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nat Bass is human after all. Loved her emotions and swearing. Goon on her!!  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Holy Shit'.... Natalie Bassingthwaite #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Arnold's agent is sooo fired!!!  #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazeem is on his usual comedy standard... flatlining #imacelebrityau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one word for Tom Arnold... awkward #ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewbrala be fair... some of them can count to potato!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes It'd be great for everyone else though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes Want me to get you a ticket? VIP meet and greet? https://t.co/7W4clXmVQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jillian Skinner wont be missed. spend about, 20 years whinging about the health system only to make it worse once she got in charge #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuntyNeville664 it doesn't suit their twisted narrative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well said Glen Matlock!!! https://t.co/Eaiw7UA96l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See old mate in The Cove wearing the FTT shirt? $10 says he wasn't wearing it walking into the stadium #MVCvSYD #BigBlue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobskiNew Not sure about bolted, but I think he should be included. do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOu'd think Troisi will be a cert for a #Socceroos call up for the next WCQ #mvcvsyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mvcvsyd Jimmy T is absolutely unstoppable. Carving up the #ALeague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wandererstragic @robvad10 spot on!  The arrogance astounds me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wandererstragic @robvad10 I think what we saw in the US shows the elitists don't have absolute power as they believed they are entitled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robvad10 Their opinion counts for no more than you and I. People now won't be dictated to, lectured by or spoken at by the likes of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our celebrity betters are lecturing again.. a tactic that worked so well in the US... right? Don't lecture me, you… https://t.co/31FO0Hiz87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interestingly with this clip, I think the support act may have been @Metallica https://t.co/BzE0IojKpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wandererstragic absolutely. I'm sick condescending winners lecturing me after they receive the award. Morrison was the worst, but not alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a refreshing choice for Australian of the Year. congratulations Alan Mackay-Sim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beggars belief.... This left me speechless https://t.co/SXzRWY2Cjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes hahahaha... well, yes!! I dont think I could argue that!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes Thats much more generous than how I would have labelled it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes the whole thing about not saying 'guys'. I mean seriously, thats 1984 stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes He was a dreadful and pathetic choice. Hopefully we'll never hear of this cretin again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westernsydneyu Hi.. allocate+ is supposed to be open for tutorial registration, but its not working. Do you know when it will be available?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewbrala @Don_Erebus @aussieblackwell @charonis @tgywyw86 I can imagine Snoke saying 'Darth Mary Sue... rise' really slowly !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgywyw86 @Don_Erebus @aussieblackwell @charonis @matthewbrala Bloody hell!!! File that next to Darth Jar Jar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Don_Erebus @aussieblackwell @charonis @tgywyw86 @matthewbrala Kylo to become Ben and Rey to become Darth Sugartits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Don_Erebus @aussieblackwell @charonis @tgywyw86 @matthewbrala umm.. yeah I'd say that is a safe bet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgywyw86 @aussieblackwell @charonis @Don_Erebus @matthewbrala I like it as its different. I didn't want another 'of the' title]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[charming.... https://t.co/q2afb42MS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussieblackwell @charonis @Don_Erebus @tgywyw86 @matthewbrala Gentlemen, what do you think of 'The Last Jedi' as the Ep 8 title?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could I have a refund please https://t.co/jAhcC6Mufe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgywyw86 @matthewbrala I"m sorry but words simply fail me right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewbrala Stop being cynical. It's not the time. Thoughts and prayers to all affected #RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG I cannot believe this has happened. What is going on in the world? https://t.co/l4ibrnMMcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spoonyman reverse those roles and the reaction would be very very different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irrelevant Triple M slams Trump. This from the radio station that deifies NRL players ad nauseum. Sharp as a marble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The same entitled cretin that preaches 'choose love', followed by a 'fuck you' chant and then threatens to blow up… https://t.co/DDkkIMUg0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These ladies are fairly safe https://t.co/0tPrkQQEf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StinsonHunter Hey Stinson. I read the transcript with Kyle. How revolting and exhausting. I dont know how you do it. Keep up the good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grubbavitch I'm against it. The best example is Martyn Bryant. Hates life and is completely miserable. No better punishment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up with a cramp in my leg. I'm low in salt I thought. Solution.. I had bacon and eggs for breakfast #forwardthinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes I rarely agree with you but I do here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nowwatching Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade. Best Indy film.. still incredible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pussaluss123 Another chattering class cretin. File with the likes of FitzSimons, Carlton etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkRudan @Prydzopolis Did wardrobe not have a jacket on standby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unbelievable free kick.. World class https://t.co/TDqvcG6gCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got this one! https://t.co/MG7S0or2sQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy T is really starting to carve up the @ALeague . A class above #MVCvBRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stickyjones1 yep and dovetailed nicely into ANH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stickyjones1 I wanted to do backflips in the last ten minutes... wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBozza From one westie to another, happy birthday big fella! Thanks for your tireless effort to promote our great game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Paul Wade would shut his pie hole. He's constant whinging about the game fuels the anti football mafia https://t.co/UfKKhxrlWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkIsJericho Just listened to your podcast with Lars Ulrich. Great interview, thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another elitist shithead https://t.co/SfEw5T9vAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes enjoy this. I still maintain a movie about the making of Whatever Happened to Baby Jane would be bri… https://t.co/r6YCqRTQqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @AaronGoodwin what do you guys think? https://t.co/41jWIW7jOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try and unsee this... go on.. I bet you can't! https://t.co/6VtoYN85vF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taaliah76 @BBCTwo I thought ISIS had nothing to do with Islam?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes I actually agree with you here. One can't say 'it offends muslims' in the same breath as 'ISIS has nothing to do with Islam']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can thank me later https://t.co/TojDKqtXWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelByrnes which one is Peter Talk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pussaluss123 lol good luck with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuntyNeville664 Dont worry. There poor sensibilities will be soothed as soon as we send them a large cheque. Always works]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>