<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Who cares about Calum, let's talk about cats.." #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen such a generic Best Bits? Beeyonka's will be the same. James C's will be a blank screen saying 'Footage not found' #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Calum done the jungle already? Next stop I'm A Celeb!Or Celeb Therapy or something with 'Celebrity' in the title, but not the show #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question: is James C a bit simple? That task really wasn't that funny #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am still baffled as 2why Calum thinks anyone would be happy to accept "constructive" criticism from him unless it's about hair plugs #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie was just one of many pointless HMs in this year's #CBB. Roll on the end already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One I found out the really nice looking bird was crazy, I decided to lower my standards and go for Bianca" oh, Jamie #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's enough now thanks, Jamie. Don't become a fixture on the reality tv circuit - you've neither the looks nor entertainment value! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim is being kinda Alan Partridge-y tonight, sitting everyone down for the 'oh, come on now' chats #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would she think he's an intellectual? HE'S AN ACTOR FOR GOODNESS SAKE #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Beejonka think they were going to stay in the house forever or something? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the last segment is a wet t-shirt contest featuring Coleen I think I'm gonna call it a night now #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be an ejector seat in the diary room that shoots them through the roof the 3rd time they say they're "100%" they wanna go #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BUSTED, MR NICE GUY #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get real: the nation doesn't give a fuck about James C.
He's practically a garden ornament #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Calum's so desperate to win and be seen as a nice guy. He's too bland, no matter how many tatts he gets #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum only "asserted" himself to one Jedward. Why does he keep  saying it was both? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People want 'Fun Bobby' Calum which would at least be a change from 'Nice Guy' Calum #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO THE FUCK WOULD TAKE LIFE ADVICE NOTES FROM CALUM BEST?! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum can only pretend to be a good man but he's really a two-faced, superficial, insincere TOOL 
#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YESSSSSSSSSS Revenge of the Jedwards! CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Calum, you talentless FORMER ladies man #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum really isn't as nice a guy as he thinks he is. He's a cowardly poser with a vanishing hairline #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't James C just admit it's cos he hates Bianca? Jamie's kids are way too you young to write anyway #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG Burn on whomever's tits jedward are talking about  #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was better last year with the US vs the UK theme. It's been a weak season #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Rylan just say "Summer Celeb House"?!!!!! #CBBBOTS #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James C is not a wise old guru. He's an actor, ffs! It doesn't get any less-wise than choosing that as your profession #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me there's gonna be an awkward scene where Jessica doesn't know which of her 3 BFs to run to off-stage 😅 #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica's voice really does not suit her face #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie is dressed like he escaped from Guy Richie's sex dungeon #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jedward turning the trolling all the way up to eleven #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From comedy to horror in one scene #JamieBiancaGrossness #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't love Jedward anymore than right now 😅 #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["BREAD FIGHT!!#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Bro would do just as well to build a granny flat out in the garden for Cosmo #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola should turn that beady little eye of hers inward and reflect on why it is Jedward wind her up so much? Just a thought #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is, as we in Ireland would say, a complete GEEBAG #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica has 3 kids?!!! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh! Calum! I almost forgot you existed there for the past 5 days #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Jr looks like a proper little mini Shane Richie. He could work behind the bar at the Queen Vic! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet Arsene Wenger is watch right now saying "That guy can really handle a potato! I'd better hire him as team juggler!" #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the house is like a prison, Nicola is definitely the Crazy Eye 😂 #OITNB #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WAHHHH! I haven't spoken to my dad for a few weeks! I'd better have a complete fucking meltdown #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is just going to be an episode of them crying messily every time a phone rings, I'm out #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She lost the plot with her wild hatred of the interlopers and her psychotic screaming at Kim. Won't miss Stacy at all #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Spencer managed to wind you up completely Coleen, so maybe he isn't entirely talentless? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't pull off talking about stabbing someone in the face while sporting a fluffy blond beard #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Nicola think it's some kind of special achievement to have squeezed out a few kids? 😅#cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a pissed-up nutter, that Nicola is #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to do the right thing, people who can vote: get Nicola and that Calum-wannabe Jamie out of there, stat! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone give Nicola a picture of her kids, or wind the clock forward to Wine Time cos she's doing my head in #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacy is fucking OBSESSED with the interlopers, isn't she? #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't take criticism from the likes of Calum Best and Bianca Gascoigne either 😅#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola has literally no self awareness whatsoever. Like, even by Big Brother standards #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why the fuck do they keep saying Nicola were their biggest supporter when it was clearly JEDWARD? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know the knife fighting scene from Rebel Without A Cause? That needs to be a task #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how everyone assumes James C is so wise and profound just because he's quiet. #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BB was right to follow all that excitement with the mind-numbingly bland pointlessness of Beejonka and Football Failure #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["WHAT PUNK ASS MAH-FUGGER PUT MY DIRTY WASHING ON THE FLOOR?!" - Lady Gremlin #CBB https://t.co/z72Y8C6mDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh-oh, Lady Gremlin is getting riled over very little. Looking for air-time? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Nicola is having a go at Stacy?! Was Jessica busy? 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does that spoonful of your own medicine taste, Nicola? Like a Hypocritini?#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola reckons she's "championed" Speidi more than the Jeds? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The look on Jamie's face 😂 more of that please #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am LOVING this task. They should just catapult whoever is left on that board into space and be done with it #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those Spidis don't deserve that. The snakes! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spidi? Didn't see that coming! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awwww...good on Apprentice voting for Jed#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the fuck voted to save Coleen?? She's been as animated as a bag of potatoes for the past two weeks #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT THE FUCK HAS STACY BEEN THROUGH? It's the CBB house, not fucking Syria  #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone throw a blanket over Lady Gremlin's cage, she's giving me a headache #CBBStacy #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...it's like trying to take down Bambi.." Jedward are indeed insightful  #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof of how much of a fucking SHEEP Jamie is: Calum did it it so I better do it! Fucking weasel #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I get it: Heidi is an uber committed mannequin challenge player! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm surprised they didn't have to use sock puppets to explain to Chloe what she did wrong #sodumb #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum speaks like Morty from Rick and Morty, dog #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old and quiet will keep you in, old and judgey will get you booted, James Cosmoan #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Callum must be exhausted from having to dodge all these drunken skanks every night #FirstWorldProblem #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body slammed by a drunk Geordie monster...how sexy! #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww, Kim ain't so bad. Insane, sure. But alright, like #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Jedward. Bet they were the type of kids who played with the box instead of the present at Xmastime 😅 Bless! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captain HA HA is a good name for Jamie because that's what all the football clubs say when they see his CV come through the door 😅 #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't anyone call Chloe out? She literally has the IQ of a pineapple #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola gets all righteously indignant when someone mentions her kids, but she drags them in front of the press at every film premier? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Nicola McClean for? Apart from populating CBB every few years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DID KIM JUST COMPARE HERSELF TO JESUS?! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Messing with their tea? What a bitch #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chloe's hero name should be Super Mess #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't he an actor? Why is he taking a stand over this? Is James a never-nude? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["NO DON'T TAKE MY THROWING WINE!" #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie is well 'ard: confronting a pensioner and Jedward in the same week. Heroic 😅 #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! Stroppy housemate having a tantrum and threatening to leave? Wheel out the Irish BB  #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola feels more able to confront Kim when she pretends she's a cyclops #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is insane. Kim is acting cray, but Nicola McClean is a total bitch. SO conflicted #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus, Apprentice contestants are less composed than they used to be! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think BB should bring in Jeremy Kyle, and him Jedward and Kim should set up a barbershop quartet that only sings the Crazy Frog song #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooooh, don't jump on James' bed! We have to keep it as a shrine!😅 Seriously, all these weeping over JAMES J?!  #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim is 6 years older than James Cosmo. A sassy septuagenarian she is, meanwhile he's practically an immobile mummy in that gaff #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim is the housemate those smug, overly-confident HMs deserve for their behaviour over the past fortnight #karma #CBB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>