<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay violence and stuff! Winning! https://t.co/qXFFWWmu5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanmdav it's a success story, Sean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needless and foolish. Better to not have the call at all. The Aussies are strong allies. https://t.co/A2rzmdkE1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives should beg every network to give this person as much air time as she wants. https://t.co/MBml8lLBBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirsalazar Gorsuch is exceptionally bright and qualified. I look forward to his confirmation. And please, lecture further on nuance 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsotopeRose this gif is so perfect. Points for self-awareness (even though I'm unconvinced it's real self-awareness). Don't change a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Johnny6speed your Trump impression needs work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirsalazar not a fan of DT but nah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelSGCC it's sarcasm, based on Berkeley situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm my own token gay, thank you very much. https://t.co/4SopMKKvXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinReevesA @emaliehill1 mean-spirited and unproductive. Not riot- or censor-worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Porkbelly_Pete @iAlwaysQuestion it sprung immediately to mind reading your anti-intellectual, ignorant drivel, actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I'm much more concerned with property rights than the alleged distress of pitiful victims who believe insults… https://t.co/E0H3mnw0TT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinReevesA I'm mocking you guys. Try to keep up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirsalazar mocking how you guys operate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonespruitt are you so stupid that you don't realize I'm mocking the Left? 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Porkbelly_Pete @iAlwaysQuestion that's because you're an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah, keep doing this &amp; you'll lose forever and ever...which would be amazing for 🇺🇸 -- never change! 👊 https://t.co/EpACTodtTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appsolutefit I know, it's amazing! He's like a farther left, less charming Pelosi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinReevesA this must be a homophobic mob. Only explanation. That's how you awful people operate. The violence is justified! Pathetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crowbro19 not convinced we'll make it. Rooting for it &amp; hope Lindsey gets well ASAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crowbro19 two key scorers are out + playing terribly. We deserved to lose badly tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinReevesA preventing him from speaking is mob fascism. Homophobia is motive you'd attribute if roles reversed. And I'm no fan of his.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow! https://t.co/fG2GwGItf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We SUPPORT lgbt rights &amp; DEMAND safe spaces, so we will BURN THINGS to prevent a gay man from speaking--because TOLERANCE! #Morons #Berkeley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm unaware of that element of his business model, though you may have "more information." Also, uh, I'm gay. Good… https://t.co/J1iPh7N03I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain totally. God, they're idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These morons are giving him exactly what he wants &amp; proving his point about them. https://t.co/8pPqvdrsJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, so very important. Keep at it, gang. https://t.co/qY1A2kEejo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Community" looks like a graffitied, overturned mobile light fixture lit on fire? You suck. I mean, he's awful, but… https://t.co/QDPRqKwlFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is wrong with you people? https://t.co/CgZ6S5kW7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strongly incentivizing continuous coverage is a key feature of House GOP plan. https://t.co/gGR2YBS2SC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn.

PM May blasts opponent's call to cancel Trump's UK invite: "He can lead a protest, I'm leading a country."
 
https://t.co/HIwnVvKnxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenanddane we found 2 awhile ago &amp; corrected them. Thx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Conservative British Prime Minister SLAMS left-wing opponent in heated exchange over Trump:

https://t.co/HIwnVvKnxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join @KennedyNation, @julieroginsky &amp; me in NJ tomorrow evening! Key topic + raising $ for good causes. Tix:… https://t.co/P8RikbG4O9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DomVacante of course not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericlopez1925 yes, the duly-elected president picked and installed two SCOTUS justices with virtually no resistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. *Two.* Let's keep this in mind over the next few years ---&gt; https://t.co/ztv3SjH8Lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Donnelly (D-IN) comes out for a vote on Gorsuch:

https://t.co/hjvBSHm6L9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JangoBear more relevant and more welcome than ever. Which drives you crazy. Jealousy is an ugly, left-wing thing. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmotionalDank lol, you're vapid jealously is sad to watch. Sad! Many people are saying I'm more influential than ever! Believe me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmotionalDank yes, alienating a large % of my audience was a brilliant career stroke. By demeaning motives, you're behaving like a Leftist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrainedinaVat because people are redefining it to mean things that it, well, never did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoMoreRomney Stop attacking Mr. Trump's position!  Very disloyal!  I'm reporting you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pchpolitical I mostly turned my attention to attacking HRC all fall. But couldn't bring myself to personally vote for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmotionalDank @warnerthuston this is probably the very dumbest attack.  I absolutely hurt my career/earnings last year bc of my stance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pchpolitical We'd have had a better nominee who'd have crushed her even more. But who cares now?  It's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DodgerNation31 I've been on Sean's show before and after the election. Stop with the fake news. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JangoBear I'm told you're a cuck. A big one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. "Never" meant I'd never *vote* for him--in the primary, or in the general. I didn't. He won. When he's right, I… https://t.co/oD6wvtEjG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warnerthuston a vote against Hillary is not a vote for Hillary. I don't accept that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart &amp; classy move. https://t.co/w27kFrfoov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warnerthuston I think that's an incorrect and uncharitable reading of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People seem to willfully misunderstand what "Never Trump" meant. https://t.co/89wc0maPO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For her epic election loss, Hillary blames...Obama:  

https://t.co/78TLAObEer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats just deliberately refused to show up to vote on controversial appointees, so majority Republicans did it… https://t.co/LJy2Aho2nm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durbin commits to a vote on Gorsuch. Looks like Dems may be reserving a filibuster for the next potential nominee.

https://t.co/PiuuHx2OnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The screaming counts as a key vote against Sessions!  Oh wait, it doesn't. Carry on. https://t.co/QR6vbK5N5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh, he backed Reid breaking the rules in '13...these guys want the hardball tactics to only go one way. R's right t… https://t.co/f4bgWd8bMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's fmr Solicitor General "strongly" supports SCOTUS nomination of "brilliant and thoughtful" Neil Gorsuch:

https://t.co/s9Q7jlaBDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazed they didn't flee the jurisdiction https://t.co/WDHwE1UxqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems often play hardball. Nice to see the GOP responding in-kind, burning them with their own escalations. Can't be… https://t.co/IINmGRbuhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecketAdams we published this a mere 7 hours before the super secret announcement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STOP THE PRESSES. https://t.co/i3rHgcUtx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mob is so exhausting https://t.co/HtY5bbwDZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They may begin with a point of agreement: #Obamacare has failed. Bernie will then argue for doubling down on the fa… https://t.co/iXhFbv0QQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems super organic and grassrootsy! https://t.co/k9iD3AIolG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sirlthr69 what a sad, small-minded tweet. Hope you find happiness one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maddow: Gorsuch is "mainstream."

https://t.co/Ga8FNPAbtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misterpillz many people are saying that I'm right. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldhickory49 @townhallcom nah. I support and oppose issue by issue. Delighted by this. Excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[::taps mic:: "WRONG" https://t.co/8y28sdAezX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a99barnsey @mkhammer Dems poisoned this well &amp; are the consistent aggressors. Reap the whirlwind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should the election winner be entitled to fill a vacant SCOTUS seat left vacant under the Biden Rule? 

Constitutio… https://t.co/467BQH4EKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, it qualifies as patronizing pity. And yes, your boring, angry schtick actually *is* rather sad to watch. https://t.co/r4pxyljsCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, honey. You're embarrassing yourself in front of everyone again. We discussed this. And for the last time, no, I… https://t.co/59juJA1gSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTW on @greggutfeld's show in Dec, I pledged to wear a red #MAGA cap on-air if Trump picked a young constitutionalist. Can anyone spare one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sasse, a frequent Trump critic, issues statement praising Gorsuch &amp; ridiculing Dems' immediate vilification of him. 

Pick unites the Right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch is 49 years old.  God willing, he'll sit on the bench for decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Justice Scalia was a lion of the law." - Gorsuch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[--&gt; Nearly 7 hours ago, @townhallcom first reported it would be Gorsuch, based on solid source &amp; other strands: 

https://t.co/0HbaJn041j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm THRILLED. Home run. 

#Gorsuch #SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous, outstanding, superlative choice, Mr. President.  Bravo.  #Gorsuch #SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox's John Roberts: My phone is buzzing with "Gorsuch, Gorsuch, Gorsuch..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyzing the coming SCOTUS confirmation battle w/ @ShannonBream earlier. Fun to be at the Court on such a big day!

https://t.co/jsIuu3XV7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From an ardent Trump critic on the Right: https://t.co/rt3VgEiY2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New hotness: IS TRUMP BLIND AND/OR LOSING ALL OF HIS FACULTIES?! https://t.co/ycpPvJE9Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBRadio2 @iptuttle this is incoherent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erickson also hearing that it's Gorsuch from inside sources... https://t.co/8yl4quVOmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh, I doubt this very much 

and big protests have ALWAYS worked out well for the Wisconsin Left! https://t.co/Mv6LJC8kIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart ahh, now I've shown how 2 can play at your lazy non-responsive/ad hominem game, dodger. But pro tip: Spell check is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artxmaverick dumb tweet -- you are so insecure. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart wow, calling Gen. Mattis "blind." Very unpatriotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart not according to Gen. Mattis &amp; Trump's own backtracking.  You're deeper in the tank for them than they themselves are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarrySchweikart they already reversed some of it -- so much for perfectly crafted.  And obviously not rolled out well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taniel huh...hope it's resolved justly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Sen. Blumenthal: I fought in Vietnam.  

Dude says a lot of things. https://t.co/2gJL92LcF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taniel @chrislhayes on what grounds?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>