<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kathy Whitworth Fade - clear up a common misconception https://t.co/FDI4e5eUjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Democrats Organizing Criminal Coup Against Trump » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/l2ubi87Kjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Clinton Moles Discovered in White House » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/lKd0u9Rt4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Miller: Trump Has 'Better Sense of the Pulse of the People' Than Any President Since Andrew Jackson https://t.co/oQz4bWSGVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virgil: Minutes of the Deep State Executive Committee on the Permanent Campaign Against Trump https://t.co/Nl5wiHg3ZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/ztqDe2srgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This One Thing Secretary Mattis Does Separates Him from the Rest of Washington's Powerful https://t.co/NUxXwRpf12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you want to cut my head off ... https://t.co/axvRTWPD4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for McCain to be deported from congress ... https://t.co/EwruGdODEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Just Gave All Christians the Gift of a LIFETIME! No President Has EVER Done Anything Like This!! * LIBERTY... https://t.co/xdsGSpGoWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Exposed For Allowing Muslim Brotherhood To Infiltrate Our Gov’t with a Plan To Destroy America https://t.co/yrmqdis0Oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They may kiss our grits and deport themselves ... https://t.co/UNFz1KJUko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to herd cattle ... https://t.co/zCQ7lSbp6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pope is Muslim and not Christian ... a sycophant of sycophants https://t.co/RF0xIiFL3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praise the LORD ... https://t.co/YzEiAHJW6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Senate Finally Drops the Hammer, Passes Vote to OVERTURN... https://t.co/nvHMUJ5Nwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeopathy officially recognized by Swiss government as legitimate medicine to coexist with conventional medicine https://t.co/JsPspmlOCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/OGBfQLLsv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just RUINED Obama’s Vacation – Open Massive INVESTIGATION into White House CRIME https://t.co/KYbj9sjOI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning: ICE 'Most Wanted Fugitive' Captured...And It's Just The Beginning https://t.co/Bvfpq5mFlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashback: Jerry Brown, Biden and other Dems refused to accept Vietnamese refugees https://t.co/rfLAosZy86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distorting the Holocaust https://t.co/dWRlPaUuR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosa Brooks for prison says ... https://t.co/B98muFx1fS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paralysed ‘robocop’ presented with Israeli-invented suit allowing her to walk again https://t.co/nuisFBuFTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS catches mother and children trying to flee: what happened next is so HORRIFIC we can’t show you https://t.co/Az77IJ16LE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH – Border Patrol Agent Comes Forward, Exposes Terrifying Truth We ALL Need to Hear https://t.co/asn6i8GhkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Who Saved 669 Children During The Holocaust Has No Idea They’re Around Him, Watch His Reaction https://t.co/W61l3xoCxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! REFUGEES EXPOSED: Here's the cold hard truth the media won't tell you…“If Saudi Arabia is refusing to accept... https://t.co/rZAXyX5r1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/5VWfrZKBtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Nap: Gorsuch Brings 'Scalia-Like Dose of Skepticism About Gov't' https://t.co/EVooWzHV6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[98-Year-Old Grandma Interrupts A Country Singer’s Performance. Nobody Expected This! https://t.co/a3QFGnc2zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Year-Old Boy Permanently Disabled from Chicken Pox Vaccine Wins His Case in Vaccine Court https://t.co/Z8QJjXIpB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Donald Trump's entire Supreme Court announcement https://t.co/EmEQat9Nnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Jeff Sessions Just Got the BEST News of His Life and NO ONE Deserves This More! * LIBERTY WRITERS NEWS https://t.co/pCt21mp0v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Trump Just Ordered Gowdy And Chaffetz Back On Clinton Case To “Go After Everything” https://t.co/h97ezSNxbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like a coffee, no Starbucks, please ... https://t.co/n14Cumw2v8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems Boycott Trump Cabinet Vote, GOP Says ENOUGH IS ENOUGH, Makes Epic Move... https://t.co/pYwdiRmeGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Questions For Muslims » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/YCCGlsxSxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi Caught On Hot Mic: ‘Tell Them You’re A Muslim’ [VIDEO] » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for... https://t.co/7OGUfJVSx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump names Ronald Vitiello to head Border Patrol » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/vxvIoRApZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-American Democrats threaten ... again ... https://t.co/IK5zuj7Sis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathetic Liberals are angry .. https://t.co/9dcx5AnTqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death to the rapist ... wrong is wrong ... https://t.co/j121ArT9U3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Trump signs executive order banning ALL federal money to sanctuary cities https://t.co/LusAmuplwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thank you all for being my friend. God bless and keep you~Amen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUMP WAS RIGHT! Look What Was Discovered About 20 Suspected Terrorists https://t.co/UumLgG8PbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mad Dog' Mattis Suddenly Walks Out of Major DC Banquet &amp; Doesn't Return, We Now Know Why... https://t.co/0LgSx2yanM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Can't Take It Anymore, Puts John McCain In His Place Once and For All... "World War III" https://t.co/BtgIFN78CR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How sad and wrong ! https://t.co/ZMg629WkTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trey Gowdy Has Quite Possibly the BEST Response to Trump's New "Muslim Ban" https://t.co/VbHmxIN2Cb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Considers Becoming Official Sanctuary State » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/9angHAFRpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Declares Globalist Soros As “National Security Threat”…Using Obama’s 2014 Executive Order https://t.co/twZtkqxi5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Bans All Lobbyists, Delivers In Spades » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/ohHs6BvNiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Navy SEAL Dies Under Trump, But Donald Does Something For Family That Speaks Volumes https://t.co/yhvELt7cYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth About Oprah Winfrey » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/0DpCAOL5JJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Defends Trump's Firing of Acting Attorney General » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/V54gAOGCka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider: Le Pen May Copy Trump’s Immigration Ban If Elected » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/4YimtViQxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Appoints Acting Director of Immigration and Customs Enforcement » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on... https://t.co/u3TtWDnt2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Signals The Left's Awakening https://t.co/BxKUUENUei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Senator: No Immigration Screening, More Gun Control » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/g1FghdYQRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: 'Dozens' of Terrorists May Be in US as Refugees https://t.co/nl4DdubGHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan Absolutely REFUSES To Let In Syrian ‘Refugees’, says it must look after its own citizens FIRST - Freedom's... https://t.co/sd4SrLw65O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STARBUCKS CEO: We're going to hire 10,000 refugees https://t.co/mtLQSk37Lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sluts R Us bound for hell ... https://t.co/pD9u3sD5B1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAIR  members should be deported ... https://t.co/Kobgke8J7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Trump Just RUINED Obama's Vacation By Announcing Plan To INVESTIGATE Him For White House Scam -... https://t.co/ClB61Tpxfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Not Stop Sharing This Until Every Person Who Cares About Women Sees This https://t.co/McG8e6KeF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Mad Dog" General Just Ruffled Pentagon Feathers With First Major Decision as SecDef https://t.co/6dbYpcBVjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Trump’s DHS Responds To Judge Blocking Travel Ban, And It’s BRUTAL https://t.co/QrUSmtAh3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eyes and words of evil Globalist ... https://t.co/aK392NrKT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/lJSzB532kB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans Plan Vote to Kill Obama's Social Security Gun Ban - Breitbart https://t.co/R9fFSg5U7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Raise Nearly $24,000 For Muslim Immigrant-Owned Limo Torched by Left-Wing Protesters - Breitbart https://t.co/B68bLR2R31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro Trump Democrat Turns On Obama's Policy Of Arming ISIS https://t.co/3IXvvlplpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farage: Trump Elected to Protect America From ISIS » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/NVsYvzBoSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soros and associates for prison ... https://t.co/EntXfA9p6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ICE Agent Refused Obama’s HUSH MONEY &amp; Exposed The Depths OF Obama &amp; Hillary’s TREASON! https://t.co/SBzwggybPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Donald Trump Just Released Horrifying Video To Warn Americans, Claims He “Had To Do It” https://t.co/XkneMDRRgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: U.S. Border Patrol Makes Massive Announcement About Trump's Wall https://t.co/KnJEMUtKcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moments Before Trump's Expected Ban, CAIR Director Issues Staggering Announcement... https://t.co/0U1dbJWxak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delta Force Just Met ISIS in Hand-to-Hand Combat for the 1st Time..With Dramatic Results https://t.co/QAW3u8Sow4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Facebook, Google Secretly Teaming with David Brock's Media Matters over Fake News - Breitbart https://t.co/0LXPhJWJkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon Torches New York Times: 'You Have No Power' - Breitbart https://t.co/vMiVtuu3V9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence First Vice President to Address March for Life https://t.co/K2vMr2HxMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE -- Roger Stone’s ‘The Making of the President 2016’: How Donald Trump Rode the Wave of Alternate Media... https://t.co/DWuYObqbh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WIKILEAKS Exposes WHO ORDERED HILLARY To LEAVE BEHIND The 4 MEN In BENGHAZI! THIS IS TREASON! https://t.co/2NhJutvczU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump DID THE IMPOSSIBLE! He Got $24 Billion BACK That Got Sent In Mexico That Will Cover THE COST OF THE WALL! https://t.co/xiOEkwboXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Obama” Republicans No Longer Have Anywhere To Hide, Trump Cuts Their Pay After Treasonous Act https://t.co/7O793nmk4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's March Speaker Kidnapped, Raped &amp; Tortured Gay Man to Death » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for... https://t.co/BJkQDEIcsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Steve King Files Federal Pro-Life Heartbeat Bill: 'If a Heartbeat Is Detected, the Baby Is Protected' -... https://t.co/MCfZJOoVWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shadow Gov't Operative and Underwear Bomber Coverup Artist Resigns From State Department » Alex Jones' Infowars:... https://t.co/8aSB7Fd4yq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: CHARLES KRAUTHAMMER Calls For The ARREST Of OBAMA https://t.co/aCZPZpQwdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli Soldiers Report Divine Intervention in Battle With ISIS https://t.co/GhGlRJJdvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right After She Threatened to Get Trump KILLED, Secret Service Agent Got The WORST News of Her Life! https://t.co/552l05lAGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portland Rioters Showed Up As Promised After Chief Refuses To Resign, PD Shows Up And Kicks Ass https://t.co/rK52X3as6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OFFICIAL: Dr. Ben Carson Confirmed As HUD Secretary https://t.co/rntPpk2Y7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Amish Don’t Vaccinate, Rarely Get Autism, Cancer Or Heart Disease https://t.co/lOhEwqgDPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST IN: U.N. Demands Trump Mind His Place…He Responds By IMMEDIATELY Removing America https://t.co/NDK2mXxu3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio Station Bans Madonna After Comments on Blowing Up White House » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for... https://t.co/OXFTy1bCkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress Announces Legislative Action Guaranteed To Put A Smile On Every Gun Owners' Face https://t.co/5QqGMTW3D5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>