<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent read: "What you end up understanding from even the sweetest [Trump supporters] still might chill you to t… https://t.co/ysAgcms7Wh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A giant cave to Big Oil, as @SenatorCardin &amp; @dicklugar, the bipartisan sponsors of the SEC rule, explain here:… https://t.co/LUMaRZWuAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If Trump wants to take on Washington lobbyists, he’s going to need more than a simple executive order." https://t.co/UgErUgcFqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is big money in politics a fundamental part of our electoral system, or can limits sometimes be justified?" https://t.co/4KeJgQaGsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people are saying Gorsuch's views on money in politics are out of touch w/ American values &amp; the Constitution. https://t.co/dMLT1Xbahd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repdinatitus Voters are with you on campaign finance. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Voters are with you on money in politics and the court. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoKhannaUSA Voters are with you on money in politics and the Court. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMcGovern Voters are with you on campaign finance. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell Voters agree on campaign finance. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is too much at stake – from women’s choice to voting rights and campaign finance reform." https://t.co/7p4y0fJB3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reasons to oppose Gorsuch: "I do not agree that corporations have a right to speak on our elections." https://t.co/nq7UAvedeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad and true. https://t.co/UU5wfMwYs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters have their backs for opposing Gorsuch. 77% say Senate should reject if nominee won't #FightBigMoney.… https://t.co/2rMFQPtFde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 45% Republicans disagreed the country should "welcome Christian refugees, but not Muslim ones." https://t.co/N5rj0iKNfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annalecta @davelevinthal Right result but his explanation is troubling. Strict scrutiny for contribution limits. https://t.co/liRg26nD0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@expagan @RoKhannaUSA @matthewstoller Details on Gorsuch's views on money in politics. https://t.co/liRg26nD0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of Congress are right. Gorsuch would help the wealthy continue to wield outsize power in our elections.… https://t.co/4ChWQS1v7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch threatens "the rights of ordinary citizens to have their voices heard in elections rather than being drowne… https://t.co/jfSxPQhprV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't need another justice who spends his time looking out for those with money and influence." https://t.co/VaxNLv3UzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Demos_Org is opposing Gorsuch for his dangerous position on money in politics. https://t.co/QVVVY6PMFo https://t.co/n1IuXcSK49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True story. https://t.co/wg1VyMKYhf https://t.co/Bf0L6awJKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Gorsuch raises significant concerns about the #SupremeCourt giving big donors even more power. https://t.co/liRg26nD0U #FightBigMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much at stake tonight. From gerrymandering to voting rights &amp; big money in elections, Trump's pick will determin… https://t.co/TBq7h6O3yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If confirmed, it'll soon be what Gorsuch or Hardiman got wrong in their money in politics decisions. https://t.co/e3HwCRN3zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NormEisen But appears open to applying strict scrutiny to campaign contribution limits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The glaring flaw: They don't close a loophole that allows big dollars to flow to lawmakers without disclosure." https://t.co/hOnDA7mtVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch is not open to limiting big money. Quite the opposite. He's open to eliminating contribution limits. https://t.co/KpMJJZAW9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's going to be a big crowd at the Supreme Court tonight after what is sure to be a terrible nominee.… https://t.co/IaykhlfIFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're eager for a radical judge to break with precedent to strike down campaign finance disclosure &amp; contribution… https://t.co/6LhQd6G7i5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New @HattawayComm poll on brink of SCOTUS pick: GOP voters want nominee open to limiting big money in politics.… https://t.co/dgfMZuYwKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jnystrange Not surprised. You can call Sen. Rounds on this. https://t.co/2vm1HTdzYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Commander in Reality TV. https://t.co/0QQkqMOdwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the SCOTUS pick tonight, @POTUS is going to fail his many voters who thought he'd #FightBigMoney in politics.… https://t.co/8o2WCYAMOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jnystrange Awesome. There is a rally at the state house tomorrow during the vote. https://t.co/WS0QBRGtQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike Obama's outside group, Trump's will not disclose its donors. https://t.co/2ZfG92BbMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A voter asked @RoyBlunt's office about the donations he received from Betsy DeVos. His office hung up on the voter. https://t.co/I45aZJpi5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenateDems should rethink this plan. https://t.co/DvegG7nqAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamliptak and campaign contribution limits. Gorsuch concurrence in Riddle v. Hickenlooper indicates desire for strict scrutiny on limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessBravin @brkend Both would strike down common-sense protections against big money, breaking Trump's promise to curb donor power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardjwolf Gorsuch wants strict scrutiny for campaign contribution limits. His nomination = antithetical to Trump's promise to curb big $]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch wants to apply strict scrutiny to contribution limits which would destroy last remaining protections agains… https://t.co/9sRYxkNd0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaileyMcC Screenshot is a @RepresentDotUs press release. The events are listed in the legislative calendar here: https://t.co/4qBh23cgUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even after Trump's lobbying ban the swamp is still quite full. https://t.co/EfFeKv5kB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all lawmakers in South Dakota are disregarding the will of voters. Thank you @SenStaceNelson.
#RespectOurVote… https://t.co/3qQzb6uOrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD voters: Don't repeal our ethics law.
A SD state senator: No. If you don't like it, "move to Hawaii."
https://t.co/EumgdBExGT #sdleg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is more necessary than ever to embrace movements to get big money out of politics [and] defend voting rights." https://t.co/1CYT1Gbzrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From this day forward, it's going to be only The Trump Organization first." https://t.co/XoYymTO1WB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SD lawmakers were in the hot seat at town halls this weekend for gutting the voter-approved ethics law. https://t.co/rbxwfzwJgm #sdleg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable. The same day the #SDLeg plans to gut rules curbing lobbyist power, lobbyists are throwing a bunch of… https://t.co/VxNnFBBD41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, he wants to break his promise to curb the power of big donors 2 days earlier than planned.… https://t.co/DMEzeIWBXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love, not hate. That's what makes America great." #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/DIiQz9dH59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What #spicerlies is this crowd size out front of the White House going to prompt today? https://t.co/qTQ0OGGuBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, hey! No fear, refugees are welcome here. #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/hw4wiw9PHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. Big money in politics gives us unqualified Cabinet picks like DeVos. 
#DumpDevos and #FightBigMoney https://t.co/QChzjeg3tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @SenateDems, this is where your base is at on DeVos. #DumpDevos https://t.co/Zbcc8kqZyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This minor action to address the power of lobbyists is pretty insignificant in the context of everything else. https://t.co/UQRtjrUzVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeRemember the victims of the Holocaust and we will remember the victims of Trump's Muslim ban. #RefugeesWelcome… https://t.co/YLEMsHL6Lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yes I'm Islamophobic, but my business always comes first," the president declared as official US policy. https://t.co/jcl33ooJK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Don McGahn selecting the SCOTUS nominee, @potus will break his promise to curb power of wealthy &amp; privileged.… https://t.co/0mN5sKFDnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blunt and true. "The president is peddling conspiracy theories that undermine our democracy for political gain." https://t.co/RMfCoXXVUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hurricaneross Thanks. Glad to hear it's helpful. A few events around the state today and tomorrow. https://t.co/4rhUeC1cBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fight to protect the ethics law in South Dakota is far from over. Find an event near you.… https://t.co/IlBI0Rd3en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A legislator who wants to gut the ethics law in South Dakota has a "Lobbyists Welcome" sign on his desk.… https://t.co/nD57XjSxyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he know it doesn't actually involve a real nuke? https://t.co/RIY0rJeVNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We want to live safe! We want to live free! We don't want no registry!"
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/ZnEaUd8h8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC stands with refugees, immigrants and our Muslim brothers and sisters. #NoBanNoWall
#RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/uLVhDIVhAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news! But don't let the pressure up. They're still going to try to gut the ethics law next week.

Keep callin… https://t.co/QBfNMTBOgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold feet or are Sen. @BlakeCurd and company just hoping all the negativity publicity will have blown over by then?… https://t.co/OnB9yaMyaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @realDonaldTrump appoints a judge who believes big donors have a right to drown out the voters' voices, he'll br… https://t.co/L5wMXItP3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next justice could quickly rule on issue of money in politics with GOP Louisiana v. FEC possibly before Court.… https://t.co/SuyxCcDhM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see why a majority of voters supported these and why the entire @sdgop is moving so quickly to get rid of t… https://t.co/kdH1lo0cmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the laws that are causing Sen @BlakeCurd &amp; his colleagues to declare an "emergency" in South Dakota.… https://t.co/6sLoM8zwO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, @AndyPuzder's hearing just got delayed for a 3rd time because his ethics paperwork still isn't done.… https://t.co/fCkHVzc8Nd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all his blustering about special interest influence, @POTUS is about to give them a big gift w/ his SCOTUS pick… https://t.co/k3jPtrqtkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a POTUS who rails against the US foreign policy establishment &amp; a SOS w/ no gov't experience, "the vacancies a… https://t.co/IgKKS1bixz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. The chairman of the House Oversight Committee will maybe, just maybe, actually provide some oversight. https://t.co/UocXwQ1kqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though to be fair we could've used @alt_fec during the Obama years too. https://t.co/rHdEpSaqqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Gotta #resist to #fightbigmoney. https://t.co/jiCGMlazPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyDoty That doesn't have anything to do with online voter registration though. Could happen to your state now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This creates the appearance of cashing in on the presidency &amp; selling direct personal access to the president," sa… https://t.co/OWvAkdZR45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sure you can have a meeting in the White House, but not before paying your $200k Mar-a-Lago membership." https://t.co/gUpLAa4X8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxpayers supplement the wages of Puzder's workers. He uses the savings for political donations to further cut work… https://t.co/GRcTWjMvb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The democratic system is weakening because citizens believe that its key institutions are not working for them." https://t.co/r919iKfS5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good stuff. #DCIsReal https://t.co/7EM8CRtlJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffPender Wanted to make sure you knew Doty's supposed fears of hacking are baseless. 38 states &amp; DC have OVR. https://t.co/Auuv1Z0bdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're kidding us right, @SallyDoty? 38 states and DC have online voter registration. https://t.co/mV5VLK9JQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never buy the spin that public financing of elections is so-called incumbent protection. https://t.co/MTPOOwPey2… https://t.co/2D7RYA30Mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The appearance is terrible to South Dakotans and terrible to the nation,"said @SenStaceNelson (R). I'd say so.… https://t.co/U4kCmUu9A0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'll fit right in with the rest of the Cabinet. https://t.co/44uot7twFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apearson15 @therealezway I got that and agree. Just double checking that I had that right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealezway @apearson15 It's not actually fraud to be registered multiple times is it? You'd actually have to vote in 2 jurisdictions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burchfield's experience leading Crossroads doesn't "inspire confidence in his ability to police ethical standards."… https://t.co/lD9E2kkuTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This hire makes sense for a company and president with no ethics. https://t.co/mEO28lWrBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's spelled "big league." https://t.co/O06mZZtks6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters will/should judge the nominee on whether they'll support all Americans' rights to be heard over big donors.… https://t.co/LKlH8U70Tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems: We shouldn't allow laws that enrich Trump's businesses. 
@jasoninthehouse: That's "cute" and inappropriate. https://t.co/6EMm5AFHqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The headline says it all: The #SdLeg votes to cast aside government ethics. https://t.co/48tsykuLgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“And so voter fraud became an excuse for making it harder to register and to vote.” Plain and simple. https://t.co/10Z3sLuhr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except the border wall is mostly just popular with his base which will hear about it regardless of the voting tweet… https://t.co/yUG51s8BlY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>