<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["When leaders undertake evidence-informed inquiry, and use it to work collaboratively towards change and improvemen… https://t.co/GGJLh5D7sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipped learning provides an avenue to ask the “why” questions  @kchalls @unenlightened https://t.co/BuabADuSaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shark tank can be used as a good shell for a project using the @makeymakey https://t.co/AKmaqSDFzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great authentic entry event https://t.co/KzWrsHvnfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great insights into managing #PBL groups.@mrpate @BridgetMazzella @BlythRenee I like the group check in rubric… https://t.co/F31wDulDAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post: Top ‘five’ considerations when starting your PBL journey. https://t.co/STAYlhc3D7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We need a fair and robust means of assessment" - so true https://t.co/3KoX2sBhYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post: Top ‘five’ considerations when starting your PBL journey. https://t.co/bVOj7504ok @mrpate @gregmiller68 @kchalls @angemhay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck. You guys will be great. https://t.co/3s5MMDrYzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamenated card with magnetic tape on the back. Can move it all over the board. https://t.co/AzzTM3kuJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great addition from Google to support students working groups @mrpate @nicvidot https://t.co/UAlPVnSMOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the idea of the motivation wheel. https://t.co/oHiUzjEIZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizMcQuadeJones leading instructional leaders through the need to know protocol https://t.co/ersAtML1aR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulstenning leading teachers through the fundamental theorem of arithmetic. Great start to Monday morning! https://t.co/a0pUTlGTwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foster a culture of redrafting. Redrafting also makes students aware of how far they've come in their learning… https://t.co/0F2cEVgqA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the idea of rose (Positive) - bud (Potential) - thorn (Needs work) critique @kchalls https://t.co/yMKNMWIjfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He understood our school context and realised that it wasn’t a one size fits all" - so true https://t.co/e88y0mlntK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to learn, relearn &amp; unlearn - the role of the 21st century teacher leader - https://t.co/6fvVTCG8Q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something to always consider when you start any #PBL project https://t.co/8qG1GqvRAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the idea of a "project slice". Great example of learn by doing! https://t.co/gRlvemrvtK @kchalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great reflection questions to ensure that you have fidelity to your PBL projects https://t.co/teSHP4kjrN #PBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have this on repeat over the next couple of months https://t.co/rtipts5CJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PBL is intentionally teaching students what it means to learn cooperatively, think critically, how to work in teams https://t.co/ffHdmPTsbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hattie Effect Size 2016 Update https://t.co/7I3JL0FfCc via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Edu leadership, is a more contentious, complex &amp; dynamic phenomenon than previously thought"… https://t.co/zjuKZKBd4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clear and succinct message on why use #pbl https://t.co/vDy3jcg9qY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data is not the answer but only the start of the questions. Very interesting study by Jenkins on enthusiasm via sch… https://t.co/F5i0TFPJSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to look beyond the basic indicators of academic success to redesign measures such as the ATAR #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critical skills needed for students to not just participate in the economy, but to change it! #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great quote from a fellow scholar @kchalls @Dan_Lynch1 https://t.co/TiX060k1Hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If our students see the primary role of education to support the economy, then we have failed them! #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My rule for 2017 - It's not about the quantity of our actions, but the quality of our relationships #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bishop Vincent - leaders must bridge the gap between the ideal and real #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some common themes with connecting the parents within our community in transforming schools #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transforming schools is learning from each other and with each other #CEDP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CEDP2017 connecting every student, every day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Trends in PBL - Internships, Design thinking, GBL, maker spaces and Agency @kchalls https://t.co/AS23rXHxyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience, perseverance, and problem solving the art of teaching! https://t.co/pFnXVIQz0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quick checklist for keeping it real in PBL https://t.co/w2wTGUZjAI https://t.co/F3AMLZnIJ8 @kchalls @mrpate @nicvidot @unenlightened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choice, creation and audience are the keys. https://t.co/KPBFmXNAPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parent engagement is considered the most important topic that gets the least emphasis on improving learning https://t.co/TQZnCXn86a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PBL is a major shift and schools processes have to be embedded in the school culture to support the work of teachers https://t.co/tRp4oYklgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When students are at the center, they are learning about what truly engages and challenges them https://t.co/Kf7zccHs1a @kchalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[authentic learning experiences that are based on student interests and designed to challenge and engage students in real environments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @tajpmahal very impressive stuff from someone so young. Congrats https://t.co/rqAhZ8KUMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The jobs of the future will demand digital literacy skills. Do your students actually have them? - https://t.co/pNhEXMCoum @kchalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PBL Rule 1 - Don’t delay launching until your project is perfect. A project is never finished! https://t.co/J1bFHGLxJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers provide regular and constructive feedback! So true. https://t.co/hqYbjX7ebe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true! https://t.co/yS5MBb7Qpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The growth of technology means that schools must rethink what they do to produce connected, global-ready graduates https://t.co/mIWM3lEjeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the role of PBL in the STEM revolution?
https://t.co/520imLn62O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregmiller68 @ConversationEDU Definitely challenging. But spell check sometimes spells the wrong words correctly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregmiller68 Not many systems in the world would be allowed to continue if they only had a 1 in 3 success rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Science, medicine and maths tend to be particularly suited to virtual environments." - need teachers to realise th… https://t.co/HHvgafnDip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great results for yr12 2016 @ParraMarist showing academic results can be achieved with contemporary learning framew… https://t.co/Lx8tLKKYXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If parents don't instil respect for the importance of learning, it's an uphill battle for teachers https://t.co/twO72sJIr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very interesting read that does explain a few things @kchalls https://t.co/YD1AL65qzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great story on the use of contemporary pedagogy to improve student learning https://t.co/iCijMZXbIO via @gregwhitby @christineahowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great example of promotion of girls in STEM #AAEE16 https://t.co/wlukBm2HWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve seen firsthand how ineffective and even dangerous it can be when leaders make decisions alone @BillGates  https://t.co/nqRypqA0iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true statements about the integration of professional learning &amp; professional development in teacher quality https://t.co/j8nrRCGG5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wide-scale improvement in Australian schools depends on promoting evidence-based teaching practices https://t.co/bQsWUF6ywo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great example of inducting students into the process rather than a focus on product https://t.co/qp0CtLkkHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great affirmation for the tools and techniques used by @newtechnetwork  https://t.co/Y7N6qm068V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for our presentation at #AAEE16 @kchalls https://t.co/kSLSgCqQmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School leaders who make T/Learning &amp; PD of teachers the prime focus, have the most effect on student learning https://t.co/LTyoPLjfSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The more I learn, the more I realize how much I don’t know.” https://t.co/fflnyiQAxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great idea for a #STEM project? https://t.co/iLRlMim82t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great model of student learning. The characteristics of students + context + approaches to learning = direct impact… https://t.co/I1rAIVhMf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good definitions of #PBL from WSU. I like your hybrid flip approach. https://t.co/qgbFWTDUrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Factor analysis of effective learning environments using Biggs survey that is reproducible. #AAEE16 https://t.co/Jg6S8p7tEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AAEE16 excited to hear this presentation https://t.co/ivRGKjCZzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting fact - students want engineering to challenge them, but it should not be difficult! #aaee16 https://t.co/W6QyOS6UFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender differences in streams of engineering. Very interesting study. #AAEE16 https://t.co/6rVy1eTV1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responsibility in educators to develop talent. In both a secondary and tertiary context. We are both part of the journey #AAEE16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take to work in a complex globalised world? Great question! #AAEE16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 1 of #AAEE16 looking forward to learning more about engineering education for the 21st century https://t.co/1V3xXepvPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the aaee2016 conference. Glad they have used my professional name. https://t.co/wD6opQfs8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Westmead prosthetic lab. Some great ideas for#stem https://t.co/TOuD7FbADK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also a good opportunity for students to construct this element @MsDiMaria @ThinkGlobalPBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newtechguy presenting on adaptive leadership to school leaders #tgPBLaus16 @kchalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely guilty of the first pitfall #tgpblaus16 @kchalls https://t.co/NAl2OT2WCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using @Mr_Kevin_Gant as an entry event by @newtechguy at PBL workshop @kchalls https://t.co/uGevpcq7jY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PBL staff workshop driving question @kchalls https://t.co/RVUA4XmsVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christineahowe Discussing smart goals for 2017 with Principals https://t.co/xkc3wXgk2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens in the classroom when you flip it? Application! https://t.co/Wa5ook3AJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larraine gudgeon receiving appreciation for contribution to Marist education - well done @kchalls @jdsully01… https://t.co/Xq1SepuGw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kchalls what a great idea! https://t.co/ZmpUtHlImb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @misterwootube much deserved accolades https://t.co/yaL58zUyUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kchalls @bbscanlon hopefully informational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important listen to where you have come from, in order to move forward @bbscanlon @kchalls https://t.co/XwySzp2qWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you build the learning culture? @bbscanlon @kchalls https://t.co/Oq3ZUsHiNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbscanlon unpacking the 5 domains of leadership with leaders of learning @ParraMarist @kchalls https://t.co/Bshp6ulEKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole school theories of action @kchalls #nswedu16 https://t.co/qEkIvs0n0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kchalls it's a staircase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kchalls learning hubs maybe a new landscape for PLTs https://t.co/wyIFJzhdlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 support staff? That is a small army https://t.co/JuwZz53EdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity to convey the narrative of the PBL journey for @ParraMarist at #nswedu16 https://t.co/BPBRONz2L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kchalls I love understanding this information now https://t.co/POZZJSZ0ZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is slow unless there is a framework for professional conversations #nswedu16 @kchalls https://t.co/DXvnUqAIij]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>