<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mightily Impressed by Michelle O'Neill. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give it up Sean. You're making yourself look foolish. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shockingly bad interviewing by Sean O'Rourke. Michelle O'Neill well able to put him in his place. #todaysor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the Fine Gael Kate O'Connell who appointed her sister as her assistant on €49,000pa 3 weeks after being elected? #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#medicationnation This is me getting Solpadeine. https://t.co/pQg06Udh6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenClouds4 @Dizzydub1 Probably sent you on that career path! Is there nothing it can't do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostjimmy Saturday bath and a huge spoon of Magnesia after. Good times!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenClouds4 @Dizzydub1 It never did me any harm though...*twitches violently*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenClouds4 @Dizzydub1 Straight through ya it went!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dizzydub1 I went to school smelling of Milk of Magnesia and nit powder!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was force fed spoons of Milk of Magnesia as a child. Oh the chalky Humanity!  #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all hopped up on goofballs. It's the weather and the government n' all. #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itchybollix Future captains of industry..and perverted politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itchybollix Yeah, but could they put an IKEA flat pack together..I fucking doubt it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody hired Van to injure Hobbs' arm. A case of Hurts Van Rental...*gets coat and leaves* #UniversityChallenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hobbs is using the old "answers written on the cast" ploy.  #UniversityChallenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm stocking up on solpadeines before this airs tonight. #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Silver Dream Racer was on..I would probably watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRHgearoid Well Earned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Pints Time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redliz Yes, it's not an easy watch. This week is even grimmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mesmerising stuff from Emily Watson. #AppleTreeYard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick McGoohan Columbo starting on ITV now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww look at Brendan O'Connor shinner bashing again in the Sindo. Maybe someday you could write something worth reading, Brendan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xerophyte12345 @realDonaldTrump Image of him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PhilEStine He deserves everything he gets! The man's an unstable lunatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Timeline is an endless stream of anti-Trump sentiment. Fabulous. I'm in the right place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Robbo They wouldn't last long over here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of my brain on the 5-15. #SkyArts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A million accumulator dockets thrown at the television. #Thistlecrack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redliz The whole thing is Shambolic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This main presenter on ITV Racing is painful. Like watching an eel on a hot skillet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's spouting rubbish. How are people to afford huge rents when they're pensioners.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzie_grime We all do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzie_grime Sometimes they want you to hear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ger_Stapleton The ads were on during A Fistful of Dynamite!..back there now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like that boring couple in the pub. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh for fucks sakes.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacebeak I'd say a night out on the town with him would be great. Such a knowledgeable and witty man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xerophyte12345 Pure shite. Hope Shearer knocks him to fuck out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjoe_dub The very one! And a brilliant Rod Steiger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starshiphonda I'm trying!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foreverantrim Yes!..love that odd little tune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dynamite is on #TG4 at 9-20. Watch it. It's Fabulous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexy song sung by Scary men. #bbc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a Furby in the house. We're all demented. I want to fuck it in the fire and hear it screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjoe_dub Fianna Fáil's Michael Martin does a Cringey one too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xerophyte12345 Yes..absolutely Dire!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckin cuttin meself. #liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueKirk It's "funny" Friday. It beggars belief!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese accent jokes. Oh for fucks sakes. #liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cappolil As if..I'll be telling everyone "Look! It's Lil..I told you she was real!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cappolil Oh Lil..someday that'll come through ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pints Time. Time for Pints.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaxicabDave I've done the full Jack Nicholson in The Pledge rant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaxicabDave Buckled he was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missloulu2 Me too!..its other people that are prejudiced ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She looked through the window, seen he was a ginger..and fucked off. #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaxicabDave Oh I suspect he's not annoying at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you are an Ass, man. #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaxicabDave And like that sober too. Imagine what a feed of drink would do to him. Oh the humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Jesus. He's a fucking moron. #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick Why I oughta..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooo..Theresa May keeps saying "Churchill" and "Special Relationship".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DecPierce Mother's Milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick Sutherland's hippie annoys me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick I sort of never liked it. Overlong and not enough action. Warmed to it a little bit more recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick I only seen it recently! Kelly's Heroes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick Eek!..I know it's a war film..I can see it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick hmm..maybe a bit more cryptic information please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick Of course you have to buy it. This instant!..before it's gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick I hope you bought that fish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamzer1 These people walk among us. Scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eclecticmick How beautiful! Real Clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I heard he crashes cars". Outstanding. #liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Almost" #Apocalypto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedailyjaws Hitchcockian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheActualSteve I don't think there's been a better decade in Cinema. So many amazing and diverse films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheActualSteve It's the Crimson fountain that really grabs you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did Spielberg get away with that Kintner boy's death scene! Still Astonishing after 40 years. #Jaws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostjimmy Larry Vaughn and his fantabulous jackets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Great fish moved silently through the night water" #Jaws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhboney1 Absolutely, great Director. Great at Visceral stuff. I thought Apocalypto was fantastically paced too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhboney1 Yes, seen that. Gritty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhboney1 Am going to go along this weekend. He deserves a Big screen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apocalypto is on Film4 at 11. Quite simply the best film of the last 30 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelane They must be shipping listeners. Lots of chopping and changing of presenters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfo1ey Yes, that oul Today FM DJ name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfo1ey Both Dire. I listen to The Last Word, that's about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today FM has been going downhill for a long time now. Al Porter certainly won't save it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lusciouslou6 Is there a fuse in the plug? Is the socket working?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanglefoot_tony Turn you into a good arm wrestler though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd looking flies are unsettling, aren't they. I always presume they're just waiting for a chance to lay eggs in me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should make more films with people throwing a sink through a window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerardsullivan Just send the few bob!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move the Dail to Borris-In-Ossory. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heather Humphreys thinks that if she says "rural Ireland" enough times, people will believe she knows what she's talking about. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure as soon as the towns get prosperous, the Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil Landlords will raise the rent. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starshiphonda Don't even go there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Supermarket owner and Undertaker". That's REAL rural Ireland! #rtept]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>