<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[To be able to keep 50+ tired teachers excited and enthused about writing until 7pm is nothing short of amazing, thank you @alanpeat, top CPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is scarily prophetic https://t.co/HrYCxj7Py3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to welcoming @alanpeat to Whitechapel tomorrow evening @StAnnesCPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dorastar1 we were encouraged to disaggregate during our Ofsted last June, worked in our favour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A school needing a Director of Education makes me think their behaviour police isn't working #Michaela https://t.co/fnF6t91Qwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So all this money the gov. have taken back from failed acads. plan is going back into education? Yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah so @educationgovuk has got an answer for the teacher recruitment crisis https://t.co/kKnVl0ykFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustineGreening needs to listen to @BBCr4today on why early education is so important especially in deprived areas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such an outrageous eg of policy to get votes-giving to the better off (who mostly vote) at expense of the p… https://t.co/Zhbi1PZZ1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So today I found out the LA is planning to charge schools extra 2.5% for pensions starting in April &amp; every yr. @NAHTnews #schoolcuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just shows how little @educationgovuk know or understand about how schools are run, that's why everything is s… https://t.co/EUBNoamBwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I can agree with this one.... https://t.co/kMWHM5tb8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing the outcome of this https://t.co/dXi021jvSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmm I pay £30 pcm, see it as a kind of insurance.... https://t.co/JxdaItSI4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be useful...... https://t.co/gW5hqNVWaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govs. proposal to cut nursery funding to pay 30hrs free childcare for working parents effects deprived families massively #toxicpolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone notice she didn't use the word "grammar" instead she said "academic track" hmmm https://t.co/SVKqjabs75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is just a matter of time... https://t.co/umMkd5q2Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah at last, something positive https://t.co/pcxEMcQjXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effect of drastic school cuts may not be too obvious yet but just wait until next year &amp; beyond, then they will bit… https://t.co/an4noMdKkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NAHTnews #schoolcuts in a school with v high deprivation and all the related issue I've had to cut sch. councillor, IT, sp. therapy &amp; more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#schoolcuts everyone needs to look at this and sign the @NAHTnews petition  https://t.co/H02etfLkXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same is happening in Tower Hamlets, Free School's opening when no need with negative impact on pupil nos. in good s… https://t.co/98TtzuF2gP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to offend all teachers #Michaela https://t.co/uGqvUthUUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstrates what happens when schools are opened with no planning or thought for where the need for places is  https://t.co/2zc7FWrdRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BridgetBurke2 @SchoolsImprove and at my school too but what child needs most is a key person to be with them to listen and talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y6 do NOT need to miss out on all the fun, ours didn't and we did very well in SATS, just saying... https://t.co/OunaQIBRxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would s school even have a "padded cell?"  https://t.co/fCAunA0akO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education system heading into total disarray thanks to ill thought out gov. policy, starting with @MichaelGoveNews https://t.co/1wBX5LyuSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dorastar1 I think this is the link, very depressing   https://t.co/H02etfLkXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am losing sleep over what is in store for education, it's the next crisis waiting to happen https://t.co/rMD2UJ3tpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree but cannot deny that  many of @educationgovuk irrational policies lead to many problems in schools https://t.co/9MoWOs9JhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of this I found difficult to understand (macro economics?)but worth persevering especially the last 2 paras https://t.co/ORPAG8Pktr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about us...... https://t.co/3sr4UXfRvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a time when I hav to cut my school councillor's hours by 50% due to budget cuts, this speech smacks of hypocrisy https://t.co/C8xoPitKmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonDLR @LDNOverground staff great, very helpful and cheerful and safe #TubeStrike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No tubes tomorrow, staff will get in to school through determination and a will to not let children down, take note @RMTunion @TSSAunion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really helpful, thank you for sharing @thatboycanteach https://t.co/iAgKoEX0Uy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was there, it's not "forced" https://t.co/fO8atPmaZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No it's not, those other schools need to think carefully about their responsibility to their children, can't always… https://t.co/6s03IT3X93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who on earth is in charge of @educationgovuk tweets? https://t.co/68V8HQVlmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we need this research to state the obvious? @tes https://t.co/ITTGcn4YBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So some Y5 children came to find me at lunchtime to remind me to run a mile with them, I walked fast anyway #fitness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems a long time ago since it was education, education, education https://t.co/bZM77Owj5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News good snippet on the drastic cuts in school funding, don't think the seriousness has hit home yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about what's happening in January in school and yay we have @alanpeat coming to us end of Jan, already looking forward to #2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This list is my new year resolution https://t.co/WYlxfCLmZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the time to wake out of my Christmas stupor and start getting my head around school stuff, who mentioned academies? Budgets? #2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hubby's Christmas present to me, a Jo Malone Christmas tree! @JoMaloneLondon https://t.co/iW7DP7ocYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eldest son so determined to spend Christmas at home has been travelling since yesterday noon and will arrive 9 tonight, £50 from Beijing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wapping station looking and sounding very Christmassy @LoveWapping https://t.co/Ekx6STAXFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to join the shopping frenzy to buy loads of things I don't need....#Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only governors, how can we get people to lead schools in this dreadful educational scenario @educationgovuk… https://t.co/kyBiUJr3E4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dandan7171 @mm684 forward planning not a strong point with @educationgovuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dandan7171 @outlandish standards back 25 years too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it take for DfE to be held accountable for its total inadequacy in every area https://t.co/VaOqlTEcwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No way this can work, maybe the plan is for school's without teachers, just childcare https://t.co/DSSxPqn1te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG I've just looked up my school and I will have lost at least £300,000 by 2020 https://t.co/s9KPlof6gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @educationgovuk sent me lovely letter saying I can access 2016 perf tables day early, highly secret, but I couldn't get in! anyone else?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our school counsellor does such valuable work but I have to cut her hours, can no longer afford it, such a blow to… https://t.co/K7CuHqydPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous carol service tonight, Christmas has truly started https://t.co/pLVznS9Lfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone please complete this and hope we get listened to. We have until tomorrow. https://t.co/HpQZIqsTpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yet another disaster for @educationgovuk https://t.co/sxvGPOr722]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to reduce ours from 2 to 1 day a week, one of the more difficult choices to make regarding cuts https://t.co/ataUgX1uJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@educationgovuk when will you wake up to the fact that leading a grammar is so so different to leading non selective https://t.co/F6I0K403s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So teachers score 88% in poll on trust and politicians a mere 15% so why do we keep acting on their crazy whims?  https://t.co/n1E9QOlup0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was a convincing case put by @JPAMDG for joining the Diocese of Westminster academy trust, lots to think about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, because governments always find a solution! https://t.co/xzkeInAkvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuts to school councillor, speech therapist, IT support, sports and pleading with parents to donate to school fund https://t.co/EtDTY2Hwhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - 10 ways to be the cleverest country https://t.co/pThsj4Gru5 take heed @educationgovuk @JustineGreening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth reading  https://t.co/jDPLK9vlwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see an assembly in that #Amazon ad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as well I left my toaster in my suitcase! @VirginTrains https://t.co/UUPMmkZ97w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSTMagazine @katieglassST @thesundaytimes especially good this week but quite depressing, too much wifi, we're doomed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbancroft79 Our revels now are ended.. We are such stuff as dreams are made on; and our little life is rounded with a sleep -Tempest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew, at last https://t.co/Vugt1cgZ98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ease off now and get some work life balance https://t.co/LwmFKY6HyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is anyone from @educationgovuk going to take any notice of this, we do not need grammars or enforced academies https://t.co/4GqdYA7xQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who needs grammars... https://t.co/lNGE3VEaQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes the #wapping Christmas tree @eastendwestend @LoveWapping https://t.co/jfgZgTEMhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't inspire much confidence in the inspection system #Ofsted https://t.co/5iYkKMfA65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is actually a good idea, I wouldn't mind having a few "teach lasts" in my school https://t.co/VjTxx36omP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please NO https://t.co/FgXhcGtiR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A young lad just offered me his seat on the train OMG am I old?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me uneasy https://t.co/KtaQ9CswPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also need to question @educationgovuk, poor leadership and those constantly talking down the profession https://t.co/u2imALWCG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to know how they are going to "mandate" LA's to improve schools when they have decimated most of them? https://t.co/XdDOjsqTKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eastendwestend thanks, that's helpful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been asked for information quoting FOI, how do I know this is a genuine request? Surely anyone can say it's a… https://t.co/8zJJiHUW0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone @StAnnesCPS is looking forward to @alanpeat running staff training here at the end of January, can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And just look what's happening to the NHS https://t.co/8SZONViZvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This poll is further proof of how #Michaela have been economical with the truth @DavidBrownNET @vicgoddard… https://t.co/O1Lt5dCfIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katie_s_ashford here's a small but more recent poll for you https://t.co/9wTzQBpDD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please show this poll to @katie_s_ashford #Michaela when finished https://t.co/9wTzQBHeuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't mess with Heads  https://t.co/YWhX5dE8Ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm wasn't it @toadmeister who said headship was a lot tougher than he thought, beware recruiting those with no ex… https://t.co/ry5MSYDGn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is it any surprise that recruiting  HT's and staff to challenging schools is such a big problem #ofsted https://t.co/MTLKCunWcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katie_s_ashford @wordpressdotcom that survey was carried out 8 years ago, believe it or not things have got better...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katie_s_ashford yes I get that teachers deserve respect but what you are claiming happens in lots of schools is not true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So not true, go to any good school and this is a rarity. People need to stop talking down teaching… https://t.co/JHSZmkaDIp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>