<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Not even sure what this shirt is supposed to be supporting and/or opposing… https://t.co/vJxeEkhpZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She must have been easy to find in that cage... https://t.co/Sbiz1eCIOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love something, set it free...etc. https://t.co/c0qLWUNJmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RauschB Many of the naturalized award recipients came from the immigrant flow in the early 20th century...most from Europe/British Isles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11/11. (Afghan citizens who speak Urdu or Pashtu are also needed)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. It's called Military Accessions Vital to the National Interest (MAVNI) and here's the details:

https://t.co/KqRhsFV2YC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. In most cases participants in the program will become naturalized U.S. citizens by the time they graduate from...Basic Combat Training]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. You can also fast-track your way to citizenship through @USArmy service if you're a asylee.

The Army says...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. That includes people who speak two languages. High-need languages.  Languages like Arabic and Persian Farsi.

https://t.co/EyKMkirTuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. Even now, the @USArmy has a program for certain jobs where refugees can join up and expedite the process towards citizenship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. And since 2001, more than 100,000 immigrants have been naturalized following service in the US military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. That's about 20% of Medal of Honor recipients]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Some 700 recipients of the Medal of Honor have been immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. One does not have to be Am citizen to be awarded Medal of Honor. In fact...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. @SenatorIsakson just gave speech on importance of immigrants in US military during @DeptVetAffairs confirmation hearing. Couple notes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shulkin said Trump admin has given what he asked for re. hiring freeze exemptions...so Shulkin must have not asked for total VA exemption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. Shulkin says "You know this Sunday is Superbowl Sunday."

Isakson responds. "And Monday is Shulkin Monday."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. VA committee chair says Dr. Shulkin has til next Monday to answer outstanding questions from committee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even this should be able to make it through Congress this year. https://t.co/K768187MxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VA has been saying this for years...legislation has not happened https://t.co/0tGIJQAvkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously. Just take a second, click on account profile--especially b/c it's unverified--and ask: should Exxon have… https://t.co/mztsu0I8YP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA secretary nominee Davs Shulkin says the VA has 45,300 vacancies at the VA.

37,000 of those exempted from Trump federal hiring freeze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation hearing for @DeptVetAffairs sec'y David Shulkin underway. 

He comes out against privatization.

https://t.co/hp56y6l5zq @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If no one knows where President Trump is, does that mean Al Haig is president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cajun Bob getting an awful lot of publicity at the VA nominee confirmation hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will likely come up at the hearing... https://t.co/6kTX2TELsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @DeptVetAffairs sec'y confirmation hearing is very civil thus far. Like it's happening on a different planet than other confim. hearings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson says there will be at least two rounds of questions in the @DeptVetAffairs secretary confirmation hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Department of Veterans Affairs will not be privatized under my watch"

- Dr David Shulkin, @realDonaldTrump nominee for @DeptVetAffairs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At VA secretary confirmation @jontester flogging the Choice Act.

Here's my story on the programs (many) shortfalls

https://t.co/k4Ta70IXUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jontester flogging the VA Choice program right now. The program has had especial problems in some rural states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introductions at the Senate VA hearing for David Shulkin has, what seems, a record number use of the word "doctor"

https://t.co/HHIEmz2dRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOT the ante room

An oddly funny sign at the Senate. https://t.co/65A5gZuvG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic lawmakers seek Pentagon probe of Flynn’s Russia Today ties  https://t.co/lcTQN3WXfU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s VA Nominee Will Be Quizzed on Hiring Freeze, Privatization  https://t.co/1QtN5Lbemt via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll spread the word: This ad doesn't speak for all veterans. https://t.co/8QQTPyLR4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @nytimes video "Ten Meter Tower" is incredible. Go ahead, it's worth the 15 minutes.

https://t.co/8VghNEDqmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Countryman was on @NPR today talking about imp't of State Dept. career employees.

Here's @ForeignPolicy on him

https://t.co/hSC2QMo727]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report finds The VA's Veterans Choice Act had troubled first year https://t.co/AS84Mbiw6P via @WSJPolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a lectern!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A dog is not a cat, baseball is not football and diplomacy is not a business."

Longtime US diplomat speaks out.

https://t.co/hSC2QMo727]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outgoing U.S. Official Urges Diplomats to ‘Stay’ and Protect Constitution https://t.co/4YHRk0RUSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dabeard @gerardtbaker what about media outlets who have military vets on staff. How much credibility does that add?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestkeane Ah! A testimony to the strength and durability of fluoridated leather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are your pouring water onto the seat of that nice leather chair? https://t.co/ruLqZ0vANd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reminder that voters didn't just take him seriously, they took him literally. https://t.co/tAwjGEMkWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seven countries under U.S. entry ban haven’t been main sources of U.S. terror attacks  https://t.co/V6AayBCpcT… https://t.co/s87i6QJWgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draft cable circulating in State Department objects to Trump immigration ban https://t.co/SAN0rYR4iB via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call your member of Congress. 

Or email me with details of particular issues and I’ll see what’s happening. https://t.co/cIKUW0le7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PFC: Jeez, I can't imagine anything worse than an MRE.
Colonel: Hey, young warfighter, try this. https://t.co/NjUZ6MZKWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we know where that plane full of Saudi hawks is headed... https://t.co/6S5NnPBNZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir, for your in-flight meal today, would you prefer the chicken, the beef or the dead rodent? https://t.co/X8lRkhP3Tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12/12 Should do what they can to make sure they're being taken care of in the ways we promised we would take care of them after the war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11/11 Then I will.  And anyone else who relied on their interpreters, as we all did...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. So I emailed him today because if I can help him just a fraction of the amount he helped us in Fallujah...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. Mike was indefatigable. He worked exceptionally hard.

And he believed in the U.S. The concept of the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. Because it's unclear what will happen to him now, even if he has a green card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. The last time I heard from the best interpreter I had in the Marine Corps was in 2014...but I sent him an email today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. He emaild me to say he was granted asylum in 2013 and got his green card in 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. I sent Mike a note, but didn't hear back. Then tried him again a few years later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. I said that having an interpreter like Mike was like having an extra Corporal in my platoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. I still have the letter I sent in support of his application for asylum...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. "Mike" was applying for asylum and needed whatever help I could give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. A law firm emailed me in 2010 to ask me if I'd write a letter of recommendation for one of their clients: my interpreter from Fallujah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad they don't have the 'Revolution X' guns that fire compact discs. https://t.co/vdGXJokevJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This --&gt; https://t.co/QtePkeLuyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khizr Khan, Gold Star Father, on the New Refugee Ban https://t.co/jsMEj0lj96 via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. service member killed in Yemen raid https://t.co/xDhwWgcaYC via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In D.C., platforms made for viewing the inaugural parade get more use as spots to watch protests.

https://t.co/4Xb50lzNjk @WSJPolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countries under U.S. entry ban haven’t been main sources of U.S. terror attacks  

https://t.co/F3nJV6bglK via @WSJPolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor of Lexington, Kentucky https://t.co/7lxoisHdYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seven countries under U.S. entry ban haven’t been main sources of U.S. terror attacks  https://t.co/V6AayBCpcT via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters leave their signs in front of the Capitol. https://t.co/SqDozMFSpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scene at the Senate right now. https://t.co/IZsVh3YVqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the @Newseum people take a break from protest to read front pages of newspapers. 

Nearly all feature stories ab… https://t.co/hBxWcaDzPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People using platforms intended for inauguration events to get a better view of protests at Trump Hotel https://t.co/k4p8hbAjFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters in front of the Trump Hotel en route from the White House to the Capitol https://t.co/cjslbUw7sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-immigrant protesters and statue of Casimir Pulaski: Polish citizen who died fighting on behalf of American colo… https://t.co/yskSwyYfJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just walked by Treasury. They keep coming. https://t.co/py3bG3Ehen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Willard Hotel. Commemorating some of the last efforts, in 1861, to prevent the Civil War https://t.co/ry0hEjaLHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington
Lincoln
Hamilton
Tubman
&amp; Protesters https://t.co/Y5M1VMDTFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters in front of statue, erected by Congress, commemorating the French citizen, Gen. Lafayette, for fighting… https://t.co/yznG5NSp4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-immigration protesters at the White House. 

That guy on the statue: Lafayette—a Frenchman who fought for the c… https://t.co/Dy6SMQEQnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-immigrant protest crowd growing at the White House https://t.co/VKN4l6TGqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the many protesters in front of the White House right now. https://t.co/wsxcCA2ppy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters are streaming towards the White House right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100%

His voters took his promises literally. The obvious hyperbole used as punchlines just blurred the parameters… https://t.co/EQZZWJxCGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters took his words literally on the campaign trail. To think otherwise is folly. https://t.co/5NKr5D4GWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Some foreign countries have already begun moving the machinery of reciprocal action, even if it's just warm-up rhetoric...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. People in other countries (including a number of lawmakers) aren't going to pay close attention to the punctilio of the US court system..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. The judge has issued a stay, but the genie is already out of the bottle with the executive order...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question: @Uber_NYC Is this in response to the cab drivers' striking and does it indicate that you do not support t… https://t.co/yIPvFdSWtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this 2006 Congressional hearing transcript:

'Contributions of Immigrants to the United States Armed Forces'

https://t.co/igvhx8DnpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for take him seriously but not literally.

I was on the campaign trail. People took him literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump visa ban also applies to citizens with dual nationality, State Department says https://t.co/RCUx2oacNB via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqis awaiting U.S. visas for wartime aid see hopes dim under Trump immigration ban https://t.co/PVc4Eaenym via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A modification of WCW's 'This is just to say' https://t.co/chn68INDFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signal is the way to go… https://t.co/L0tAZ4i486]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From one of the leading voices of the Jesuits in the US —&gt; https://t.co/1xeiZSkB5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point, you could make a case for @DosEquis using @GenChuckYeager for the World's Most Interesting Man...at lea… https://t.co/Wn7MMvJ2Be]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>