<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie leader Turnbull worst leader Trump dealt with put in sin bin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lashes 'dumb deal' with Australia on refugees after fraught call with Turnbull https://t.co/blUvk4ATc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has US President Trump put Australia, China, Iran, Mexico and North Korea in his sin bin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie speaks out against President Trump's immigration ban in op-ed https://t.co/2wMPAwNWcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad day when US President can win votes by attacking concept of free press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adani are on the brink of a $1 billion handout, tell your MP #NoAdaniHandouts https://t.co/cgWJx0PCHl via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting attorney general who said travel ban was not lawful – live https://t.co/QZfohlXGYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Costs of private schools 'substantially met' by public funds, says report https://t.co/1trDLUAxjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests spread over Trump travel ban on Muslim majority countries – live https://t.co/wVBkreuEIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese New Year Sayings and Greetings - Popular Phrases in English and Chinese https://t.co/UWB6Lg79dA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier urged to allow apartments to ban Airbnb rentals https://t.co/nQGeTJ12Lu via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simon Birmingham wilfully ignores the evidence about school funding and outcomes | Trevor Cobbold https://t.co/brYmv2RV1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb hosts beware – it's not just Centrelink using robo-debt systems https://t.co/h9ukuF5Vpy via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started reading novel the Maker of Heavenly Trousers by Danielle Vare concerning early 20 century China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen: 'We are part of the new resistance' in the age of Trump – video https://t.co/8sEIzntIe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tritton trained champion pacer wins at Menangle NSW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing about climate change: my professional detachment has finally turned to panic | Michael Slezak https://t.co/FqdOJDoN49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economists warn against tax-deductible mortgages after Coalition refuses to rule out option https://t.co/fHsMiQGxD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Soros says uncertainty over Trump will cause markets to falter https://t.co/MHA3Xm4YdD via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open societies are in crisis, and various forms of closed societies – from fascist dictatorships to mafia states – are on the rise. Soros]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IUDs and mammograms are free under Obamacare. How much will you pay if it’s repealed? https://t.co/Ch540OYcnY via @doublexmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Europe's fate is in our hands': Angela Merkel's defiant reply to Trump https://t.co/5oSfrELFMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Buddhist and Muslim institutions get fair share of massive Aussie taxpayers handouts to religion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private health insurance premium plan sparks fears of patient exodus

https://t.co/EAM6tTCcey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Black Prince largest shareholder in Aussie baby formula company Bellamy controlled in Australia, China, Dutch West Indies or Singapore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Brennan: Trump's 'Nazi Germany' tweet to US agencies was 'outrageous'

https://t.co/75pE3NV467]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Brennan: Trump's 'Nazi Germany' tweet to US agencies was 'outrageous' https://t.co/nVw055clH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the inscrutable Singaporean Black Prince determine control of Aussie baby formula company Bellamy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did 46% of US voters go for an inexperienced, show off bully?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bellamy’s lost key to success https://t.co/e6QFO1LOjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is religious fundamentalism gaining influence in Indonesia, Islamic State and Israel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adani coalmine activists gear up to fight: ‘This will dwarf the Franklin blockade’ https://t.co/hhXQNWHap3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have Turnbull government &amp; Aussie Greens taken part pensions away whilst hosting expensive meals for religious fundamentalists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump claims voters don't care he concealed his tax returns unlike other Presidents because 46% of voters supported that action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie leader Turnbull dinner with religious leaders cost taxpayers $30k https://t.co/8d8F8I9K4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left Renewal: since when has taxing the rich and saving the planet been so controversial? https://t.co/uYxKnnGxrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is behind Black Prince Foundation shareholder in Bellamy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bellamy’s ditches McBain https://t.co/LRbbvhdP1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie tennis star Nick shows courage to wear anti Trump T shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney weather: NSW Health issues warning on heat, smog https://t.co/yPvcnLKCu1 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young champion Salty Robyn wins again for Tritton camp in fast time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Boss Man driven by a female wins the main trotting event at Horsham Victoria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s secret farewell bash https://t.co/4FdhukaSTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli diplomat caught on camera plotting to 'take down' UK MPs https://t.co/BBskpXGp1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian minister says Melbourne protester's actions 'intolerable' https://t.co/0v0ou9iimS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Aussies suffer if a trade war is started by Trump against China and Mexico?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Aussie ASIC missing in action in relation to the Bellamy farce with Bellamy suspension of trading &amp; lack of timely disclosure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bellamy's chairman likely to quit if board spill succeeds https://t.co/U2t9hwfOUU via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie Health Minister Sussan Ley bought $795,000 flat on impulse on taxpayer-funded trip https://t.co/dvhpVOMN5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record-breaking extreme weather in Australia in 2016 devastates ecosystems https://t.co/sqtcRZM2Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ROMANTIC DIPLOMAT » 29 Sep 1938 » The Spectator Archive: https://t.co/Xukuv257Wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to the cheap electricity promised by right wing Aussie government if no carbon tax?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey: armed attacker kills dozens in Istanbul nightclub

https://t.co/CzQZxdgdzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long will the Putin &amp; Trump bromance last?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourth case of measles in Sydney visited multiple suburbs while infectious https://t.co/cxDmK84yJr via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnaby Aussie Deputy Prime Minister is good for pork barrelling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Xenophon rides on

https://t.co/t9P6dHBsIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former One Nation senator Rod Culleton declared bankrupt https://t.co/NT925opckS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Aussie voters get rid of anti Aussie pro foreign polluters Turnbull government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie big business Turnbull government attacks Aussie ABC media over comment on billion dollars loan of taxpayers money to Indian firm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have shareholders of up to 3 year sin bin companies Australian Careers Network &amp; Bellamy's Australia lost all or most of their money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If so should Indian Adani be the kind of legal person to receive a billion dollars of taxpayers money in preference to hospitals &amp; schools?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Indian Adani the kind of legal person who should get a Million Dollars of Aussie taxpayers money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems Bellamy accountants, directors, lawyers &amp; spin doctors want more time. Bad signal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie shall not make any law for establishing any religion, or for imposing any religious observance s116 Constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians have an increasingly complex, yet relatively peaceful, relationship with religion https://t.co/i4lUMnAK5C via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish religious fundamentalist police terrorist assassinates Russian Ambassador.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Eddie Obeid and the support of the proposed new Crown casino building and dog racing is it time to disband Labor in NSW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change sceptics control Aussie Turnbull government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump faces Senate backlash over ‘cabinet of billionaires’ https://t.co/bhNlRpkogx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could press freedom in Poland &amp; Turkey be in danger? We already have severe restrictions on press freedom in China, Islamic State  Nth Korea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tritton family win with odds on favourite in the main event at Menangle NSW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian 'thieves' paraded with signs on Indonesian streets https://t.co/hjyhOKKByj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the fight against Adani and their $1 billion handout. Tell Turnbull #NoAdaniHandouts https://t.co/lPqsgjdt7L via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larry Eastman &amp; Chris Alford win for prostrate cancer charity at Charlton NSW harness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Tech joins big oil in Wall Street Trump cabal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Obeid sentenced to five years in jail for misconduct https://t.co/FymIG8qrp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Martin: Our copyright laws are holding us back, and there's a way out https://t.co/0kuseLAn2N via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems white working class US voters prefer big oil executives to control them rather than academics and worker representatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class actions may commence against Aussie baby milk formula company Bellamy's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Indonesia moving towards intolerant fundamentalism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bellamy's shares suspended from trade https://t.co/K02LeVk42v via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big oil tall poppy scored top job in Trump administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ho Feng Shan: The 'Chinese Schindler' who saved thousands of Jews @CNNI https://t.co/4RdJ4pLswb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feng-Shan Ho | Jewish Virtual Library https://t.co/3BeDw5G0lQ via @JewishVLibrary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition to introduce broadband surcharge to help pay for rural NBN. Yet another new tax slug. https://t.co/ile1SK2Rcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tritton trains another winner at Bankstown NSW paceway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull was right in 2009: ruling out emissions trading is 'bullshit' | Lenore Taylor https://t.co/7vR9V9WByp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie ABC seems to have gone downhill under Malcolm and Michelle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should BAL &amp; SRX have known and warned shareholders at recent AGM meetings of sales and revenue problems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is UK providing weapons for use by Saudi Arabia to commit atrocities in Yemen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will West Aussie pacer and driver defeat Eastern and NZ pacers and drivers in big Group 1 pacing final tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Iran nuclear agreement is a deal worth honouring https://t.co/ff4TUU1LVP via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Malcolm Turnbull, the victory of climate sceptics is almost complete! | First Dog on the Moon https://t.co/J1VdcItxRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnaby Joyce and NSW ministers target charity status of animal rights groups https://t.co/rWY32cBl15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Aussie right wing government give massive handouts to foreign companies polluters to damage Aussie environment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter influences investor behaviour whether companies intend it to or not: new research https://t.co/levXtrbhSM via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian GDP: economy shrinks by 0.5% in September quarter https://t.co/zYf3jG5KjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull Aussie government puts political expediency before the welfare of Aussie citizens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opposition to public funding for Adani rail link outweighs support, poll finds https://t.co/75oc6D3Iq4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>