<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In other important news, thanks to everyone @StateDept for their courage: https://t.co/mHB8uCAIa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently Congressman Chaffetz' phone works now. Call him at  (202) 225-7751 and tell him you don't want part of DC split off into MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff do you think the ban was a head fake/trial balloon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly this is irony https://t.co/PjsHVmx7KI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say "so it begins" but we are already so far behind the curve that we can barely respond to all the transgressi… https://t.co/cswiHUucQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! https://t.co/dQrVoslnrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he wear the same suit and tie every day? His ties are also consistently too long. Maybe it's a tiny hands thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deliberateloris interesting. They def were not there for the protests this weekend. Wonder why not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fences are out today https://t.co/QZkesl1XsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if a nominee got up to make an acceptance speech and instead quit right there in front of everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's the Koch brothers who bring sanity to this circus so help me god but literally anything would be better than this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Immigration Ban is a Headfake, and We’re Falling For It” by @jakefuentes &lt;--TERRIFYING https://t.co/h3ier3QvgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so @peterthiel are you taking trump literally now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates Thank you for being a hero today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally Yates #hero Acting Attorney General Orders Justice Dept. Not to Defend Refugee Ban https://t.co/sAp16h7guL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmodern3 Yes that is exactly what I'm worried about. We are too busy responding and totally stunned right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Either u stand up for your principles and what u know is decent behavior or u go down as a coward or opportunist" https://t.co/yyuLT4WPU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This entire government will be leaking like a seive https://t.co/Wlp3uh947E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if the ban and the wall are just meant to distract us from the scarier things he's secretly doing under the radar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And am now being detained by DHS..? &lt;-- hopefully not the case but I wouldn't be surprised https://t.co/EW5Vof6G5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a bobcat on the loose from the DC zoo. If you see it, call me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peak millennial? I think this time it *is* different https://t.co/0JEvgq6TJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otis_reid wow they totally got me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to see what the markets do on Monday. My bet is down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands marching from White House to Trump Hotel #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/HxzaiicsQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This right to life march on a Friday, I guess they don't have jobs to be at or anything like that right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9am meetings cutting into TV time #ovalofficeproblems @maggieNYT https://t.co/9Xv1l6QHCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS44 to @POTUS in letter: "If I thought your health plan would be better, I'd support it." #SHADE https://t.co/PKJoRZIxhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mateagold Hilarious finding BUT duplicate reg. don't show fraud, just that states don't know how to use computers https://t.co/60j0DbGZPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnemployedKat Mayor Bowser just released a survey to get community input on public safety https://t.co/tRdpSxy4uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFallows Mayor Bowser just released a survey to get community input on public safety https://t.co/tRdpSxy4uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Mayor Bowser just released a survey to get community input on public safety https://t.co/tRdpSxy4uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is the kind of action we need. https://t.co/t62jeSa4eb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatureValley just smoked through an entire pack of #sweetnspicy bars. can you do single bars that are the size of four bars??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As will I https://t.co/GrkrwVaqZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadIandsNPS just changed their name to @BadIandsNPSFans #twitter cracking down???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see #nofascistusa protesting in front of Trump's hotel in #DC tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YETICoolers cmon guys it's 2017, your web forms can handle hyphens https://t.co/nOtvd0UdZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not know about this amazing moon race: https://t.co/sMdUuA0QSm so cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Comey gets to stay. Rewards for a job well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I meet Trump I may first grab his crotch -- to get his attention --then discuss Science with him @neiltyson  https://t.co/jmv4147OOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swingleftorg also potentially with Putin? Who to trust!!! https://t.co/LbYqi0suK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Signs Anti-Abortion Executive Order Surrounded By Men - The Huffington Post. Wtf.  https://t.co/lPjQXcc6la]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelMoore360 I autocorrected Trump's inaugural address as if it were for the #womensmarch https://t.co/5eYVGfZST4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddow I autocorrected Trump's inaugural speech for the #WomensMarch https://t.co/5eYVGfZST4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ECmadtown But that's about all the data I have access to at the moment... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ECmadtown I did do an informal survey of about 40 people--only one of them didn't vote in 2016; everyone else voted for @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ECmadtown thought you might like this: Rewrote Trump's inaugural speech as if it were meant for the #womensmarch https://t.co/5eYVGfZST4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ECmadtown Not sure what you mean exactly, tell me more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFallows I rewrote Trump's inaugural speech as if it were meant for the Women's March: https://t.co/5eYVGfZST4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i rewrote @realDonaldTrump's inaugural speech as if it were meant for the Women's March: https://t.co/5eYVGfZST4 #WomenMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pink, so aesthetic on a foggy day #WomansMarch https://t.co/w45o9YQ5Ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump can dish but he can't take it; muzzling his agencies starting with the #NationalParkService… https://t.co/RyorBQ2QU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much goodwill in this city today. And so many more people #dc #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure @jeffgiesea said we should give white supremacy a "fair hearing" on the @kojoshow lmk if I missed something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump needs to shorten up that necktie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I for one welcome our insect overlords #MAGA #TrumpInauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The angry trolls have hijacked #reddit front page right now on behalf of @realDonaldTrump When will he give them a… https://t.co/WaEthhSVe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many sirens in downtown #dc today I don't think anyone is paying attention to them anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This graphic by @flowingdata sums up why Hillary lost pretty simply https://t.co/LSds201bpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting computers to project onto the conference room screen continues to be one of the most under appreciated problems of our day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse Won't let me email him from my DC zipcode yet he feels fine legislating on my behalf… https://t.co/XyJe4CfA2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FenitN Thought u might find it interesting that I called @jasoninthehouse re: #deathwithdignity and BOTH his voicemail boxes are full]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest impact of cell phone cameras? Awareness of discrimination has gone up; evidence of aliens/ghosts/Sasquatch has not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out LEDs are &gt;&gt;&gt; CFLs. Never liked the delay to full illumination anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when I had to pay like $10 for a CFL --"It will last for EVER" Until we get LEDs that is https://t.co/0VpTxLBev4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't realize that cabs were not allowed to go certain places in NYC. Another reason why cabs are on the out. https://t.co/KJGe34qUWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why it's so expensive to get a tow o the Jersey Turnpike #barrierstoentry https://t.co/4UmcaYUr2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This mouse costs $12 at Best Buy #procurement  is f***ed https://t.co/41yoQPhiK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this description of Benjamin Franklin https://t.co/HoDGspiF39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse Explain what right you have to block #deathwithdignity act in a city that you don't even represent? https://t.co/H5UoYYKhbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hooverwhalen thinks @realDonaldTrump gave a more informative press conference than President Obama ever has. Add him to the list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait what? All Trump hotel profits go to the USG? WTF????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have a no conflict of interest provision" DJT. "I could actually run my business and gov't at the same time."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's talking about himself in the third person now? #TrumpPressConference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh boy here we go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just like a scattered rehash of stump speech spliced with words like very and beautiful and tremendous and incredible and very very]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airplane companies sh**ing bricks right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it's ok do release that stuff if it's negative towards HRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think we maybe won the nomination because of news conference"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzwinstead @ECmadtown bc there's no such thing as press conferences anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Props to @BuzzFeedBen for pulling the trigger. https://t.co/fayh4qZw3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thoughts on algorithmic regulating from @timoreilly https://t.co/SmZLerHux2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmodern3 don't know off the top of my head...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come Democrats never talk like this: "Democrats need to grow up" https://t.co/kwUfzUJNjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to see what the Donald has to say in response https://t.co/LceJi1fGBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL that you can't test an LED dimmer switch with a multimeter because it's a triac circuit and those work by chopping the AC waveform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's in the #onepercent? (hint: @HillaryClinton) https://t.co/vUmTgwaDMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How DC's laws were made (almost) open #NoteToSelf  https://t.co/KQnLi2L2j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For comparison: Mozart: 1.25 million CDs in 5 weeks; Adele's Hello: 1 million downloads in one week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently Mozart sold more CDs in 2016 than anyone else. Not surprised--this is who still buys cds https://t.co/HDMqmf1Wxq via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[favorite thing about #IndependenceDayResurgence so far: DC lifts the height restriction! truly the future is here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@questdiag just exposed 34k patient records and notified people BY MAIL https://t.co/Rw3XivClYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fix procurement" by @pahlkadot. Articles like this are the reason I read @Medium https://t.co/HeEHl5NkWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Results are in: one bottle of #TraderJoes gyoza sauce gets me through exactly 4 bags of frozen gyoza https://t.co/2ZXLGgPOmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about these: https://t.co/Hm11N0JBqV #NoteToSelf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’re ripe for a new cultural movement. Culture movements and art and punk rock thrive under bad presidents." -@Joi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Joi Ito Explains Why Donald Trump Is Like the Sex Pistols” by @StevenLevy https://t.co/6yaIjO7SV8 https://t.co/hqBQFMkH3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDOTDC what's this mysterious construction on 14th and U? https://t.co/4ry4EJRIIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFallows Unfortunate indeed but if picked, definitely a win to have someone who knows not to answer calls from +886]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>