<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanmcleod When did "balance" become a euphemism for "let's put a reactionary right wing racist on the air?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NVSD44 It would show leadership, and set an example for your students, if you cleared your sidewalks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Yellow Pages are arriving in #NorthVan ! I trust the recycling station has added a second shift?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stuff that sometimes pops up on Google. A Lynn Valley #NorthVan Local Plan from 1998. "Youth" want pool halls.
https://t.co/A646w3gzrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RioTheatre is double-billing Singing in the Rain and LaLaLand. Talk about setting people up for disappointment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing about @jk_rowling isn't her skill at nuking trolls. It's that she's a role model for MILLIONS  of childr… https://t.co/XO95VXLnHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appalbarry Fwded from SNAPPS Facebook. I know nothing more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NorthVan: (2 hrs ago) Attention dog owners 
Older choc lab with NO COLLAR hit by a car on R'side and Dollarton Hwy. TO: Blueridge An. Hosp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut Mom is 89. Routinely has cornflakes for dinner. "Because I can.  What? It'll shorten my life?" https://t.co/38ZNwt7f8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #NorthVan talked about trails below Keith Rd Bridge, did they mention wire mesh fences either side, like slaug… https://t.co/kdByZVixGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found deep in the forest above #WestVan https://t.co/L7ccg5Y8cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also in the City of #NorthVan, dog waste disposal! If only the District and  #westVan did the same! https://t.co/sKrGqNkQ06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City of #NorthVan would like your input about walking.  If you remember when people actually DID walk places: https://t.co/SFFcXgnqwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This should scare the living daylights out of you. https://t.co/8Xbv2Egbhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk Welcome to Harper era Canada.  Burning libraries full of research will be next. (It was fisheries data for us.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awolfman He also creates web sites that - I kid you not - only work with an MS browser.  I didn't think that was even possible any longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of "computer professional" sends a Microsoft Project file out to a general audience, esp one with many Apple users?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Facebook Ad that I actually shared: @Notontwitter @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/MA34Bcvp1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dream of a day when @Windows will let you cancel a print job. Maybe Win 35?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only @CBCNews would do a major story about #WomensMarch without ever calling it "Women's March."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed Happy to see that @dog_rates supported the March! https://t.co/5pCqVSi3qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dog_rates is still my absolute favorite thing. This just makes it more so. https://t.co/5pCqVSi3qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed in other words, what do you do if Trump just ignores the marches and protests?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed Or is it like Twitter  &amp; FB "activism," with snappy memes but no actual influence on those in power? (2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed A March is fun, but can it translate to the kind of actions that can successfully challenge an entire government? How? (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tammyrobert @Paul_Jorgenson Let's be clear, BC still allows kickbacks, Clark is  turning them down 'cause election. Nothing has changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My modest contribution to the Trump drama. #Inauguration https://t.co/o9gtPYWQHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougSaunders Apparently Trump's choice to head the National Archives is a guy named Montag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCStephenQuinn Via Facebook. It seemed appropriate this week. https://t.co/mj7YD1yKyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews: reprinting Lib govt press releases again. #bcpoli  Alex Fraser Bridge to get additional lane https://t.co/7vXswKhjsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stratapress Just back from a hearing in front of our strata council and ...  Impression none of them knows what the CRT is. Yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed Moved to US; amazed that people REALLY believe the nation myths in movies and TV. Even if they know they're untrue. Doublethink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilkesitgirl Or, as they're known in my strata, "Those People."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IjeomaOluo @Dymaxion Major university, not many years back: The wheelchairs can come in by the loading dock to avoid stairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeLydon @mrmathewbond Most important, your branding needs to be World Class™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw Bowser trending on Twitter and assumed we had lost yet another rock god. #shanana @JonBowzerBauman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of North Shore mountain biking. Seriously fascinating stuff. #NorthVan https://t.co/Vi3S1bSYQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just in: A letter carrier found lost dog Charlie today and contacted the Shelter and they notified the owner. #NorthVan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed "ethnomasochist" I really need to ponder that one. Or better, use it in conversation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaSpitale nope, I'm President of the North Shore Professional Dogwalkers' Alliance, and just forwarded the post from a member.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaSpitale Hi Maria, if I hear anything more  you'll be first to know. Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK folks, we don't want a repeat of Boaty McBoatface. https://t.co/PnjLb88Wr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Thanks Mathew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are our local #NorthVan heroes? And should we name them at city limits? 
https://t.co/j1APUVhyte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Incidentally, if anything about those awards is on the DNV site, I can't find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Hi Mathew - Racking my brain trying to recall the name of the trail builder who got the award from the District last Nov.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one goes in my big scrapbook of "How cops mangle English." https://t.co/Cj0SniEWT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord, save me from people who write only in sentence fragments, then complain bitterly when asked to explain what, exactly, they meant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntjeWahl @mrmathewbond I live in the Diostrict. I can complain about ANYTHING, at ANY TIME!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Mathew, I did want to be there, but am buried alive. Would have asked about sidewalks (more) SW snow clearing (also more).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet again a tech firm grabs a handful of tiles out of the Scrabble bag, slams them down, and says, "That's our new… https://t.co/K9Iizgnssf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed Air and Space Museum. Up close and personal with real space capsules!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanHaynes @alexhern Nice nuanced article.  I feel very sorry for your Twitter feed in the next few days though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @wordpress and @_gravitar I give up. it apparently is impossible to add a profile pic to Wordpress. 3 times aro… https://t.co/vB5Z6D07bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentRichter @mrmathewbond Fascinated to see that almost every @NVanDistrict tweet this morning is about clearing sidewalks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmarkevich Obliged to say that we could afford to boost foreign aid AND income supports to poor Canadians. Doesn't need to be either/or.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shell will sell gas to #disabled peeps if a) they phone ahead b) can reach the intercom c) staff isn't busy with o… https://t.co/Z9vksnYRbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NVanDistrict I'm sorry, but "blizzard??". #NorthVan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the heck is @PlayHearthstone and why is my @twitter feed cluttered up with their stupid ads? #rhetoricalquestion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have your say about the District of #NorthVan 2017 Budget! https://t.co/lhXPMYkHcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentRichter "Storeys"? Shouldn't it be "Stories?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is a good 5 day forecast for the #coquihalla  highway? #bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NorthVan bars, restaurants. If you have  a website, Twitter, Facebook  etc, can ONE of them tell us when you're open during the holidays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Saw a guy do that with an aluminum boat. Made one heck of a noise when the ropes broke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farhanmohamed @mrmathewbond Until after the election, when it will magically become impossible again. Or fares will go up by another $2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Twitter: best place to buy firewood in #NorthVan ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zommd9LJa2 Three popups in fifteen seconds. Why I never, ever visit their site. @yellowpages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @Paul_Jorgenson @iancapstick @CBCNews Where "interesting" means 'not indistinguishable from Liberals."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5kids1condo At a minimum, we need to move past the either/or equation and make decisions that reflect a transportation mix, not just autos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appalbarry but here, think of all the money they saved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4" of snow and our incompetent #strata council and equality incompetent property management can't find our incompetent snow removal co.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomgreen_ Found it: https://t.co/h9UFfVvhd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomgreen_ FB URL plus. All I find are lame ass Facebook "generated" pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking over @dnv finances on their website, and found this utterly charming photo. #northvan… https://t.co/gy7gd9xYPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stratapress Council refuses to fix road heating; says if temps too low for salt to work, people are advised to stay home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreshStMarket Wow! Best cake ever! https://t.co/V5p3gOUyrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Esso, now managed by @7eleven. "We Care" sticker covering up call button used to talk to station employees. https://t.co/kJ8W34DjWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SafewayCanada Dropped basket of grocs and walked out of Lynn Valley store 1/2 hr ago. 6-8 people in line; 1/2 checkouts not open. #NorthVan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lottomax Where are tonight's winning numbers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByJamesKeller @CBCStephenQuinn Also, really, truly, after this election, wine in grocery stores actually near you! (We mean it this time!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndertonLift @Canal_Boat Peterborough, Ontario, Canada  65 ft lift. https://t.co/jgmxiqs1Av

Crummy picture: stops you dead in real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOnTheCoast Lynn Valley is looking particularity festive this week. If you ignore the 4" of slush on the streets. https://t.co/Nq3LvQ3yKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOnTheCoast West Van snow clearing : excellent as always.  Shame I live in District of North Van. #slushcity :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsk. You shouldn't criticize  #mydemocracy unless you can suggest a practical, workable alternative.... Oh.... Never mind. #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut Missed /7. Would appreciate insight from people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut Then again, I look at this org chart and shudder. /8 https://t.co/DWfwSIv6RU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut  Also guessing that most of the fights are in a specific areas, w. longstanding grievances on both sides./6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut  We're trying to get a sense of where the reality lies, since it looks like both sides are only presenting one side /5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut   ... and crazy, and the Trust look heavyhanded and overly bureaucratic. with insane rules, boat seizures etc./4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut But she's hit on some youtube videos of battles between cruisers and the Canal Trust that make former look derelict /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut We're in Canada right now, but she's Brit, so no problem there. Boating and the life looks v. nice, and being in the UK /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut Hi David - overly long tweet thread here. 1. GF and I have been looking at a boat as a retirement option. /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCStephenQuinn The impact of fireworks on birds and wild life via PriceTags blog. https://t.co/4Etm6v9HEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Jorgenson @CBCNews Astonished that Those in Power have such difficulty changing the system that empowers them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomeDepot These horrible ads hijack any page I'm visiting. So bad I will NEVER shop at your store again. Worst, mo… https://t.co/fu7IGvnkMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CruisingTheCut Or a girl/boyfriend...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icbc Do NOT want to waste half day going to bank for special letter, then driving to agent. This is stupid. It's 2016. Use electronics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @icbc All I want to do is change my auto-withdraws to my new business account. Thus far it seems impossible. Just want to fax a form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmathewbond Re: @TransLink  fare hikes too? https://t.co/mtViKmFTeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bunglepants_ @CruisingTheCut Hah! Amateur! This is how a REAL Pro does it! https://t.co/YpeUGyPEMk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>