<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[US makes exceptions to sanctions on Russian spy agency - VIDEO: Treasury Department easing restrictions on Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallen Navy SEAL gets posthumous promotion, recalled as devoted family man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative Vince in trouble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to hunt a coyote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUDGEMENT CALL Dems including Schumer, Clinton, Obama all backed Gorsuch … in ‘06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burger boss' wacky move]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret behind Trump's hair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hitler's phone up for auction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police: Girl fatally shot brother after fight over video-game system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman booted over cleavage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guard found dead in Delaware prison standoff was 16-year department veteran - Prison guard found dead as Delaware hostage situation ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spears flashes concertgoers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suicide wave grips Columbia University]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher has personalized handshakes with each of his students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials: Body of Tennessee police officer who fell into river found]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Paso residents highlight the positives of living with a border wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the dinosaurs died]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring Tom Cruise home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: One hostage found dead, another rescued as police secure Delaware state prison - VIDEO: Prisoners in Delaware revolt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil's forecast: Groundhog predicts 6 more weeks of winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUMP TWEETS POTUS rips Iran deal, pays homage to slain SEAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man accused of killing Colorado transit officer reportedly self-described 'radical Muslim']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inmates at Delaware state prison hold 2 employees hostage - VIDEO: Hostage situation at a prison in Delaware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan's Abe to propose major job-creating plan to Trump, reports say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car crashes through Maryland man's home for fifth time in 45 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston man who 'lost tooth' hunting for Tom Brady Uggs faked story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE Report: Daughter of Anwar al-Awlaki killed in US raid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['TUCKER TONIGHT' Milo: Berkeley riot 'ironic, self-defeating' for left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jersey girl expelled after suing school to be on boys' basketball team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Gov. Abbott cuts funding to Austin over sanctuary city policies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detectives investigate bizarre disappearance of missing California man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7-year-old South Carolina boy discovers bag of cash stashed away at gas station]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imam comes clean about Michigan man's claim that mom died due to travel ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['WORST' CALL SO FAR Trump blasts Australian leader over refugee deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE DHS chief wants border wall finished in 2 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PROTESTS TURN VIOLENT Riots at UC Berkeley over Breitbart editor's speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PRISON UPRISING 2 staffers still held hostage, standoff continues in Del.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Today' - Hall out, Kelly in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive lava stream exploding into ocean in Hawaii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby: All about my sex life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas man wins Super Bowl tickets for life after finding golden Bud Light can - Former President George H.W. Bush accepts NFL Super Bowl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing bobcat found on National Zoo property after slipping out of exhibit - Donations needed after 123 dogs found in California home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HONORING THE FALLEN Trump pays respects to Navy SEAL in surprise visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experts: California voter registration system 'highly susceptible' to fraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bud takes on immigration in ad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chevy's secret sports car?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden backs Perez in race to lead Democratic Party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WARNING WORDS National Security adviser Flynn puts Iran 'on notice']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer's big poker win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom can't remember son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clever cat: National Zoo keepers call off search after bobcat slips out of exhibit - Donations needed after 123 dogs found in California…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TEAM TRUMP ADVANCES Key cabinet picks on to Senate showdowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooters without famous servers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a roll: Cool cargo robot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does 404 error mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell: Trump is not my pal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPREME COURT SKIRMISH Dems go ballistic, Republicans eye nuclear option over Gorsuch choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whirlwind heist: Video shows thieves steal $250G of gold and diamonds in seconds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snake stuck in woman's what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli forces begin evacuation of West Bank outpost - VIDEO: Military orders hundreds to leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB stars memorialize fallen Navy SEAL, one of their biggest fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clock restarts on '24: Legacy']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California lawmakers want 'third gender option' for drivers' licenses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospital: Turkish cop tries to kill self, causes panic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White privilege essay contest sparks outrage in Connecticut suburb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama may challenge Trump more forcefully in coming months, report says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York City teacher accused of training roosters for cockfighting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body of Ivy League student reported missing found near New Hampshire river]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel announces plan to build 3,000 homes in West Bank settlements, report says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Democratic lawmakers move to become 'sanctuary state' - Trump's 'sanctuary' order sets up showdown between cities and states]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACK ON TRACK? Army Corps told to clear way for Dakota pipeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO IS NEIL GORSUCH? History of Colorado judge tapped to fill Scalia's seat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIGH COURT PICK: Trump nominates Neil Gorsuch to Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Behind the scenes of the Super Bowl security operation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Americans will be targeted in terror strikes, White House says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thing is your ancestor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bieber too cool for Grammys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold takes swipe at Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 soldiers injured in Fort Campbell helicopter crash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life may indeed flash before your eyes at death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors weigh child-pornography charges against Anthony Weiner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FOX NEWS INSIDER: Former NYPD Commish to Schumer on 'fake tears' — You didn't cry on 9/11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[700-car stash revealed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran launched another ballistic missile in secret last month, US officials say - UN Security Council to hold emergency meeting over Iran…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lynch surprises who?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US-led coalition delivers armored vehicles to Syrians fighting ISIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montana fire department rescues dog who got his head wedged in wheel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Museum finds WHAT in exhibit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dodge building 1-seat car]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 3 soldiers critically injured in Fort Campbell helicopter crash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First responder adopts baby he delivered on call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ancient carvings show WHAT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia rocker dead at 67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids burned in challenge craze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump joke offends on 'Bach']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Deranged cannibal’ hamsters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First glimpse of Amazon Reef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affleck: It was mutual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Pentagon believes attack on Saudi frigate meant for US warship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White: Rousey is 'done']]></document>
	</documents>
</author>