<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnfieldHub Thank fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VintageCoutinho His throw ins would cause all sorts of shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathxnK Don't know Jeff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Add top class to Clyne Matip Hendo Gini Lallana Mane Firmino Coutinho and were laughing, no more bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clyne Matip Henderson Wijnaldum Lallana Mane Firmino Coutinho, there good enough imo, add to that properly and were going places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Yep coz we know Hull away will be the test, games we need to start winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills You anymore confident with how tonight went]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intensity especially 2nd half is what's needed all the time, we all know the problems that need sorting but that was much better tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We almost got robbed aswell coz that was never a fucking penalty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After our recent collapse that's much better tonight, obviously a win was needed but you'll take that in the circumstance, much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be on it from the 1st Liverpool, we can beat these cunts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People actually want Klopp out, get fucking real he's the best thing to happen to us in years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Whatever else happened we'll never know but he's apologised, so let the man back in, we're fucking desperate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Come on Jurgen, just look at Lovren coz that should be all the motivation you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I'm worried and yes I think we need big change in the boardroom and on the pitch, and yes i may be going on but I care about our club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to fix up and be ready for Chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I've already said it's times like this you find out who's good enough and surely Klopp will be doing just that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cutting a long story short, the majority of the players we have just ain't good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm not naive to know it won't happen overnight but 3 defeats in a row against teams we should be beating is a worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You started to believe we were slowly becoming a proper team and finally turning that horrible corner then we hit this bad run......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You knew with it being Klopps 1st full season you'd have a couple of knocks along the way, but with how good weve been up until new year....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Not like he can play cb or anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Musker_LFC @bailey1_nathan Tell this to the players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Klopp may have thought over the short spell last season that he could generally work with the players he had, turns out.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnfieldPulse Its killing us and it needs to change now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CudiRed @FalseFirmino Just hope Fsg don't put him under pressure and give him money to buy real fucking players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D10_LFC They weren't saying that in November, and coz we're still fucking shit it's gonna take time again, fucking bollocks mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills I'm worried mate, the position we've been put under by Fsg is very concerning, it'll be Klopp who's put under pressure tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say we need a mass clear out in the summer, it should've happened this summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D10_LFC Same here mate and it ain't fucking changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not saying we definitely would've won coz were pathetic at the moment, but give yourselves a fucking chance, not good enough all round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our confidence is shot and you make that many changes, Fsg are the cause for where we're at but Klopps responsible for that shit today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to fucking panic, were in serious trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy do we need a boost, let's win today and let's fucking win well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate ranting and being negative but i just want success for our football club, we now have the right manager so let's move forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjSelectaSkills Majority of our squad don't either, your not playing for Southampton Newcastle or Augsberg now, your playing for Liverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@96merseyside @chrislfcslater @AnfieldHQ @LFC Hopefully we see that today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to put in a performance that Warrants that fact coz I can't take anymore of this shit weve been accustomed to just accept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for these players to realise your not playing for the shitty clubs we brought you from, your playing for Liverpool football club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karius Arnold Gomez Matip Moreno Wijnaldum Henderson Coutinho Origi Firmino Ojo, we need a win no fucking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndigoLFC Same mate, we can't deal with Lovren no more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carl_M79 Having the right players with the right mentality will help, something we lack in abundance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next couple of years are massive and we can't fuck up, let's be thankful we have Klopp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Klopp will get us back and do great things, just not with this group though, time and again the majority just ain't good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnfieldRd96 fucking spot on mate, the only players we have that don't bottle it either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much promise turning to shit its worrying these last few performances just scream of the last few seasons, Klopp needs a rethink and fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet again we dont show up when we need to yet again certain players are fucking shit, although tbf everyone of them were, not good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This boy, and he's ours. https://t.co/9WzPntYy1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's players like Mignolet Lovren and at the moment Can who are problems and need to come out of our team, starting… https://t.co/2Wv21v7MgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateLFC_ @MattiasArvidss1 Just frustrating that some players make the same mistakes, but with Klopp were on the right track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make sure that shit on Saturday is forgotten and we refocus and are ready for Wednesday, few changes needed to restore confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its all well and good when your flying it's when your struggling you find out how mentally tough your team are, time to find out who got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThoseScouseLads Worst cb Ive seen at the club for the money we paid, the cunts like a lost puppy and has the mentality of one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have ranted a bit since yesterday but I just want us to be the best, moments like yesterday make it so fucking frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just goes to show how good Klopp is fucking love the guy, we should be thankful we have him to guide us on our way, world class manager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have improved under Klopp and the table suggests that and we will get better, but there are players we have that simply aint good enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for Klopp to find out who he can really trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could be struggling in 6th or 10 points clear at the top and I'd still say we have players that will always let you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we're losing coz we don't have Mane available, nooo we're losing coz certain players we have just don't have the brain to function]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFCroundup How about at 2-2 you go on and win the game, that shows how good you are, not always having to react after defeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kopice86 Lovren makes me sick, how he's a defender I'll never fucking know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kopice86 Yep he's joke and how the fuck is it Milner marking Llorrente, where the fuck is Lovren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VintageCoutinho @klopp Should leave us with about 10 players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndigoLFC He's fucking mentally unstable the cunt, thats been clear for ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 2-2 theres only one winner and then yet again we Fuck up ourselves, really is fucking frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Est_1980_ Don't think I can handle Lovren anymore mate, oh if there was never a problem with Sakho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who partners Matip from now then coz I'd probably go with Gomez if I'm being honest, Lovren will never be good enough and Klaven is back up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flanners85 All I'm concerned about is us fucking about again, fuck Wayne Rooney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way to react is book a place at Wembley, and we make sure we fucking react well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defensively we are so pathetic, no toughness at all fucking embarrassing really, look at our defending for the 3rd, not a fucking clue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our decision making today has been fucking dogshit, fucking fuming with that out there today, you don't concede 3 at home to Swansea, fuming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matip can play, what a day this is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news about Steven Gerrard, the man is back home where he belongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been impressed with what ive seen of Alexander Arnold and Ejaria, future stars for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a crack head https://t.co/BQjSddFNjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We kept a clean sheet with Lucas in our back 4 and he scored a header, got to be some sort of record surely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good experience for the young players again, a 1st appearance for Harry Wilson, Ojo looked lively and Lucas got his 1st goal after 7yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was always gonna be a dodgy fucking game and yeah we didn't play well but we're through and that's all that counts in knockout comps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud to be a red, were moving in the right direction #WeAreLiverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flanners85 Thought he was one of our better performers today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Pogba is just a waste of time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FFArsenal Fucking state of the bastards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got the best https://t.co/gff7Bokvm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFCJosh23 How about we put in a good performance at Old Trafford and got a good point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still unbeaten against the top 6 this season and that's not bad at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrNeale92 Yeah all day United had to win that, would've been been great to hold on but it's a good point and keeps us in good shape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How impressive was Alexander Arnold aswell and Mignolet too, great to have Hendo and Coutinho back also, much better point for us today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I wished we held on but it's a good result today in a tough game where we defended very well, we worked our bollocks off today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good performance defended well, Mignolet probably kept us in it so happy to take a point even though we were winning, good point taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnwez01 Ah man, hope all goes well for Alexander Arnold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been away for a few days sorting a new phone, what's happened to Clyne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when we fuck shit up at old toilet on Sunday, coz we are fucking winning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Graham Taylor, rest in peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mignolet Lovren Moreno Lucas Can and Sturridge are the only players we have that give me a constant fucking headache,  the rest are alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting Playing for Liverpool and Klopp, we can all dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting I know innit, although that would be lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting No its not but were doing well anyway, 2nd in the league challenging and players are coming back, no need for panic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting People don't want much do they fucking hell, last night the whole team were shit, we do have some out of form though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting Yeah until he has a bad game then needs to be sold instantly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Cutting People like that need to give up with football tbh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>