<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[when you slip on the no-slip bathmat in your hotel bathroom and whack your shin on the side of the bathtub 😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to know where this woman went to law school. Anyone who took con law knows about the rational basis t… https://t.co/G3AtRWeie7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awesome =&gt; Pope Francis Takes 12 Refugees Back to Vatican After Trip to Greece https://t.co/lTGH8We994]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering the Armenian Genocide - #oldpost https://t.co/J2Ju11aFqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading out to meet my cousin Kelli &amp; meet her wife for the first time - haven't seen her in like 10 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weeks 4 and 5 of NYC Marathon Training - #oldpost https://t.co/WfFOgtk9Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has literally become the laughingstock of Europe. Check out @itsgreateu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great pic of my friend @AllieHarned protesting at ORD! https://t.co/niib0Zvsq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great time at the Phoenix Open today! So cool to finally see so many top golfers in person! https://t.co/RfUtWfHkHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How likely are foreign terrorists to kill Americans? The odds may shock you  https://t.co/OZopoZ7ZTP via @BI_Science #facts #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely need to go to more golf tournaments. Why haven't I done this sooner? @WMPhoenixOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Volunteer with Pandas in China - #oldpost https://t.co/5C26f5wVfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so wrong https://t.co/mTzoMmCLhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting in line to buy my @WMPhoenixOpen ticket &amp; some guy came &amp; gave me an extra he had for free! Lucky day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the sporting events I've been to in my life, I've never been to a golf tourney...until today! Hello @WMPhoenixOpen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Moving to Washington, D.C.! - #oldpost https://t.co/sTzn89qAPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyGlockner and they didn't really find a conscience...could've voted no in committee vote, this is purely political calculation now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Journalism Brands Where You Find Real Facts Rather Than Alternative Facts via @forbes https://t.co/RD2oNzmnPj #realfacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to understand what Trump and Bannon are up to? Look to the Russian Revolution of 1917 https://t.co/ZTl1rgbpk1 via @qz #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeAbbamonte totally! I was driving back up f/ Tucson tonight at sunset &amp; it was even better than Tuesday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeAbbamonte i landed at sunset Tuesday - it was gorgeous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and there were people who actually thought his election would improve our standing in the world... https://t.co/iybfz0rREw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Game Drive in Awash National Park - #oldpost https://t.co/OcfXDwazsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 6: From Theth to Valbona - #oldpost https://t.co/q1M6xPhVxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also remember back to when the GOP claimed to be the party of morals and family values and patriotism...so much can change in 2 weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember back when I could go for weeks, even months, without even thinking about what the president was up to...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm off social media for like 4 hours and come back to find out Trump has messed things up with Australia!

Australia!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pointless. Both on the HELP Committee, could've voted against her in committee to prevent her getting to full Senat… https://t.co/YintwiIu0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Binder Park Zoo: A Taste of Africa in Michigan - #oldpost https://t.co/THyIOsOaMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DangerousBiz I have the same ones!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in Ukraine... https://t.co/rgtc7XA6Yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skopje: One of the Weirdest Cities I've Ever Visited - #oldpost https://t.co/e1N8wC5Xqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtwdave thanks. hard to stay away. there's just so much going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/IJEu8IXpoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Previewing My Trip to China - #oldpost https://t.co/mV1kcp8Ey3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to get off social media again. Making me feel increasingly hopeless about our future. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtwdave haven't tried one in a while. i've stayed off Twitter almost 48 hrs. No FB since Saturday a.m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[taking a break from my social media hiatus to tweet #ThankYouSally for @SallyQYates standing up for what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Month in a New City - #oldpost https://t.co/ZEZJbJJlzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queuing at Wimbledon - #oldpost https://t.co/4vE8tEnQFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 8: Hiking to the Triangle Border and Back to Kosovo - #oldpost https://t.co/eauoUVnL3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Weekend in San Francisco - #oldpost https://t.co/ifcLZtW1xh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that the #AusOpen is over, I'm taking a digital detox for a week. See y'all again on Super Bowl Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoSeeWrite too bad he seems to have forgotten he ever thought that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #AusOpen has provided a much needed distraction from all the crap happening in the US this week. Thank you Roger, Rafa, Serena, Venus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a point! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer breaks back! 3-all. Wow. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Twitter eggs just liked my last retweet. What's up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Nadal come back? I want more tennis. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was watching replay of 2007 Wimby final before going to bed &amp; announcers were speculating how much longer Roger would play. Crazy. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 am here in Santa Fe and I just woke up to catch the #AusOpen final tied at one set apiece. Perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had planned to start a digital detox today but the #MuslimBan got me too worked up. Will start tomorrow. Now for sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been almost 10 years since I stopped practicing law. This is the first time since then that I wish I still was so I could do more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahPinsker Amy Klobuchar of MN has denounced it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summary: they are already subject to "extreme vetting" #NoBanNoWall #NoMuslimBan https://t.co/Myuqezxxey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am simultaneously appalled at our government for the #MuslimBan and so proud of the people standing up to it! #NotWhoWeAre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers often get a bad rap. These lawyers are awesome! https://t.co/Qq0S0loW1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd stop in Albuquerque - Petroglyphs National Monument. Pretty cool &amp; nice to get out &amp; walk around a bit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the newest state reps in my home state of MN, @IlhanMN, would've been denied entry to the US under Trump's order. #nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First stop in Albuquerque: the Indian Pueblo Cultural Center.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just landed in Albuquerque! 30 minutes early - thx @SouthwestAir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great Ethiopian Run/Walk/Dance Party - #oldpost https://t.co/phm3St5ead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees Detained at U.S. Airports, Prompting Legal Challenges to Trump’s Immigration Order https://t.co/7hKmJVUEvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s executive order on refugees goes way beyond a temporary ban https://t.co/pkkaR3sxPx via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#factsmatter #MuslimBan https://t.co/i9Y4ecOigK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: please don't wear strong perfume/cologne when you fly. You might make the person next to you seriously uncomfortable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the road again...DCA-MDW-ABQ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hasn't lost before the semis at a major in 3 years! #AusOpen #Serena #BestEver https://t.co/acrgIrYBNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisAune no I'm in DC. Flying to Albuquerque this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisAune right but why would you say I'll miss it? Will be up to watch tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisAune what do you mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tennissmash I know, right?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad I got to see it end before boarding my flight! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Serena does it! #23 Kind of a shame it had to come against Venus. But maybe more special then, who knows? #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now on my way to the airport to fly to ABQ...watching the #AusOpen final on the WatchESPN app on my phone. Go Venus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter! Who else is up watching Serena-Venus at the #AusOpen?? #upallnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RealFacts #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/YgczOpfilz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/K5GgdO732y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a big movie person but La La Land was SO good. A much needed escape for 2 hours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we please call it what it is: anti-choice. Not pro-life, not anti-abortion, but anti-choice. https://t.co/w9yXNWCHzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training for the Great Wall Marathon - #oldpost https://t.co/i1QOCv2492]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering the Armenian Genocide - #oldpost https://t.co/J2Ju11aFqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twpolk @maddow @SenFranken they need to pick their battles. DeVos is definitely one worth fighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[raise your hand if you predicted an all-Williams final on one side and a Roger-Rafa final on the other! Love sports! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Rafa #AusOpen https://t.co/MGkyRCvF5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok guys, I have to leave for work in like 15 minutes...can someone break please?? #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg do they enforce that at all levels at the #AusOpen? At #USOpen, fans in the nosebleeds can come/go at any time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big winner of this match is Roger Federer. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dimitrov!! We're going to a 5th set!! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLawTennis no it hasn't. there's a sick fan being tended to in the stands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racheldulitz sorry! I couldn't help it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whenever I hear "special relationship" I think of Hugh Grant's press conference w/ Billy Bob Thornton in Love Actua… https://t.co/lRGsgGDams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes! getting at least 2 more sets of tennis! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm awake! Looking for some good tennis now, Rafa and Dimitrov! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharing the #CuteAnimalTweetOff again. Because we all need a smile today. :) https://t.co/ENFAS0WrMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 real actions you can take after the Women's March and 1 you shouldn't. https://t.co/xOqsFWtik9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG watching #ThisIsUs from Tuesday! Every week just keeps getting better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random Thoughts While Walking Around San Francisco - #oldpost https://t.co/SjNBvibeOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly. It's like equating pro-choice w/ being pro-abortion. No one wants anyone to have an abortion. But they shoul… https://t.co/g4wO50wGoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racheldulitz haha...sorry, I'm a huge Stan fan!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>