<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 true! BUT I wouldn't be shocked if they won on Friday. They have some cray cray fans ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 I don't think #CBBJedward would've been gone. Think they've more of a fan base than we know. Ye, agreed about Calum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimCashel no, don't think so. Think it was immunity until the finale night. Like they've done before ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, did #CBBCalum get the book because he's as boring as watching paint dry? OR cause he went up against #CBBJedward !? ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taught #CBBJamesC had a ticket though to the final of #CBB then why is he part of this eviction? Don't get it ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBB tells #CBBCalum he's boring = Calum going off on one for no fucking reason......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBBianca looks so cut up about #CBBJamie getting the boot ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colleenhoover in my head, I so just heard a whip noise. 'Whooppa!!!' ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ You show em' Colleen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still laughing at #CBBKim saying she's not confrontational. Weren't you dragged outta #CBBÂ  by the scruff by security last week? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBKim so #CBBJamesC said something u didn't like&amp;upset u? So imagine how every1felt when u done it! And ur %100 confrontational!! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneaky exit, for a sneaky bloke ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now #CBBBianca can get back to remembering she has a fella ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJamie looks fucking gutted ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ No one will save you when your pulling a line with another blokes bird. Learn your lessons, fool #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear it was Friday morning two minutes ago ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜¬ðŸ™ˆ #MondayBlues #MondayDreads #ComeBackWeekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBCalum starting a water fight after been told he's boring isn't a bit suspicious ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 towards them. ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How #CBBColleen wasn't pulled off John McQuerick by the security guards is beyond me! Cunt would be eating his balls if I was Coleen ðŸ˜¡ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He did not just throw the menopause into this ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ Get off the stand you fat, snot eating vile pig ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ fugly little cunt #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking cringe for you #CBBCalum ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 at the start I taught she was alright. But no, I just see her as a bully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['you smoke&amp;eat to much' says John McQuerick2 #CBBColleen John, were'd you get the big belly on you? All the snot eating u do, is it? ðŸ˜¬ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBAustin Hello pot, meet Kettle ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ You was only short of staring an argument with your shadow when in that house! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Yeah! Just calling the lads pricks&amp;moaning about them as per usual!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBNicola you'd know all about pricks. Didn't you marry one that cheated on you? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how #CBBCalum is all 'Don't b in woman's faces' 2 #CBBJedward but stayed quiet when #CBBSpencer was shouting in #CBBColleens  #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying #CBBJedward is intimidating is like saying  a puppy is gonna rip your throat out. Just doesn't work ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJedward you scummy fucks! Change your sheets, FFS ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real battle of wits!!! #CBBJedward V #CBBCalum ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJedward has finally grown a pair and are fighting back. Don't know how well they'll do, but there doing it ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG, #CBBJedward gave #CBBColleen her family letter and she bleeding nominates them! Cringing for her! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, #CBBNicola you don't have anything #CBBJedward want. Now if they walked in on #CBBCalum that's another story.... #CBB ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor, #CBBJamesC just love him. Not a bother on him not getting his letter so someone else could ðŸ˜ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBColleen should've picking #CBBJamie #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay #CBBJedward calm it down a little ðŸ˜¬ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knew #CBBKim would out do #CBBSpeidi fucking morto for them ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #AlwaysTheLoserNeverTheWinner #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if #CBBSpeidi was next2go &amp; #CBBKim beat them. #CBBSpencer wouldn't be a bit impressed ðŸ˜‚ He'd have a shit freak! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its girls like #CBBBianca that give us girls a bad name.Soon as them #CBB doors closed her inhabitants went out the window with her knickers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blair witch ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #Jedward #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor #CBBJamesC looks lost compared to everyone else ðŸ˜ž #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eh, was #CBBJamesC &amp; #CBBCalum not giving a part in the task?? ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, #CBBNicola is having a serious case of PMS'in the last few weeksðŸ™ˆ As #MickyFlannagan would say,she's creating an atmosphere #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJedward may be head wreckers, but that was funny as fuck saying that too #CBBNicola  ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #GoFuckYourself #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBNicola harping on #CBBJedward again. Please sing us another another tune! Cranky bitch #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf was that #CBBJessica !? Practicing what you'd do if you won? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Rona for real in #Emmerdale !? Swift kick in the nuts is what Pierce would be getting. Handsy bastard ðŸ˜¡ðŸ”ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin gets a smack of a bus, nearly dies, and is up dressed and eating a pie? I get a cold and can't leave the bed4a week ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #Eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denise is gonna think Mick and Whitney are pulling a line #Eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it half seven yet!!?? #eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schofe @hollywills you guys should get tattoos, but4charity. Make ppl sponsor you's. Like TextSanta ðŸ˜˜ @thismorning #ThisMorning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Right? He's definitely her muppet master. You can practically see the stings it's getting that bad! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is #CBBHeidi running after #CBBSpencer like a lap dog? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U couldn't have a proper conversation with #CBBJamie ?Eh, how abt all them times U were locking lips with him?U could've done it then #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The look #CBBNicola gave #CBBBianca when that video started ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Brothers bit on the inside ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ There's an innuendo in there somewhere ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBStacy their names combined makes #CBBJedward there both not called Jedwards. There's only one jedward, not a pair. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There she's goes again, #CBBNicola bullying #CBBJedward YES there annoying as fuck. But so are you with your bullying antics! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBBianca really let herself down. Been with that sleaze ball when youve a fella.&amp;saying yous love each either? Stop that&amp;Give over ðŸ–•ðŸ» #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god, Whitney ðŸ˜žðŸ˜ž #Eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wan the #Eastenders crowd coming together!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone slap the shit outta that prick child in #Eastender !?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus the drama is 90 in #Eastenders tonight ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No fuckin way! #CBBSpeidi slaggin #CBBJamesC &amp; #CBBColleen on der careers!?Is it cause dey have1&amp;U don't?Poxy dried up reality stars! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wore it better? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #ManBun #MissTrunchable #CBB #CBBKim https://t.co/vJSvtexMtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh #CBBSpeidi build a fucking bridge and get over it! Someone voted you, that's the fucking game. Grow a pair and move on. Saps ðŸ˜¡ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBKim 'Who can't hear u,your becomin the town crier #CBBStacy ' eh, Kim. Pot, meet kettle. U haven't shut up since you went in der ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor #CBBJamesC does look lost when sitting near an argument ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Told yeah ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #BusCrash #Eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, showing so much of #Eastenders outside of the square usually means drama. Big ass crash coming up. #Emmerdale style. ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any1else think Whitney and Mick r getting a little close in #Eastenders ? &amp;does she Eva shut up moaning? U owe money out, stop spending it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Has to be done ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder was #CBBHeidi spraying #CBBSpencer with an anti knob head spray there? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Loved the way most of them nose dived into it, as soon as they seen it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 I know!! The puppies over the stripper, any day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJamesC looks like he'd like to be having a root canal rather then be there with that 'entertainment ' ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time the housemates trigged what's going on ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 I think so too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not der fan,but has2b said #Jedward has become the house punchin bag.Any1whos pissed off just takes it out on dem cus der so softðŸ˜¬ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBNicola y r u justifyin who u voted4?It was UR vote. Although,u wouldn't feel guilt if u made the right choice #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO NOT call #CBBJames, a piece of shit! That will, for sure get you voted out #CBBSpeidi Simple drunk fuck ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaand the real #CBBSpeidi comes out to play! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else think #CBBStacy is the whitest black person ever? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whys #CBBJedward (1of them) molesting a strawberry, while looking in a mirror? ðŸ™ˆ #CBB #JustWhenYouThinkTheyCantGetWeirder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats shockin that none of them turned around for him!Are u's4fuckin real. Talk about letting talent slip through your fingers #TheVoiceUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBStacy must be handing around with #CBBKim too much ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #CBB #TakeYourMeds #CBBJessica does have a point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't like #CBBJedward BUT #CBBStacy is so only going off at them over her guilt for fucking #CBBChloe under the bus. Fuck off twat #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBChloe does #CBBJamesC look like the Ibiza kinda bloke!? He's got class. You've got buggers on your fingers. See the different? ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone think that #coronationstreet is mental violent tonight? ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else think #CBBChloe is acting like Ilsa fisher in wedding crashes over #CBBCalum ? ðŸ™ˆ #IwillFindYou #CBB #WeddingCrashers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBJedward are obviously heavily medicated every day. It's the only answer as to why there so bat shit crazy ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plz JESUS tell me #CBBKim isn't comparing herself2Jesus!?Ye,he went around callin ppl bitches as well.She needs2b fuckin hospitalisedðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone saying #CBBJamesC should wear the costume&amp;lighten up please give it a rest. He's an older man, with an actual career may I add #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Piece of raw bread' where's #CBBKim From? Oliver? #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 She'll go off on one tonight no doubt ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #CBBkim buzzing 'There conspiring against me' ? She fucking started on everyone one by one! Get back on your meds, you Lula ðŸ™ˆ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 she won't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Aw Hun, you've no idea! But she's the biggest one of them all ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Chinless wonders' 'Chicken livered shits' seriously? Your so graceful in your old age #CBBKim ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever #CBBKim is taking in #CBB I want some ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ cause she lives in her own fucking lala land ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And all that 'I don't know what's going on, or what I've done' wouldn't fly with me! You know exactly what your doing ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry I wouldn't b taking abuse off #CBBKim If the dried up hag got in my face like that,she b removin my foot from her hole! #CBB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>