<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmucinc I work for the NSW Govt. Do they pass on a business tax cut to my family, too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orangutans Are Now Looking for Mates on ‘Tinder’ https://t.co/QRGUnDYCK5 via @thescienceofus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One wearying week on, 95% of my Twitter feed is outrage at Trump. I'm proud of every last one of you magnificent motherfuckers. Fight on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dungeon ceilings — a flaw in design: https://t.co/GGpF0aylPq #dnd #rpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere, John Shirley frantically outlines a new edition of "A Song Called Youth," due out shortly before his rel… https://t.co/fuVu9VfQoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers seize hotel systems, lock guests in rooms. So much for fire safety. https://t.co/2VbYibu5ZF via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PETA petitions GW to ban fur textures on #Warhammer minis. #WTAF https://t.co/Mc79c80rM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This powerful Twitter account is sharing the names of Jewish refugees the US turned away in 1939 | Mic https://t.co/F9T5ooer1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia zoo urges people to catch deadly spiders as antidote... https://t.co/ODFrdzkUJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A long-overdue opioid revolution is finally here https://t.co/H3cVIVloYK via @SmithsonianMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hydrogen Has Been Turned To Metal, And It's About To Change The World https://t.co/H7tiKX4GPo via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I want to buy a Kinetic Algernon. https://t.co/qJTPMgSA2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like @cubicle7 may've picked up the licence for #Warhammer FRP 4e: https://t.co/jgWOQAjxnq #wfrp #rpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Australia Day message: America has "no better friend." Why do I feel like we'll never see our mower again? https://t.co/X9YzgnKEFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know about Australia thanks to supermassive black holes https://t.co/WQ1eTjUUDy via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to think that Goya would approve. https://t.co/qDdyu7lOdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DnD5e players on Fantasy Grounds: ~58%. #PFRPG: ~12%. Knew 5e was well-received, but surprised just how well. #rpg https://t.co/hVZ693fLpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine learning could finally crack the 4,000-year-old Indus script https://t.co/aoXoU8Y62C via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fred Nile denied visa for Trump inauguration - The Sydney Morning Herald #nswpol #auspol https://t.co/ks4mpexMd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The demon voice that can control your smartphone https://t.co/Fjge2zjOfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blood-repellent materials: A new approach to medical implants https://t.co/TNxoDCJzKF via @@ColoradoStateU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Alien Style of Deep Learning Generative Design” by @IntuitMachine https://t.co/1Z3GcHTjmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Pakistani police rescue 24 from organ trafficking gang https://t.co/aBtlbqdErb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - US military tests swarm of mini-drones launched from jets https://t.co/FjvalUWxTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultrafast Camera Captures 'Sonic Booms' of Light for First Time https://t.co/zQLyNbS2h5 via @SPACEdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Map of American Lynchings That Spans More Than a Century  https://t.co/2ZvJYJz4Tn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad Squiddo's commemorates Phoolan Devi with a 3-set of 28mm minis. https://t.co/9BKhIO7GAv https://t.co/l13pkRWEYO https://t.co/9zmOv3MIGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine by me. #punchingnazis https://t.co/qqh5HH99pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists make significant breakthrough in fight against antibiotic resistance https://t.co/FGjyEXhdUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stairway to Heaven, played on koto and shakuhachi (bamboo flute): https://t.co/IOILk0IIkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. I had no idea. Good for her. https://t.co/d7YM8i9eDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've discussed Canberra's mystical weirdness with regard to #UnknownArmies before. It's also a town chock full of c… https://t.co/WiiIsTQcTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphene’s sleeping superconductivity awakens https://t.co/QdHLA0gMte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than one day in, and I'm already sick of the taste of popcorn. https://t.co/cg0ZnVtwgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lincoln Administration Turned Down a Chance to Populate the United States With Elephants https://t.co/8hSpftDSJc via @mental_floss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwardjolmos My sincerest condolences. He was truly a master of his craft, and in my own small way, I'll miss him, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Island Life Drove Lemur Evolution https://t.co/S8b85vUomt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know a black hole lurks at the center of the Milky Way, but seeing will be believing. https://t.co/YEkiYpQ2s4 via @airspacemag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Karen road to Nhill | SBS Topics | https://t.co/Mgk5Xb08in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if the NSW Libs didn't have Bronwyn to police socialism and save them all from falling like dominoes.… https://t.co/9D867TFWAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackmonkeygames Start general, describing salient features. Encourage players to prompt for details. Let their attention guide the scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, an explanation of strange African 'fairy circles'? https://t.co/WZ8BywCAyM via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baird quits as NSW premier. Dammit, leadership spills still get my heart racing. #nswpol https://t.co/UzgDsV9xQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horses more likely to kill in Australia than snakes or spiders. Even the introduced fauna wants you dead. https://t.co/NKVlMSpawO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stellar Discovery: Scientists Find New Galaxy Type https://t.co/3eVfpHB17o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 101 Most Recommended Call of #Cthulhu Scenarios #coc #rpg https://t.co/bm7d9Y6IfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face of 9,500-Year-Old Man Revealed for First Time https://t.co/dueh2uGbp9 via @NatGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring the beautiful old maps of countries that never existed https://t.co/MMqIQ7Ch9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much like working for a Senator, I'd imagine, but with fewer tantrums and more straightforward accounting procedure… https://t.co/qvBLOWiwek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some warriors wield swords or axes. A great halfling warrior defeats his foes with cheese." #torchbearer #rpg #ettincon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our map for #Torchbearer #RPG. I feel kinda spoilt. #ettincon https://t.co/zf6X9LkNcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Of course clerics are awesome. You'd be pretty hardarse, too, if you had to shave your tonsure with a mace." #ettincon #rpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explorers find disease-cursed City of the Monkey God and nearly lose their faces to flesh-eating parasite https://t.co/tl1xJqm4HW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when algorithms design a concert hall? The stunning Elbphilharmonie https://t.co/ufHwPVa5DW via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hachette Announces A New Gary Gygax Biography In Graphic Novel Format https://t.co/cw5zULcma9 #RPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paleontologists classify ancient strange cone-shaped sea creatures https://t.co/hSGejYOBzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM: "The runes state the altar's consecrated to the god Murdah."

P1: "The god of healing and love?"

P2: "And unintended irony?"

#ettincon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[King Tut's Dagger Came from Space, Discover Researchers https://t.co/HPiIwVml0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alien-looking shrimp of the desert appear in Central Australia after flooding rains https://t.co/4u39oNlMiD via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's AI Has Reinvented the Master Language | Gil Fewster https://t.co/YzSsbAjMKV via @feeonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA releases footage of Huygens' landing on Titan https://t.co/75ZVenBpyl via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Brazilian Vampire Bats Have Started Feeding on Humans for the First Time https://t.co/d8bSKG3xTV via @ScienceAlert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blacker than black: How the world's darkest material is being used https://t.co/8PvkG5G7AO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This desolate English path has killed more than 100 people https://t.co/ld4C6DGn57 via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lasers activate killer instinct in mice https://t.co/FKuWKWmQ4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ancient retroviruses emerged half a billion years ago https://t.co/SrSzS234yU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Chinese Were Unspeakable https://t.co/ApCOnWglDy via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What, with our agile government and world-class NBN? https://t.co/hjrfxWZh4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pluto Has Towers of Ice 1,600 Feet Tall https://t.co/JyJHTahfeR via @motherboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Ronin 2017 Releases Announced https://t.co/yeZFzM04Nl #rpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alexa Told Me Where The Bodies Are Buried" https://t.co/SEeiVN8shX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mforbeck @BundleHolding Shouldn't that be a SPATE of Murder Parties? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit recurs. https://t.co/0msVAgmSkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers design one of the strongest, lightest materials known https://t.co/yH989YnXIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commonwealth Ombudsman launches Centrelink investigation #auspol https://t.co/DSlJmojetl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Ration days again': cashless welfare card ignites shame https://t.co/XCikkz6UHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat Covered in Matted Fur Looks Like He's Dragging a Carpet Until He's Completely Shaved https://t.co/AkXEuwDCMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth I’s 
long-lost skirt to go on display after being found on a church altar in Herefordshire https://t.co/YvvEMa9ocZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really good summary thread on the current catastrophic #Centrelink failure. https://t.co/DCNFczQRzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colliding stars will light up the night sky in 2022 https://t.co/lTSGlnWpq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ‘Sherlock of the library’ cracked the case of Shakespeare’s identity https://t.co/FDEvuWdsZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 3,500-year-old Greek tomb may expose the origins of Western civilization https://t.co/l1H6EIQ6ph via @SmithsonianMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Russians Imagined the Year 2017 In 1960 https://t.co/kEE95FzCSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Carpenter Is Fighting With Internet Nazis Over His Cult Classic They Live https://t.co/AuGpKb8I96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shadow lands: Europe mapped by sunset shadows - Imgur https://t.co/t1HkqeNcyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The very idea of chicken psychology is strange to most people.” https://t.co/J0tOnA3pMC via @TelegraphSci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure whether @FT is arguing against Bitcoin, or cheerleading for the gold standard: https://t.co/Vb0l1xUs9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't just wipe out Neanderthals by competing for resources, but because their voices were as annoying as hell: https://t.co/okoRRB4KSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a very "Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?" vibe about this. https://t.co/w52wEe7xPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calm down, Dave. French-language brain takes a little while to engage. "Grenade gel douche" isn't nearly as horrifi… https://t.co/NNBEoUXAmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I love Twitter. https://t.co/YPMxNXP7bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the off-tune recorder/accordion duet nearby, I suspect I've woken in a Sierra game. This time, I hope, I warrant Leisure Suit Larry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting in a takeaway in Penrith. Sofi Tukker's DRINKEE is on endless loop. I feel like I'm trapped in a McDonald's recruitment ad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the British Empire Reunited Today? https://t.co/zDWSd0n29U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you say the word butter? App tracks decline of UK's varied dialects - ABC News https://t.co/kFBzomvhuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama orders sanctions against Russia. Goody. I was starting to miss the Cold War. https://t.co/mzaA4ndLrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so hot out that Satan offered to sell me HIS soul for air-conditioning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, FFS. https://t.co/GB5XfMMrMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tad patronising, but good advice nonetheless. https://t.co/Yzdm4bSGt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You've come a long way, baby. Now, let's see you fly." — journalist George Plimpton (recounting graffiti atop a Br… https://t.co/ZHobUhuSUl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>