<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall: Over 150 Labels &amp; Artists Join Us in Donating Friday’s... https://t.co/5svfVm11VX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's coming? https://t.co/oDlgVV5Z3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think wrestling is fake? Watch Seamus deliver 10 over arm chops to the chest and STFU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The WWE Royal Rumble 2017 is an absolute masterclass in video editing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright! That Chris Jericho/Kevin Owens Vs. Roman Reigns promo bit was some of the best editing I have ever seen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems that you can't just dismiss a persons opinion, you have to dismantle it with facts. Real facts, that is...... https://t.co/z0kmw02l67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because other people do it, doesn't make it right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going in on The Royal Rumble! 
If you're a naysayer, you just don't understand and I will happily explain it... https://t.co/U0Cjs0VQwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I know any Boomtown bookers or people in that loop?
I have an American friend who is one of the best fire... https://t.co/fHkwXESC9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just scored this awesome pair of shoes for £20 in the Wood Green Traid! They also have a bunch of gorgeous SuperDry coats in there for £25!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May start having to play video games again! (Probably won't get past the jump tutorial.) https://t.co/VHBgsYWQzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiddleywinks next then. https://t.co/TkiZKV3tB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galactic Empire - Star Wars - The Imperial March https://t.co/qtJZUvS03u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear friends... If you, like me, are struggling to deal, please remember that there are things such as this in... https://t.co/jBMctcrTEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hip Hop heads... I can't stop listening to this album, Danny Brown is fully genius! https://t.co/ZU69C5f4o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooooh! Week off work and BFI drops this! https://t.co/qHGjZJEDBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out I'm a Giggs fan. This is a TUNE!!! https://t.co/8u71RglvmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm done sharing Drumpf stuff, there is just too much of it and my jaw is in danger of smashing through... https://t.co/cWGngqAxCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those with more than a passing interest... https://t.co/Jir9z3WZEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is allowing Trump access to the UK a tacit approval of his actions?
Oh, your a racist and a liar? Yes mate, come on 'round for tea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit! I posted two spurious 'news' reports tonight.
Watch out for lies and half truths masquerading as facts on... https://t.co/Ao6SJNOaoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Presidential level, an inferred incitement to violence should be treated in the same way as an actual incitement! https://t.co/HQVpzr1Xdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is necessary to acknowledge all available moves before sacrificing your piece. 
Can anyone offer a deeper... https://t.co/LqW2TI4qJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has a distinct likelihood of going crazy. Please exercise caution y'all. https://t.co/dkSFGadgK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's hard to do bad chips like, but these were, soggy in the worst way... I don't know what it was constructed... https://t.co/OFWeID9Kv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode 10 of The Pengest Munch contains a TUNE!
Watch through the revue or jump to 4.43 for the track. https://t.co/WM31fXRL0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took me ages to figure out where to start this tune when mixing it in! https://t.co/8ND28GZMA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New game!
Comment on how you met me using only alternative facts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, California doesn't even want to be part of America anymore! https://t.co/OqCvIXH8OJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait... The what? https://t.co/gz33nyA6DZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[t may have been Camelot for Jack and Jacqueline
But on the Che Guevara highway filling up with gasoline
Fidel... https://t.co/GTfEyt1opH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian Dub Foundation - Free Satpal Ram
As relevant to anyone who is imprisoned for defending themselves against... https://t.co/Bv35LNM5yK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking Dub War! https://t.co/VzhcJ7odKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking Fight Songs!!! https://t.co/kzOk0xU6Sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a Crass!!! https://t.co/Cw3Jm21PMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? https://t.co/Qe2iMfH4YV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'ma take it through some genres now... https://t.co/Y3CvZElEFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'ma take it through some genre's now...
https://t.co/5ImPUW8sc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned... Grime is Punk! https://t.co/htUkuIOZgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And where would we be without the Ken Nedys? 
Napalm Death - Nazi Punks FUCK OFF
About as ferocious a diatribe... https://t.co/xGba4ea0Nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full fucking bore revolution noise...
Atari Teenage Riot!!! https://t.co/b2BtdaW6dM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As any good DJ should, I'ma take the ferocity back a step to let you catch a breath...
Front 242 - Moldavia... https://t.co/Gi4saqnSSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to Industrial Metal... This... THIS is the the template!
Fuck that pusilanimous version, this is... https://t.co/zShtUtxri4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I am concerned, this is one of the greatest songs ever EVER!
For me, this ranks up there with Marlena... https://t.co/N6dS8lu4o7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'ma spam your feed with Industrial Metal tonight!
Kill Wighty! https://t.co/geyGUPQlNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolting Cocks - (Let's Get) Physical https://t.co/0oq1PNTseq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know the phenomenon that is Ministry and it's rise and fall and rise and fall and etc... Get to know... https://t.co/CMT3Xggj5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Ya Think I'm Sexy - Revolting Cocks https://t.co/NSF0gXBIfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a Wonderful World - Ministry cover version... https://t.co/9nov4oic6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to cover versions... Ministry are the masters! https://t.co/2TxiWZfcEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Wish there was something real, wish there was something true']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Nedys... As relevant now as they have ever been! https://t.co/9JQyYG3tsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brief sojourn through my mindset right now...
&lt;3 https://t.co/gSvqY3PXH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got hit on by three really attractive customers today! 
I wish I could bottle 'too mentally unstable to date at... https://t.co/LTfrJWAT3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female Legislators Unveil 'Male Ejaculation Bill' Forbidding The Disposal Of Unused Semen https://t.co/U6uxRMZTYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New from *anker. The 2.4g Vertical mouse.
Seems like a reasonable position for the male music producers hand to... https://t.co/JUWZNfnDC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to dissuade my housemate from feeding somebody else's kitten whilst battling my own urges to feed somebody... https://t.co/D1TazlInWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best things about festivals becoming a viable business opportunity is that niche line-ups are fully... https://t.co/oGuaARjjdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouting 'No he fucking hasn't you TWAT!' At your computer screen counts as constructive criticism right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Day of Patriotic devotion'?!?!
Bring on the 2 minute hate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have known a few people with this horrendous condition. All have been heavy smokers. https://t.co/oFtpS8Nzny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooooh, anybody up for this? https://t.co/lwByNFiXuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fully fabulous night THAT was! So many friends getting down and dirty in an amazing venue. The decor and... https://t.co/GL2EGxO4JZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, this is Ian McKellen at London Womens march carrying a Jean Luc Picard *Facepalm* sign!
Ledge! https://t.co/GSkh6mtOMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It turns out that saying 'Adam Fs' dad is Alvin Stardust' no longer blows peoples minds! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two electronic drumkits, a keyboard, a two deck scratching table and Beardyman's huge loops and F/X... https://t.co/mxruxfWU3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night... Perverts paradise! ;D https://t.co/XuJMQGfsig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you're music hunting for a pounding house set and you discover a deep groove, off kilter, bongo monster... https://t.co/g32ZzK19z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New game for you!
I'm music shopping tonight so may only play intermittently. 
Try to guess each others films? https://t.co/TBmM8yY9lN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat owners 'more likely to be into bondage and BDSM than everyone else' https://t.co/EzzHByMlvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Muppets know the score yo! https://t.co/MJMlxOcKBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subversion Noir/Hard On family... https://t.co/uP0Yoxl9DH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously now... if you're a music lover, I urge you to listen to this! 
Please spend 4 minutes of your time... https://t.co/1RrSFT8h0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, my Ay-Mayzing Mum sent me this... https://t.co/N1t4s1GksF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is interested, the best piece of music I heard today was Ibrahim Maalouf - Y Ha La (live) on Cerys' 6... https://t.co/UsE5ctrxUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment where you drink from a half full can of beer that you inadvertently dropped a cigarette butt in and... https://t.co/eP7lWvvPAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Dorian Blacks' recommendation...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's unlikely but, can any of my friends recommend any recent, floor destroying, house music I could play... https://t.co/PFM5QqZYPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw an advert for a paid site and thought you might be interested in teh free version... https://t.co/NSMUx6J1wY https://t.co/IYXmQb6Dm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can barely wait until 3D interactive video and haptic feedback herald the demise of zoo's! https://t.co/osKzytiPxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh FFS! Shitport now has a main category called 'Future House'! How the eff is it the most popular online dance music shop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Daniel's Releases Whiskey-Infused Coffee https://t.co/bQAlKixbIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought a ticket for the Brixton event on the 23 March. Anyone else up for this? https://t.co/P4j4sEMczr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This recent 'a friend is typing a comment' dialogue box hingmy.
1. An ingenious way to suck you even further in... https://t.co/LsxioZR45L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shall definitely exercise caution from now on! 0.0 https://t.co/bFzAxuzcWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not just me saying it... https://t.co/kni4KoUHrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a stunning piece of propaganda. https://t.co/U5pzLJg0Sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately this will change nothing. :( https://t.co/z00YWfwc4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... Today, a lady is shopping with her child in tow; she chooses two items, one large, one small and hands them... https://t.co/qnCAEpXm2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many terms before Zucks is President? https://t.co/Z3BvJnu3B6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Take your broken heart, make it into art.' &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Service Broadcasting are brilliant! Listen here and then buy their albums so that they can afford to make... https://t.co/NdjmnsaTdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a bath and need some music? https://t.co/A0nTBmmQUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know what the definitive childrens Sci-Fi puppet show was?
Fucking 'Star Fleet' that's what!
Unparalleled! https://t.co/Ha7VeKaj64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of several shitstorms just waiting to happen! https://t.co/THMRk8VkBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS! Is it the 80's again? RAGE!!! https://t.co/cRp8NFSZVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the many reasons that David Bowies' output resonates so deeply with me are the lyrics to 'Space Oddity'.... https://t.co/BsAjcQxGsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They tell me Son, we want you, be elusive, but don't walk far
For we're breaking in the new boys, deceive your... https://t.co/cDOqAbg39P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any DnB heads who havn't heard Lazarus... Check this out!!! https://t.co/Ahswvb8sTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seemingly, you must play the game to attain success... 
Fuck the game! 
Be an ARTIST! &lt;3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>