<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Yep, can show you multiple letters refusing a referral until after they have been on an SSRI first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarydaly @juneshannon The codeine and benzos arent completely blameless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annf32 Oxycotton, is that Dot's long lost brother ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Or when Psychiatrists refuse to accept referrals until they have been medicated first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dualireland The same if not worse, hours are longer here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo Did mine saying he has a tiny weiner make it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afneil @brianmlucey Does that mean that for every executive order he signs he must rescind the previous 2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Velorooms @KeiraBronte Roubaix and flatter races when weight not as much an issue definitely. Any substantial climbs though no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faustonef @ulif @MedSportSci @Digger_forum @IlCobra21 Dunno about that, rats and sinking ships etc.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighNoonNT @ciarakellydoc I hate to say it but GH is right ! Some ear drops for wax have hydrogen peroxide !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeflonDub @ulif WRT Froome, lets just say I'm not a believer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedSportSci @ulif @Digger_forum Maybe because they don't weight 800g more now ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulif @Digger_forum And that day cannot come too soon, at best useless, at worst a stooge for elements working behind the scenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squinteratn ?Ye bleedin West Brit ye ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Digger_forum The UCI needs to comment on this, if true an absolute disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a weekend, I would like to dedicate this song to @realDonaldTrump and his team https://t.co/0ndxbviFd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulif I am friendly with one rider in particular and it's entirely for the tax, image rights otherwise would be heavily taxed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulif Weather, ease of access, proximity of other cyclists to train. Many reasons that aren't dodgy. Drugs/motors could be sourced anywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of GPs support legalising medicinal cannabis https://t.co/VSNOXwGlXB via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjohngalloway Good luck and hope all goes well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewBloch @WalleyRay That couldn't be @realDonaldTrump the hands are too big and his gut isn't bursting out of the suit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrPsych @DermotBannon Feck, he's not is he #didntdoit #nobodysawme #cantproveathing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrPsych Don't like the extension from the outside, inside looks fantastic though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpperGISurg @realDonaldTrump No of 9/11 hijackers who would have been affected by this, Zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@140CharTerror The image of my Eevee, looks so happy there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farah Mo you came from chaos and have been honoured by your country. Banning you from USA is a disgrace. Praying for you and your family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReadaCronin So true, its shameful Work with and have worked with so many dedicated muslim docs propping up our health service, this stinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc Good luck with show, off cycling buy will catch it later. Kids are ok with bags and HPV vaccine saves lives (my tuppence)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newschambers The greatest fighters had the greatest opponents, losing no shame and looking forward to epic no III]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosspeaks And his wife don't forget  !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fettygriffin @frankieboyle Nice girl very shy and over protected as a kid, mother literally dragged her onto flight to UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorphinney Stay here, we love your tweets and thoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc @BrendanCourtney @NewstalkFM Huge bags but neither of my kids have any complaints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ibrahim_M_ Met and worked with many great medics from these countries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankieboyle The most vociferous anti abortion family i know forced their daughter to have one, rank hypocrisy but there you go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffflow It was a Raleigh road ace 531c tubing, nice bike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My racing bike circa 1990 ! I loved that bar tape 👽 https://t.co/MJNsKZnh5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My race bike from 1990, I just loved that bar tape :) 👽💃💥 https://t.co/MkhcVjasoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveRaynerFund @Jakerscott14 @dan_gardner96 @matthew_teggart Good luck, such a great organisation and massive legacy for DR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My lovely if daft dogs at Gormonstown beach https://t.co/Jr3qRgiAB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AddictionsPMC It'll take more than this summer to shift all the dead wood unfortunately :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffflow @vayerism Big pecs or plastic boobs with white teef and an orange hue (or so I'm told ....)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AddictionsPMC Klopp the right man in the right place at the right time. Just needs, and will get time ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cyclopunk Well done all, sure some disappointment at missing the podium but all good solid rides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pariswheels @lukascph 92k and hilly efforts with club done ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorbenlfc @Robbie9Fowler Such a legend, named my youngest after him ;) #Robbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkNutrition Its a state of mind rather than a chemical detox, wouldnt say no such thing but definitely misrepresented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowtown and other stories, an adventure in pain ;) #VCB https://t.co/9VB8Kwrqe5 https://t.co/ePc2iaOobG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IzzyKamikaze Horrific just horrific #NeverForget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens Cant doze off without admitting I was not being entirely serious (apart from the Lfc bits ;) ) Love the show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davisszef @tomhappens Traore won the champions league with us, talent comes in mysterious packages ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens Not sung with the same soul though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens Love me for a reason makes my heart sing every time I hear it, up there with Big Fun's classic 90s dance tracks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davisszef @tomhappens A good run and a few slips by Chelski and this year could still be ours !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davisszef @tomhappens But eternally believing that we will suceed #YNWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens What about some classics? Like Westlife or early Boyzone? Before they sold out like??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SvenPres @EuroAthletics This is a good initiative and the panel as is looks credible and experienced. Tough job and I wish them well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankieboyle He thought that because his weiner was too small to penetrate it wasnt really rape....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheball French??? Hitting the ales early there lads #Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukascph @Caoimhin78 @TheRaceRadio The boy who cried wolf !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caoimhin78 @lukascph @TheRaceRadio Thats or else he's selling a story without having much to back it up, still can't believe its major prob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Digger_forum Coming from where he did with very few new signings Klopp has done superbly, has my full support FWIW #YNWA Agree fully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Digger_forum But TBF you don't believe anyone in any sport is clean, do you? #HonestQuestion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc 1 tea and 1 Americano already, will make a cappuccino when I get a chance !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc That will be sunday when he orders the tide to stop ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet @spillaneda No chance, even he realises his teeney hands means a teeney weiner 🤗]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc Nah, just votes taken off women and non motorists banned from roads ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DervalORourke @eosull Looks like Trump is not the only one to favour middle aged white men in suits !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElsebethYNWA @bambula The Orange goblin with yellow hair and abnormally small hands !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner Did they have to widen the door so he could get his lardy arse through?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclist No, Just No. Looks like was based on the design of a 1950's American Coupe ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@140CharTerror They are still very pretty :) You see better kit at a local B race these days though !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimesSport @140CharTerror @DickinsonTimes Waste members money on spin doctors when they can't be bothered to spend money on proper records]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eurosport @SkyIreland Added my voice, myself and friends already looking into alternative to Sky which will give access to Eurosport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Velorooms Do you remember the Tour de Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary "I'm worth it" Harneys legacy (also with HSE/FAS) HSE faces €350m bill for breaking agreement with consultants  https://t.co/2ovBpYoZ92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Digger_forum I feel Nicolas makes a genuine and honest effort to discuss and explain things, lives and works in a corrupt sport enviroment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[95% of the reason I keep @SkyIreland is to get @Eurosport if its going time to move on, #homeofcycling https://t.co/Q2TQjEzgvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government signs off on €2.2m salary top-ups for TDs and senators https://t.co/n9NNetNgto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevPharmacist The formality and appropriateness of contacting people via sm is new to me and changes all the time, never sure how to react]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamhboney1 Thats some size of an arse you are carrying then !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScalareSorpasso @KevCawley Get ya, been there. Made massive changes myself and working out far better than I could ever have expected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens Something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScalareSorpasso @KevCawley Work is over rated ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesFinch @Suz_cc TBF she could be a darts player ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GTCost It works to an extent in the likes of Switzerland, not an outlandish suggestion for many or at least some subjects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffflow @TeflonDub Phil Phil is that you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeflonDub @ffflow When it the last day - 1 we can all start to relax !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TourDeJose @mewmewmew13 Make us a cuppa tea there luv and dont worry your pretty head about the hard stuff #UCI #OfficialPolicy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angusde @docsuzy Scotland doesnt pretend to be a united collection of seperate countries though, does it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Hutch @nedboulting Is this a form of haiku ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@140CharTerror Never heard of her until now :) Real cycling fan there, prob thinks Beryl Burton was a brand of marmalade #HoHum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vayerism Ive heard worse reasons !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vinthevet @cooper_m @PaulKimmage Multiple national champion, top 10 in the World Championships, Olympian, multiple GT's and classics #Elite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@festinagirl Sure it was only the wimmins worlds, Olympics, Giro, TDF she won. Its not like it was "proper" mens cycling ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vayerism Shes a strong woman and shouldnt have been sidelined as she was, deserves to be listened to and respected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjohngalloway Strange situation where leaders of both main parties not tested by election and both seem a bit oblivious to reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffflow @lukascph @bikejourno Any way time for a spin ;) Can't waste a few hours free :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffflow @lukascph @bikejourno Having unelected tossers like Tush commenting doesn't help either !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukascph @bikejourno @ffflow I still think once reality of Brexit dawns that it will be reversed, may be wishful thinking on my part though]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>