<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @WSJ i know it was supposed to be a joke but I really do believe he could shoot someone and his supporters would cheer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @WSJ the comments on the original tweet are so telling. and frightening. DJT is 'just being honest.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephensWSJ @FoxNewsInsider I am blown away by the lengths some of you people will go to to excuse the inexcusable. Brainwashed. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump shut up already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump because the Boston order doesn't address the nation, only Massachusetts. Cant believe you need this shit explained to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabethforma i have been unsure about this, afraid a resistance could backfire, but I have decided that it's better to go down swinging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump fear is the only tool left in your sad little arsenal. turn on your tv. we aren't afraid of you. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean Thank you. This is something that needs to be said daily, until they get it. *We* are not in the minority here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cootercarver @GovHowardDean is that what Bernhard told you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebonstorm @realDonaldTrump it is their choice to continue on in a dysfunctional marriage. we should not have to pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLastWord @Lawrence I think this on pretty much an hourly basis. Then I do some angry coloring. https://t.co/e5GpM5KXfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump he is a real judge, I assure you. but you are still a fake president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PaulRyanIn4Words  puts party before country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald not to mention counterproductive. @KellyannePolls will be crowing about this all weekend. The media should brace itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews seriously Bernie, even though I agree with you, shut up already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steph_bello @VanJones68 its the pro-life Hispanics that hurt the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothypmurphy for now, for now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natemcdermott @KFILE  if she hadn't spent 2016 enabling and defending a bully, her incessant whining would be so much easier to take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN is this a rhetorical question?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second stat will bother @POTUS more than the first. #youresovain https://t.co/5V1K0ifnKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLoBiondo Apparently many of your constituents have bigger fish to fry than your made-up war on flounder limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLoBiondo @bethsmith7439 I asked him essentially the same thing yesterday but he deleted it lol. Frank likes to keep his voters dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I wish someone would ask Spicer today for specific details on how this benefits @POTUS's rust belt base.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usatodayDC @gregorykorte @USATODAY will someone lease ask @PressSec today how this, specifically, benefits @POTUS's rust belt base?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls how childish and embarrassing that you can't just admit it outright. #hypocrites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls is this your backhanded way of saying #BowlingGreenMassacre was an honest mistake?  Seriously snowflake, just say as much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN and unintelligent.  and unbecoming.  and unwanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRightShift @JordanUhl @realDonaldTrump that lone attacker did it in the name of TRUMP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump yet no tweet from you when one of YOUR supporters shot and killed a bunch of Muslims in Canada last week.  #disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theamerpatriot @biggest_crowd @CNN the Clinton Foundation murders, second only to the #BowlingGreen massacre amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN the people have spoken. the people want to stay poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy he's going to like totally #MAGA today. or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ @maggieNYT can someone ask Sean Spicer today how this benefits Trumps rust belt base? Would really love to see him try to answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here @POTUS  is, as plainly as possible, making it perfectly clear that he gives not one shit about ordinary, avera… https://t.co/VlrpYYJibQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does this #MAGA ??? https://t.co/r1f7sbwt4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Omarosa has an office in the White House, with a view of the Washington Monument. I. Just. Can't. Even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLoBiondo @ASMFC but thanks a bunch for ensuring today that my schizophrenic neighbor can still buy a gun. feeling much safer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN We can put the crash cart away. The GOP cannot be saved. Time of death, 4:39.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLoBiondo @ASMFC our president is destroying our global standing. a white supremacist sits on the nsc. and you have flounder outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latimes except for, you know, the family of the dead navy seal.  and all those civilians.  doubt they would call it a success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @NBCNews it's disgusting to me that @SenJohnMcCain  is the only one willing to salvage our nation's dignity. GOP are gutless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio i also am not a radical. just a mom and a patriot who has a hard time watching our country being run by a lunatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryschmidt @SenJohnMcCain Seriously!  I know the world has gone mad when I find myself wishing @SenJohnMcCain was our president lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain keep it up. America needs you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepDonBeyer @RepStephMurphy does it have a bill # we can reference when calling our reps?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[never thought I would live to see the day where I longed for a @SenJohnMcCain presidency, but these are strange tim… https://t.co/wHewMgjLxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @Schwarzenegger it's almost as though he wakes up every morning and thinks, 'how can I make today even worse than yesterday.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews just because you are stupid enough to swallow Breitbart's bullshit, @realDonaldTrump, doesn't mean the rest of the world is too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews right, because during black history month everyone should be thrilled to listen to a speech by a racist wackadoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @NBCNews @realDonaldTrump we need a sim war room. so he thinks he's making these life and death decisions. but nobody dies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @NBCNews a raid Obama vetoed on multiple occasions, it bears pointing out.  If only @realDonaldTrump had those same smarts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust don't give in!  he is a pig who has no business running a mcdonalds, let alone the free world.  please accept our apologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neeratanden @PaulRyan @jasoninthehouse I am sure he felt he needed a YUGE distraction from the immigration EO. GOP will surely understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC lets talk about the 'dumb' raid @realDonaldTrump  ordered over the weekend that killed a navy seal and a bunch of civilians. #killer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump how many more of our brave servicemen will you kill? this isn't a boardgame. #resign #killer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart breaks for anyone with children who are currently enlisted. What a terrifying time this must be. https://t.co/7fmULyY4cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmaher we tried to tell them. they wouldn't listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta i would be very worried about deliberately false leaks. fits their dishonest media narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katiebre123 @CNN Yes, vastly different. Michelle Obama could do nothing right, for a large portion of this country. Trump can do no wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump @washingtonpost the only bit that surprises me is a willingness by the GOP to look the other way. Spineless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWSJ @maggieNYT @WSJPolitics @SenSanders and I value their opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN if this was michele obama it would be a national outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWSJ @maggieNYT @WSJPolitics maybe once @SenSanders declares himself a democrat i would care more about what he thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWSJ @maggieNYT @WSJPolitics i am beginning to think that @SenSanders exists solely to fracture the Democratic party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @MarkWarner @POTUS i mean don't get me wrong, it would be tons of fun and worth it for the entertainment factor alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkmak @maggieNYT he will tweet about it eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @MarkWarner but here's the thing...gop would just confirm bannon anyway. they are mere rubber stampers for @POTUS at tbis point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoePerticone @Fahrenthold i think he is heading to the delaware prison riot. he and he alone can fix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @maggieNYT @StevenMufson @washingtonpost @jasoninthehouse other mistakes, not so much...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @maggieNYT @StevenMufson @washingtonpost wow @jasoninthehouse was so quick to forgive these 'mistakes.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics all those patriotic Trump voters will be first to enlist, amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SybilT2 @maggieNYT Oh I know, and we'll never know what she would have ultimately decided.  But that pressure was there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT  i mean, i distinctly remember this being discussed in the leadup to the election, i.e., what would she do about garland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT all the garland love is touching, albeit disingenuous. HRC would have faced immense pressure to nominate someone more to the left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio maybe because it worked like a charm for you and your buddies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLoBiondo constituents = special interest groups.  is this your attempt at an alternative fact? try harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @SenateMajLdr Mitch McConnell is perhaps the most disingenuous, dishonest politician of all time.  Who on earth voted for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics i hope so. dems can live with gorsuch, whether they realize it or not, and this sets a precedent that will benefit them someday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics @AP Says Republican party: it's okay to lie to the American people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairwinds10 @SenJohnMcCain @washingtonpost unbelievable to me to see americans happily complicit in the undermining of their own democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fairwinds10 @SenJohnMcCain @washingtonpost exactly.  and now the debt is paid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni there should have been a companion IQ test administered to poll respondents.  that would certainly clarify the results for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latimes @latimesopinion he is neither.  i say this as a lifelong dem, who hates @POTUS, and also as someone who covers courts for a living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump and 5-year-olds.  and women who are dying.  and doctors.  etc. etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom dems should use opportunity to expose repubs torpedo of garland as unfair/craven etc. grill gorsuch mercilessly.  but confirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey Agreed. It is essentially a push and Scalia enjoyed waning influence in recent years.  Pick could have been much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Liberals Should Back Neil Gorsuch https://t.co/Gkyfi4vUva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @realDonaldTrump @SenateMajLdr wow. well there goes your right to bitch about obstruction ever again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RacistJohnTrump @timkaine and scalia had minimal sway in recent years. lots of dissents, no major rulings. the sky is not falling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RacistJohnTrump @timkaine exactly!!! the base is rabid, and i get it, but i almost feel like djt is SUCH a madman that gorsuch is a gift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RacistJohnTrump @timkaine agree with this 100%. I am a lifelong dem, but gorsuch is no monster. Choose battles carefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine he's not the easiest to block. I don't envy you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN the balls on this guy. What a shameless, soulless pig of a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postpolitics @washingtonpost exactly!!! scalia held minimal sway in recent years. missed opportunity for dems but the sky is not falling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattizcoop @chrislhayes i still think he goes in for rbg in four years but i am sappy and a hopeless optimist. aka, a democrat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta sock drawer reorg commences in 11 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @NBCNews There are plenty in my small town who are horrified by the EO. Its not a big city/small town… https://t.co/EWWgSuUf3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreatAmericaPAC @newtgingrich @politico I can think of no two better philanderers to push the agenda of our manwhore in chief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neeratanden The skeptic in me thinks that this was/is DJTs call, and that it will become his rallying cry to crack down on protesters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes At the risk of sounding all wingnutty...polls (as we Dems know painfully) mean nothing. Don't let it rattle you #resist]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>