<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to spending quite a lot of time in this special part of the world this year. ðŸ’› https://t.co/eiEj3TKEWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving my seascapes just now.... perhaps not entirely accurate.. but how the sea feels to me ðŸ’™ https://t.co/2YD4CDW57y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone a peaceful Christmas and may 2017 be filled with light. I'm looking forward to seeing how my... https://t.co/bmpcmlBzqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kristen_SA thank you Kristen. It was such a treat to meet you and your mum too. Made my day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 2 of the Edinburgh Art Fair and some re-hanging of work. Very nice day in Edinburgh and its been non-stop at... https://t.co/LpcRl8gRwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy hanging work at Edinburgh Art Fair! ðŸ’› https://t.co/1mjAYgjXYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in the Edinburgh area....these evenings with Shirley are fab https://t.co/kp3YKedXKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My final 4 for the show in November - December ...
I've really not been able to get near enough on the photo... https://t.co/qYARLRaGLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super moon meant super low tide this morning. Always a special place this....but today, it really was amazing. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope everyone's had a nice weekend. I've been doing the business end of finalising my preparations for the... https://t.co/tSKbpmKrtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope everyone has had a good weekend. Finished this piece which is for the Edinburgh Art Show, November. ó¾¬• https://t.co/83CYRGPoJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're finally there..... &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...a little healing painting I did for myself a few days ago : ) It was a bit of a 'flat' day. I'm usually quite... https://t.co/B4ihXW8yge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Wave........ https://t.co/AAMgXELIwa on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting and I have been on some journey : )) It all began subtle and pastel-like under layers.....

Then we... https://t.co/IATcjoc9hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little healing painting l did today. The intent was 'healing that people need today'  It all felt very much to do... https://t.co/bZ5pHh8ZHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are my latest two paintings. These appear to have gone off on a bit of a tangent...

I've been hankering... https://t.co/eJLFKX4eqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working from the Heart....... https://t.co/U3TQxlXGzT on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for paint to dry.....

... so.....

for once....(!) actually taking the time to appreciate my pots and... https://t.co/iAfz4kc1yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very often as an artist one can get too caught up in how a painting or creative piece looks.....

Its so much... https://t.co/WYUOeRSXqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lynne Harkes https://t.co/lMbwf7zdpC coming soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another of the big canvases that are underway just now in the 180 x 120 cm region. This one is needing lots of... https://t.co/9wVkiAcoJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for lack of posts lately! I've been engrossed working on paintings for the exhibition towards the end... https://t.co/FTTd2WqFwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do we cope with the phases of turmoil in the world...? It feels a like too many of us are absorbing the fear... https://t.co/Myt3hXdq3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely to see this on Instagram : ) https://t.co/SbE4tD2XeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody is going to be busy.....ó¾ https://t.co/m7YMAc7MuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of things happening in the studio just now. I've painted this piece with the 'intent' of assisting with... https://t.co/b9eBaXzCQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beginning work on work for a big show later in the year. Sorry for the lack of posts lately... Busy behind the... https://t.co/8fu56rOzgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive been doing some cloudy day photographing of some paintings. This is as close as I can get to the real thing. ó¾¬•ó¾¬• https://t.co/plvOK0faQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting has been Sold and off to hang in a fab new modern space! ó¾¬• https://t.co/bcsxdA1wdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balancing the hues......... https://t.co/I2ijpE9v1J on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a good weekend everyone X https://t.co/l1Ye4hCkOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Emerald Vibrations' Sold and off to a lovely new home ó¾¬• https://t.co/2aiebuH47U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a lovely weekend everyone x https://t.co/1o0K2panG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary of a painting and the agony of the artist....... https://t.co/WisxyT86R6 on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful start to the day here in Edinburgh....

North Berwick beach walk 1 : Cardio Tennis class 0

It was... https://t.co/nxki672Byp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some reason my newer paintings are getting harder to depict in photos! I spend ages on this both in the photo... https://t.co/nHTlY6Uo2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under layers beginning on a big new canvas. Small section here. ó¾¬• https://t.co/33rcHWU7qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved working on this ó¾¬• https://t.co/aamYvfWmND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been doing some more work on this painting today...
The little crow ( that I just love â™¥) is by Mikael... https://t.co/HKNsgeQc1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been doing some more work on this painting today...
The little crow (who I just love &lt;3) is by Mikael... https://t.co/I8RPv8KM49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been working a bit more on this piece today ó¾¬•ó¾ „ https://t.co/T57X8lYmEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a good Weekend everyone and remember if you have a few minutes to spare pop into see the new Bon Papillon... https://t.co/n5sOUKTnEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhibition Time..... https://t.co/nCtuQtqLDO on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhibition time : )) https://t.co/Q9HktAAJEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just picked up my framing ó¾Œ° these will be unveiled on Saturday at Bon Papillon, 15 Howe Street, Edinburgh EH3 6TE... https://t.co/q7m98pH1Yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 6 photos on Facebook in the album "Diary of a painting" https://t.co/iHQQTdlthP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to showing some paintings @ Bon Papillon, Edinburgh in April : ) https://t.co/WeCPY6zWAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bonpapillon looking forward to it!! : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decided to use the remains of my palette to paint an egg...spent time covering its smooth surface with brush... https://t.co/LKyevRkcCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little painting being wrapped to send off to its new home! Travel safe #mystudio #healingart #edinburghartist... https://t.co/kmJ7o0aH4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be the change...... https://t.co/RgT1EYt1qE on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneak peek.... corners of a selection of recent pieces I've been busy with. Some of these (and others) will be... https://t.co/uIMwE9eFlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another on the go and about to re-stretch some canvases after sizing. All go in the creative dept just now... https://t.co/HgHo2xDQZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be taking the latest cobalt green and turquoise obsession too far! #mystudio #lynneharkes #lynneharkesart ó¾ó¾ https://t.co/guPek0rOUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just voted in the #peoplesprojects. Have your say! https://t.co/obGlUvC4Pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the next layers on these. #lynneharkesart #lynneharkes #stockbridgeedinburgh #interiordesign... https://t.co/JuCudgdpYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK my first (and last maybe ó¾) studio selfie! What to do....make the painting look better or the artist look... https://t.co/lVP7zKipbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy and unexpected weekend in the studio : )) I should have know I'd not be able to resist the blank canvases I... https://t.co/OzAG80rJmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely sunrise this morning in Edinburgh ó¾¬•ó¾¬•ó¾¬•#inverleith #lynneharkes #stockbridgeedinburgh #interiordesign https://t.co/wJV51CXQW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest commission was delivered to its lovely new home yesterday. I've really loved creating these two... https://t.co/KBoxILZ5Pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit wild in Edinburgh still....happy to be indoors! https://t.co/pk5lWSjxov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small section of larger piece. ó¾¬•ó¾¬• love this section #lynneharkesart #abstractart #mystudio #mystudiotoday... https://t.co/hBJi0HSYzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My book is very reduced at the moment in paperback or ebook
 : )  https://t.co/arXMhTiWpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine going to a dentist you've never been to before. Then imagine discovering that the new dentist had come... https://t.co/kK7kxMXxXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A detail area of the diptych commission I'm working on just now ó¾¬”ó¾¬”loving the calm colours . #lynneharkesart... https://t.co/lTiJbGmDJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Restrict the use of fireworks to reduce stress and fear in animals and pets https://t.co/yhPbHYKICF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...time for a web site revamp....exploring the dreaded profile images..!

Have a good weekend everyone x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New You..... https://t.co/VejuG5iEjz on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was the last painting of 2015....looking forward to seeing what comes from the studio in 2016.

I'm busy... https://t.co/QOsF4R8MhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It might only be January 3rd but some of us are hard at work already ó¾¬“#myworkspace #stockbridgeedinburgh... https://t.co/HmZIDJWaEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year everyone!! Wishing you all a 2016 filled with joy.... &lt;3

We've been spending some lovely family... https://t.co/WxhWMJWzgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few Christmas angles.....
Thank you to Fergus for gallantly posing in his oversized reindeer costume gift....... https://t.co/LPJ14x4Ami]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've 4 copies of my book 'Spinach Soup for the Walls' to give away. Its a memoir style book with a large part... https://t.co/LkezmmPbUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in the Edinburgh area try to pop into the Open Eye Gallery to see their festive show. I'm delighted to... https://t.co/bu69XuQJNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spontaneous little Christmas tree paintings from yesterday...
some paintings can be re-worked over and over..even... https://t.co/sIlj77XNjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been hanging a few paintings in a medical centre in Aberdeen. Older style 'power flower' here. I struggle a... https://t.co/S8OT0eQrYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted this image to be displayed on the walls of a clinic-health centre. I decided to begin the creation of... https://t.co/AHoQzbTsd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are off to a new home.... Must do more for myself ....I was loving the vibrancy â¤ï¸#lynneharkesart... https://t.co/NfY7YkAKel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My paintings + some lovely Middle Eastern light and drama. These (and a few others )are for sale if anyone is in the Dubai area : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 of 4 gallery submissions. Small challenging boards when I like to work huge! #lynneharkes #abstractpaintings... http://t.co/eRx3Ed6pGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning morning in Edinburgh.... Soooooo beautiful #edinburghsky #autumncolours #stockbridge #inverleith... http://t.co/zgvZyRGY3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small board for gallery submission 1of 4  huuuuge challenge for me to work so small and stay loose with brush!... http://t.co/n6F38XJ2ww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for some Blog thoughts...
http://t.co/zC1wtoXcNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honesty of Art.... https://t.co/3o3WDtUczU on @bloglovin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early spin class followed by studio day working on commissions. Now..... All tidied up and cosy in my living room... http://t.co/k6xhsUMzmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stretching 3 canvases for a commission  can't wait to dive into these!  #lynneharkes #lynneharkesart... http://t.co/WYHbAl5Cxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been re-stocking my art prints after some lovely sales recently  thank you #lynneharkes #lynneharkesart #NOTHS... http://t.co/iu0UZBr3UY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a couple of weeks out of the studio whilst other exciting events have taken place. Most importantly I'm... http://t.co/Tvoq22z2mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've updated my profile on the SSA site http://t.co/tIzqfKQBkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing day here in Edinburgh. #northberwick #eastlothianbeaches #eastlothian #bassrock #fidra #beachlife... http://t.co/7SmGjaTsgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely weekend and Birthday Boy was a delight.

 I'm feeling inspired to paint something to mark the occasion : )...watch this space..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More party #interiorstyle #childrensparty #interiordesign #birthdayweekend #birthdayboy #birthday #inverleith http://t.co/STn2pfSj9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#birthday #birthdayboy #birthdayweekend #interiordesign #inverleith #childrensparty http://t.co/2gA6O2ZiVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little party is happening here today more pictures to follow #interiorstyle #inverleith #stockbridge #birthday... http://t.co/LbTPCf1DrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning evening in Edinburgh #inverleith #stockbridge #lovelyevening http://t.co/buFhROIiuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest pieces....! I'm a little taken aback to see flowers creeping back into my paintings, albeit in a... http://t.co/6yCaD7zLoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Scotland's Skies" http://t.co/v0JepTRRHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 16 photos on Facebook in the album "Scotland's Skies" http://t.co/RcR6dfO3wI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring and Sharing..... https://t.co/APM8Mv2I4U on @bloglovin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>