<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You will be the one starting WWIII https://t.co/j4xuZUf3H3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_timasavea this guy is going to cause so many problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReelBigSmith im having this debate with myself too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLeBrizzle people used to come from around the country for this so its not just Wellingtonians that have given up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLeBrizzle i have never been less motivated to go...i have been every year since it started this year i jat didnt want to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawdonChristie the fun police ruined it...not even a parade this year...needs to go back to how it used to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLeBrizzle dont get me started on my rant abt how one of NZs best events has been ruined by the fun police]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieWall2 they need to go back to how it originally was...courtney pl street party and everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Trump #Nightmare #whatwereyouthinkingamerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just watched an episode of The Only Way Is Essex...what the f$&amp;k did i just watch?!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone take the twitter off the orange one...he is like a petulant teenager #goodluckUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 week till Guns n Roses...a childhood dream coming true!!!ðŸ‘ŠðŸ‘ŒðŸ”«ðŸŒ¹ðŸŽ¸ðŸŽµðŸŽ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #MichaelJackson  #ThisIsIt i dont give a f$&amp;k what the haters say the guy was a genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks PC brigade and Fun Police for offically ruining what was Wellington and NZs best summer event #RIPWellington7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife as a life long Canes and ABs supporter its fair to say im pretty...pretty...pretty happy about this ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BravoNewZealand can we please have #WWHL back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben_Boyce_ @TheEdgeNZ Thought id seen it all till i saw @JonoAndBen twerking at an old folks home @SharynCasey ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought id seen it all till i saw @JonoAndBen twerking at an old folks home @SharynCasey ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendyWings read the replies to Morgans tweet some are gold #idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimFCoates executive power is always going to be his thing ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4LittleJanes sympathy #ManFlu ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValerieAdams84 welcome to my world...this is why im on twitter lol ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps wife steals Michelles speech...Trump steals lines from Batman movies...good luck America #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now @potus is Trump will he still use his personal twitter to have his rants or both? Lets hope he has a social media adviser now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh NO! Its windy in Auckland #theywillrebuild #suckitupbuttercups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well Trump is in charge now...think i just vomited a wee bit in my mouth realising that reality #Inauguration #ThankYouObamas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tacky will the White House look in a few weeks?!?!?! #Inauguration #ThankYouObamas #bringbackobama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendypooh spoilt!!! Mine would just tell me to pay for it to be fixed..."thats wht comes with owning a car Emma"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepaulego what would the stickman have to say about the price of this sour cream during deals week? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜› https://t.co/7VZoRYg7Nr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristynMargaret i dont understand whats going on ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeatherBomb my ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are apples the new avos? There are NO apples at my local supermarket!!!! ðŸŽðŸŽðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most New Zealand thing I have read today is about the woman who called the cops when her weed didnt show up!!!ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayHarvie i feel like its just been a normal windy welly day though...we have had so much worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really dont feel like that was a #WeatherBomb more just another windy day in #Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikajayne is life goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this is? Or are we still waiting for the #WeatherBomb im asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im not ready for this #WeatherBomb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TV3nz is the ondemand app down? It keeps saying tap to try again ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching old @TheGNShow &amp; so cool seeing @charliesheen so happy and relaxed on it talking about EVERYTHING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since the quake ive noticed i now sleep in shorts tshirt sports bra and undies. #incaseofemergencysleepwear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone please shed some light for me on this Trump pissing himself story?!?! It sounds awesome ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KMBalmain oh my god thats us to a T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im missing the #GoldenGlobes cause im working ðŸ˜¢ðŸ˜¢ðŸ˜¢ #ERedCarpet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colincitizen @RHOMelbourne @JackieGilliesTV  and @Gina_Liano and @GambleBreaux too hard to pick just one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colincitizen @RHOMelbourne those women are for real....LOVE them!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MusicKillsKate is the shizzle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can NOT deal with princess biatches!!!! To much work!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope....not in this house!!!! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No getting judgy today #Fitbit ....im not moving from the couch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair to say i wont miss 2016...but ummmm we get Trump as president this year...F$&amp;K!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And parts of the world says New Zealand is slow...you dont have 2017 yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly im not going on a NY diet all i can think about is @HELLpizza666]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year...new bottles of wine to drink #2017 #happynewyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy that sprayed wine on shoppers at Pak n Save just won 2016/17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it weird that i think im in love with Michael McIntyre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ media you are slipping...you havent found the NZ connection to George Michael yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a cool gift from Dad...Grandads war medals photographed and framed https://t.co/4B8qOCXTza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the Die Hard dvds &amp; watch Hans Gruber fall off the Nakatomi building.its not Christmas till this happens #DieHardIsAChristmasMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the women in TKs life die...RUN KYLIE @ShortlandTweet #ShortlandStreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristynMargaret nooooo dont do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing @PaulHenryShow and @JimKayes cry set me off this morning...now go and have a long boozy breakfast going to miss you guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow my mornings are never going to be the same im going to miss you Paul ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wondering how you should feel if you get offered a gym membership for xmas ðŸ˜ðŸ’ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the debate about who is going to be PM stop and just put Richie McAwesome in the big swively chair in the beehive...problem solved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bryce_Casey they are about as much fun as stepping on a plug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLeBrizzle they all die but then wake up and it was just a dream...wht do i know...never watched it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DevlinLive if not lets make it a thing ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least John Key resigning has taken the media heat off #CrateDay right @therockfm ðŸºðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 you have been a weirdo crappy old year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richie McAwesome put the Versatile Homes on hold we need you as PM #johnkey #keyresigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair I would resign too if i was going to have to deal with Trump #JohnKey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife bloody horrible things lol...one day you will understand lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife that made me literally shiver and want to vomit. The fact its a picture stopped that happeneing lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife and that was the trigger of my phobia...that and there horrible faces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife one of my biggest phobias!!! Have a lump in my throat just thinking about them ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump having another cry about #SNL...and this is the President Elect...mother of god there is no hope #playniceinthesandbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These earthquakes sure do like to creep back in on Sundays ðŸ˜¯ #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh i see so its ok for the Aussie media to portray Eddie Jones as a clown but we do it to Chekia and all hell breaks loose ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rove please please please come to NZ...more specifically Wellington â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colincitizen @BravoNewZealand im so pissed they never did one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManojaStJohn @DangerDaveHITS like i said was just what someone told me once and it stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife i swear America was drunk when they voted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife @mike_pence america has a lot to answer for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheComedyWife @mike_pence what a prick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ i think @ronanofficial need to change his twitter name to Roman #SummerWonderland #AirNZXmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristynMargaret allll the instant coffees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for tradies and insurance guys seems to be my life these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Season 4 #pumprules reunion is going to be awesome...yup we are waaay behind in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManojaStJohn @DangerDaveHITS dont quote me!! Someone told me this once and it stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DangerDaveHITS i think if people die in them they biff them for cultural reasons...feel better ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st of December tomorrow...Christmas is about to throw up all over everything everywhere if it hasnt already #Grinchmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 NZ is the best...i may be somewhat bias â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope they gave @SharynCasey a pay rise for babysittng @JonoAndBen next year ðŸ˜œcant wait to hear them together its going to be awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan yusss bring car park chat to The Morning Rumble ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after 5 years of not working &amp; 1 solid year of study for the summer holiday im going back to my retail roots offically employed againâ˜ºðŸ™†ðŸ‘ðŸ‘šðŸ‘¢ðŸ‘—ðŸ‘ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh the waiting game #jobhuntingsucks #justhiremeimawesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever took twitter of Trump before the election do it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMattLucas sounds like NZ we had a $26 mill referendum to change our flag then we kept the one we already had #moneywellspent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind or quake? Ahhhhhh its to much ðŸ˜¯ðŸ˜¢ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜³ #eqnz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>