<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@macleanbrendan @HClaytonWright  You're a China Girl! 
https://t.co/t7pw8MVaXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rock he crawled out from under is free right now. https://t.co/Ux4A1poymM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS. https://t.co/iCeFl3f8qE @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autocorrect just changed “important” to “nice moor tang”. This is now a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's just mad because Meryl Streep played him so well in "Florence Foster Jenkins".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the way it's called “The Legend Of Tarzan ®” as if we might be tempted into industrial theft while watching the opening credits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Merry Christmas, George Michael died” kinda sums up the whole year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Who wouldn’t want to be a green Venusian Love Boy?” https://t.co/6X6pEI3thd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally some good news! Fleet Foxes announce their first live show in 5 years https://t.co/dYEkUmH9Xb via @TheAVClub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So today I got my first suggested Facebook post from a hate group. https://t.co/cPPgy4jSKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was going to write a tweet but Twitter beat me to it. https://t.co/fppTWNu2LH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This coffee is terrible, but on the plus side he gave me so much of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyArcadeNYC This is now my favourite typo of all time. PS love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rowdy Kim Wilde fans spilling onto the street singing the “na-na-na” part of “Kids In America”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard in the mosh pit at a Kim Wilde concert: “Come on,
Kim, get your magnificent arse out here…“ (female)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard in the mosh pit at a Kim Wilde concert: “And I was fighting for human rights so I was like boooooooo….”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard in the mosh pit at a Kim Wilde concert: “So you know the robot chick from Star Wars…”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m in the moshpit at a Kim Wilde concert and I’m pretty sure this is a safe space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you’re about to sneeze and you shove your hand in your pocket for a tissue and smash your keys into your face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been drinking, bowling and eating pizza so I'm basically everyone's new stepdad now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Winding Refn, we won! Thanks so much @MadmanFilms ! https://t.co/BNzwhhIlSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vale Rod Temperton, co-writer of 1 (amongst many) of the greatest pop songs ever written. https://t.co/GCe02ZvkQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW a work colleague's ring tone is the same as your alarm and for a brief movement you wonder if you're only dreaming you're at work...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Irish cafe worker just called out "Halloumi Burgers" and for a second I thought she said, "Hellooo, me Burgers" in a pirate voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reallykazcooke Really didn't need "engorged" and "George Christensen" in the same sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @SUFFfilmfest day pass is free, but a donation to @Twenty10 would be good karma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to a calendar stuff up, I have to offload a @SUFFfilmfest day pass for this Saturday. Hit me up if you're interested!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plebiscite planned for Feb 11 so Liberals can piss all over Mardi Gras again. https://t.co/KQjoSSt6CP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They approached me to do a film that would not be seen for 100 years." John Malkovitch in @GuardianAus https://t.co/oIKKpG9xa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love, love love this: Mike Birbiglia’s 6 Tips for Making It Small in Hollywood. Or Anywhere. https://t.co/10mxpVW28m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Train announcer: Please allow people off the train before you board. Wait... wait... wait... waaait... GETONGETONGETONHURRYWE'RELEAVINGGETON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INTERVIEWER: Do you have a reader in your mind when you write?
BALDWIN: No, you can’t have that. https://t.co/o3Uw9tR1KK @parisreview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one to notice that in "Little Red Corvette" she takes photos of men and keeps their DNA samples?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wee guide to shyness. I'm very familiar with all of this: https://t.co/u03vrbAfO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SUFFfilmfest Hiya, does the Saturday all-day pass include admission to the masterclasses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, basically. https://t.co/pUvtFrLyAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a date to @SUFFfilmfest ! Not one friend will go with me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnerHabib I bought his autobiography purely because of this cover photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. #censusfail is failing hard! https://t.co/9iV8M67QEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, THAT'S what cupping is! What was I doing all this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a brilliant. A list that mixes high and lowbrow, and understands the pleasures that great films can bring. https://t.co/g3z0Mkv2fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another of the great has gone. But what a body of work he left behind! https://t.co/gVaKdUHbW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can confirm these are all true. https://t.co/yemaMkZjFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIngers crossed. https://t.co/Uma9E0gqZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's make Melania president with ALL her policies and speeches written by Michelle. If that's what the crazies want, I can live with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast: it's what's for lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read it and learn. https://t.co/aC71NkXfkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favourite line from the real estate ad: "Mostly original details from the Steve McQueen era." https://t.co/YuDdJ6Au4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite possibly the greatest review ever written. https://t.co/hvmdzCVbdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagicRealismBot Life is starting to imitate art! https://t.co/MyuGAD5nze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am on board with this. @BoingBoing  https://t.co/G9R7H5HxI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't tweet haikus.
They are bloody annoying.
Stop it. Just stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dandebuf She has to sky write her reply or it doesn't count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadmanFilms Serious question: why do you keep giving Dendy Newtown exclusives? The screens are tiny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What is the logic of rage?" A thought-provoking article in @aeonmag about male violence.
https://t.co/xOHr7R3q6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting words from Larry Kramer. https://t.co/3AFWGH2LVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knew? The kilo against which other kilos are measured is an egg-sized hunk of platinum and iridium in Paris. https://t.co/fDExjnju0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm a fantastic beast and you've found me." #harrypotterpickuplines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yay! The plebiscite's starting early.  https://t.co/i5X9oSFwe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaand just as I'm writing a silent feature, one of my favourite directors beats me to it. https://t.co/IY0ncf2Fja @IndieWire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weirdly, when I searched for more info about the Greens and Fred Nile, I got this page. https://t.co/Xf0LW6XpU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WT actual F?! https://t.co/SCUNHMm33F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you're plotting a story about doppelgängers and you walk into a store and the owner says, "Oh, you came back."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Ashleigh!  https://t.co/AkXatAu9sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And the saddest part is that there will be no winners. Nobody will emerge unscathed."  https://t.co/7teFNEq08h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting take on several of my favourite films from the last 6 months.  https://t.co/m2KOHCrEKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man calling out names at the food counter sounds like he's caught his wife having an affair. "Lisa? Dave? Steve?..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it that people with 9 credit cards are so flummoxed by ATMs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer to believe that Prince merely got on board the same spaceship as Bowie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the right thing to do when a homeless man pulls a knife out of his sleeve and sticks it in his ear? (Turns out he was cleaning it.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love and support to all the women sharing their #WhenIWas stories. Essential and deeply disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know how this kid feels.  https://t.co/wHynAHKNIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/6BAH6qp23D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you edit the footballs out of rugby, you're left with a lovely video about grown men chasing each other and cuddling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are a solid 283 registered firearms in Surry Hills, 78 of which belong to a single registered owner." Uhhh... https://t.co/SpzIN9OjEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret lives of women who broke taboo to act in Shakespeare - great, illuminating read. https://t.co/J6jrQWigmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrScienceCat Oh cod no. https://t.co/2Th8RX4P25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent - and eclectic - collection. And it's free! https://t.co/vjBWkXdoEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction. They drowned somewhere else.  https://t.co/bHp1imlNKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite living singers is coming to Sydney! https://t.co/LBvk37ma57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had all my hair cut off, then realised I'm wearing all black and look like a cult member.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristianStella @MrJeremyGardner Stahp! I need false uplift to carry me through my project! (But seriously, you guys do great work.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't we all just get along? https://t.co/D4q86YT70g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day. Have a true love story - with SCIENCE! https://t.co/zxLq17cwzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's back! “@NYTmag: After disappearing for nearly three decades, Pee-wee Herman is back. https://t.co/D4DjvEwED4 https://t.co/3rKYOVSDmo”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does @billshortenmp know there's going to be a justice-for-asylum-seeker theme at MG this year? https://t.co/t8YhTeKchq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI: 2GB free Google Storage today if you review your settings. https://t.co/uNApmP2Hiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mom is me: "Mom Holds Knife To Throat Of Dinner Guest Who Offered To Help" With Dishes https://t.co/z7Z6Cx9oMX via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney Town Hall, just now. #LetThemStay https://t.co/2cH5ZYdDmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting underway at Town Hall. #LetThemStay https://t.co/NjK1aPaejU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently @twitter thinks this crap is is what I want to see. Exactly why I don't want their algorithm on my feed! https://t.co/xJaqyu98Uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @Twitter, I already have a newsfeed that hides everything I'm interested in. It's called Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drowning en route to somewhere other than Australia =/= "saving lives".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to come with me to this? https://t.co/NbqP9ur7iV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The planets are lining up - literally. https://t.co/5a6u4vieRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dragged out my old recorder to catch the @rageABC David Bowie tribute &amp; found their Michael Jackson tribute still on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have to get off my phone," I told myself. So I got on my computer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China just bought into Grindr and the Jurassic Park franchise. There's a connection there somewhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe, you know, Jerry Hall could fuck him to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamCSchembri I'm so sick of these sensationalist Daily Telegraph headlines.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>