<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[He is doing it to himself https://t.co/LSH3J1jKb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get rid of Bannon to move forward https://t.co/X5R0c9CYey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway Says She Misspoke on Iraqi Terrorists, Calls Some Critics ‘Haters’ |  https://t.co/BVPE2SPLHQ ashamed of yourself !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less educated, more manipulated https://t.co/DCBpYVVNq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's business interests worldwide.....direct correlation https://t.co/YzWk85RAJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: Constitution has to be protected from you https://t.co/CfmYJhsLQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: Well regarded Bush appointed Judge. https://t.co/CfmYJhsLQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Turning people away was heart-wrenching’: Dubai airport worker on Trump's travel ban https://t.co/0RDprYa3YY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's belligerence towards Iran plays into the hands of Tehran's hardliners https://t.co/XKz00S7ZR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London protest against Donald Trump travel ban - live coverage https://t.co/O6xWTE7n7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan refuses to grant new ID cards to Bin Laden doctor's family  https://t.co/IXD6FvAw6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China accuses US of putting stability of Asia Pacific at risk https://t.co/ihdOo2jNW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway cites fictitious 'Bowling Green massacre' to justify refugee ban – video https://t.co/i3t7oPEAYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi inquiry into Yemen abuse claims like 'marking your own homework' https://t.co/kPeWB0y1XK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU leaders round on Trump and reject May's bridge-building efforts https://t.co/H31hqOkLV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Has Provocative Words for Allies. Congress Does Damage Control. https://t.co/ImqlRfsGs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘White Privilege’ Essay Contest Stirs Up a Connecticut Town https://t.co/CuY47uMUlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian baby girl in need of heart surgery blocked from US by Trump travel ban https://t.co/KSw4BOSDo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN/ORC poll: Majority oppose Trump's travel ban https://t.co/7QhNqPwxnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 ways Dodd-Frank has benefited you https://t.co/Kq3qOu6Q9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hill Republicans revolt over Trump's plans to build border wall huge cost to taxpayer https://t.co/esogASCq13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Sweden's deputy PM just take a swipe at Trump? https://t.co/xFJbLCQrKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU leaders try to convert Trump anxiety into solidarity https://t.co/xVfZA7yLO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin "weaponizing misinformation" to undermine West, U.K. warns https://t.co/wyAUdmAFKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must not turn our backs on journalists who lack our freedom https://t.co/YV8Jcnh1VA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible definitely. White Supremacist killed 6 in Canada, no comment? https://t.co/uMKR6fL142]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing standing between Trump and authoritarianism: the supreme court https://t.co/jEc6R0Uhi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DressLikeAWoman: Twitter backlash over reports of dress code for Trump staff So Sexist https://t.co/I5WxBUOP3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians form 'rings of peace' around mosques after Quebec shooting https://t.co/k25alM6b1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Washington Post: Eric Trump biz trip cost taxpayers $97,830”

https://t.co/5uUUNx0sdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you are right. Please leave asap https://t.co/IL9FIWf9nI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done former President Obama https://t.co/YhgA5HsIuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conan jokes that White House alters Trump pics https://t.co/kaYiAwaPX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schwarzenegger proposes job swap after Trump takes jab at Apprentice ratings https://t.co/rq9MkWXQOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House votes to scrap gun regulation affecting people with mental disorders  https://t.co/pHk4Wd99Id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European parliament leaders call on EU to reject Trump's likely ambassador pick https://t.co/GYXXPWvxra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you mean reckless USA! https://t.co/eZcS5CNRAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[? Alternative facts https://t.co/N8GHDy3Ic9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellen DeGeneres hits back at Trump by explaining Finding Dory plot https://t.co/DZ9wPv5bWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine Le Pen refuses to repay €300k of 'misspent' EU funds https://t.co/ifcBrkmstk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ISIS is celebrating Trump's immigration ban https://t.co/INl1atHNyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The anti-Trump resistance will fail if we don't ditch establishment Democrats https://t.co/s9G5DFoKKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans move to sell off 3.3m acres of national land, sparking rallies https://t.co/0lWfSTyTpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan urges Republicans to back travel ban despite anger over its rollout https://t.co/kahw09k2PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally Yates and the US constitution: two fatalities of the Monday Night Massacre https://t.co/7kDp1dLGZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact check: he lost popular vote https://t.co/5euEbihYLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim countries with Trump businesses, not touched by ban https://t.co/JpCBduvRIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact check: he lost the popular vote https://t.co/dycjVwBiJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly badly written english https://t.co/LbPpc7FYwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Sad life if you don't care for woman https://t.co/PuO6oA1NN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “African Union speaks out against Trump's immigration ban”

https://t.co/a98t0gGlp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “These are the men who died in the Quebec attack”

https://t.co/KmVkgSo1Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Prince Charles says we are in danger of forgetting the lessons of WWII”

https://t.co/3agBhBoEjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Parliament shows anger against Trump visit https://t.co/vZDXGH0vNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No,not Betrayed. Yates stands up against unconstitutional decision https://t.co/m0OQ9gNAgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's ISIS recruitment tool https://t.co/zcGIhwHaXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget protest. Trump's actions warrant a general national strike https://t.co/fYnIdOZSI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Québec City mosque shooting: man charged with six counts of murder https://t.co/4t8guT34dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump faces growing state department mutiny against immigration ban https://t.co/L07eWScomn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backlash against Trump migration order grows as Obama issues warning https://t.co/tTZsNNgCZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merkel 'explains' refugee convention to Trump in phone call https://t.co/fiuyCwnfS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is Master Putin? https://t.co/3UVrYzB5mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim countries with Trump hotels  are safe!  Phew! https://t.co/lTZnTIgRny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Even Piers Morgan says Trump has gone too far this time”

https://t.co/Fl1NApk7VD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is uncivilized https://t.co/MJvfZS6XpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard run for President https://t.co/iPlKaP5CbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump defends ‘extreme vetting’ order, says visa restrictions to be lifted after 90 days https://t.co/1FjGbsHNgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very scary https://t.co/3UDXHjBnGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look GOP have a voice https://t.co/oet8SBqaTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How one Virgin Atlantic team member found her purpose https://t.co/lPihyXbg5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narrative of Colonist, not peace https://t.co/N8QSXjmEhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's immigration fiasco might be more premeditated than we think https://t.co/1vfnitP9RH via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's state department purge sparks worries of 'know-nothing approach' to foreign policy https://t.co/KP7H9UU7bu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corbyn: May will be failing Britons if Trump visit goes ahead https://t.co/Cqbe0AxADN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Official, in Reversal, Says Green Card Holders Won’t Be Barred https://t.co/P9WWJ49p9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally! PM May, why so slow https://t.co/yC9JT4DeLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about Tweet Be A Leader https://t.co/wjBfP5wQ0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes Americans unsafe https://t.co/Fnhc20bEpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Trump is worried Prince Charles might lecture him”

https://t.co/5KYtc7RWQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Kim Kardashian challenges Trump's 'muslim ban' with statistics”

https://t.co/gdRsIP0ZGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How foreign leaders are reacting to Trump's travel ban https://t.co/mMlLNSag5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House defends Trump Holocaust statement that didn't mention Jews. Bannon's far right influence  https://t.co/fDyvSdSquj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mylan CEO on EpiPen drug price controversy: "I get the outrage" https://t.co/5wNn6mvkIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee group's CEO shares concerns over Trump's ban https://t.co/ncwXvO4rnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers condemn Trump order on refugees, citizens from Muslim nations https://t.co/0Kbhrba6sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK’s £100m weapons deal with Turkey ‘turns blind eye to rights abuse’ https://t.co/uTJd6IZjGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollande: Trump administration is 'encouraging extremism' https://t.co/N5gtDiYMsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s America, where even park employees have become enemies of the state https://t.co/qJxhvsjsI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's voter fraud expert owes US more than $100,000 in unpaid taxes https://t.co/VImotKFheD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqis lament Trump travel ban that disregards their service to America https://t.co/dSIjlcyCbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Protest As Politicians Fail Us https://t.co/2ynqvMCbJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ikea flat-pack refugee shelter named 2016 Design of the Year https://t.co/OcKuYyZXC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Republicans came to support Trump's wall https://t.co/B5OsNXUe6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech leaders condemn Trump's immigrant ban https://t.co/oYUnXpsehu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What! no banning of Putin.. Why..mm https://t.co/VlDRggzhFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Immigration Ban Draws Deep Anger and Muted Praise https://t.co/8Rqtlx6PJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No mention of Jews in White House's Holocaust Remembrance Day tribute https://t.co/imbATJmEkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May 'does not agree' with Donald Trump's immigration ban https://t.co/Hu1IEBfZHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global fury as Donald Trump’s ban on migrants takes effect May is a coward  https://t.co/DxwQyAtSt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Conservative MP talks about Trump and his state visit”

https://t.co/PtEPJ8kNim]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>