<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone get me a goat to calm my nerves https://t.co/SXyBUOvhrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're hungover and desperately need a drink https://t.co/FffGWcAq6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon my hearing is at about 60% of what it should be. The years and years of in ear earphones and deathcore have ruined me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a UFO knockin around outside gonna get pure abducted https://t.co/KVZhS7Q9D3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasedSwine that is actually a million times better than I imagined it ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasedSwine WHERES THE MERMAID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman WAS LIVING HERE BEFORE YOU WERE BORN LAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman I run this city you just live here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman big posh cunt in rathfarrrrrnham arent i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman Yeah I'm reppin the south side https://t.co/3jF4m7Cpse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman im pretty sure you're legally a dwarf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman have you grown a foot since i last saw you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone said hi conor to me on Camden st earlier on and I didnt cop till they had gone, gonna annoy me for months till I know who it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweekusMaximus saw you tweet for the first time in ages and was all AH ITS YER MAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman it's adulting when you have the 30k deposit you'll need!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bendleshnitz you know I took it cause spelling my name conorml is my trademark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out with @Bendleshnitz the ultimate duo https://t.co/KxAU4faHvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I've had a lot of sobering thoughts in my time, it was them what started me drinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EMMURE GOT IT BACK ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/FzVaQvSOgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bendleshnitz it's good isn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmarshmason can't wait to see Jens Kidman gurn in person https://t.co/uYkPnVeSKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not far off https://t.co/6Y6OIOW1Qj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very good pup https://t.co/ejd9VCbVMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is turmoil" - Grandad Smith 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elaineroisin livin that flagline lifeðŸšŒðŸšŒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on this day 7 years ago Conor became a knacker https://t.co/vpcYsHXATY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DONT PAINT IN ANY TYPE OF BLOOD FFS https://t.co/N5DE2YMMKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAYHEM ARE PLAYING IN MARCH https://t.co/KMi7OZxskK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scenes in Tullamore last night "YOU WANNA FUCK ME YEAH?" https://t.co/XISXUu8jNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im gonna have a FEED a pints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just counted and I have 160 people muted. That's a lot of intolerance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_BK MY MAiN, GOAL iS TO BLOW UP! AND THEN.. ACT LiKE i DONT KNOW NOBODY https://t.co/LHiFjjehOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exam tomorrow and I am wholly underprepared https://t.co/MQS3nnuU21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaCharlene_x gaviscon was always a weird one, the feeling of drinking gaviscon is worse than heartburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaCharlene_x I'm a long time advocate of the spearmint Rennie, I don't want to ruin a good thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking apple cider vinegar and cayenne pepper as my placebo of choice. Can't wait for the heartburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreamt the house was being attacked by xenomorphs. The RELIEF of waking up and not having to deal with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SLEEP IS GOOD BUT DEATH IS BETTER https://t.co/aQTRRoCFMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NPvXJXggNY DO A LITTLE TALKIN AND A LOTTA ACTION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I AM SO EMBARRASSED FOR THE GIRL ON POINTLESS RN WHO HAD TO NAME A COUNTRY THAT ENDS IN 2 CONSONANTS AND SAID "PARIS"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Sovereign was what it was all about â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH MY GOSH MY DAYS ARE GETTIN LONGER AND THERES NO TURNIN BACK IM WORKIN 9 TO 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is a very bold statement https://t.co/6MXc5cl0IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've given up coffee and as a result there's nothing that gets me up in the mornings I'm off work. I got up at 7pm the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachelsmachel_ nothing starts the year off better! https://t.co/zqXwdjP6fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Denial, Timothy Spall is my favourite person ever https://t.co/NYjgwuXvYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Godzilla Resergence and it's so so weird he's like a giant tadpole at the start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[have an unhealthy paranoia when it comes to calls from unknown numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rang for a taxi and yer man just sighed down the phone at me like napoleon dynamite. YER IN THE WRONG BUSINESS MAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAIRWELL AND ADIEU TO YOU SPANISH LADIES https://t.co/dTwV9BnCRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna go out but also wanna stay in but also wanna go out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever fuckin had a Marlboro red?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cunts that exhale miss out on pretty much 70% of the smoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsElisha_ gonna be eating sticks of butter like they're going out of fashion ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lillymun In a nice way Lauren!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@audreykerr I'm not complaining I'm SPECULATING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@audreykerr WILL I ENJOY IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off till the 3rd, WHAT AM I MEANT TO DO WITH THIS MUCH TIME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMZ0_ that's actually heartbreaking ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALIEN COVENANT OH GOD YES https://t.co/UsCwV6zdjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made what may be the most perfect Christmas dinner ever. The MOISTEST turkey ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first coffee in a week MERRY FUCKING CHRISTMAS https://t.co/GssfAAsICM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParamitePies it's all about that Ivan Dobsky life â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ https://t.co/7bcfNYkcHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOUR WORST NIGHTMARE ISSSA COMIN!!! https://t.co/XKaws7utH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dickinsons Real Deal is really trying to appeal to the younger audience https://t.co/izGjqmFwsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have 10 days off, going back to Tullamore and sleeping myself into a coma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GingerQueen3 AAAAND AS I RECALL I THINK WE BOTH KINDA LIKED IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND I SAID WHAT ABOUT BREAKFAST AT TIFFANYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 NO I like the Spanish, it's the Brazilian!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's incredible, everyone on this bus seems to be designed perfectly to irritate me in every possible way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS  BETELGEUSE TWOOO BABYYYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Autolator to be fair this is the best thing to ever happen to Dublin https://t.co/GpxYwp7uXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Autolator this is your legacy, Jack https://t.co/ehDqZAv1Vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Autolator I'm not afraid to say it, ye need to learn to be hard and quiet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Autolator ITS THE IDOTS JACK, WHY ARE SO MANY PEOPLE CAREFREE MORONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mylo was the BABBBYYYYY https://t.co/6vfUyUKtGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee being my favourite thing in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been weaning myself off coffee lately and it's a harrowing ordeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Autolator whennnnnnnnnn ya gettin the tattoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Granny told me I have to get a girlfriend before I'm an old bachelor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So so ropey. Have the shakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This family adopted a mouse, what happened next will AMAZE you https://t.co/DZuAkHscud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won an award for most addicted to caffeine at the xmas party. This is what my whole life has led up to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triggered by skinny fit clothes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 well according to google it'd take 20 hours to walk to where i live in tullamore :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 its not that far!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunrealness that is such a quality bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 an hour and a half with a trip to the shop :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 was sick of waiting for the bus :P and I wanted to see how long it takes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked to Rathfarnham, I AM SORE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elaineroisin THE POOR LIL PIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THEY REMADE DIRK GENTLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love watching Noel Edmonds pretend he's a real person on Deal or no Deal. WHERE ARE THE BODIES BURIED NOEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 the cheek of being told not to order a drink :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS LITERALLY YOUR JOB TO MAKE THE DRINK FFS https://t.co/yo1oDhpJmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobJJKelly getting a thorough check over just to make sure I'm not dying :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastryslice LIVING THAT RINA LIFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two ECG's, chest xray, bood tests, 5 doctors and 9 hours waiting and I'm still here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been hooked up to one of those heart monitors where they put stickers all over your chest TWICE today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddwolff25 gotta tease out the quality https://t.co/BqenKWeSpB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>