<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@imawayforawalk I'm working ðŸ˜¢ but I hope for the next one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls let there be filming tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have biscuits at home! Morning saved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a very stressful day, don't mind me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like he said last night, his everlasting memory will be the affection, the support and the kindness of the people. That's what matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway I was just talking about that side. I know there are a lot of people who love him and his doctor, who support and respect him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_Mysterio yes absolutely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WEATHEREDMAN @twelfthcapaldi I generalised a little bit sorry but yes, he's very much loved as well, that's all he needs to know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a beautiful person who loves his job and fans, he doesn't deserve this :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand if you don't like his doctor, it's ok, but it's been disrespected just because of his age, looks or portrayal of the character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been thinking about this all day. It breaks my heart thinking about how bad peter has been treated by people during these years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I was like "I love this interview I will listen to it every night" then the punch in the face arrived]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm finally at home I'm screaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived in Cardiff and of course there are aliens https://t.co/KjxHZEZJYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because you know I'm made of money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've wasted 18 pounds because of a flight delay, so I had to buy another bus ticket and the coach driver didn't even have change. For real?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If life assists me, I'll be in Cardiff soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm finally in Bristol dear god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me the last couple of days https://t.co/tRDyUb5RBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another hour delay what the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 3 hours and we have to wait another more for the spare plane to arrive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to be in Cardiff already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time ever I'm not happy to be stuck in Venice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or do we have to expect to see him in Victoria at some point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope someone is already writing a screenplay of educating rita for peter and jenna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi deserves all the happiness and love in this world pass it on https://t.co/4YyNJCBy28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning. I want to fling myself into the sun ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If twelve regenerates because of gunshot wounds I'm going to sue everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twelfthcapaldi I retweeted without realising what the fuck chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope to meet peter soon and have the courage to tell him how much his doctor meant to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0hmanitsang exactly the same for me. I will forever be grateful for what he brought to my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to wake up in 5 hour to go catch a plane. I better get some sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0hmanitsang i feel you... and it's not silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This feels unreal. I'm so upset, sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to miss his doctor, I'm going to miss him around Cardiff. This is harder than I thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so grateful for what peter capaldi brought to my life. He gave me the strength and motivation to change my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas is cancelled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not happening, please tell me it's not real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not ready please Peter don't go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart just broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm landing in Bristol tomorrow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APRIL THE 15th YES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another girl another planet. Help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when a room full of Italians screamed Capaldi and Moffat sent him the video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's peter time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbyiis nope, my mum would never say that... other relatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my mum were talking about dimples and the first person she thought of was jenna. Same mum same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've got chocolate but not for you" "you got fat" fuck you I mean I didn't come home to be attacked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at this ball of fluff https://t.co/ROSTWy3AD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twelveslapels it's mysterious but it also says so much? If it makes sense... anyway I love them so much sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twelveslapels idk if rachel talalay already talked about this but I want to know everything about this shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my parents and staying with them but after a whole month I feel the need to go back to Cardiff and my habits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to feel less mediocre and useless asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owedbetter_ I am! Thank you lovely ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owedbetter_ I'm still at home in Italy, it was a general thought! :)) but I'm going back soon so I hope...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OPieceOPi I shouldn't be laughing but OH MY GOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going on set is actually so nice. I really hope to be able to go in the next weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did they give up on peter's hair already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellofabird oh oh and one last thing... https://t.co/F0qy3Sk6ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellofabird seriously omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellofabird bringing this back because https://t.co/yZZYORjQdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OPieceOPi thank you ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sherlockly thank you thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeckerstarOTP thank you! That's a really nice picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellofabird they even have the same spiked hair now i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait is sharing the hot drink an actual scene? It's so adorable ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pics in my last rt are so adorable I need a moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kribu13 yes! And they look amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter's hair though https://t.co/BWH0ZaiGMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idk I'm really liking what I'm seeing/saw/read about series 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad they are going back to the studio soon. It looks like a really cold day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway I think that new costume looks really good https://t.co/1nCUXWVjyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I'm in another country when there is filming...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINGERS CROSSED FOR VICTORIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who remembers collide? best Randall/Clara slowburn au to ever exists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok jokes over when are we getting the series 9 soundtrack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in the mood to hide away for the next three years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love peter capaldi like seriously what a beautiful human being]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgot to show you all this masterpiece by @marshcaps https://t.co/0c154DJSlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But maybe it's just because I don't speak english that well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always considered this song close to twelveclara (from kill the moon to motoe) https://t.co/nZn4LTVrb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a spider in the sink. I'm taking the first plane back to Cardiff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owedbetter_ jo oh my god it was amazing. I could feel the colours, the coziness of some scenes, their emotion... so beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, I'm a happy person. https://t.co/DBm4qVVF1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly what I want to listen to. https://t.co/uZkAX0FtnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss going cycling around Cardiff bay. Summer hurry up please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut the fuck up if you don't know shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[twelveclara au where clara gets lost while hiking and asks for help in a mountain hut in the middle of nowhere owned by the doctor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshcaps if it wasn't obvious already, I love Venice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "I don't know what to cook tonight" last minute solution https://t.co/3HIk8ZvxkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously though, I'm the weird and insecure little sister while @marshcaps is my protective big sister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we know why twelve talked about ikea https://t.co/aU2BHN0cOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so in love with this city https://t.co/bceXIU2FhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshcaps I've gained 3 chins today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guess who's a happy person https://t.co/j7J0p9XB0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshcaps cat apparently finds me comfortable https://t.co/6tlDEp7sCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kribu13 eheh! I really hope he did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kinda like it though... even though it scares me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My cousin downloaded this game on my phone and it has fucking slender and five nights at freddys characters in it how about no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when peter was like "yeah jenna broke this thing but I'll give it to her if she leaves" https://t.co/8ICvtcp9PW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>