<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I one hundred percent just complimented and compared me and my girlfriend to the monkey and the puppy. #luckygirl https://t.co/QIPqILRkSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to listen to a song that isn't anywhere. @MikeArches singing time after time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johndaddyy hope your good though mate. Let's not hope she wants to come see mk haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johndaddyy hahaha. Dick! My dad will be up before me anyway. Good luck for the boy 😊😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahwitt of course! Haha https://t.co/DM3johclRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahwitt blew them down as well homie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahwitt tell me about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little sister is getting ready to go out and i am in boxers playing skyrim with my cat sleeping on me. Who is re… https://t.co/rchXmg0oGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OGheavyshit haha. It's a word. I told you this. Miss you homie. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thing heartburn is Satan's grasp on your heart. Worst thing ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordonACooper your mum sounds rad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss these dudes but there voice still rings clear. @Cane_Hill #life #music #livemusic https://t.co/n7LBihJnf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B bomb? You know your thinking it! https://t.co/pRVcqhvIUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @edsheeran do anything wrong? @catrawr two new singles are perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eyes are heavy as fuck and it's only half 6... old man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up at seven in the morning craving cheese... this is a thing apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really want a slush puppy machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@devinclark_ @_georgecollings fucking miss Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want all the smoothies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_georgecollings idiot. We are not in Germany anymore lad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slowely but surely ruining @_georgecollings life with pictures of me naked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My cat is the neediest thing on this planet. Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahwitt @Cane_Hill @devinclark_ @AngryVeiny @OGheavyshit see you fuckers next year for sure. Get weird in the US if you aren't over here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My face cause I am missing my boys in @Cane_Hill @devinclark_ @AngryVeiny @elijahwitt @OGheavyshit https://t.co/2IPAAnbAev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How fucking good are lamb of God?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this dj doesn't up his game then it will be fight 15... angry Kyle against dj canny dae it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up at 7 and being wide awake... fuck off. https://t.co/9pjhBEkmgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahwitt same dude. I need put in the fucking bin. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megabusuk it was on time to pick up but broke down several times on the way to Scotland from London. Resulting in me being hours late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even better when the bus is going slow as fuck and then we hit traffic. @megabusuk you have successfully pissed off a loyal customer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a problem with @megabusuk on there sleeper services now. Never on time, constantly breaking and now making me late by nearly an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still not home. @_georgecollings is sending me snaps of him all comfy. I hate my pals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night with @Cane_Hill in Brixton and the last night of tour. It has been a fucking… https://t.co/hZFzLe8DQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobDamiani nah!!! Don't be silly. Thought you were better than that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting sent videos of your mates back home in there local with no trousers on and a cock just swinging about... looking forward to hometime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lads in @MalloryKnoxband @lonelythebrave and @fathersonband are tearing up the uk in March next year. Grab your… https://t.co/vTC3Rr0uQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't function in the morning. Just left my key for my hotel room in my other jeans. Picking up a piece of paper I believed to be my cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boys in @Cane_Hill have arrived in Manchester and we have nothing to do. Bring them weed and plans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 can't wait to see her tomorrow. Going to pester her till she hates me. Then loves me after a week away again. Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 I also got tattood today. Got a little cat portrait. Nala might be happy. https://t.co/XrJSGkAYsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 p.s games are bad  can't be fucked with that noise. Just someone who is like a giant cat and likes me being one as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 true. Little bit of fun and games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know what's good? @Cane_Hill. So go listen to them if you want your ears kicked off your head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 aye well I am sound and braw. There silly (not all them. Just a select few)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sixesand7s I will get a mould of my sack and you can gift it off...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassies are a great laugh. Fucking hell man. Any lads want a man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's scenes were pretty mental. Newcastle your emergency services are fucking mince though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 from a toilet in Wales? No problem haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 what a tit Robbie is haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nailing it to the first show of the uk and all I want is a McDonald's...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sixesand7s I miss my little man too much. I will be stealing him when I come home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 i will probably be home the morning of the 12th though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 I will be back December 10th. See you then miss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 In belgium. It's got nice beer and that's about it haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After finding no pubs open or public toilets I came to the realisation I may need to shit outside. In a bag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I eventually found a gay bar and danced my way through to mamma Mia and eventually got to my goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MHP arena in Ludwigsburg tonight with @Cane_Hill @kseofficial and @bfmvofficial. Should be a HUGE show. Stoked to see everyone smash it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cane_Hill I will choke all of you dudes out. At the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joesavins mate we are all in the same boat with that haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tour with the dudes in @Cane_Hill has been sick as fuck. Like a proud dad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanwrighting @BenOFT God yea you will. Well it's happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanwrighting @BenOFT perfect. Well I will grab it when I come down and we get drunk and celebrate life and such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @BenOFT and @hanwrighting should hold onto my jacket. I will be down soon to see the little one and wet his head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanwrighting well no but it has been worn by a sound guy. And it's nice. And I have badges on it. And I want a dog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hanwrighting swap it for a doggy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know those people in life you just can't get away from... there is always something there... best/worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordonACooper yup. I robbed him for food. Tour life. Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two good deeds today. Helped some old dude up and picked up his coins for him. Also shared my sandwich was a pigeon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My next year is going to blow people's faces off.  😊😊😉😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight in Prague has been flawless. Sick gig. Sick Merch. Lift home sorted and new boys to work for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fathersonband siiick there tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cavorting_1885 @KathrynDownie noooo just saying she won't die haha. She is a survivor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynDownie leave me alone. I am tired and stranded in Germany. But I love you and you won't die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynDownie fair. Fair. I would defiantly keep it up if you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fathersonband fucking hell lads. Where about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynDownie well calm down then ya mental ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenOFT fuck yea dude. Can't bloody wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 every fucking day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to join my dudes @TINBand @Matthew0Kennedy and @johndaddyy today in Glasgow. Tour kicks off today. https://t.co/8eKJW6HvcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catrawr you will indeed. Be good to see you. Been a while. Hope you are well :) x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my back is agony. Tried picking up my nephew and pulled a muscle... such an old bastard. Anyone good at massages?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean, pack, forget, pack, forget, clean and pack. Tour packing is not my thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johndaddyy @CathouseGlasgow @MalloryKnoxband should have told me earlier would have been there in a heartbeat boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait. Stadium packed with spurs fans for the start of the champions league. #COYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least with cammys house being 50 degrees, tomorrow in Berlin won't be so bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 it was pretty obvious he would end up in some state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 he was rolling round April's in just his boxers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 not really. Had a good sleep, didn't drink loads. Just shattered somehow. The sun and gingers don't mix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 pretty much haha. I am fucking shattered as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 just cut his grass and then getting dinner I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmcneill_14 cammys. How come?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veganbear good dude. Get out and enjoy this... summer... Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veganbear same as me dude. Get your but out and love it when you are :) hope you have a great day dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from 'honey' being a banging 10 by @mooseblooduk. I love the video. Just reminds me of the 10 minutes of good time in fallout 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisJohnMilly hey dude. What's your top four prediction for the premier league?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonoBLITZ top four prediction before the league starts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker excited? Top four prediction? Let's see home much it changes over this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZachSIO you sir are an asshole. I don't know how to play!!! Should have shown me on tour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super stoked on my dude @bigbadolz with two top ten smashes from @officialgiggs and @mooseblooduk. Both deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartburn. Killer... throwing in the towel like.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>