<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougAndres woulda clicked faster if it said #dbcft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kpomerleau And LVMH and Diageo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Was that tweet funded by Soros or Koch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@professortax autozone and the dealers are on there. automakers up in the air. or positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nike, Walmart, Target, Macy's, QVC, IKEA, Diageo and more lining up against border adjustment: 
https://t.co/7k9WjP6eWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that sometimes it's businesses who want regulations. https://t.co/HCxzYZKjS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@professortax yup. and budget 2 is really messy. and both recon bills are tough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Mattingly @VP Couldn't Sessions replacement just do it if he goes first?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@professortax @AlanMCole No, second reconciliation bill, after the second budget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nielslesniewski #TRIH #MontanaBeef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between the lines, Hatch is saying, even if I ultimately like border adjustment, Senate math is tough.
https://t.co/B8uFu8pDiB via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The text shows openness. But with a warning/reminder that the Senate will Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Hatch speech is the polite, thought-through version of his "good for Kevin" reaction to House GOP tax plan. 
https://t.co/B8uFu8pDiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Senate Homeland Security committee is now singing "Happy Birthday" to Mike Enzi. But no vote on Mulvaney nomination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateDavidson @saabhash_shiv Former employer writes about father. Not sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Hatch also noted that it will have to be written to get 50 GOP senators. So not just his staff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you somehow thought the Senate would just pass the House border adjustment tax plan, think again. 
https://t.co/B8uFu8pDiB via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hatch on border adjustment. Not opposed, not for. Got questions. https://t.co/B8uFu8pDiB via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fine #TRIH piece right here. https://t.co/nADeVRAJw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hatch to @USChamber: “Look, it would be wonderful if we had some free-market Democrats in the Senate. We don’t.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is counter to where some other GOP members are -- worry about having to come up with their own taxes to pay fo… https://t.co/zyJnrUEKLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hatch is walking the line here. Not embracing or rejecting border adjustment. But also noting the very slim margin in the Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hatch: I get asked about border adjustability every single day. 
Senators are just like us! #DBCFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCOTUS pick may have some state sales tax implications. https://t.co/zIl1ucoBBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG Must be some muni bond trick they could do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG Unless IRS tightens definition as it has threatened to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole It's economics. The scarce resource is Senate floor time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an incredibly important question - how fast does border adjustment revenue ebb? - for the Byrd rule. https://t.co/OBtD2Hff1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kpomerleau @lieber2k Raytheon-Target actually kinda works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler Therefore, his approval ratings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler Jersey. Don't knock it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would think currency adjustment happens FIRST. If the market is really efficient, it adjusts in preparation for tax change, not after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good read on the currency assumption in #DBCFT, but.... 
https://t.co/D7dPvDtOOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabeth_malm @AlanMCole @wmata Sorry. Unscheduled track work has delayed valentine's day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabeth_malm So it took you 11 days to get to all caps and serial misspelling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottlincicome Try shouting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottlincicome Lawyers and economists. Will they ever understand each other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tons of great border-adjustment content from us this week -- small businesses, a Q and A and this video. #DBCFT
https://t.co/XJmpd0ORas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey there #DBCFT nerds, my colleagues in the @WSJ video department explain border adjustment with pictures. 
https://t.co/XJmpd0ORas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanNeidle Every time I think I know what will happen, I wait 30 minutes and have a new idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kpomerleau Problem for people on fixed-dollar pensions. Transition problems to get wages and SS up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremydcape I mean, it's oversimplified. And remember that to the extent it is a VAT is is replacing the corporate income tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To oversimplify, the #DBCFT is VATtish if the exchange rate adjustment happens and tariffy if it doesn't. 
#TRIH https://t.co/8DOKY3cmuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UPSbanker Meeting not announced yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole So who is paying the $1 trillion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big companies use sophisticated economic models to plan for tax reform. Some small firms are worried. 
https://t.co/h8PsfX0NeS via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacobPalmer500 @WSJ Tell me what you think is wrong and I have been talking to a lot of importers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro If you are a GOP senator and you like the border adjusted tax plan, call me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro Lee and Graham and Perdue more critical so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro A one-party agreement? Even that looks hard. #DBCFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmShipEric @RWhelanWSJ Agree. Trade lawyers worries. House staff confident. Bill still not written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ObjectvInvestor @WSJ Corp tax paid by shareholders and labor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet small business owners who think a border-adjusted corporate tax might put them out of business. 
https://t.co/h8PsfX0NeS via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a border-adjusted tax and why is everyone talking about it?

https://t.co/xwdrBJB0rU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to write about w conflict of interest and the phone wants it to be "confit," in which I am interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec @RFrances2 Farmer and dealer could negotiate on price to share tax break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec @RFrances2 Exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec @RFrances2 What if I order something from a bookstore in Toronto?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec @WSJ I think the latter. But not sure. Again, no text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec @WSJ Great question. Don't know. Big possible loophole if it doesn't. Administrative mess if it does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The border adjustment q and a you've been waiting for. 
#DBCFT 
https://t.co/xwdrBJB0rU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confused by border adjustment? Try this Q and A:

https://t.co/xwdrBJB0rU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know about border adjustment and how it would work https://t.co/xwdrBJB0rU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG Nope. Big open question on that and transition rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the #DBCFT be a "disaster" for small business?

https://t.co/h8PsfX0NeS via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some small businesses are very worried about the House GOP tax plan. 

https://t.co/h8PsfX0NeS via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that Sen Hatch has become a Trump ally and spent an hour with him this week. https://t.co/NRv4K39qlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+1. @dylanmatt puts the pros, cons and nerdiness in one place. https://t.co/xCUth702We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLEllis @kpomerleau The Auerbach-Holtz-Eakin piece is good. So is the Gale 11 facts piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimtankersley @BCAppelbaum Friday news grump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some @DBCFT Truthing going on at JP Morgan: https://t.co/k3G0LHqq9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, his closing remark makes me want to ask, "How do you like this, @Apple?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #DBCFT economists, isn't Navarro right that it shouldn't affect prices/retailers? https://t.co/rM5WSWIhAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattZeitlin @AlanMCole I woke up at 5 am this morning because I was thinking about the incidence of the DBCFT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Not if it's yoked to estate tax repeal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we'll have immigration reporter @laurameckler on hand to handle all your wall questions. https://t.co/zzatQ50WTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there's nothing better than border adjustment on video, I'll be doing a Facebook Live at 2:30 pm ET. https://t.co/7wxfF0oigc 
#DBCFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caption: "Do you think the dollar will rise to fully offset the border adjustment?" https://t.co/uJUye181hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replying to reader e-mail on the #DBCFT. Lots of "but economists say the dollar would..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lieber2k The wage deduction in the #DBCFT is economically equal to a payroll tax cut combined with a VAT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmarron Yup. But this is just as valid as any offset (timing shift considerations, notwithstanding)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zachy224 That is a big potential problem. Yes. House GOP says it will work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dem philosophical complaint about the House plan is more about regressivity of the individual tax changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a VAT and a payroll tax cut that limits inversions. Lots for Dems to like in it, oddly enough. https://t.co/WZKGoS4i62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_bunker We've been saying this for a while now, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which @paulkrugman tries to untangle the #DBCFT:
https://t.co/T3KYSuWFDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGreen Shh. The border adjustment doesn't actually do that. (The overall House GOP tax plan probably does.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGreen That is the opposite of my job description.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonfurman Yes. And causes Byrd rule problems. Expensing cuts the other way, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaGreen So something loved by economists, used in VATs and included in a GWBush tax panel report is "nationalist."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deactive #DBCFT Twitter. Active #passthrough Twitter. I'll be moderating a panel here Feb. 8. Mark your calendar.
https://t.co/kBYyQduAMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take that, Byrd Rule! https://t.co/gmGLbSf7zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEI's Alan Viard econo-trolls you all by looking at the infinite horizon on border adjustment:… https://t.co/pqswhrHZFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what about the guac? @dylanmatt has answers for you. 
https://t.co/kRLwDzycyR via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kpomerleau Also the Club for Growth is promoting an Ed Kleinbard piece. What a world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressional Republicans and Donald Trump are trying to understand each other.  From @kristinapet and me:
https://t.co/CJO3rq3zbQ via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on Americans with foreign-denominated assets. https://t.co/5EqxWDhXb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incidence fight! https://t.co/QrAG7POQ9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcknssMONSTER @TimJHanrahan @MikeSacksEsq Yup. Just for clarity in later editions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeubsdorf Dreams
Be 
Crazy
Full of
Taxes

#DBCFT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>