<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtoxvaerd @sarahwillers you will be missed, but it is the best way to spend a year when you can afford it! So good for the kids too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiliaFox I am waiting for my husband to come home to watch the finale! I love the story, good to refresh the show in a different setting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghdoyle Some wounds never heal. No matter how oft discussed, how far back in history it goes, it's never settled. Balkans is the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So beautiful. A drone footage of the bridge which inspired Ivo Andric's novel "The Bridge on the Drina". #Bosnia… https://t.co/NypuO8mxpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. This is a very powerful message, @rezaaslan. Thank you. https://t.co/EoraPoftEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me when I write, most of the time, minus peanut butter &amp; the cleverness :-) Plus: feeling too warm beside t… https://t.co/EergIplibt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was wondering about the meaning of the two books featuring in #theaffair finale. Here it is, explained perfectly https://t.co/k90QYD2k5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War Childhood Museum open in Sarajevo as of last night. Symbolic, given everything that's going on right now https://t.co/zIZFAOLMJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda Kenny should not visit the Trump Whitehouse on St. Patricks day - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/hL07VsF4IF via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insularity &amp; fear of "other" in a world which is more tangled than ever. Dangerous, frightening, heartbreaking. #immigrationban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it was Lewis Carroll's birthday yesterday... https://t.co/89fl56lPX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colmoregan @OisinOhAlmhain Another incentive is: a cafe charged me less when used a coffee mug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, #Dubrovnik Marks 601 Years Since Abolishing Slavery https://t.co/xEzdEB38du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neasaconneally The one I still remember years on: I was in a choir &amp; the organiser said: we have to give her a solo. Used to love singing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between there and here: the anatomy of temporary migrations - new exhibition at @MMSU_Rijeka #rijeka #zaljev https://t.co/iULHYY9KW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto Best of luck :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto the world of Python, SQL, R, Statistics, and much more :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you doing this @ NCI, @ickle_tayto? Finishing Higher Diploma in Data Science &amp; Business Analytics (12 months, 3 semesters). Welcome to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's thirty seconds closer to midnight... https://t.co/wlBZ9hPAN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatherynWinnick after your amazing performance as Lagertha, what other roles would you like to take on (acting &amp; other)? #winnickwednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @DrJaninaRamirez! https://t.co/betrHKCbZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Indiefilmgirl Yes, it gets very repetitive &amp; loses on power &amp; meaning when found in nearly every CV. I would like to see the alternatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born: Ethiopia. Irish Mum &amp; Ethiopian Dad. In London for the past 11 yrs. Described as “from Limerick” “Irish-Ethio… https://t.co/vLYv2WSgUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't agree either - would be interesting to see an example of CV without these words but conveying the same info… https://t.co/gLKQzEe1lP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much, @WalterPresents! The show is definitely off to a good start, will continue watching! #case https://t.co/Npc1QI0Tpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @WalterPresents, just about to watch #case. Is only the first episode going to be shown on TV and the rest online? This happened before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reklamne alternative facts :-) https://t.co/ntfFttuihZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin today. https://t.co/hYEO50PWeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSueOosthuizen @HouseHistorian @Londonist Fantastic resource as I read Rutherfurd's London!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite coffee places in town! @BrotherHubbardS @BrotherHubbardN #lovindublin #dublin #coffee #coffeemug https://t.co/fgLMkyyB4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Plitvice #winterwonderland https://t.co/cn0nJenqnE #croatia #croatiafulloflife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#eire #ireland #brexit #trump https://t.co/3HetSnS44H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In other towns, clever people go out &amp; make money. In #Dublin, clever pple go home &amp; write their books." A. Enrigh… https://t.co/S6asVZ0tpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful. The past few months have been un-inspiring for me! Not a word to be squeezed out. Kravis shows: look a l… https://t.co/ooa4iUu3OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling the same. Done my 5 km walk, but with heavy heart. Nothing's calling me out of my cozy home... https://t.co/r8Zxn9Hscz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet! An animated movie based on children's tale “Ježeva kuća/Hedgehog's Home”. Will be shown on Berlinale Festival https://t.co/utEMO8CtUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have two homes. I write, passionately, about both. This piece is about my hometown &amp; childhood… https://t.co/YuxQFDWI8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Post40Bloggers A fighter. Heart on sleeve kind of gal. Scatterbrained at times. In love with words, places &amp; people, in my introverted way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lisadwan I admire the ability of actors to do this; it takes much energy, physical &amp; mental strength. Anna Karenina certainly requires it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck, @feelgoodman! Started the book few days ago myself. Enjoyable, for now! 100 pages in. #rutherford #london https://t.co/CaLTIPnEsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneachta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowing lightly on the Ucka mountain... photo Mario Durkic #rijeka #zaljev https://t.co/9MUuyDKIBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coquito_Loquito Ugh, missed the first episode! Hopefully will catch it later... recording from the 2nd episode onwards. #vikings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter is coming! https://t.co/yCkXv3AduZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great TED Talk, @jessicajackley! I have an interview tomorrow, picked up some useful hints. Intrigued by… https://t.co/zjhSn4jtup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like coming to #Dublin for filming? What do you do there in your free time? Favourite sights? #WinnickWednesday @KatherynWinnick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyce's first novel A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man published 100 yrs ago. Centenary marked with map project https://t.co/egvEKKaSzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, the White House was partly built of Croatian Stone, from the Island of Brac. #croatia https://t.co/wKb6Ry8jrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland and been working in HR for the past 10 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland I worked in the travel industry (as a tour guide) in Croatia. Economics is handy, but I also have a degree in Human Resources...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland Studied Economics &amp; Hospitality Management (my first degree). Had I followed my heart, would have studied literature &amp; history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland 1991, when I was deciding what I should study. Looking back, would have made a different choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieOKelly1 Listened to the IT Women's podcast, in which you &amp; others read the Clay! It was wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an ending to the season 2 of #Gomorrah, @damore_marco! Curious to see what lies in store for Don Ciro!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Husband's photos taken in @thomashousedub on Saturday night #lovedublin #dublin https://t.co/5CkWaYBpXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment, @CHIMPSINSOCKS, when we all thought Mary might have survived! #sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rijeka #zaljev Carnival madness captured in the #novine TV show. Loved it. Real carnival starting later this month! https://t.co/BBQDzkmgEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I've let out a little cheer thinking: She's back! And then... https://t.co/h1Dyzu82OA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's here. The first official trailer for THE HANDMAID'S TALE- https://t.co/eAyWUifnvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #NollaignamBan to all the ladies, enjoy #LittleChristmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were brilliant, @KatieOKelly1! https://t.co/oIXH5CNd3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie O’Kelly reads an excerpt from the interview w Joyce's sister Margaret Alice "Poppie", &amp; from Dubliners story,… https://t.co/BUrZXl2aaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dublin tram timetable from 1910. As much of the population was illiterate at the time, the symbols were used to di… https://t.co/phFE8RGoG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched it the other day, it's a lovely movie! Love that part of town as well. https://t.co/1ZcckLCOgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad there will be a season 3, @SalvioEspo! #gomorra3 https://t.co/xYS6UjBYsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a delight to come across @VasjaPinzovski's photos on my Facebook feed. #rijeka #zaljev https://t.co/Ed0rwDFM2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bettiekins Yes, I've read it, it's a great book! Finished the Laszlo story. Though some parts were fascinating, it was very dull at times..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic of this festive time - hard to recall which day of the week it is. Sunday, Monday? Days blend like they rarely do throughout the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#happynewyear #nye2016 https://t.co/PqZIN7C7ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived in the post this morning! A lovely box containing three bags of tea from my hometown's tea shop/bar Samovar… https://t.co/EPDjp4oOau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted by @RadioKorzo on Facebook. The clouds above #rijeka #zaljev this morning were something indeed! https://t.co/NA3GBTh9SZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bettiekins noticed an inconsistency which is pretty annoying. Laszlo is Hungarian, nevertheless he says he has "high Slavic cheekbones" :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading Laszlo's adventures @ the moment, @Bettiekins! I like the period atmosphere in the book, but I agree, it's not an outstanding story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee &amp; a book. Good morning from my cozy corner. https://t.co/nMwrW4nRp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is nice! https://t.co/GifkJ97J6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_andmother Never thought of it :-) It is a little water fountain I think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gornjapolica Jesi li pogledala The Young Pope? Law ce te iznenaditi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This scene :-) #HailCaesar https://t.co/GEPLfNpchg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lisadwan You were superb as Anna! An unforgettable afternoon in the @AbbeyTheatre Certain things haven't changed for women since Tolstoy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna Karenina @AbbeyTheatre. Wonderful. Poignant. #theatre #drama #dublin #lovedublin #lovindublin https://t.co/MIOQMmLuUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, @nyfdublin, will check the program for sure :-) https://t.co/NGSxHNFOSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my New Year's resolutions: to let in more colours, more sounds. #templebar #lovindublin #lovedublin #dublin… https://t.co/gHy9DgRUIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I miss anything? Tourists checking their maps, rolling suitcases. Freezing wind made the chapped skin on my hand feel like it's burning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then I got to Grafton Street &amp; saw the queues. On a bitterly cold St Stephen's Day morning. Could list 101 things,… https://t.co/vd0DuHoPx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I stood in the middle of Church Lane to take a photo of St Andrew's Church. #lovedublin #lovindublin https://t.co/EUZOR8yTKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful sunrise perhaps. A scene, or a detail I wouldn't have normally seen amidst the usual chaos of people, cars and buses everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I decided to go into town so early this morning? It must be because of this nagging feeling that I am missing out on something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear his voice and all of a sudden I am thirteen again, leaned against the the schoolyard wall. #RIPGeorgeMichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas, @IrlEmbCroatia! https://t.co/x5pv7ECftR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must do this! Good for taking photos without people and cars everywhere. https://t.co/0U266pMk5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PocketaPocketa that sounds good! Prague must be lovely at this time of year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, @PocketaPocketa, hope you're enjoying this holiday season, Merry Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone! #ChristmasEve #happychristmas https://t.co/TWfftDwf89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Victorian ghost story set on #Christmas Day: A Strange Christmas Game https://t.co/7ddpOgGp0N #amreading #merrychristmas #shortstory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas in #Dublin https://t.co/a55MPb0SDQ #merrychristmas #dublinatchristmas #lovindublin #lovedublin #visitdublin @discoverdublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was some year for my dear friend @ERMurray! She has done so much. Elizabeth, wishing you &amp; Mick a Merry Christma… https://t.co/fTweW8g6tB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The timeless story of James &amp; the Snowman at @stpatrickscath. Morgan Crowley &amp; the choir did a marvellous job, in b… https://t.co/zHBsxkBKCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making my favourite winter meal #stuffedpeppers #food https://t.co/1W5XQFVLbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Newgrange myth busted :-( "the “roof box” which was central to capturing the winter light has “not a shred of authenticity” via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching a Croatian movie, "I Believe In Angels". And this scene is... aahhh! Want to live in a place like this! On… https://t.co/2pwZ65NNa6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>