<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft speeds up genomic sequencing for doctors fighting cancer via Puget Sound Business Journal  https://t.co/amg7eUAni2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my most popular #marketing tweets from yesteryear : Potbelly v Subway https://t.co/b1o7qFh9QW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switch from Dynamics CRM Online to Dynamics 365 (online)  https://t.co/pLo7szV3OR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State and local IT spending to grow in 2017 via GCN  https://t.co/4dhJ1BYlOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me impatient, but some business meetings make me subconsciously reach for the fast forward button.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog -- inviting #Startups to Disrupt the Public Sector https://t.co/wDTGveo2dF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand Makeovers  viaThe Partner Channel #marketing  https://t.co/scOCHPWTwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: #DigitalTransformation with #ClickDimensions and Dynamics 365  https://t.co/sFrVCq5OzD  #msdyn365 https://t.co/CKjtpNiLg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's next for government innovation groups? (such as @18F) via @FCWNow  https://t.co/19ltKGf3eG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Create a Fast Track for Your Sales Process https://t.co/WOAjAnIEWj https://t.co/sx2bKRfjlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping Up with Microsoft Dynamics GP - Microsoft Dynamics GP Community https://t.co/2YgZfTmFWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft #SharePoint Training Courses via Microsoft Virtual Academy  https://t.co/RuPSXcRPsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM for political campaigns https://t.co/18DPBlM9ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel the objective of customer service is to close the case  rather than solve my problem #custserv https://t.co/j25uK0Z4wH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics Marketing today and what comes next  – Microsoft Dynamics 365 Team blog #msdyn365   https://t.co/8UKQ6ri8Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM for Government Contractors #govcon #mscrm https://t.co/1v1XI1NzH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Power Hour: PowerApp Galleries via YouTube  https://t.co/T1myEtutfa #sharepoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Service Hints: don't explain your internal processes -- just fix the problem #custserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics #GovCon Alliance  https://t.co/IriwDHz5Bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM for Correspondence Management https://t.co/HmQ8wgtoK8 https://t.co/yNOxo8OMSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In business software, sometimes "one size fits all" means it fits no one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Dev Center - New SharePoint CSOM version released for #SharePoint Online  https://t.co/M7HK0uqYZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Standalone CRM is Not Enough #MSCRM https://t.co/7OXRQNyurR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Top Challenges to #DigitalTransformation - Microsoft Dynamics Blog by @TriciaEMorris   https://t.co/Tw93e0ruuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the long term implications of your short term business decisions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tap the power of Microsoft Dynamics 365 directly from Microsoft Outlook via YouTube #msdyn365   https://t.co/24mRW0cY5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM and Office 365 bundle https://t.co/NhHELbSobA https://t.co/sOz0HQpJZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins APL, Navy Demonstrate Autonomous Swarming Unmanned Surface Vessels  https://t.co/30DOsEyoxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: "6 Reasons Microsoft's #LinkedIn Acquisition is Different" https://t.co/SR4Qh0K7je #microsoftlinkedin #msft https://t.co/C0ePikG29o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs To Lead #DigitalTransformation In 2017 via @forbes   https://t.co/JwqM4BlrQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2015 Upgrade is Time to Consider Deployment Change https://t.co/JTqlJZxXus https://t.co/uqVB2eQern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm starting my Twitter day earlier for the sake of my UK and European followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics 365 First Look video #msdyn365 https://t.co/unQafPI6uV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Microsoft Software Licensing for Non-Profits https://t.co/oxV6VqC12k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics 365 for Sales - User's Guide formerly CRM #msdyn365   https://t.co/6tHQuxPE1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merylkevans good point -- some only have first name in their signature though so I think they are just not offering contact info]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[InfoStrat re-certified as DC Certified Business Enterprise (CBE) https://t.co/jEy7dbDggN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Understanding Microsoft AppSource and Dynamics 365
https://t.co/74jepF79YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expected Impact of Trump Administration on Government Contractors #govcon  https://t.co/KGmXY0nXyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Don't use email when talking is better https://t.co/nlVxnb7wQp https://t.co/jxzbTf8u84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to people who email me: a signature with your phone number can come in handy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What .NET Developers ought to know to start in 2017 - Scott Hanselman  https://t.co/ektGlnJyH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Things That No Longer Matter in Business https://t.co/n2nDZJ9Pk9 #startup https://t.co/uehkXtu4m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Azure Logic Apps innovation – general availability of cloud-based Enterprise Integration Pack   https://t.co/wEowrVmk3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Holly Springs teachers tap technology to ignite young minds - Microsoft Enterprise https://t.co/RMNC7gaufX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My LinkedIn Post: Cloud First is Better than Cloud Only   https://t.co/DjQWdI4TDp https://t.co/vQVQGXfNTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create Account-Relevant Messages in #ABM by @Alex_Sessoms   https://t.co/olm5YwEUCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the Common Data Model used in Microsoft Dynamics 365 https://t.co/IBIRR37tKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Webinar Video: Marketing in Dynamics #CRM with ClickDimensions 
https://t.co/A3b5Fkr0Tm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the video on how Dynamics 365 uses the Common Data Model with PowerApps &amp; Flow : https://t.co/VRGnAnmt5N  https://t.co/VRGnAnmt5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish all news sites would include Twitter handles in text created by Tweet this buttons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Office 365 Roadmap 
https://t.co/iCY5XmAcSR https://t.co/dsR17vej76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Handy Opportunity Views in Dynamics CRM #MSCRM https://t.co/vIkF9GWCpF https://t.co/CakqGc4rE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics 365 subscription pricing for non-profits is $28.75 for Plan 1 Bundle   #msdyn365 https://t.co/0yE7X89X84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it's wired when: a government RFP for IT services comes out with three days to respond #govcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Service Hints: don't assume it's the customer's fault  #custserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics GP is not going away any time soon. via Martin Olsen    https://t.co/d9ZBC71bE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Holly Springs teachers tap technology to ignite young minds - Microsoft Enterprise https://t.co/Mxb9hXWWXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Favorite Fanatics of 2016 via @BillGates  https://t.co/nsmQtrzkqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Ten Things You Need to Know about Microsoft Software Licensing https://t.co/yjAQ3KFYlN https://t.co/FRpVHOtkMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fine print on Dynamics 365 Team Members https://t.co/D4VBZgHO0c #msdyn365]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: #CRM for criminal investigations https://t.co/08ijWSLFKy https://t.co/eQRb1LVqzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[easyJet offers instant customer sat poll after airport security #custserv  - press a button to rate your experience https://t.co/u9YXNJxfQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 of the Greatest Lessons I’ve Learned as an Entrepreneur via Medium #startup   https://t.co/SE6cLWsY8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM for executive scheduling https://t.co/bCOwCjhQc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aligning the Organization for Its Digital Future via MITSloan #digitaltransformation  https://t.co/wFtxxYPSle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Tracking Government Subcontract Opportunities in CRM https://t.co/rbdngt7m3M https://t.co/HtqN7IWQ9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who gets the mural? Clyde's of Tysons to close in short order, clearing way for new development https://t.co/Vv6y5GPL1H via @WBJonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the Common Data Model used in Microsoft Dynamics 365 https://t.co/ixfEMnvnVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet some of the people at the heart of digital transformation happening at Microsoft, thanks in part to Office 365. https://t.co/PXUgs0DVyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for a walk because my watch thinks I'm being lazy and it might be right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neostek @InfoGovCon you are the man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guess you need a hardhat to do that @CrestwoodAssoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking the AppSource Path for Dynamics 365 via @SteveMordue #msdyn365   https://t.co/Vaul3cDCWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Microsoft Dynamics CRM MVPs and their Blogs #MSCRM https://t.co/rB4yTjZaRS https://t.co/NltUzO5ZOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measuring the impact of #marketing on sales is fiendishly difficult, especially for small business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folloze approved on Microsoft Apps Store #ABM account-based marketing via @folloze   https://t.co/EqDJj5R1OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: Dynamics CRM integrations for government contractors #govcon https://t.co/RfNOXjZtlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft can help you find the right solutions to transform your business in a mobile-first, cloud-first world. https://t.co/CZ0cYRvUxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Atlanta to Lisbon, discover how Digital Transformation empowers one classroom to travel the world. https://t.co/gLILObQbof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Teams in Office 365 and Dynamics 365 team up to increase your productivity, improve customer experience  https://t.co/8uPbnyekRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Power Hour: PowerApp Galleries via YouTube  https://t.co/T1myEtutfa #sharepoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s How to Set Goals This Year That You Can Actually Meet https://t.co/VCBvqPFkQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Startups: How to Learn from Mistakes of Others" by @jamestownsend on @LinkedIn https://t.co/XA4EIvQVav https://t.co/GZVw4Y4ZZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics 365 SDK Backwards Compatibility  #msdyn365  https://t.co/AXChvN452Q https://t.co/Iqbb04T3Zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuaverville but good for marketing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my most popular #marketing tweets from yesteryear : Potbelly v Subway https://t.co/b1o7qFh9QW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to see one of your major home appliances fail?  Wait until the warranty expires and invite lots to family to stay with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you sign up for a trial Microsoft cloud subscription, be sure to buy it before it lapses if you want the domain name you chose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data 2017: The future is cloudy https://t.co/8xgzqEaN7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: You May Not Need as Many CRM Reports as You Think https://t.co/3LwQqJbFte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switch from Dynamics CRM Online to Dynamics 365 (online)  https://t.co/pLo7szV3OR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meaningless word to add to software requirements: "intuitive"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For your quick reference favs: Microsoft #Dynamics global pricing list https://t.co/5PGIogIcJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Blog: Microsoft's New CRM Product: Project Service https://t.co/z4IByyQPmo https://t.co/mrHXwAT42M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johns Hopkins APL, Navy Demonstrate Autonomous Swarming Unmanned Surface Vessels  https://t.co/30DOsEyoxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Simple CRM Tips for Small Government Contractors: from my blog https://t.co/JoB58oA9SG #govcon https://t.co/JOuSIsQOdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a hard time closing browser tabs I'm not using, much less throwing away stuff I'm unlikely to use again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Extensibility Options for Dynamics 365 via YouTube #msdyn365   https://t.co/kTql7tT3dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My blog: The Responsibility of Entrepreneurship  https://t.co/U1GmkBYnDK https://t.co/NvgYGAlW4C]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>