<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@etnow @MattMurph24 #TheTrumpEffect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katu01 @DavidYankovich If the Fed government owns rights they will sell, rights but not land no revenue. Louisiana is in that mess w Gulf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidYankovich I can make a few calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mediumvillain @maudglib There is that, the flip side I'm gonna start a church worshipping myself collect money tax free and lobby for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand Only 5 k per year but what else does this verbiage open up!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza @tmwinsett We are fucked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bros4America @JJohnson2u  Read 2nd Timothy Chapter 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prisonculture @soit_goes Help spread the word. https://t.co/A6wytxIBvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important folks my rep was Trump's hype man. So call all you reps #StopPresidentBannon https://t.co/Nej0Yxct37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRomeiPHD You're welcome and thank you for your service. I'm gonna defend the #MilitarySpouse sisters and brothers at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRomeiPHD Well I agree with that.  As a mil spouse for 30 years I can't say I'd show him the respect normally shown to the office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRomeiPHD Who took that picture? I thought she wanted privacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics @JJohnson2u Never occurred to him people my boycott because of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan @DunkelMary He is after all a rich white guy with nothing to lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton I believe the entire GOP is compromised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BruceBartlett @Mediaite I'd vote to change the law for that. Like today can we do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shoq Nope he'll try to reinstate the draft, then learn politics is an ever so fickle mistress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BunchOfPuppits Should be fair to the people. Look at NC, that's some crazy stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BunchOfPuppits I think gerrymandering is keeping the voice of moderate everyone from being heard. Districting shouldn't favor one party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolynMcC Well there's that this entire ordeal is one big mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolynMcC @realDonaldTrump Now that I believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolynMcC @realDonaldTrump He met with big Pharma, they said no. Behind the scenes a campaign contribution since he's file papers already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@activist360 Last wars we fought in Asia didn't turn out as expected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Yeah I should have added that company to my portfolio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Yep, that's for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Time will tell won't it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs No arguments from me I've been a mil spouse for 30 years. People would think twice about these crazy people if their kids suited up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs @BarackObama Yep only one cup this AM no do overs with Twitter either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Sheesh I thought you said 4 years ago, only one cup this AM whoops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs They're not that loyal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Those people with "economic anxiety" it's their kids by and large that are gonna do the fighting,. What if he brings on the draft?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Our world with technology is a gift,  to people who choose to educate themselves. I try to learn something new daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs Let's see 2006 my mortgage rate was 6.125 in 2012 3.25, bigger house better schools, more money in the bank. I am better off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs I used to watch a show called The Following with Kevin Bacon, had forgotten that thing like that actually happened in history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs I like PBO, did not would not follow him blindly. Too many people take Trump's words as gospel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeLevinCA @Schwarzenegger Well of course if show gets cancelled he loses $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarrenRowley @DavidYankovich Crickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atleecs My wonder/fear is that entire GOP has been compromised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fmrgreenberet 14 hit the street to do God knows what. We own too, not everyone needs to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fmrgreenberet We have a Crime stoppers show on our community cable channel last week 14 weapons were stolen out of unlocked cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance Is it possible for the entire GOP to be compromised!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaShanneStokes Perhaps he could show that publicly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @Deanofcomedy I call an end to this now! I'm a 30 year mil spouse telling you both to go to your corners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaTCardona @Reuters Obama vetoed the raid because the Intel wasn't good risk vs benefit. Here we have a man who won't do Intel briefing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandiLib Trying to take our eyes off the raid in Yemen and Putin bombing the crap out of Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse So are you warming up your investigatory chops!?! https://t.co/kGlnvd3a46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaHol @prisonculture @bpolitics That means they'll change a few paragraphs and take credit for the success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I don't want my son to die because you want the oil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roflmaoism @Sharon_L_C What he did to Leslie Jones let's not forget that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineHatf19 Oh I've seen people shut down for less, I was buzzed Tweeting l/n. No telling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDejam @MalcolmNance @jihadwatchRS Is he Richard's father!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prisonculture Not if they can, if they have the will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Would you sponsor a bill limiting political contributions in Florida!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweeps this is what Trump's hype man is promising let's give him some phone love. https://t.co/V2X1ErAyU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Many people are saying that #PresidentBannon is running the show because you don't know what the hell is going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So how many of your children are signing up to fight for our country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Which one of your children are you sending to fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports That's a real fact, this White House only deals with Alternative Facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@epitomee @kbeninato Did you see the video where he lost Rudi Guilani and he was right in front of him!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbeninato I thought he had tons of stamina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomadlives @trumpbigregrets @realDonaldTrump @voxdotcom They just said no, he's no negotiator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mworobec @trumpbigregrets @realDonaldTrump To Trump and Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mworobec @trumpbigregrets @realDonaldTrump Oil matters more than your countrymen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mworobec @trumpbigregrets @seanhannity @realDonaldTrump You need to start call your Senators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigCo62 @MalcolmNance @YahooNews Why does anyone think chaos is good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanmdav Do you know who he actually is!?! Ask Leslie Jones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance He promised to it in his campaign speeches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA It is like the entire GOP is compromised or something. All of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProgressOutlook Yep cause he projects, his  minions are now using the term on TV too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kate_Goldsmith Used the death of a SEAL as a photo op, his press secretary released his wife's name. Killed a bunch of civilians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mla1396 @nailbomb3 Insufficient Intel, ordered by a guy who doesn't do Intel briefings. https://t.co/HrMrDpWyuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA That's the date that will put something in you drink when ur not looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 The illegal word is for his minions, to keep them loyal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @POTUS History will not be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can we ban people like this guy too!?! https://t.co/2T0l6sHVL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babblefishie @th3j35t3r Have you noticed that they all only go so far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregAbbott_TX @keranews He cut funding to the state capitol where he is governor. https://t.co/VTGyewFIvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@th3j35t3r @DaWh33L Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@th3j35t3r He's said not one thing about the OP in the Ukraine, neither has any GOP. Starting to think they've all been compromised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @jljac1313 And Vlad is raining rockets on Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes but Putin is raining rockets on Ukraine don't you care about that!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@th3j35t3r Look at this. https://t.co/2RdQ2UmBXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prisonculture @soit_goes WV y'all. Not a lot but brave. https://t.co/3NS1rQOWp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IraqiSecurity @MalcolmNance @realDonaldTrump Mexico is going to invite China to build a base at this rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindyfinn @realDonaldTrump We know why he has no friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews Careful out there folks! We love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul It's noticed they won't do anything about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@albertxpat @JJohnson2u 2nd time I've been a refugee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAOpolitics one of my followers the article is from Reuters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scholtz73 Look legal residents can become citizens, citizens become voters. Frightened that they won't be majority in a few years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAOpolitics ICYMI What the hell!?! https://t.co/YylousLjDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RAOpolitics @SFGate #Berkeley Since forever they aren't having any crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prisonculture Berkeley set it off, Tangerine Terror will try to put the next peaceful protest down hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clutch_Mat @ScoonJenkins @bertuck5 @mateagold @DavidCornDC @washingtonpost They just told him no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallySallys @WSJ Yeah I know me too me too. I probs should go to confession for some  of the things I think about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallySallys @WSJ 2018 when we get the assholes out of there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willcarless ICYMI, We are in some trouble here. https://t.co/G1pQcB2oay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColMorrisDavis We are in a lot of trouble if people are loyal to him and not country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@th3j35t3r I don't know what the hell that was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallySallys @WSJ Russia they have shit on the GOP.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>