<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Star packed @ianmastersmedia show on #SCOTUS &amp; #JeffSessions with @CommonCause @acslaw @AFJustice &amp; @prwatch 
https://t.co/1vFX80jtOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so about that separation between the Trump Org and the White House...
https://t.co/ybXj7gF1JM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asmith83 I was just thinking that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOTE: Donald Trump announces SCOTUS pick at 8pm. CNN has a town hall with Pelosi at 9pm. Great timing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CommonCause President @KHobertFlynn asks: What was Jeff Sessions’ role in Trump’s immigration order?
https://t.co/j5Y3glgqAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you are an asshole @DonaldJTrumpJr 
https://t.co/OOCLcsOsrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question: what happens if Trump says he is appointing both Gorsuch &amp; Hardiman to #SCOTUS tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Koch personally called Mike Pence days before the inauguration
https://t.co/UbM0Z4rnpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former FCC Chair &amp; @CommonCause advisor @coppsm calls @realDonaldTrump's 2-for-1 reg EO unnecessary &amp; dangerous
https://t.co/RmkulywUxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mddems are pushing to rescind state's call for #ArticleV convention as constitutional threats rise in Trump era
https://t.co/9aT0yFUVZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer is lying about SCOTUS opening in last term of a president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CommonCause: Senate Must Stop Sessions Nomination in Wake of Immigration Ban &amp; Rash Firing of Acting A.G. Yates
https://t.co/GMZi9uIPTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merrick Garland tells me this is false.
https://t.co/s4cK6WxPHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sloppy: DeVos appears to have plagiarized her questionnaire to the Senate
https://t.co/2g1vdCqXDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyletblaine we are still waiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@springsteen's "Wrecking Ball" was released in 2012 during Obama's reelect, but is really an inspiration for resistance in the Trump era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: @CommonCause calls for @senjudiciary to delay Sessions vote &amp; hold more hearings on #MuslimBan.
https://t.co/tJ8kJdKUDC #StopSessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PatToomey credits the Koch network (not @realDonaldTrump or PA voters) for his 2016 reelection.… https://t.co/6rj2sSAlI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Carter, opposing party of POTUS wins 19.3 House seats on average in midterms (24.8 since 1994)

Ds need 25 to win the House in 2018]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's HHS Nominee Tom Price Got Privileged, Discounted Offer on Biomedical Stock, Company Says
https://t.co/cMRJKEyxcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling President Obama won't be staying silent over the next 4 years
https://t.co/GQJ3arSu6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So after 10 years of not having complete control of the federal government, Republicans sure have made a mess of this place in one week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if @realDonaldTrump's #SCOTUS nominee will have an opinion on this case or disclosure in general...
https://t.co/fVlJlLLtx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega-merger alert: Comcast tried &amp; failed to buy Time Warner Cable. Charter then bought TWC. Verizon bought AOL &amp; now wants to buy Charter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa
https://t.co/bJZbxKPP8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: the Kochs spent millions on Senate ads bashing @HillaryClinton and helping @realDonaldTrump &amp; Republicans
https://t.co/PTf198t9jd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure if we are chanting "don't build the wall!" or "hands too small!" #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/hL8KkZGdGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History is weird. The Republican Party both saved the Union (Lincoln) and is about to destroy it (Trump).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeah, this is why I'm not just going to forgive and forget when it comes to Trump voters
https://t.co/YojofF641i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenJohnMcCain - who is much smarter &amp; more experience than @realDonaldTrump - basically just said Trump is doing everything wrong on MTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see @NBCNews has @KimStrassel on @MeetThePress w/ @chucktodd this AM. I turn the channel &amp; watch @FaceTheNation w/ @johndickerson instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon has a seat on National Security Council and the joint chiefs of staff does not
https://t.co/nusp23CT5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art Pope use to like nonpartisan redistricting reform in NC. Not so much anymore.
https://t.co/UdXWDPuea9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump still hasn't come to terms with the fact that he LOST the popular vote by 3 MILLION votes. Sad!
https://t.co/Q05zd29mAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Judicial panel orders Wisconsin to redraw legislative districts due to partisan gerrymandering before 2018
https://t.co/QWodN2xasE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird for me to hear an administration that supports torture, the death penalty, &amp; war discuss the sanctity for life. #MarchforLife2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President of the United States - who controls the largest nuclear arsenal in the world - is mentally unstable 
https://t.co/QgfydVMiLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems like a really good use of taxpayer money
https://t.co/lusW5oSawD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if the media is truly the opposition party to Trump, then for this first week the score is media 1,… https://t.co/VdNJsHIB77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@rickhasen unlikely but let's see if they will

cc @campaignfreedom @CommishSmith @ProtectTheFirst @KimStrassel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what do you think @GroverNorquist?
https://t.co/lnlCu4y3mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All are career foreign service officers who have served under both Republican and Democratic administrations."
https://t.co/qHD4HgsjG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is another example of the Kochs actively gutting reform efforts. Check out @by_jmiller piece from last year: https://t.co/LHwI7Lae0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koch brothers' advocacy org is pushing #sdleg to repeal voter-approved law that strengthens ethics &amp; disclosure 
https://t.co/RfhOlEfe52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sdgop's work to repeal voter-approved ethics law has received national criticism in @nytimes @washingtonpost @MSNBC @HuffingtonPost #sdleg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothycsimons imagine an 18 month interview when you warned everyone you were going to be this bad and you still got the job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so are they going to cut $8-14 billion out of some other program?
https://t.co/vAs4mD645G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible idea: GOP bills in NH, VA, &amp; MN attempt to award electoral votes by (gerrymandered) congressional districts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guy reviewing conflicts for Trump Org:
- challenged McCain-Feingold
- chairman of dark money group Crossroads GPS
https://t.co/fW0VMmPMWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[acting head of Trump's DOJ Civil Rights Division helped Texas Republicans write their discriminatory voter ID law
https://t.co/YOC94yEzZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @CommonCauseCA &amp; @commoncauseny will have something to say about this
https://t.co/alwbnWcDut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When @POTUS lies about voting actions of millions of Americans he directly threatens democracy" - @ChapmanAllegra 
https://t.co/sJaUCLoNey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @BadlandsNPS for tweeting
https://t.co/aOKWbJgPlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has signed nearly a dozen executive orders so far....none on his promise for lobbying reform. https://t.co/Kopjt6hSmW #draintheswamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s 1st congressional endorser, Rep. Chris Collins (R-NY), also said there’s no evidence of massive voter fraud: https://t.co/Z9nlMqlZ0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan (https://t.co/gokOMPdp5Q) &amp; McCain (https://t.co/bMwfp6mvii) &amp; Graham: (https://t.co/DRap220yVV) push back on Trump's voter fraud lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Secretary of State in Ohio &gt;
https://t.co/BWbqkBYdql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buckle up folks. Trump's war on voting is set to launch. 
https://t.co/lyyMPu1eVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what lies @PressSec will tell tomorrow to derail @realDonaldTrump's message on immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PREDICTION: @PressSec is not good at his job and won't last long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is an irresponsible tweet
https://t.co/XYbgPtiVLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, then who did McCain vote for?
https://t.co/p0ZnQNW4U3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's likely SCOTUS nominee Neil Gorduch struck down Colorado's campaign finance contribution limits
https://t.co/EDlI3L2bWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@washingtonpost points out @realDonaldTrump is full of shit
https://t.co/0sS43ROf0O https://t.co/LOgqcrfyAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Marco will do whatever his donors and Trump want him too
https://t.co/HrOaNdslzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pai has been a friendly guest speaker at #ALEC, lobbying org funded by Comcast, Verizon, Time Warner Cable, &amp; AT&amp;T
https://t.co/pt3QNAtQkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a 10 point drop in 2 months, in between Trump naming megadonors &amp; Wall Street execs to his cabinet, not acting on business conflicts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 CNN polls on how likely it is Trump will reduce corruption:

Nov 2016: 51%
https://t.co/pBdTTzKM6l

Jan 2017: 41%
https://t.co/q2NdvOkKFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaMirandoCNN can't find that question in the full survey. Do you have it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“President Trump won’t be draining the swamp, he will be swimming in it" - @CommonCause's @ThePaulSRyan 
https://t.co/0qJvdylP5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case someone hasn't told you already today Jason, I will: you are a piece of shit.
https://t.co/uiRs5Jj670]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS GUY BUILDS BUILDINGS IN THE US WITH CHINESE STEEL AND HIRES LOW WAGE IMMIGRANT WORKERS. HE IS FULL OF SHIT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is giving government "back" to the people by putting a bunch of millionaires, billionaires, &amp; career politicians in his cabinet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is a class act, unlike the incoming president
https://t.co/0xP1TYhPcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginsburg better stay alive for the next four years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just made a "getting through next 4 years" playlist w/ lots of @springsteen @StevieVanZandt @PearlJam @SteveEarle @pattismith @WoodyGuthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is amazing
https://t.co/q5tY4f6RZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBlu from last night's transcript, it sounds like Trump is leaning towards Cruz's plan to elimination contributions for full disclosure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@springsteen gave the Obamas a private concert last week
https://t.co/e11mlUC7qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 fed law enforcement &amp; intelligence agencies are investigating whether Russia covertly funneled money to help Trump
https://t.co/f0N2FiG3DO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone ought to bring this up at hearing of @realDonaldTrump's EPA nominee who is a climate denier #PollutingPruitt
https://t.co/70iTdImls7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pollutingPruitt is a former member &amp; speaker @ #ALEC, which was dumped by Google, Facebook, Yahoo, eBay, &amp; Shell over #climate denial. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump's EPA nominee has put big energy donors ahead of enviro &amp; health safeguards
https://t.co/Nt5JEnFHUv #pollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@commoncauseny renews call for @NYGovCuomo to make campaign finance &amp; ethics reform a priority for 2017
https://t.co/KLjxGn5VBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles may be improving their citizen-funded elections program this year: https://t.co/uOgAKjQ2iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CommonCauseNC calls on @SenatorBurr &amp; @SenThomTillis to reject Jeff Sessions as Attorney General
https://t.co/xB8PuQ4rc5 #StopSessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump got Toby Keith, 3 Doors Down, Lee Greenwood

Obama got Springsteen, Aretha Franklin, Beyonce, Garth Brooks, U2, Usher +more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Approval rating for President-elects before inauguration
Clinton: 68%
GW Bush: 61%
Obama: 83%
Trump: 44%
https://t.co/BcYdPG10QC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frazierallen extremely disrespectful &amp; unAmerican to say people who dedicate their lives civil &amp; human rights and rule of law don't matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes everything better
https://t.co/AGGbFYUxmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great - foreign leaders are trying to use Putin to influence Trump. Good job America
https://t.co/NnUSO2RSiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe it's time we rethink presidential term limits
https://t.co/vnwG4E9CBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Lewis: ‘I Don’t See Trump as a Legitimate President’
https://t.co/ANgOTIRK2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is a reason why this story is in Buzzfeed this week
https://t.co/nDKJU05GFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain's former attorney lays out why Donald Trump hasn't solved his conflicts of interest problem:
https://t.co/CB6E20slZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If all of these events and stories were taking place in another country, we'd say that country had become unstable

https://t.co/CPiPNwCEat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum someone tell Chris politics isn't a sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna miss these two
https://t.co/xPzqiNYipq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't realize 60% of the country were employed as journalists
https://t.co/PgWJUsKu7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it stuffy in here]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>