<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna do this @NationalTheatre. Despite the sand, don't bring your bucket and spade. Delighted to be on board. https://t.co/Ib4TWJGILi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @realDonaldTrump @LBC You must mean the "alternative" democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final run through on the @AbbeyTheatre roof for @24HourPlaysDub. These guys rocking it #24hrdub https://t.co/ZtxHzKPzwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PallantPallant I can hear your voice when I read this https://t.co/P1ZLIthzcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell on the Special Relationship. Other end of this picture on Monday featuring Turkey's Erdogan? https://t.co/0Ihyjk3fye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienmark me and Gilljo sitting on a bus in London admiring this x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much did the gov spend on  fighting #Brexitruling and what exactly were they afraid of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianloydanderson alright dude. Seeing you next Thursday. Looking forward x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama day v Trump day. Lordy.  #Inauguration https://t.co/dG7A7y37IX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seumas Milne quits The Guardian for Labour long after The Guardian quit Labour, Socialism, true equality and the thinking working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lufthansa many thanks. Have completed the form. I look forward to a response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute RUDEST air hostess on @lufthansa LH 0936 from Frankfurt. Smarmy insults to passengers. Clearly in the wrong job. Nice flight ruined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#brexit great 4 #DonaldTrump coz then he and other unscrupulous dudes can build without those pesky Euro environmental law thingys. Go UK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienmark We'll take it. I thought we had it, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienmark 1-3. Rooney breaks wind on the bench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the @LFC online shop just muck or is it a scam to try and stop using gift card? Have tried for days to use one and no joy. Demented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many trains cancelled @ London Bridge tonight. Thanks @SouthernRailUK &amp; @TheresaMay_MP Misery brought on by anti-un… https://t.co/6TZtcsk84z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amandatravel ask Labour. Point is the elected gov behind the misery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're caught up in #southernstrike today, remember the words "Tory" and "who fucking elected them?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilsonjames_23 squeaky bum time #LIVWHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManusHalligan Cavan is more exotic, but.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there any Remain voters out there who now really really regret their decision? Asking for a friend. #brexit #brexitdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fusion_LS nice one. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MesserBest Mane and Coutinho too big a loss. Henderson very quiet. No leaders. Fell apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fusion_LS overflowing bins outside Forest Hill pools. Up to staff to keep area clean? https://t.co/hJH5Nr63v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes @jeremycorbyn this is bullshit. You need to up your game, man. Less of the usual politics-speak https://t.co/dXHUd2fLTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAdamChrist Maeve and myself were at this. This was worth the price of the ticket. Enjoy. https://t.co/nlmyb5M6gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am thinking Twitter missed an opportunity to call this game #ARSEBURN. Too bad. #ARSBOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThierryHenry calling handball against @Arsenal. That man should NEVER talk about handball. ever. Ever. EVER #ARSBOU #IrelandvFranceRobbery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the world becomes more polarised, I'd like to nail my colours to the mast by stating that @MailOnline is Satan's spunk formed in letters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at @harveynormanIE trying to wipe everyones eye.  Good example of what a shameless con the day actually is https://t.co/jixHg3Wsyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How bad must you have been in your last life to end up in that 7th Circle of Hell that is customer service for trai… https://t.co/XKGllgWy1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonpal70 thanks for coming dude x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simone1Kirby @shoddyroddy youse did that to me I'd be sitting beside both of you *heavy breathing*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DulwichHamletFC people just cheered. I think they just got served.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pubtheatres1 thanks for the correction #RigorMortis @TheHopeTheatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sian_Rowland @pubtheatres1 thanks a mill for that x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sian_Rowland Hi Siân. Many thanks 4 the review of RIGOR MORTIS. Just wondering about a correction. Part of Jimmy played by Michael Quinlan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boys from RIGOR MORTIS. Play what I directed. Almost sold out here in London. 16 tix left!… https://t.co/QOPAwqkQXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stonking sold out show with the #RigorMortis boys tonight. Almost sold out for the rest of the run. Get in there!… https://t.co/g2lh9EVvWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First night for the boys of #RigorMortis. They're in fine fettle @PConnaughton1 @TheHopeTheatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MesserBest careful dude- according to recent global patterns, she'll be Queen of England one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Molly_NYC @GeorgeTakei incredibly hard in such a polarised country as the US. Centre ground-re your def-is a no mans land. Fallow ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always slightly disturbed by big men wearing black nail polish...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelegraphNews her point is when there IS no nhs...why do I bother...you know this- you're just brainwashing the stupid people. And it works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei oh George. "Centrist" is what led to the problem. No one knows the difference. You're Right or Left. And you're Left. Enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched #questiontime. @KenLoachSixteen unafraid to tell it like it really is. He's the bees knees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo Hard luck, darlin. Maybe a peno there. Would have changed the whole game. The 'pool over the hoodoo, but. X #CRYLIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo ok, headers count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo cracking match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo only deflections off the head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo headers shouldn't count]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahReevo playing our hoodoo team tonight. Mind you... #CRYLIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've made it when you're in the jacks #RigorMortis @TheHopeTheatre https://t.co/k3iHBmL484 https://t.co/QHdOou7Nwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come see this! https://t.co/fV2bZUSgsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a Tory Party political broadcast by @BBCr4today on #UniversalCredit with IDSmith. Soft questions, zero balance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthernRailUK I teach my kids that "sorry" means "I won't do it again". I'm not feeling that with your announcements... #TimeToNationalise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easyJet thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stumac1974 @easyJet try Budapest to Gatwick- more than 3 hours. However, got £3 off my £15 burger, so that balances it out, I guess...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emsler maybe I'll go book a hotel and get the head down for an hour or two! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello @easyJet. Is there compensation for flights delayed more than 3 hours? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @guardian is left-leaning, why does it only mention Tories by name and never Labour peeps? This their way of continuing #Corbyn grudge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerHerrin true but from what I see here, it's rosy in the garden. Need to see thoughts of #ukip and #kkk (apologies if you see it too now)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to the excellent #AdamCurtis we're being fed a diet of what we already agree with. Best to confuse the algorithm so? #ilovenazis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdoch lapdogs @TheSun out in force against @GaryLineker this evening. Sad little people have to make a living too, I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I support #DontBuyTheSun though I need Sky Sports to see TV footy. However I'd support millionaire working class players over scumbag hacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kant77 @MomentumTrump2 and MomentumTrump have marked their own card this evening- 1 or 2 toffs who disdain and put down working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kant77 @MomentumTrump2 Nothing wrong with being any class! It's how you perceive other classes that marks your card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomentumTrump2 so what are we dealing with here- A comfortable kid with Tory parents having a safe little laugh with some dolls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomentumTrump2 you clearly know absolutely nothing about the working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationalexpress you're a NIGHTMARE! Took me longer to navigate your broken website than it took you to build it. Your app is even worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simone1Kirby @fitzykizzy I know- it's like a contradiction in terms. Lovin yer gúna what I saw xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simone1Kirby @fitzykizzy not before I get there first. See you Friday, Fitz. Mwah haw haw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run #Brexit ref again. Now if you vote leave, you know you're only voting to close the borders and for absolutely nothing else of worth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 16th of shitting October. Shame on you #B&amp;Q https://t.co/CNEFSVj23Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulinewright2 @LibrarySE23 @crowdfunderuk my pleasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #TheresaMay finished her sermon yet? Can we all leave the church and go home for Sunday dinner now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Britain to become a sovereign country" I thought it was 4 countries?  #toryconf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two men laughing on  #channel4news and really not laughing at all.... #tories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great girl on #channel4news. More sense than most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthernRailUK @RMTunion if you acted like a decent employer rather than a pack of shits, you'd never have to resort to bullying like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelBermingham all good. Keeping busy and staying out of trouble. Keep up the good work x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelBermingham *don't write tweets on a bus* been copying this in her art folder. You've got a fan x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelBermingham there's a 13 year old who has been co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leicester don't look like they're going to do a Leicester this year.  #MOTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clownio Bravo   #MOTD #ManchesterDerby https://t.co/6zLKJNWeJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewishamCouncil any chance you could police this on Sydenham Park? Inaction only encourages this. What a mess. https://t.co/xLruKalLRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to Sam Allardyce- He's brought a freshness to England's scoreless draws. #SlovakiavEngland #SLOENG #SlowEng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top class. Proper sport. #AllIrelandFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kloppholic Mané capable of making that list too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunny_hundal &amp; will continue to be until Corbyn has PLP who aren't bent on sabotage. Corbyn's problem is the PLP, not the other way around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunny_hundal @georgeeaton @YouGov maybe try supporting him? Opponents of Corbyn the reason Tories destroying the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gatwick_Airport you're only @STN_Airport in disguise. Cattle-pen security and delayed flights all day. Too many people? More staff then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienmark clearly not. The woman in the news today wasn't even wearing one. It's now down to the Secular Police to decide who to humiliate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tallsingingkate @PallantPallant what's the craic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoWomenTravel A tough day but focus being brought to the issue with some brilliance. All power to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harringay Arms, Crouch End https://t.co/jbEqNX3vBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to completely piss off almost everybody in #ForestHill https://t.co/DLPhMey2lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilsonjames_23 ps them's flies around it, not superheroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw #SuicideSquad in 2D. They lied. It's only one dimensional.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>