<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[1 new follower in the last week and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hidden toll of workplace incivility | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/AqWdjgoHaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers -3, Unfollowers - 0. I didn't know I was this awesome. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Name is Refugee https://t.co/b1XOkeg1N7 #mindfood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 4 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 1 new unfollower. Stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 2 new followers in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 1 follower in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 1 new follower and NO unfollowers :) via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Approach to Automating Services https://t.co/memS3a4oMA via @mitsmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CEO guide to customer experience | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/7Id9JoMQSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 2 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFO outlook https://t.co/5OA8LoUijM via @raconteur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who is awesome? My 1 new follower in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 6 new followers and 2 unfollowers via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tech-enabled consumers are reordering the healthcare landscape | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/EoK89ffWr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 weekly followers. 9 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transforming government through digitization @mckinsey https://t.co/20EzNdARn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reorganization rules that work | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/fkrk2UAjAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connecting Business Strategy &amp; Project Management | PMI https://t.co/r7Hr5uSEA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 weekly followers. 0 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick -via https://t.co/ozaFs7YXoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 new unfollowers in the last week. Via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KPMG is proud in supporting the Attitude Awards 2016. Good luck to Rodney, Steff &amp; James in the artistic awards. https://t.co/FhYHbB1CJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy 2050: Insights from the ground up | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/2DtLcFQt5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 tweeps followed me in the past week. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 2, Unfollower - 1. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're simply the (second) best  https://t.co/0Msm6HemMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 tweeps followed (thank you!) and nobody unfollowed me in the past week. Thank you https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 tweep followed (thank you!) and nobody unfollowed me in the past week. Thank you https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 new follower in the last week and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new tech talent you need to succeed in digital | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/QGEaYup1td]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Strategic Predictions for 2016 and Beyond: The Future Is a Digital Thing https://t.co/IahctxOmM5 #GartnerResearch via @Gartner_Inc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where machines could replace humans--and where they can’t (yet) | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/YfHNvm2XzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CEO guide to customer experience | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/7Id9JoMQSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 4 followers in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: The latest on the one-armed robot that can lay 1,000 bricks an hour (via @BIAUS) https://t.co/UsXQcz3wRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Many Benefits of Training With a Plan https://t.co/p48TRLxGlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sleep-Weight Connection https://t.co/9vtUMhktbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New week, new tweets, new stats. 6 followers, 3 unfollowers. Via good old https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overcoming global turbulence to reawaken economic growth | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/I5nzdCZNnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 2 more followers in the past week. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 tweeps followed me in the past week. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 4 new followers in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 weekly followers. 3 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New week, new tweets, new stats. 6 followers, 4 unfollowers. Via good old https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending the right infrastructure message | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/p77JZshl3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget unfollowers, I believe in growing. 4 new followers in the last week! Stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article, thanks Colin Ellis.  Are Your Project Managers Sheepwalkers?: https://t.co/bFM7oVXY3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In pictures: Wearables at the Rio 2016 Olympics https://t.co/qXEDafl4e8 via @CIOonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 weekly followers. 6 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How companies limit project success https://t.co/s2OsnqVO0h via @CIOonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get weekly? 5 awesome new followers for me! Grow with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the World’s Immigration Visualized in 1 Map https://t.co/dtMUyrgSbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 Things Ridiculously Successful People Do Every Day https://t.co/EmkoAXIQIP via @Entrepreneur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get weekly? 6 awesome new followers for me! Grow with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using ‘asset genetics’ to unlock hidden capital | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/IFYu7hhWck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five questions boards should ask about IT in a digital world | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/vSbpRePF9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adapting your board to the digital age | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/TBqhcjJBPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why You Should Care About "Bro Talk" On Wall Street" by @SallieKrawcheck on @LinkedIn https://t.co/zYqJiWQIfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 new tweeps followed me in the last week. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where machines could replace humans--and where they can’t (yet) | McKinsey &amp; Company https://t.co/YfHNvm2XzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who is awesome? My 1 new follower in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is afoot 41% of CEOs indicated their co's will be transformed in the next 3 years. To review more results. https://t.co/tIT3rJEyfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 5 new followers and 2 unfollowers via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUCCEEDING IN DISRUPTIVE TIMES  Business Transformation and Change Management | KPMG https://t.co/5KJLHIl11X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 3, Unfollowers - 2. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction pushes higher NZ growth https://t.co/B1NkzmCgfS via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 new follower in the last week and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 3 new followers in the past week. I know them via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just joined my neighbourhood on Neighbourly! https://t.co/7AsAfzVGQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 2 new followers in the past week, courtesy https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bracket creep occurs when inflation increases peoples’ incomes, into higher tax brackets. https://t.co/Uxj7B2ew2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-budget, the PM indicated personal tax cuts will be part of its election year arsenal. https://t.co/Y2RJcxFz10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re seeing the Government take an increasingly ‘hands-on’ approach to the housing market. https://t.co/G04hCVWfCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt is growing the number of agencies that are improving the lives of at-risk New Zealanders. https://t.co/4rq0ZA1K4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget 2016 can be seen as both continuing the trend of recent budgets and preparing the ground for 2017. https://t.co/pF4UDqixBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follower - 1, Unfollowers - 4. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your weekly stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m pledging to reach my step goal for #GoalDay2016! Join me at https://t.co/wvYDL75BS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m pledging to reach my step goal for #GoalDay2016! Join me at https://t.co/wvYDL75BS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 4 new followers and NO unfollowers :) via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 3 more followers in the past week. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 tweeps followed me in the past week. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget unfollowers, I believe in growing. 3 new followers in the last week! Stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 3 more followers in the past week. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 weekly followers. 2 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get weekly? 1 awesome new follower for me! Grow with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 new tweep followed me in the last week. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New week, new tweets, new stats. 7 followers, 3 unfollowers. Via good old https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 2 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past week. Thank you https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get everyday? I got 2 in the last week. Growing daily with https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 2 followers in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past week - 2 new followers and 2 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 new tweeps followed me in the last week. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 6 followers in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I traveled 804 kilometers with my Fitbit, and just earned the Serengeti badge for it! https://t.co/OzdYsoUwqa #Fitstats_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KPMNZ_Cyber is thrilled to be named a leader in Information #Security Consulting Services by @forrester  https://t.co/ij2nqgau9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 6 new followers in the past week. I know them via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 tweep followed me in the past week. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the week have arrived. 1 new follower and NO unfollowers :) via https://t.co/ozaFs8gyNp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMO Trends To Watch In 2016 https://t.co/BLn5JpFAbM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>