<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[While my friends are all hip and cool and playing Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege, i'm stuck in 2013 playing Surgeon Simulator...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normanstrange FOR SHAME NORMAN! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normanstrange WOO! Twitter polls for the win! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normanstrange BUT THE RESULTS ARE IN! 3 TO 1 COOK SOME DINNER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normanstrange DUDE you're gonna feel so much better when you cook something. Then you can look forward to spend money tomorrow at lunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@praveenamz It's always such a thrill to watch! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of ODI that I love to watch. What an incredibly nerve wracking match!  #nzvaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I just alerted my new neighbors that i'm a cricket fan... I shouted for joy and forgot I had the window wide open... #nzvaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if Australia lose, Stoinis is King of the match. Incredible!  #nzvaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boult... Have I told you lately that I love you?  #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester Thanks Justin, he really loved his job, and I know he'd be so glad (as am I) that you're Wellington's mayor :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was going through some old photos of Dad, found this one from the 2015 Anzac Parade. Looking proud &amp; happy as a cla… https://t.co/1fU4fEBvcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandieditchburn Agreed - alot of missed catches already, and poor running.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyEllenRenee You go girl, You walk with your head held high. You are beautiful and wonderful and I love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! Wanting WCC to pay for her tattoo. Seriously?!! https://t.co/vhL5p6wky9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely fantastic. https://t.co/2TJS0wVJzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aah back in Wellington after an epic holiday in Tauranga. I thought I was getting a tan at one stage... but I just had dark sunglasses on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LorieBriggs I skimmed through the rest of the book... and didn't enjoy it. So i've started reading Stephen King's The Stand instead haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I needed a new book to read on holiday so I picked up The Lovely Bones... 8 chapters in... not really feeling it... should I keep reading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drunk singing Fairytale of New York is what Christmas Eve Eve is all about!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awkward moment when you wear @DLancasterActor's @KrampusMovie hoodie, and people ask you why "you're putting a downer on christmas"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoodHeaIth Thank you for the food identification. Looks great btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got to open my #nzsecretsanta gift... and I LOVE IT! Gonna be great when i'm on holiday! Thank you and Merr… https://t.co/hDMt85UJoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #nzsecretsanta has made her tweets private again. Looks like i'll never find out, but I hoped you liked your gift! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #nzsecretsanta prezzie has arrived! but since I sent it to a house with an actual mailbox, I will have to wait till Wednesday to open it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts Feelin' like a bit of an editing wizard at the mo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I am happy with what i'm achieving - getting all wedding, funeral, &amp; birthday videos out to clients before deadlines &amp; before Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy it has been a tough week. Had to say goodbye to a close family friend, plus an extra work load, mixed with frantic Christmas preparation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryteatowel I hope I get you for #nzsecretsanta next year so I can send you a bunch of gifts! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryteatowel Yeah I gave something a little personal, had to dig deep to find clues to what she likes. Fingers crossed I did good! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryteatowel If they tweet that they like the gift then I might come out of hiding, if they don't like it... I might stay in the shadows...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmorganphotonz Oooh decisions... thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best finale from a 1st season of any show, ever.  "Woah, WHAT!" - yelled me at the TV screen. Many times.  

 https://t.co/yZgKN3CSnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're allowed to tell our secret santas who gave them their gift after they receive it, right? #nzsecretsanta #thisismyfirstyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else think the pulling of this ad is a bit ridiculous? The kids look older or close to 12 years old anyway. https://t.co/uCKhqinciG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAAAS! My secret santa prezzie has arrived at the storehouse! Thank you kind stranger I can't wait to see what I get :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #nzsecretsanta present all wrapped up and ready to send tomorrow! Woohoo! https://t.co/l1mCGNl6Pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved listening to She's a Mod on my walk to work. A great bouncy song to start my day. Love to his family. https://t.co/G8FjbDO3Yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me editing audio: The first 3 seconds out of an hour long outdoor shoot sounds fine... So far so good... 4 seconds in: *car horn*. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well while i'm waiting for my #nzsecretsanta match, i'd better give some more hints. I like artsy creative things, plants, &amp; fun jewelry :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nzsecretsanta Seriously though, at the moment i'm really keen on novelty gadgets, like fun little items, eg. The c… https://t.co/OpkNxCIu6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOBSTER. CAVIAR. PUPPIES #thingsIwant #amIdoingitright #nzsecretsanta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH HELL YES! https://t.co/JKOThzfIfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up to do #nzsecretsanta this year! I will try my best, twitter stranger to get you something awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With NZers really pulling together &amp; helping each other at this time of need, we do NOT need this kind of hateful bullshit from Brian Tamaki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I know what I want for my birthday... https://t.co/bCAH1QmraV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Masters of Sex is REALLY raising the bar on quality television. This last episode was so beautifully written, with such incredible acting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sick to my stomach. It's all downhill from here. #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts Present company excluded of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts ...And although he continued to walk on by, my ponytail and I felt greatly violated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts I saw the fire in his eyes as my elegant ponytail caught his attention, gently blowing in the breeze...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a risk today. I knew John Key was going to come into work. But yet I chose to wear my hair in a ponytail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey fellow kids, we're hip! We like emojis! Buy our new car!! Ugh. One of the cringiest commercials i've ever seen. https://t.co/zLflMo6dfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredibly excited when Green Day announced that their tour was coming to NZ. Not too excited about the $153.30 ticket price though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Bathurst Day! I know Dad will be watching eagerly from above, fingers crossed for @FabianCoulthard   #Bathurst1000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never try to go somewhere for dinner at 6pm in Wellington city when A: It's school holidays, and B: The WoW festival is on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the K.M.A.R.T. #kiwibeatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Long and Winding Rimutaka Hill Road #kiwibeatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts An unconventional source of toilet paper... If you're that desperate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts Oh. Damn. I am once again behind in the development of technology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if someone made an MP3 player with the option to time the music to the pace you're currently walking/running...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished Stranger Things Season 1. It's fast becoming one of my favourite shows. And this guy. Best character. https://t.co/DmM8CPSNKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at my latest wedding highlight video - a beautiful mid-winter ceremony at Zealandia, Wellington. https://t.co/AWxAMVBoK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up to episode 5 of Stranger Things. Haven't been this excited about a TV show in a long time. It's reawakening my old X-Files addiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a ripe avocado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously though, Life is Strange. Get it. I absolutely loved the game. More twists and turns than a psychotic pretzel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This decision.. hands down the hardest. Shaking, head in hands, wondering if I made the right choice. #LifeisStrange https://t.co/PWYUvKpx3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished playing #Lifeisstrange. Boy, some of those decisions... just.. just.. a rollercoaster of emotions. https://t.co/3B4nNXUVwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completing company tax forms got me like: https://t.co/Rd0W0Wwuii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rounding off the evening with some https://t.co/uWx43AIfGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts Like almost all the papers I handed in at University, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally upgraded to Windows 10, and am finally getting myself a new monitor that doesn't flicker when you turn it on. Moving with the times!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drink it, drink it with tonic, drink it and rethink your life choices. https://t.co/dWp3WxhUVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put 'Rock&amp;Roll Dreams Come Through' to the wedding video i'm working on for a lark. Strangely, it fit. Hope they are @RealMeatLoaf fans...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this what court is really like, @louderthoughts? Please tell me it is https://t.co/1gKZ9eKSP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you buy lipstick it should come with a bonus straw for drinking without ruining the colour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just gonna leave this here. This is very cute. https://t.co/qRrQZzOzbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is actually pretty darn exciting. https://t.co/DqqdYpVMSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This last #GameofThrones episode was artistically incredible. Gonna try and find as many interviews with director Miguel Sapochnik as I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have been watching a ton of short films lately. This one is so funny and creative, and narrated by @Nick_Offerman : https://t.co/VVHYbflWzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody Preston. I do SO many missions for him, and each time I report back, he's asleep. In MY old bed. I'M BUSTING MY ASS HERE!! #Fallout4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a two week break before my next wedding to film, I have been researching and discovering new inspiration for my work. Feels great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making banana cake. Everything was going well, until the recipe gave instructions for... the LEMON icing. No. It's chocolate. everytime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editing confessions: I love editing a video clip of a bouquet of flowers in between video clips of people. Then I get to BOOST THE CONTRAST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met a guy called Levon the other night. Had to ask. Yes, his parents were Elton John fans. I was very glad I asked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OspreyDawn @therosiewall Another one of Stuff's intriguing intellectual articles: https://t.co/3jcnyjoJe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, this is me. Every. Single. Time. #editinglife https://t.co/iK1NUGEAjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was listening to one of @qikipedia's podcasts, they said that 1% of New Zealanders are allergic to kiwifruit. Yay that's me! I'm in the 1%!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad I live in walking distance of the National War Memorial Park and got to experience the Dawn Service there for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only pet an art teacher can have is a cat. That's it. It's just the way the world is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the blandest designs for a blender I have ever seen. And it's $1000. https://t.co/AIxREPdfdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know that Rowan Atkinson was back on TV but i'm looking forward to watching him playing a 1950s detective. https://t.co/y1arfbiqix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope it'll be a windy day across the whole country tomorrow so the #nzflag can wave mightily at the top of flagpoles in its rightful place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to filming a wedding out at Pencarrow Lodge on Friday where the bride &amp; groom will arrive by helicopter!! How cool is that?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therosiewall Ah! I thought I recognized the plant wall! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louderthoughts Nice! Lamb &amp; a potato/kumara cake thing.. I was too tired/hungry at that stage in the night to identify what exactly it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therosiewall Are you by any chance working at the biz dojo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man oh man am I tired. Such a full on day, but it was a pleasure to film such a beautiful wedding. Such wonderful, fun, friendly people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a beautiful day, perfect for filming my first kiwi/indian wedding of the year! It's gonna be a long 13 hours, but it's gonna be great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time baking in the new house. Realised I forgot to bring the cup measurments... So here I am adding 26 tablespoons of flour to the mix]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>