<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cutting like a Champion! Great morning to be out on the Legendary Jacobsen LF570. Go you good thing! https://t.co/ERbBzXO72f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the road New trailer &amp; new Jacobsen LF570! Trailer tows well &amp; the LF570 Awesome! The balance is perfect! JTTURF https://t.co/SqCcJb3mei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey get a load of this! Orange every where! Another great drop off! As the Oils would sing,The power &amp; the passion! https://t.co/2X7cgLZXAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great Delivery of the Jacobsen LF570 fairway mower. Customer is overwhelmed with its performance! JP JTTURF https://t.co/13e3Navgjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sisis Veemo in action at Terrey Hills GC Sydney. This machine is powering &amp; does a Great Job! JP JTTURF https://t.co/uHE5NOaZau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Legions Championship at Mollymook. Course looks great! Greens are superb! Well done to Ray &amp; Staff! JP. https://t.co/hN5Mk2BgTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for the Australian open. Looking down the 18th at Royal Sydney GC. Enjoyable day of golf. JP https://t.co/sa9h2zy9Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks fantastic!@GolfScotland18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virgin Airlines! Shove it!! Inflight entertainment non existent &amp; food fit for pig!! Crap in other words!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellturf Yep funny thing I do. An old Cushman mmm Bullet Proof!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught up with an old friend Alvin in Fiji. He loves his Jacobsen Turfcat mower. Does the job brilliantly. JP https://t.co/a1S8CrdhF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delivery of the new Jacobsen Eclipse 322 Hybrid Greens mower! No Hydraulics to worry about. JP JTTURF Sydney. https://t.co/vI29hNhJrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Road with another Jacobsen AR3 Delivery! These TrimTek decks are the go! Clean cut and productive. JP JTTURF https://t.co/ApYHH7jt6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen LF570 in action today! Just an unbelievable cut, performance &amp; comfort. Go you good thing! JP JTTURF https://t.co/icIq8CgqzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrey Hills GC accepting Delivery of their new Sisis Veemo! Great bit of kit, &amp; gives great results. JP- JT Turf https://t.co/HQLK717V05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd starting to pack into Leichhardt Oval! Wests Tigers V Raiders! Ground looking good &amp; sun is shining! JP https://t.co/eNxCkB6hjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Liverpool taking delivery of their new Jacobsen Hydraulic Wide Area mower! A real happy team here. JP JT Turf. https://t.co/mF6Eky0llV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Jacobsen Wide Area mower ready for delivery! Best performer in the market! JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/AqKVR2wGfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Peruzzo Elk Flail mower in action! Fantastic cut! Easy to set up and use. JP, JT Turf Australia. https://t.co/f8OyjJTj7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great to see all the Jacobsen Mowers at the Olympic Golf Course" https://t.co/VSsXJpQXen on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick,Stu &amp; JP on the course today at Caulderwood Golf! Illawarra Assn Golf Day. Course was great! Great job by staff https://t.co/WWKFYm3iVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great cut from our Jacobsen 322 today! Very quiet and precise! My first cut today blew them away! JP JT Turf https://t.co/noD9vfCkD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JP spreading the Jacobsen word at the STA day today! Good attendance, good Venue! A good educational day. JT Turf. https://t.co/KZyFnLaY0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Jacobsen Tri-King working at the Rookwood War memorial site today! Nothing more proud! JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/aoGzOPyaGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers Taylor does not know what cohesion is!! Or means! The club would be better off without Taylor! When will our board see this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers #WestsTigers Dump the Coach! How on earth can you put State of Origin hooker in reserve and expect to keep members? Bad Coach!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Tigers should listen to Maddog! What Taylor is doing to our Club will have long term effects! It is giving a bad culture! Dump Taylor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Coach Taylor is at it again with Robbie! Taylor doesn't care about the Members, Fans &amp; loyalty! Let's Dump The Coach!! Members stand up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellturf What is pig dog? JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDaneo Yep sure is. JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen Turf Truckster doing a great early morning job!! JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/JF3ixIl4CZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out spraying early this morning morning at Kareela GC with our  Jacobsen Truckster spray unit. JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/NhSgmfeL15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Purtell representing Australian Army Basketball in Whyalla Victoria. Very Proud Dad here!! JP https://t.co/sStTyDgvjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jacobsen Fleet Delivered To Golf National « Golf Business News https://t.co/Oti63trD41 #GolfBusinessNews via @eGolfBusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up the Sisis Aer-Aid Air injected Aerator at the  Links Shell Cove. This machine is great!! JP JTTurf Sydney https://t.co/K0lAhLMdMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sisis Aer-Aid working today at the Ridge. Check the Pattern out! The air being injected works unreal. JP JTTurf. https://t.co/hZCdz6SpTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said before, when will Wests tigers get rid of Coach Taylor!!! 18-0 already with kick to come!! JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP on the Jacobsen Stand at the Aussie Turf Conference Melbourne. Many came on our stand. JP JT Turf Australia https://t.co/yq2aRzh81I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sisis / Dennis stand at Aussie Turf Conference Melbourne. The Aer-Aide proved Popular. JP - JT Turf Australia https://t.co/SeVbmPnl91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Supers enjoying the great night put on by Jacobsen on top of Melbourne's tallest building! A fun night!! JP https://t.co/cAktxH0Bd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great morning cutting greens with our Jacobsen Eclipse 322 Hybrid. Lovely cut &amp; very comfortable. JP, JT Turf. https://t.co/2Op0jZVlyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers when will we get rid of the problem coach? State of origin hooker not starting again!! What is he doing to us members &amp; Fans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great cut from our Jacobsen 322 Hybrid greens mower. Impressive, precise &amp; quite were the words used! JP. https://t.co/MjwAPXUrE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen R311T now in full operation in central west NSW. Operators at the Council Love it!! JP JT Turf, Australia. https://t.co/FqaPsn1Kp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen R311T. Now in full operation and operators are thrilled, comfortable cab and great to operate! JP https://t.co/L8G7OQnQgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going through procedures and safety, a must do before going through safety &amp; operations! JP JT Turf. https://t.co/FYHxV8Mid4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great delivery by JT Turf of our Jacobsen R311 to central west NSW. Just about to unload!! JP https://t.co/aMGivjmrZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers no more, no more, Coach Taylor and his coaching staff must go!! Members can't deal with this crap anymore😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will we get rid of coach Taylor from wests tigers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strathfield GC getting the new Jacobsen AR 3 straight to work! Does a great job. JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/tctu1mPZj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another fine Jacobsen delivery. Paul from Strathfield taking delivery of his New Jacobsen AR3. Loves it!! JP. https://t.co/Pofx86tmoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great job at The Links. Well done Shane! https://t.co/Yi5BjJvHnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Leichhardt Oval for Wests Tigers v Storm clash! Ground looks good, of course they use a Sisis Variseeder! JP https://t.co/ZPxULKDKgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JT Turf Hole in one Sponsor at the STA golf day. A foggy start but a great day. Riverside Oaks GC NSW. JP https://t.co/pyTMTeUWxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ANZ crew ready for tee off on the JT Turf hole in one hole. STA Golf Day riverside Oaks GC  NSW. Great Day! https://t.co/uGUqyEukSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers how do we get rid of coach Taylor? He is our problem!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen Zero Turn in action Central west NSW! Real Productivity, mowing fast &amp; Clean! Unreal! JP, JT Turf. https://t.co/cl4loMyk0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JP on demo today of the Jacobsen Zero Turn Mower. Absolutely fantastic!! Big boys love big toys! JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/uObibRnFmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen R311T hard at work at Mt.Broughton GC Southern Highlands NSW. Doing a great job! JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/GCQld7c6WG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delivering the Jacobsen Turf Truckster to Kareela Golf! It's very good &amp; precise. JP JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/oXcYzJgOSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been out spraying with the new Jacobsen Turf Truckster at Kareela Golf. Unreal! JP, JT Turf Sydney https://t.co/3Wa1HvHDIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been out spraying with the new Jacobsen Turf Truckster at Kareela Golf. Unreal! JP, JT Turf Sydney https://t.co/KWmRaziaeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen AR5 still working a treat at Condobolin central west NSW! Hot out here &amp; Jacobsen works well. JP https://t.co/isY5RuJkIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen Eclipse 322 handover at St. Michaels Golf Club Sydney Australia. Course Staff are very happy. JP https://t.co/0k0Add3cqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting roughs mowed before the golfers! This Jacobsen Turfcat does a lot of work at Cowra GC NSW &amp; does it well! JP https://t.co/LAY3r8Gf15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen AR522 hard at work at Cowra GC  south west NSW. Course looks great! JP-JT Turf Australia. https://t.co/tUgIZXKEtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new grand stand at Sydney Uni grounds is  starting to look good! The Jacobsen LF570 makes the ground look great. https://t.co/jthJlao8WS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helan operating the Jacobsen LF570 Fairway mower with JP! Kiama South Coast! JT Turf, Sydney Australia. JP https://t.co/9DLG6DyV8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen LF570 in action at Kiama NSW. Fairways look good! Operator &amp; members love it! JP -JT Turf Australia. https://t.co/BFg6D0BY5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jacobsen R311 wide area in action! These guys loved it! This operator mowed the whole park! JP - JT Turf Sydney. https://t.co/v8IdyhO4oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This operator is still going on the Jacobsen R311 wide area mower!! It is good to operate! I know that for sure!! JP https://t.co/MSHeOZe6je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen R311 wide area in action! The operators just loved this mower! A great cut in less time. JP- JTTurf Sydney. https://t.co/9fXd8cohaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Road with the Jacobsen R311 Powerful wide area mower! Unbelivable mower! JP. JT Turf. Sydney, Australia. https://t.co/BKqkLWN0in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FARAH+REQUESTS+RELEASE+FROM+TIGERS https://t.co/N76EfEE8gK tigers should get rid of Coach Taylor instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when are Wests Tigers going to wake up and get rid of Taylor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On road with the Sisis gear! The Veemo &amp; 1200 Sweeper working together at Bexley Golf Club, Sydney Australia. JP https://t.co/eFG9ghMo2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sisis Sweeper being hooked up for Demo at Charlestown GC mid north coast NSW.
Sisis &amp; JT Turf Teams.
JP https://t.co/GfIdxOvyOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veemo demo, on mid north coast NSW. What a machine!!
JP https://t.co/Ut9gWSskye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Road Central Coast NSW demos with The Sisis equipment!! Good gear!! Great Demos!
JP https://t.co/eJDAevosxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacobsen on the Go!! The Fairway 405 with Air Con Cab at a Sydney Council. Look great!! JT Turf Sydney Australia. https://t.co/z8SivKUiYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How good is our new golf lift? Perfect in our new workshop.
JT Turf Sydney, Australia. https://t.co/lQVq4kZzGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new signage at our Sydney Warehouse looks a treat. JT Turf Sydney Australia. http://t.co/jST2gBx6Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russ &amp; JP out spraying on the Smithco Sprayer! The Course looks absolutely fantastic😎 St Michaels Golf Club. http://t.co/YqS9EscMCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russ checking his greens on a beautifull sunny morning. St. Michaels Golf club. http://t.co/Uftin1l7oS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeagueWeek yep, Wests Tigers were hard done by! Refs rulings are killing the game!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestsTigers what about Robbie? Sack the Board&amp; Taylor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeagueWeek shame on Wests Tigers! Sack the board!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Leichhardt Oval! The ground looks good, hope the West Tigers do to!!! Go the mighty wests Tigers!!! JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi all, JP is now a happy grand father, a brand new Lovely Grand son, I am very proud!! Mum &amp; son are great. Regards to all, from JP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Gold Coast Airport, waiting to see what suff up Jetstar can do this time!!!
JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Jetstar stuff up!!! Now we are stuck at Brisbane Airport, should have been in the Gold Coast!what terrible Airline!!
JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Jetstar has done it again!!! 3rd time for me this year with a Jetstar stuff up!!!! Happy Holidays, try another Airline!!
JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lumpy2265 what Beer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lumpy2265 How good were those Bunnies last night ! I know you love them!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lumpy2265 Farrah's a Legion! Blocker will take over as CEO!! Yeh ! Yeh!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The SIsis variseeder on show today in Canberra, ACT. Australia. Good Show Today ! Regards, JP. http://t.co/rClNDd3jdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday footy, go the tigers! #NRLwstsgi #anzstadium #weststigers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lumpy2265 what do you mean no, you got it didnt you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lumpy2265 what the ! Did i get it right or not ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it in this country we can say what we want to say about politicians but just don't say anything about an NRL Referee!!@NRL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>