<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[10-year-old Texas boy invents device to prevent hot car deaths https://t.co/9sgeUls7I0 via @SFGate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pity the translators at this meeting https://t.co/c1Maeh2ENg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkeley Republicans VP: University 'worked tirelessly' to protect our rights https://t.co/sgmR8sAwpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trader_Moe please identify source of stand down order claim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump White House scores first big legal win on travel ban order https://t.co/SS1Ycs8NP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlomarResponder @dailycal If you can, please read the article which clearly explains no check ever written. It was a promise to reimburse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlomarResponder This, too, is false. Security fee only covered inside event. Security on the streets paid for by university.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlomarResponder No. This is false. The check was never cashed. Please do some research. https://t.co/Iok7iAv4mA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlomarResponder I repeat: they didn't have to pay it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlomarResponder This is false. Just false. The fee was only chargeable if event occurred as planned. Also, fee is applied to all groups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Bernie Sanders doesn't like how Democrats conduct their affairs, he doesn't have to be one. Oh, wait.
https://t.co/kPBAjmNGDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Now you're not just agreeing with me. You're repeating what I said on Fox panel last night!! And got bombarded with hate for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Totally. That has been my premise all along. And there's really no "seems" about it. These are national anarchist orgs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it turns out that Milo &amp; campus GOP won't have to pay a dime after all. Fee was payable only after event.
 https://t.co/Iok7iAv4mA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remedy here is offer a do-over for Milo and Campus GOP with beefed-up security applying fee they already paid, amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Bingo.
POTUS Tweet accused them of "practicing" violence when their failing, if any, was failure to stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the venue essentially failed and it became necessary to cancel the event for public safety reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A question for him: I hope he does not accept view that Berkeley is at fault, institutionally, because it's attempts to secure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBeinart Pleased to find myself in rare agreement w/@PeterBeinart here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other UCBerkeley groups also asked to contribute $$ for security; some cost more than Milo had 2 pay https://t.co/uxmnyY4gEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lashes back at Berkeley after violent protests block speech by Breitbart writer Milo Yiannopoulos https://t.co/t28rpSlfaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-fascist activists take on Trump and the far right: 'Resistance is our only shot' https://t.co/uuXWr2AXfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Weimar Germany should be required class at Berkeley. It would help students understand what is happening on their campus today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suggested new name for Antifa, based on actual effect it has:

Profa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VonWally Yes and in their professional judgment which a lot of Tweeters are casually second-guessing, that's what they did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in fact UC Berkeley attempted to allow free speech and actively "practiced" violence on zero innocent people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The president said "If U.C. Berkeley does not allow free speech and practices violence on innocent people with a different point of view"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did not fault UC Berkeley for failing to prevent, or incompetence, or any of the other things people on Twitter are saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm almost done for the night. Just remember that what started this was the president's tweet. And that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fine with that. https://t.co/TmXosCzCIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EF517_V2 And in fact, they did warn the crowd and then opened up with rubber bullets and tear gas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EF517_V2 Berkeley has 66 sworn campus officers, lightly equipped. Against 150 trained, weaponized anarchists. You do the math.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeking documentary or other evidence of UC order to police to "stand down."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riley1535 I dunno: they were busy protecting Milo? Which they were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is interested in Berkeley's side of the story, here it is: https://t.co/xOzaTvNBE5 via @ucberkeley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyamas the thought that you would so calmly lie about what I said is even more. But hey, it's Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voice of reason https://t.co/CI6f4ikNwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VonWally I am sure that the first amendment education you propose explain how firing people for expressing an opinion helps free speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@topsecretk9 @EpochTimes This is not a picture of a SWAT team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within half hour of first report of violence, police deployed rubber bullets and tear gas. Is that "stand down?"

https://t.co/FIkiwfHaXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell How do we know this for sure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did you read this? https://t.co/4tAcWDHQBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pouliedawg Sir, please stop lying about what I said. Where did I say they had total control? I said they tried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell but there were hundreds of arrests and tear gas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell So you think the DC police "let" riots go on on Inauguration day? They lasted hours. People assaulted. Cars burned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell I can guarantee you that if Berkeley, like UC Davis and others forbid Milo event ahead of time, you'd vilify them for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the DC cops made a couple of hundred arrests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bear in mind that same/similar anarchist group kept Washington DC police tied up in running battles on inauguration day for hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's incumbent upon people demanding UCB "stop" riot, as if that were some simple matter explain exactly how]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FederalSpyGuy @RichardGrenell Do you even listen? I have always said they were outsiders violent and reprehensible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell and the university does not remotely deserve to have its federal funds threatened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell I am not minimizing the violence, which was horrific. I am addressing the question of appropriate federal govt response]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact, UC administration insisted on letting Milo appear in the face of many faculty demands that he be barred, as UC Davis had done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And of course at least Berkeley tried — unlike the many other campuses that would not even let Milo come in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but the university itself and its students are victims here, too, and do not remotely merit federal punishment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for Milo Y. on its campus. Of course, Berkeley did not succeed in deterring highly organized violent gangs from infiltrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the context of violence that the University itself did not condone and attempted to prevent while attempting to have free speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear: it is unconscionable to threaten UC with cutoff of federal funds for violence committed by people who were not its students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComradeArthur Today Berkeley PD arrested two people for assaulting Trump supporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realblakepool no pattern of mass planned attack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrussRSF @TwoSevenRight they did plan for peaceful which is what their students did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennethanderson @UCLA True but only because there's no Oakland to supply anarchists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds good https://t.co/ZiBrOOtThr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@day1038 That is SOP for many campuses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Berkeley's fault anarchists got out of control certainly no basis to cot funding https://t.co/Q91WY703C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane. Scary. All too predictable. https://t.co/ZpnUwgj2bF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About Half of Americans Say Trump Moving Too Fast https://t.co/ynZJCX8P7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I suspected https://t.co/jWD2nJwoyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tactics of Berkeley rioters and DC ones the same, in detail
burning trash cans
crowbarring windows
attacking BoA ATM
This is a playbook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that is to say, NOT Berkeley students (though some might be mixed in) but career anarchist vandals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From what I can see, the group that smashed and burned in Berkeley is pretty much same bunch that rampaged in front of The Post on Inaug Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesimsez @washingtonpost You should know from reading my article that it specifically noted that the green card issue is being resolved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. This is real important.
@IngrahamAngle for VA Senate? https://t.co/RknJUyv0gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesimsez @washingtonpost Judge Birotte did not rule on the central issue I discussed in my article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Impressive, though a simple repeal would have the same effect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Peculiar Populism of Donald Trump https://t.co/Qm5nQ3LxYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too https://t.co/HBWzFZ2EIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why America is great https://t.co/8zAyxfICwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will he ever have lunch in this town again? https://t.co/YgH9vbLm8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting analogy except that Scott Walker had self-control https://t.co/pWFVRfLyPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netherlands PM says those who don't respect customs should leave https://t.co/sH52v22gRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWelch 
Which would create an inference . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csmatteson And the suspicions that would arouse!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what would be a pretty interesting question for Judge Gorsuch at conf hearing?
"Did you vote for President Trump in 2016?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SalenaZito @POTUS Well, @POTUS did mangle the intro by saying Gorsuch was on the Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EB-5 visa racket -- Chinese dollars for US green cards — violates all Trump administration principles. 
Will Bannon lead charge to abolish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test of Steve Bannon's nationalist-populist principles: will he speak truth to power in WhH about pro-China, pro-developer EB-5 visa program]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, and a Trump-branded project in NJ managed by Jared Kushner takes advantage of EB-5
https://t.co/kCBZhAdRmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sell US green cards to Chinese investors in the name of "creating jobs"? It's shot through with corruption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for White House: will @realDonaldTrump soon take aim at EB-5 visa program, which essentially lets rich real estate developers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it actually true that Trump brought both Hardiman and Gorsuch to DC? Or has that been debunked?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait @jonathanalter What if paves way 4 end legislative filibuster -- not to Dems' advantage given GOP long-term hold on House?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait @jonathanalter Smartest pro-filibuster take I've read so far, but . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given recent caught on video incidents of excessive force against students, this Gorsuch opinion reassuring re indi… https://t.co/3QGCsWZUtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important: @SenatorDurbin is not for filibuster on Gorsuch. https://t.co/7VD0EvSnyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If his vote would change the outcome, then they'd order them reargued before a full 9-member court (including NG)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI once confirmed, Gorsuch gets to participate in all SCOTUS cases from current term not yet decided by published opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because my read of a lot of early Democratic react is that some see this as an opportunity to purify party ideologically, leverage power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One description of the task before @SenSchumer is to avoid turning what's supposed to be a fight vs. Gorsuch/Trump into intra-Democrat fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonBrownstein Actually, I have a hunch it is probably a lot better in theory than in practice: #MoreHeatThanLight]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>