<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm embarrassed I ever called Australia 'home'. Scott Morrison: Trump travel ban shows 'world is catching up' to Au… https://t.co/rcn61GyIdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilyallen, thank you for this song. Going To A Town - Lily Allen (Rufus Wainwright cover) https://t.co/RCLmesSB49 https://t.co/C2ZMCDQynG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Alan Davies: 'Nowhere has more beautiful scenery than Wellington'” https://t.co/9orbe78jqU https://t.co/iLyPVDKjHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family of five living large in a 20sqm off-grid tiny house - thisNZlife https://t.co/aGmiWBA4jn https://t.co/X3bB13fESy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What 44 Women Want You To Know About Their Abortions https://t.co/PMHGBd0ES9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to put plants at the centre of your plate (Anna Jones) https://t.co/M6kIuwmJQL https://t.co/F8bBICieXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so confused by this Moosin' Trudeau Sweater https://t.co/isGQZsPlUq https://t.co/QNGH7sxMW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful album! Wood of the Pilgrims, by Marcella O'Sullivan https://t.co/oeCQw67om7 https://t.co/a2yYD0opec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, I can't find words to describe this beauty. Otherworldly Images of Andromeda Galaxy Over a Tiny Swiss Village… https://t.co/JQCBWnMZzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unmissable - #AliciaKeys reciting #MayaAngelou &amp; singing 'This Girl is on Fire' at #WomensMarch on Washington… https://t.co/VpVm04VWXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect to #SummerZervos for taking a stand. https://t.co/oKXZVGMqLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's largest tropical peatland found in Congo basin https://t.co/3iFIUro517 https://t.co/AFWdMx8tVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I confess this makes me nervous. https://t.co/fzhhgI6aKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz Variations on the 'Harry Potter' Theme (Hedwig's Theme) from Postmodern Jukebox https://t.co/Xf1VI0S3TG https://t.co/NMehD46dUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Geographic's 6 Unexpected Cities for the Food Lover... including #Wellington. https://t.co/50VXZYERkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did having a baby leave you with a horrible, debilitating, embarrassing injury? You’re not alone.… https://t.co/k8YvWL7o6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I wasn't hacked... just enjoying the dialogue between Russia and the USA. https://t.co/vpEh7JoUjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was little, #babettecole told me she wrote Winnie Allfours about me, but I know it was secretly about her (j… https://t.co/zfWUjUHaHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am genuinely shocked by this. https://t.co/IKt9spqzkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great press for @YDialects - Lost British birdsong discovered in New Zealand birds https://t.co/iE8D4arlyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spotify, you make me happy! President of Playlists https://t.co/O2xAo2gxcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Chou - Compression is Again Driving the Evolution of Media #VR https://t.co/cm4Kv3y9BZ https://t.co/9kN7g4wmCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShareWaste is a free composting project that connects people. Time to sign up guys! https://t.co/8SgoDM0Sd3 https://t.co/2UUdVXMzVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Loop on the dawn of Holographic Telepresence #VR https://t.co/rBL1h10lkF https://t.co/XOzer3h18d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#8iReality Appoints New CEO, hints at Holographic Telepresence Research in Seattle #VR https://t.co/e9fsdLkmtK https://t.co/9ZTfqheoi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats off to @aubrey_logan and PMJ... yet again! https://t.co/A5OIPghiWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So beautiful! https://t.co/iWrBiz2qvF https://t.co/vAsXck3RPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Things to Know About Augmented Reality https://t.co/GQC7MbwvcV https://t.co/gNaKMM8948]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scotland is planning to pilot a universal basic income https://t.co/4hwfTSy3uV https://t.co/BdFcXxB9x9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you educate a girl, you educate a generation. Find out about our work in #DRCongo at https://t.co/corE8rlKfE https://t.co/568JfN9vn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 predictions and opportunities for virtual and augmented reality in 2017 https://t.co/FUduRgoCm2 https://t.co/HS1nYCUH4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joel Sartore: The man who takes studio photos of endangered species - BBC News https://t.co/jnUmooJy2H https://t.co/RfYZKMxFvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very proud to be one of Ethique's female investors! https://t.co/eHOXydKlDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never played with Barbie dolls, but maybe I should have... Imagine the possibilities advert… https://t.co/XTmxTurnzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contortionist Pencil Drawings Show Bodies at Their Most Intimate | The Creators Project https://t.co/fEvahID2cr https://t.co/XZ9kNmpb1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A College Student Created A Powerful Photo Series Inspired By Brock Turner's Release https://t.co/fw4VTHU3Wc https://t.co/HJlBHClpJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s Improbable Deal to Recreate the Real World in VR (and Maybe Teach AIs to Live In It)… https://t.co/Quf4w2c9AU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The serious artist behind a children’s classic (Spoiler: it's the Moomins) https://t.co/dqm7ebygOY https://t.co/PZnhOWtIUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DR Congo anti-Kabila protests 'leave more than 20 dead' - BBC News https://t.co/Qv03Y3agrl https://t.co/rTWJU2L8I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 Women: The English girls' school reborn in a Nairobi slum - BBC News https://t.co/3etO8LbJLD https://t.co/KVoLMFhm6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We've had enough': Kinshasa holds its breath amid talks to end violence https://t.co/lKJdORaftg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story of an Auckland teenager's 7000 kilometres journey around New Zealand's coasts. | NZ Geographic… https://t.co/pJPwNuXrFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took me a year to use contractions &amp; speed up my speech again after living overseas, but sadly my vocabulary shr… https://t.co/Nacj1Xrvox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New spider species resembles Harry Potter 'Sorting Hat' - BBC News https://t.co/dorh4YIpaj https://t.co/ByNyqhAbAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethique founder lands spot in US Foreign Policy 'global thinker' list - NZ Herald News https://t.co/L5l8NcMXLQ https://t.co/2Yi7YZUHep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio Garden - explore live radio stations by rotating the globe! https://t.co/lB2SPynOcv https://t.co/M5KR7P2lGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black model Deddeh Howard shows the beauty of diversity in fashion – in pictures https://t.co/FrO2lBJrRD https://t.co/yuIeB4Coo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media blackout in the #DRC shows that #Kabila is on edge, as mandate ends. Read this to find out more... https://t.co/ZKNUpsDh0z #drc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC on a knife-edge as opposition  leader calls for #Kabila to step down https://t.co/rEsTr1ZCPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The German doctor's surgery left untouched for 30 years – in pictures https://t.co/PxXMRXcKX8 https://t.co/OAh20Nmdl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You're Horrified By Events In Aleppo, Here's 6 Charities That Can Help Syrian People https://t.co/NZOB9AezUc https://t.co/zmZta344Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always been facinated by this. A Soviet scientist created the only tame foxes in the world… https://t.co/XVoXlgME0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the holocaust happen? Google is not ‘just’ a platform. It frames, shapes and distorts how we see the world… https://t.co/bUOOwm1QL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World’s oldest known seabird lays an egg at age of 66 https://t.co/LDwgKgcIXe https://t.co/oMu9RIPIx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Chair Created Through Generative Design - Design Milk https://t.co/HxSTbPWVW5 https://t.co/A7rG2Am2tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to keep your followers engaged and also save time throughout your day, RoundTeam is a great solution. https://t.co/IVmEeMtkz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making America Worse: Jobs and Money at Trump Casinos, 1997-2010 by Jonathan C. Lipson :: SSRN https://t.co/hlNlyJdJro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zero Waste Holiday Gift Guide https://t.co/txcoFckWPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Children’s Society has unveiled a bold new brand identity by Someone. https://t.co/v8hEvivHsv https://t.co/rTwqdok10q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out NZ design company: Curious Design. And their new look for Kapiti Organic Milk. https://t.co/rNVTKKKSAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toniemoyes Apparently you need a key to achieve Liberty these days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THis is perfect! Retro-modern Scottish tiny house is all about simple comforts https://t.co/T2W5grmQb8 https://t.co/51Hhmqz8sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sip your gin in the 2015 Shed of the Year https://t.co/S2k3148JHN https://t.co/COJv23bAKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, Theresa May, save my husband from death in Bahrain | Zainab Ebrahim https://t.co/EFaf3VMzbB https://t.co/urP8mIntTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the most dangerous time for our planet | Stephen Hawking https://t.co/5EHPg0jKyg https://t.co/DQ4qr88wBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viewpoint: 'Why every woman should be offered menstrual leave' - BBC News https://t.co/gcypcCdUOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If 100 people lived on earth... https://t.co/w7ZCvXkj7W https://t.co/1hz9fJWiHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I confess that I've never been Ronan Keating's biggest fan, but this song is AWESOME!!!  take my hat off to you and… https://t.co/98i91OFrF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clever biology! Elephants are now being born without tusks because of poaching https://t.co/4IwkOE2spZ https://t.co/Ef8RQusY5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VR industry’s biggest threat is underwhelming content https://t.co/N4ChP8kdU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holocaust survivors' 3D project preserves testimony for the future https://t.co/OWwPM6m8gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PREDICTIVE_WORLD, the program that predicts your future/ https://t.co/ZtePzt7VZD https://t.co/6NH9jtCEqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of coconut water? The world's trendiest nut is under threat of species collapse https://t.co/rJ9kBxT3qi https://t.co/a8k0HJmTUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fabulour idea! Support @PatchOfCountry quilting shop in #Kaikoura by buying a mystery pack of fabric/wool/et… https://t.co/qHNHacaXV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dakota Access Pipeline Map Everyone Should See https://t.co/ZKygqaM8Be https://t.co/Fl9CScet3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviva - the game which helps you plan for a major natural disaster https://t.co/Kf54wiV6Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Daily Show's Trevor Noah: ‘I am extremely political’ https://t.co/GcjsDd53kg https://t.co/Boo2lmEVHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help save Australia's orange bellied parrots. There are only 14 left! | First Dog on the Moon… https://t.co/EAVXRvk3Bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tiny robot is incredible! https://t.co/c7MQdOI2M9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling to find more time to share content that will connect with your followers? You don't have to! Use https://t.co/2cfRPDBn5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very intersting - Students have 'dismaying' inability to tell fake news from real https://t.co/aIH2s8SmaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 14 wild orange-bellied parrots left – this summer is our last chance to save them https://t.co/UGSQoqEhsw https://t.co/xt84TggwWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking! https://t.co/ELd3JdHVnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you want to get out of your bubble: try reading these conservative websites https://t.co/xdhuuXs6xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lifting the covers on boudoir in the Holy Land - BBC News https://t.co/nHKM3JacaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Be Passive Observers of Last Night's Terrorization in Standing Rock: Here's What You Can Do… https://t.co/PcBNnkfNPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In pictures: A young girl's life in Chad https://t.co/NmozUa7XM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic riches and where to find them: how to grow a $22bn franchise https://t.co/Xt4oVh4l1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difficult to watch, but important. The video of an air raid hits children's hospital in #Aleppo. This is a disgrace… https://t.co/GaT6kEKCRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of Jewish scholars of holocaust history call on Americans to 'mobilise in solidarity' against Trump https://t.co/6qSmrLYlQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My family were in WW2 concentration camps; thank you to the Jewish historians speaking out out on the USA election https://t.co/i8RLwjAueC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese photographer Ryo Yamazaki makes cat-hats from his cats hair. I have no words... https://t.co/QG7V0LBeS9… https://t.co/32fhleeVbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Watson’s Beauty and the Beast is a good start – we need more feminist fairytales https://t.co/s1gHbmsD67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethical Style Hunter: Solid Beauty https://t.co/EndXB2fhyo https://t.co/h4AM3pKIIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, I've got this alright! Disturbances in equilibrium function after major earthquake https://t.co/iYC9RAkfDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute respect to @StellaMcCartney for using viscose from sustainable forests! https://t.co/Dq67UQlSoF https://t.co/tRWI2PSw4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M7.8 Kaikoura Quake: Future Scenarios and Aftershock Forecasts https://t.co/3HQHfqcdSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oxford Dictionaries Word of the Year 2016 is... "Post-truth" - how very fitting! https://t.co/IPDgf40be2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isle of Skye named most desirable place to live in the UK... in the week my new home in Wellington gets earthquakes! https://t.co/OxhiBPfpeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon I love you more each day. I'm proud to be a Scot. Scotland could offer N. Irish women free abortions https://t.co/kIInv2t1WV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>