<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @CityofSarasota! Go see @Bonniecomm on Feb 9! #HospitalWarrior https://t.co/uBmp8HlBwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for calling out left-wing almost falsehoods. Now how about admitting your own? https://t.co/qcqlvjNHgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who you are...  https://t.co/6JPV8UhPMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he wins the lightning round does he get to be Chief Justice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the reaction from the right if Obama had done this to Fox. White House ices out CNN https://t.co/WSQTumQkgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking bets on SOTU containing the line, “I know you are but what am I?”  https://t.co/BniuBHQGy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s why he’s the expert.  https://t.co/bq4tbUQcwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And reality. You forgot reality.  https://t.co/p96JNVLF7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1a Which is worse -- a president who lies or one who believes what's clearly not true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership from someone who knows how to do it. CDC's canceled climate change conference back on thanks to @algore https://t.co/o0HCug45mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure that's the plan. https://t.co/IsEpvMLmtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything in &amp; about this story is terrifying. Trump, in CIA visit, attacks media for coverage of inaugural crowds https://t.co/VFKPwMS7xW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An administration unprecedented in its corruption, but also completely unprepared to govern." Donald the Unready https://t.co/j5fCsBUPM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think this is a surprise to anyone. Trump, Clinton Voters Divided in Their Main Source for Election News https://t.co/Qjx18JERyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First spin class in way too long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extrapolating this logic to the final vote tallies, he's even less popular than the polls show. 65,844,954 (48.2%)… https://t.co/Of9hHLkOUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there’s an even bigger circus about to hit The White House.  https://t.co/M0Gf3eSCA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovative, workable solution fr @FedCityCouncil 2 US lawmakers want to fix Metro by rewriting its governing charter https://t.co/erB5eKrKUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TDBank_US VERY unhappy now in Delray Beach my account. Unnecessary check holds. Time for a new bank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't avoid @Facebook, it dominates all demos. 86% of U.S. Adults Aged 18-29 Are Social Media Users (Report) https://t.co/CoC5diHq4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new normal.  https://t.co/IsT1UU8o2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional PR is dead, across all sectors. As Trump shakes them up with tweets, Democrats are flummoxed https://t.co/NFV3wOJgkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughtful preview of DC's faux populism, ideology from @econjared. The end of policy, at least for now https://t.co/A6YO9QmT5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling conned, Trump voters? Trump will ask Congress, not Mexico, to pay for border wall - https://t.co/9XUU6cgOXZ https://t.co/pDbgTU6Dv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work w/ Russia? Sure! Work w/ Dems? NO WAY! GOP Rep. Plans Trip To Russia To Explore 'How We Can Work With The Duma' https://t.co/i0PwKj8SUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting and plausible, but not sure everything he says/tweets is strategic. Lots of randomness. https://t.co/MPCEFJPjNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perspective. Happy New Year! Eternal Optimist Talking Points for 2017 https://t.co/ocVteBlfzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prepare for the Tweetstorm!  Obama Bests Trump as Most Admired Man in 2016 | Gallup https://t.co/WUSxfkLVTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to miss Diane Rehm. @drshow  Via @NPR: Radio's Diane Rehm, A Mainstay Of Civil Discourse, Signs Off https://t.co/1yd6a4iuNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forward thinking fm Mayor @TonyWilliamsDC &amp; @FedCityCouncil  DC Metrorail need to be on the right track  https://t.co/hTcPZ7Eoof @washtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important reminder about how much we live online.  https://t.co/00kxOR8DAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that settles that.  https://t.co/24FEh5XjIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's just call #FakeNews what it really is: #StupidGulliblePeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insightful column from @AshleyMerryman. Leaders are more powerful when they're humble, new research shows https://t.co/igiW7hjj8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your platform? Why CEOs Need Social Media - Edelman https://t.co/QirSUcRgqk via @EdelmanPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ACA is fulfilling its objectives for Floridians. https://t.co/c58PyK30rO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs! @Bonniecomm @datagoodies @Lisa_K_Cutler @bonominiyogini @RaySalesWord @raehanbobby @maura_brophy @gregstevens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs! @kjcousins @pascalguyon @KarlaBardinas @jkravitz @armandos16 @stevekerrigan @iOgrapher @GregWells_EP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is your next president, complaining about states he lost.  https://t.co/BoWPoarFKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is diplomacy!  https://t.co/a6MiBbeS1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many in Florida Count on Obama’s Health Law, Even Amid Talk of Its Demise https://t.co/4IwyONGLi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump voters fell for a con man. How long before the white working class realizes Trump was just scamming them? https://t.co/H0Vo40WOWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press would be more inclined to report on this if it happened over email. Obvs.  https://t.co/6fZ07hvvrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but all levels of the federal government are soon to be run by climate deniers. Ideology over facts.  https://t.co/KV7zCHlAKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news, so sorry to hear this. Gwen Ifill dies at age 61 https://t.co/KQEDIcJmiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lisa_K_Cutler can’t wait for the Wikileaks release...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s supporters will be glad to learn he’s above the law.  https://t.co/WM5YC6tu3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another industry in crisis. Pollsters face hurdles in a changing landscape https://t.co/0Lh1FXAV7y via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t wait until these gems start coming from the POTUS account!  https://t.co/sB3zMJo1xN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That change has now placed the United States on a precipice." Donald Trump’s Revolt https://t.co/rD62hbZ2gL #fearful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's Melissa Alt-Right https://t.co/VZ5gGMYzNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump may disappear tomorrow but sadly we will always have Ann Coulter. https://t.co/Z3DEXeH6xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t tell if this is supposed to be satire or brilliant political analysis.  https://t.co/X0Q3isw48F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What this says. #ImWithHer
Roar | Hillary Clinton https://t.co/35Qzid0Svk via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immediate &amp; flexible. K Street: social media growing faster than traditional lobbying as way to influence Washington https://t.co/byPLDrqQRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no longer agreement on what "facts" are. How the Internet Is Loosening Our Grip on the Truth https://t.co/Q21dBZvORt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holed up in the bunker. Sad! Fox News fans pessimistic about the country, and Clinton https://t.co/y40cHqOwPW via @CNNMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we thought this election couldn't get any worse! Lifetime to air "The View Live Election Special" https://t.co/oFAIFR004I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview with Bonnie Friedman @Bonniecomm, author of #HospitalWarrior, on patient advocacy. https://t.co/TZJm0o7pzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at you, #GOP. Your Facts or Mine? https://t.co/KXs8iroMdB #truthiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm assuming Trump is skipping the national security briefings, based on this Mosul answer. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a bleak outlook on life and the world, @realDonaldTrump has. Sad! #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautifully crafted by the Comms staff but belied by everything we’ve seen &amp; heard from Trump since he announced. https://t.co/w2hCWnALac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Math is in the tank for Hillary. https://t.co/dbPmoRtQKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can this get any more embarrassing? Trump Cites Bogus Story From Russian Propaganda Outlet At PA Rally https://t.co/mMtnIqs2ME via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @Safeway This is every line at 450pm today at your store on Maryland Ave in NE Washington DC. Why is it ALWAYS li… https://t.co/LPwMqwkhDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has to end. Trump has to start tweeting in 3-4 hours #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martha Radditz is going to heaven for moderating this mess. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just going to queue this up every few minutes. https://t.co/8pkoliuWxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is he talking about? #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the guy at the bus stop was giving this same Trump rant the other day. Just as credible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is calm now but you can tell he's going to burst into flames soon. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@algore to campaign with Clinton this week in Florida  https://t.co/6j7qUtDT93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an ass.  https://t.co/ZIBXjLWasB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next next big thing. An island no more: Inside the business of the #podcasting boom https://t.co/JqQbRiHxVi via @NiemanLab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s officially time to stop adding “bro” as a prefix to everything. https://t.co/UoVvHmobwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In addition to illegal activity, it’s also a classic case of how not to work with the press. Hubris never wins. https://t.co/KPmMgEPB6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs: @Bonniecomm @kjcousins @_MJBarrett @GuldenComm @Eric_Jotkoff @RealLaurenCross @davidjchie @LP_Florida]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were we watching the same broadcast? #debate  https://t.co/QFBHsMPX7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to guess this will be Lester Holt's only gig as a presidential #debate moderator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS: Hillary Clinton for President https://t.co/rrLO23qKfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s easy to become obese in America. These 7 charts explain why. https://t.co/RoPLc55BTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs! @WolfOfGrowth @JZspeaks @MyHumanCompass 
@TheMindyProject @letreze @DanSpiegel @Rrruffler @CarrieWofford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraged the media is united in calling out this @realDonaldTrump lie. Now look at the rest of his statements. https://t.co/80PYKTqaZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems obvious, yet Trump-Pence won't go there. Hmmm... https://t.co/IdQelnwyAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13% of Americans don’t use the internet. Who are they? https://t.co/Iz82yOVuRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating analysis using tax data. The Most Detailed Map of Gay Marriage in America https://t.co/WclHfijhcF via @UpshotNYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is tricking, rigging, lying -- such a positive message from @realDonaldTrump campaign. Politics is hard! https://t.co/QSO06oGvcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People, it’s FLORIDA. Of course there’s improper behavior.  https://t.co/pMuiyH2hw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart move, although that new name...? Newspaper Association Drops 'Newspaper' in Re-Brand -  https://t.co/Hu3yrhitdH via @odwyerpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diplomacy! Trump says he would have left G-20 summit in China over Obama staircase flap https://t.co/eR1BIX0jxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State motto should be "Florida: It's Funny 'Cause It's True." Saturday Essay: Florida, the punchline state https://t.co/Ain8leubhD via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great analysis of the current state of DC. How big business lost Washington https://t.co/AwuWl7ESNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We knew this. Repubs offer a solution in search of a problem. No, voter fraud actually isn't a persistent problem https://t.co/y2pbS8NHIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mtng is no-lose for Trump. Any movement from Mexico is a win for him &amp; no movement proves what he’s been saying.  https://t.co/SQNiag5giE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs! @2HYPTCH @Ljb2Liam @duplexdiner @madampresidn @PhilGerb @PhilShearin @ampliagroup @JeanneMeserve @nomadicboys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for follows/likes/RTs/MTs! @philip_Du4 @SocialMoveTech @PeloBlancoPhoto @Bonniecomm @screenrobot @due @BrittanyWallman @realkmmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great long term planning meeting w @scottwilliamsdc and Forefront Strategies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad but true. Oh, Florida... Rick Scott’s list of how to fight Zika in 14 easy steps https://t.co/uUYKGcwu6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for today's tone-deaf non sequitur. https://t.co/Z3oj8cVsSc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>