<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHerridge91 Probably 5s now, tops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHerridge91 Hardly 5,000/1 for that?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meathgaalad1 @seanmacdonnacha @truefergallynch Centre field seemed to struggle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanmacdonnacha @MeathGAA @meathgaalad1 @truefergallynch Bitterly disappointed letting in 3 goals but not wanting to read too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa's World Cup win when #Madiba was alive changed the world - not just sport. #Joost was a leader on and off the field. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazzachef @IrishTimesMag @IrishTimes @cooksacademy Thought that, still looks delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimesMag @IrishTimes @cooksacademy @gazzachef What way is it re Gluten?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/uMi8tO7DB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalachyClerkin Depressingly cat ;(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AineBelton And it's comforting to receive too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honest insight. There'll be better days https://t.co/Q0Uvr0CU7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraMullen34 And that goes for life as well as sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GirloftheSummer @gelliott_racing Super shot as always, Susie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard luck to the @MeathGAA players and management, tough day at the office but what doesn't break us will hopefully leave us stronger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @tuvastables and @emmacbutch Great to see dear old Texas Jack get his head in front again @Fairyhouse today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartyM_RTE Great to see Kepak jerseys afloat too, the late, great Noel Keating would be very proud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@truefergallynch The late Mr Keating would be very proud indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimzer111 @Fairyhouse I'd a half score and came home very happy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoKavanagh Ah quiet enough, coming out of the toughest part of the year, I hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoKavanagh @_fllwrs Life's a fickle journey Leo! Long time no chat my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/uMi8tO7DB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire They know us better than we know them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire Boy, Buddy, 30th birthday present, 6 years ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow I don't think he'll get away with it that easy https://t.co/OEyBHkJ1Wt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire Here's my Buddy looking after me when I was out of sorts https://t.co/Qubp5lthnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire And my beloved labrador at my wheels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire And feck all furniture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire Noted! Slowly but surely learning how to do a bit myself, there's a knack to getting a wheelchair round a kitchen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ger_Stapleton Now the injection bit of that has given me a smile -:) Interesting how he'll be fixed with Lordan in Ballydoyle now too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ger_Stapleton They should know at this stage he doesn't like being interviewed and leave him be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beef cassarole with diced smokey rashers - will definitely give that a go again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWebb121 Comply Or Die and Timmy Murphy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eamon4prez @offtheball @SecondCaptains @ballsdotie A great job, think I had one of them years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miambo Hiya, though sport is my main 'area' I've written a Trump rant! Will send you the link when up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant to see this... https://t.co/GT1YgOrhpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Carolan Hope you're ok x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelDevil71 Looking it presently, the Henderson news from today is interesting, I like Yanworth though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intriguing news... https://t.co/TkRm9OaftU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelDevil71 What did you make of the weekend's racing? Not sure what to think re Faugheen now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge fan of this fella... https://t.co/DpSyCYqZMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelDevil71 When it happens to me I tend to put it down to sarcasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having had dementia thrust upon our family in the last year I can't begin to articulate how this makes me feel https://t.co/L4BCv2IZcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealPMurphy Unlike certain other political people I bet she didn't have you arrested!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsHelenCarroll Good to be in touch again -:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsHelenCarroll I think it's some way tied into Eir, but I couldn't swear to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for the lad, glad it got done in time https://t.co/nyAzOV5mSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsHelenCarroll @BeingAFarmWife @IrishFarmerette @Rural_WiFi I'm with IFA Telecom many years now and find their wifi good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/uMi8tO7DB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meant to post this yesterday. I was deeply saddened to learn of the passing of @GFC_Syddan and @MeathGAA stalwart Patsy Duff. May he RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Carolan Jazus, when/what was that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilovetodreamat3 Are there many in that practice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilovetodreamat3 Have you ever been 'there'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're just at the stage when you've built up confidence with a new GP and then they leave, so bloody frustrating and upsetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsfile @MeathGAA @DevenishNutri @PaORourke89 Great to see the big keeper back in the fold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this not a surprise... https://t.co/JRayXTLR6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@truefergallynch Doesn't the fact it was all over so early in the year illustrate how little was thought of it then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babyspud29 @R_EmmettsLondon Please pass on my best, though I'm not sure if he'll remember me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeverleyGlazer And yet change is often the single toughest thing to adjust to in life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love stats like that... https://t.co/nArh8o8ASc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpTeam @SkyHelpIreland I've only recently upgraded my Sky package but am considering changing unless you #keepdiscovery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@truefergallynch Now that's a press box!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadCollier And a lovely guy to as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadCollier They've been amazing, my old friend the ex rugby man is some operator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StColmcillesGAA Congratulations on another great day for ye and @MeathGAA , I may end my Croker exile for final day!! #Traintrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@museandchat I shudder to think what he thinks of the disabled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManonGustave @Tweetinggoddess @PictureIreland @igersdublin That just has peace written all over it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear https://t.co/bxBWJZaG7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good win for a Meath team today. Been a good day on that score https://t.co/PXPEbR3pGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozsaraKelly Will do, and thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghmc10 Aye, free taker needed for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozsaraKelly Thank you.major changes in my life the last few months, but slowly on a rebuild mission,including cooking a little bit por moi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghmc10 Yeah, he'll certainly have them more competitive, I just hope people don't expect miracles, much work to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghmc10 Yeah, true that. Are ya still abroad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethgregan My worry is that, if we don't play ball to some degree, he may pull the multinationals out of here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghmc10 Top class man, the one thing I don't like about Mourinho is the way he's treated him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethgregan As important as America undoubtedly is to the Irish economy, we can't stand idle during the Trump stampede]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethgregan I whole heartedly agree with both of your last two tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done lads, any silverware is positive going forward https://t.co/Otb75P0e15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozsaraKelly So far I've only managed the frying pan, not healthiest I know, but a start. Chicken stirfry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozsaraKelly Hi friend, how are things? Long time no chat. Still haven't got my garden set up, but, I've actually started cooking a bit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozsaraKelly I'd certainly take some of the last two please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susie_k86 Hopefully something I'll get reacquainted with when the weather gets better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heroic https://t.co/FlANPaU4xF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/uMi8tO7DB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolineobmcg Oh yeah, but I hadn't been out in yonks, so I was delighted with meself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolineobmcg You could apply that here too, mind you, Mr Guinness helped me last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Willie Twiston-Davies back riding over jumps full time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in other news today is Friday https://t.co/C1C2n9N3dO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Secret looks a seriously good recruit to jumping there for Paul Nicholls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyOldGooner Why I'll never know, a manager of Wenger's longevity deserves respect, and they do play attractive entertaining football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyOldGooner And (almost) any cause of conversation is good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyOldGooner Agreed, mind you, it did lend itself to some conjecture in warm places!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The42_ie Is Denis related to the other man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolineobmcg And here is I resigned to a life of bachelor-hood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiritualNurse So The Donald's new borders could be in bother before they start!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miambo Biatch, excuse the French! How's you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miambo @NewstalkFM That's what I meant, who was it? I'm ok, kinda, DM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire There's a lot to be said for practical presents!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miambo @NewstalkFM How was/is the gas bag?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHaywire There's something special about seeing the home-reared ones do well]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>