<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @TedTedwin @____andria what is this I'm so confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindawampler @chrissyteigen How the fuck is this an appropriate question to ask someone?? Let alone someone you don't even know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single word of this is perfection https://t.co/CveKxe5JpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez @PINKYFANG https://t.co/zuOlPFnzTJ This is the best I could find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez @PINKYFANG Might be worth flicking them an email about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmaydillon DEFINITELY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ @TedTedwin @chennanigans All good Spark! My fault for not checking your website to see if you had an outage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin @chennanigans Yeah work internet was out as well. I was running round my office like a headless chicken trying to troubleshoot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin From what I've read they're live streaming it from the Greens fb page when it's actually underway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greencatherine Is there a livestream online? Can't see anything on your fb page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omfgwhateveretc Ooh ok, yuck. Did you say anything? So difficult to know what angle to take with stuff like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omfgwhateveretc Where do they volunteer?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has your MP condemned the #muslimban? If not, email them. Silence is complicity. https://t.co/g7X9kiGtAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just emailed Bill English about #muslimban and #DoubleTheQuota . You should too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence Keep track of bills happening at a state level, put pressure on local MPs, try to squash out white-nat movements overseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin It's at 2pm today apparently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin When actually is the speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchyyyyy @AndrewLittleMP @grantrobertson1 Oh yeah I figured. I meant specifically about Trump's post-inauguration actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relevant poem of the day. So much to be gained from trying to overcome borders :/ https://t.co/3zam8VfSE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 Is @AndrewLittleMP going to release a statement on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence Chur, bro &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys @Cjameskennedy made me a gingerbread recreation of the nazi being punched + @thomas_violence's tweet for my bi… https://t.co/rcgu8cwtdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madrunnerz Yeah, I'm very lucky. They were a bday gift from my bf. 3/4 flatmates in our flat have them now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flatmate's cat is very very excited by box my @Allbirds came in https://t.co/TbUmFZ608I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieMarija They....are? https://t.co/Xhx6UPgAnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SofaRobb It's funny because obviously SHE should be cleaning and HE should be putting his feet up and watching the game #equality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual quote from this article about #WomensMarchOnWashington : https://t.co/8oPYc5XCiT https://t.co/DvcTEzviJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer Everyone saw you cry on tv, Richard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieMarija @DebHarkness It's from this!! https://t.co/wgS7xonnHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have photos from wellington #womensmarch consider submitting them to @guardian? They have nothing from New Zealand protests yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much love and support to everyone going to #womenmarch today x https://t.co/NXjChuy1tA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexFeinson @alexa_ruthless No I've heard that as well. I think crows might mourn as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington is finally turning on the summer weather https://t.co/xUN3s7tdMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans Urgh I don't really know. I doubt anything will change his mind. @TedTedwin, ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans Did you comment anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews @Am_Em YES. I saw this a while ago, I think it really captures what's good about the song: https://t.co/OKiOyRcRSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews It reminds me of this: https://t.co/KN5T7D1aHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews I know?? I hate the trend of ~edgy~ male acoustic covers of female pop songs. Let it die already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samieywylie This is so perfectly timed. There's been a weird uptick in boob negativity in my corner of the internet recently &gt;:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antheaw I like the focus on "cull things that make you feel like shit" instead of "turn yourself into a different person"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know new year resolution-y listcles are pretty much always bullshit but I found one that I really really like: https://t.co/1EKE0UDtYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe I heard someone label it #goldengate which is obviously the best version of that hashtag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe That's comforting. Nearly 700 people thinking that's an ok opinion though D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @JJPalethorpe @farmgeek @MorganGodfery THIS is what gets me about fb comments like this. How many people are backing it up. Jfc??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellerennex know him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fuller_Si YES. I was just recovering from dying Grandma and then it shot out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw Moana.

 "Guess I picked the right tattoo" https://t.co/3FVCSW62jd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnomespeacock https://t.co/5CvoNBlKlA and another is in the notes of my original tweet somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badblackbarbie @ohyoufox He's pretty charismatic and convincing apparently. And broculist is SUCH a good word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillettMickg90 @ohyoufox You probably do, especially if you went to Vic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkdeedle I know right?? Apparently every one only realised through talkin to each other on IG and comparing timelines...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves Know him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_emc92 Gaslighting and emotional abuse :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkdeedle Yeah apparently he's hiding at at some girl's flat in Christchurch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnomespeacock Either through Salient (ex editor) or through like, like, five call out posts you would have seen circulating facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower It's fucking crazy. There are three girls in my friend group alone, apparently more in Auckland and Dunedin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladyhorrors @gtiso @rgay I keep seeing that around! Worth it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just fyi Welly girls, this guy has been cheating on his gf with tens of girls from around NZ so maybe swipe left... https://t.co/INWiTm4N3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews Urgh and political posts that guilt people by saying shit like "90% of people won't share this, will you" uuurgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LOLGASMS Yup, used to be editor a couple of years ago I think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin Obviously instead of a Chinese garden it should be another war memorial surrounded by rusty #8 wire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope Blackcurrent is the devil's jam. Bought it accidentally once and almost cried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_aldous Yeah, racism aside, the dude who doesn't like *murals*...? What's up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower Plus her racist ass co-opting Maori culture??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower NZ has a long history with China?? Chinese settlers have been here longer than A LOT of Pakeha??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower It wound me up so much. It would take so many tweets to outline all the reasons that comment is shitty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riamail I know right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeEGe Buy a tent and you can come live on our porch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeEGe You're not going to be homeless because of immigrants George.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeEGe Oh god can we not have this discourse. You can be Pro-Refugee and Pro-People-Wanting-To-Escape-A-Hellscape-Of-A-Country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigonSyl And the pacing of their confrontation in the hallway https://t.co/1yOgMfU5Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigonSyl YES. That and Malcolm's arrest in the finale are my favourite scenes. The acting is just incredible??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso I remember this article!! Because there was also this hot mess https://t.co/YJaOwC7qJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexiebond ...my brain has switched into "oh shit" mood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexiebond Yeah, I feel the same way. I felt like we were over the worst of it with the election and now with the inauguration coming up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexiebond I know!! It's such an end of an era :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaydenDonnell Try emailing Archives NZ? They're super helpful and might be able to point you in the direction of some resources?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerriKimber @KMSOCIETY Have you read his letters to her after they stopped living together? They stop me from feeling guilty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@probabIyeating I definitely don't trust myself making meringue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@probabIyeating @Te_Papa My fav was the tiramisu/pavlova hybrid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Award for most wholesome internet thread goes to the people swapping lollycake recipes on @Te_Papa's fb page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie Is this in Wellington??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie Yeah?! Were they American?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie Apparently it has a history of WS, with three soldiers from there killing an african american couple :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie 'A' usually stands for aryan; apparently 5 can stand for "I have nothing to say" (the recommended response to police questions)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie You've sent me into a wikipedia spiral now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immysophie Oh god, yuck. What are the patches?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil "Although she would not go as far to apologise, she said she never intended to offend anyone." ...........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope I've seen this article a couple of times now, where is it from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillHumphreyMA omg I love Heidi. Goat's milk, rustling pines, and fresh air = cure for every illness and disability apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobjakeybrown That's such an awesome idea!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sock_review So in love with the Rowdy 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sock_review Isn't it?? I'm the only person in my flat/friend-group who's watched it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @JJPalethorpe You are a wiser human being than I, clearly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @JJPalethorpe @Megapope From the guy who brought you "why be sad about 2016 when millions died during the plague"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobjakeybrown Like Cassandra at the fall of Troy, we didn't listen until Kylie's prophecy until it was too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Polychromantics oh god, what's she done now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe  Fuck people who invalidate people's feelings by finding THE ONE TRUE CAUSE FOR PEOPLE TO BE UPSET OVER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe I read this like an hour ago and I'm still annoyed over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seawall That's so sad. No wonder depression/suicide rates are so high in men...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>