<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Juno is extremely excited about her new glasses. Party dog in the house! https://t.co/CMlpZTmic3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ, what will they call the camps this time around? https://t.co/SBWwa1yhcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am /certain/ that if we euthanised everyone who has commented on a Stuff article in the past week, we'd have a fucking utopia on our hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did a YouTube ad just try to convert me? Is that a thing that legitimately just happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is /cold/ https://t.co/beAaSicpm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First they came for the Asian-run dairies..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being told that it's not immigrants 'like me' that are being targeted by NZ First doesn't exactly fill me with confidence, tbh. Silent "yet"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CateOwen Oh God, why did I go to it? As an immigrant, even one that doesn't look like one, that is some absolutely /terrifying/ shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like it's not the most impressive thing ever, but still, milestone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first Play Of The Game in Competitive #Overwatch #PS4share #Tracer https://t.co/Qn2JxbEa5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah shit, John Hurt. I guess the man could only handle so many dystopias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay The mirror also hurts :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay You know your words? Sometimes, they hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't not be in love with this photo https://t.co/TO5SsQk0uU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love the #KnightLife, we love to boogie... #ForHonor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Oooooh, bypassing the no record. Edgy :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of NZ gaming: online maintenance at noon on Saturday. But hey, For Honor is pretty fun. Knights 5 Eva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess we're playing the waiting game for a while. 

... Aww, the waiting game sucks, I want to play #ForHonor! https://t.co/1TwMhOq2Ga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank fuck for Laura K Buzz sometimes, amirite? She knows what's up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving here, finding a job, buying a house; none of this compares to the pure, long-term stress of formally immigrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd seriously just put the application in and hope for the best, if it wasn't $1250 and I wasn't so irrationally paranoid about forms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Immigration just called me and somehow crashed my phone. This is the exact opposite of being helpful, friends...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ross_McDougall Any night that includes calling bigots on their bullshit is inevitably a stellar fucking night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the thread. If anyone ever told you that a punk cat wouldn't show you the way, they lied to you. https://t.co/q5vU2bRMcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yeah, I ain't alone in this https://t.co/Rw0n8EJwxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bastion is a beautiful lady robot and you can't stop me from thinking that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For everyone saying #RE7 is scary, c'mon, I played Dementium on the DS. You don't know true fear until you know handheld first-person horror]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, who's excited for the latest adaptation of #TheHandmaidsTale? https://t.co/edSdeVmZJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Under the trucks at the end of Hollywood is especially frustrating. And the arches in Temple of Anubis... Wasting my rockets on em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay I hate her because she kills me, but some of those players are absolute pros at hiding those little bastards. Respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay I can't, that's the problem! Especially in CTF, she wrecks my poor edgy grandpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, does everyone else get an immediate hentai suggestion whenever you try to hashtag #Overwatch, or does Twitter know something I don't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like this, but damned if it doesn't get me every time #overwatch https://t.co/nKiQdROhOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Someone on the internet is proud of something they worked hard to create. I must tear them down." - A surprising number of people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems that certain portions of the revolution will, in fact, be televised https://t.co/nus8sXfbnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MC_Odd Yeah it was a late one alright.

I feel like the 'each' was implied :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, we don't speak about what they did to The Time Traveler's Wife. It's barely hyperbole to call that film a hate crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've only read 3 books in one sitting; #HarryPotter 6, The Time Traveler's Wife, and #TheMagicians. All great books, two great adaptations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lunar Loot Box: no awesome Tracer skin :(

Did get that sweet Sigrun Mercy skin though so, ya know, that's something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo Britain, I know you love claiming everyone else's stuff is yours, but Ruth Negga is Irish and would you mind terribly fucking off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay So he's straight up living the 'Gattaca' message, respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want for Chinese New Year is that friggin' gorgeous Tracer skin #Overwatch https://t.co/orcnRJOcwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost makes me wish I played Zenyatta... https://t.co/h4ciRngT78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Merc_Rustad What lights?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin Do it. Do both of those things :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin If you haven't already, I swear by Uncanny Magazine. Gloriously diverse, amazing SF, not like anything I've ever read before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm I figure it's because foxes in urban areas are more nocturnal rather than crepuscular, so they interact with cats less. But IDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm I'd love to get back to it, but unfortunately have moved to a country with no foxes :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm Everything I have is purely anecdotal, but it seemed at the time like they just didn't see the point in competing. Really weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm I didn't! Someone else in the course was doing his thesis on foxes, didn't want to step on his toes. Never got back around to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm But a friend did good work on urban foxes, and that went pretty well. I got distracted by new media and transhumanism :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm Wanted to know why they never seemed to conflict much, outreach seemed like the best way to get evidence. Never went anywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm I was interested in the interaction between urban foxes and feral cats in Dublin City Centre, so I went and did a Masters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat street gangs are literally, LITERALLY, why I went into #scicomm. The dream is becoming reality https://t.co/Cs2xl3w7b2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds. Let me tell you, it's great death. It's American death. I'm going to make death great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was going to be remembered as an unpopular President. But it seems he's bent on being remembered as a monster https://t.co/zP0bo8LtOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 24: Still on the motorway off-ramp. Learning the ways of the cars, to better adapt to my new life among them. Cannot remember old life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, if the Nazis were bringing us pizza... No wait, no, still not a good thing. https://t.co/6BhH76kNzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library jobs are the dream for most people, right? https://t.co/c6q2E9zVgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No seriously you don't understand, I don't care who you are, I will like all your cat photos. ALL of them. Consistently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not saying I don't love our group chat name, guys, but... https://t.co/YDgJ2JOnrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleThatKyle Oh oh, and rogue hoods instead of umbrellas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several achievements are purposely out of reach, because it's not a game without impossible trophies, amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to #gamify my life last night with my #bulletjournal. Yes, my goals are super sad. No, the acronym definite… https://t.co/7yCdKBu7xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Nah bro, you just crave a different kind of buzz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More #nzsecretsanta gifts? You spoil me, kind stranger.

This is super useful though, for real thank you :D https://t.co/P3kYKi12JH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FEChoose #FireEmblem #Lucina #FightMe https://t.co/QwoPvSGzjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay :O https://t.co/SceXvfj7pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lon'qu cosplayers, guard your virtue. That dude was all about you #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexaRayC He's sooooooo dreamy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HA! Suck it Lon'qu! #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you dare talk about Olivia like that, she's a goddam precious flower! #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever Chrom isn't on screen, everyone should be asking "Where's Chrom?" #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amiibos you will never find because Nintendo will make like nine of each #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooray for the return of the good map! #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want this narration guy to narrate everything I do #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit is totally coming between those kids #FireEmblemDirect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just hook it Nintendo Direct-ly to my veins! #FireEmblemWarriors #FireEmblemDirect https://t.co/ERY7nMI9FD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Christ, I think I actually agree with Family First on something. I'll wash, but I'll never be clean...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'd be great if guys would stop yelling shit at women on the street. You're making us look bad in front of the oth… https://t.co/jrFKpRhIzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave house: no rain
Get bus: no rain
Go to New World: no rain
Leave New World: LET THE HEAVENS DROWN THE EARTH

FFS, Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how in my early 20s I was, I loved that shit and could probably still pull it off https://t.co/tzONEqBNXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, I'm also seriously considering dying my hair blue again because I miss it SOOO much, but I may be too old and employed for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May start using my preferred pronunciation of my name. It's not my fault it's spelled the same, but it is my fault that I stopped pushing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay That's all the encouragement I need, haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay It's more should I bring all my notes with me tonight and work from home tomorrow. It seems worth planning for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Yeah, but that's Irish standards. Wellington is always windy af, I assumed this was just another day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Stuff is saying 160+, which is alarming, but I wasn't freaked our until I saw all the Welly locals losing their minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Which means what, exactly? And so why are people losing their shit? I'm Irish, we call anything over 60kph a hurricane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is the media just being silly, or is Wellington seriously about to experience the Weatherpocalypse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You like adorable magical girls and mining with your feet? Good, play #GRAVITYRUSH2 https://t.co/QyNTqWvs39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #biosecurity contest ends Friday 20th January noon. Like, retweet, and follow @HorticultureNZ to win one of our… https://t.co/Umi4qDeqrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MC_Odd I'm itchy just reading this. But I also vouch for antihistamines, they are the best for the scritchiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I am this guy to some of you. I am not ashamed of this. https://t.co/QcpIUPffMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely and unironically want that jacket. Giz. https://t.co/uYsXysbmuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xenojay Alternatively, parasail to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a monstrous beast https://t.co/PKWy3Psbgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews I'm waving in the general direction of your office :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't no migraine like a deadline migraine cos a deadline migraine is inconvenient as hell, seriously WTF Immigran I pay good money for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After watching Kat flail across maps for a while, all I want to do is look after her. Her gracelessness is so endearing #GRAVITYRUSH2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>