<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Jedward have got more than a few loose screws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults on twitter make me cringe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted is not the word! Hate when games get called off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure that's Blaise Matuidi he just happened to bump into ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/1geCI550F3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goood mignolet! What a come back for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal from a free kick that shouldn't have even been given]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea must be shitting themselves after how loud the fans were there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking time off football for a while if Liverpool lose today can't deal with the heartbreaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-1 Liverpool and Mane to score the last goalðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What u want me to do about it mate? https://t.co/hCWWTY7hmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do American tv shows look like they've been filmed on an iPhone 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accident management companies belling me when Ive never been in a car crashðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sainsbury's extra special range is another level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice day planned for tomorrow â¤ï¸ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chloe_legge it was so fake! Can't stand them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayaJama is such an underrated spice ðŸ˜©ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly? Shaw ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/6EIO3akHr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bianca pretending she doesn't believe Jamie has left to hide the fact she isn't even upset cause none of it was real :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ur fitness app starts getting cheeky ðŸ™„ https://t.co/FTTa9lmPWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad that the highlight of transfer rumors this window is that Liverpool are looking at a left back from real betis #lfc #shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been about an hour straight now ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having the worst laughter fit I've ever had and joe is loving every minute of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love when people go on about how private they keep their social media! If u were that private you wouldn't have it all Sherlock Holmes x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If i gotta be a bitch ima be a bad one @Kehlani]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My patience is crap someone can annoy me once and that's it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaomiNoah3 well I never knew that was on twitter x thanks x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FairPlay mate Callum knows how to neck a red wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing power nap sorting me right out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When British people say awesome it makes my skin crawl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crete and Barca could not come quicker ðŸ˜©â˜€ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenlfrieze she's so underrated I think she's literally so pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch everyone who was meant to go to AJ Tracey end up going to temple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone screenshots your Snapchat and then says it was accident you're definitely getting violated ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u take training too seriously @JameronFGU https://t.co/jarBDae6Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some man got their feet up on the kitchen counter trying to show off their balenziagas but hide their corsa halfway down the roadðŸ˜‚ðŸš«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked joe what he thought the picture of the beauty blender was and he said:
'You put your make up on with it'
Me: https://t.co/ZSrIC8vz1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ask for much from my lecturers. Just my assignments marked on time ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a scale of 1 to bianca gasgoine how much do u slur ur words drunk ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coutinho signing a new contract should be a big boost tonight #LFC âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally not a betting or airplane company ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/STxkAGnpmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guilty ðŸ˜‚ but someone could use ur plates whether u own a lambo or a corsa soooo... ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Vnvs9HzMLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosie_hoskins was too busy watching police interceptors x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine how much money and time the police would save if most drugs were decriminalised ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My poor lil baby still having her op ðŸ˜© so worried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_m1naj_ @FemaleTexts hahhaha me too never mind all that napping shit ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_m1naj_ @FemaleTexts these things make me cringe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dieting but no regrets on that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ate a whole plate of chicken nuggets and don't regret any of it ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chanabellax it's honestly hands down the biggest piece of crap I've ever wrote ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not even 1 wifi connection in the area when there is normally at least 6 including mine? Is the internet down in treforest? @virginmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeleddD I hate it! I've left it so late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2000 words to do before tomorrow shall I commit now or x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_LWalker_ same if someone else is in there I wait I don't wanna betray my fave toilet ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely I'm not the only person who only goes to the same toilet in work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to do 2nite ðŸ’­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needing that spa day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate 'friends' who let their mate look like a twat tryna get into a boy that's not into themðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww Chloe Callum just isn't into u ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww Kim give it a rest love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe: its not Netflix and chill it's firestick and dick ðŸ˜©ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 2s ham and coleslaw sandwichðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm currently writing the biggest load of bollocks essay I have ever written xx :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dog has to have an operation and I can honestly say it's one of the most upsetting things ever ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg watching steaming people goes through me ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chanabellax glam is shutting down?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my Spanish ting convinced that I know Spanish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckin goals mate https://t.co/SddLol9Kk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MooresAlys I genuinely think she just talks on songs like I could do that how is she even famous ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MooresAlys @AstrologyOnIy omg the worst ðŸ˜©why her hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta get my thinking cap on here really ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your driving and someone picks up your phone and tries to change the song ðŸ¸ðŸš«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every fucker bringing out a six minute belly blitz DVD!! Mayswell start filming one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw love Chloe but embarrassing with Callum ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just eating carrots and hummus before football training feeling like a health goddess don't think ur meant to eat the whole pot tho tar x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea who needs an automatic toaster when your fire alarm goes off as soon as your toast starts to cook xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home @ 2 when I booked the morning off work aaaah life :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking past foot locker and asylum without going in is a real will power test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many perves with egg dp's on here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzzing for tomorrow now ðŸŽ‰ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even 4 year olds got side chicks! #trustissues https://t.co/cbylnD2VMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaomiNoah3 nah boo unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BargainLovingBritsintheSun awww the spice girls ðŸ˜©â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get why people have to get involved in other people's decisions. Live and let liveðŸ‘‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian's body just makes me wanna sort my figure out ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜© https://t.co/V8YbynblcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe didnt agree to go to the shop until I said 'get to the shop and buy me some biscuits you wet wipe' because he found it so funny ðŸ¤”ðŸ‘‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payet refusing to play for West Ham unless they let him leave and West Ham refusing to select him til he changes attitude? Losing battle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to finally get Barcelona booked with the girls tomorrow ðŸ‘Œ sun sea n cocktails get at meeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzzin I won that game before Ea servers went down would have been fuming ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet Southampton are so proud to have signed Sam Dingle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone borrows less than a fiver so u make them borrow more so it's less embarrassing to ask for it back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't relate to hair washing day tweets cause when ur hair is this dark it's hair wash day litro every day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patchbecca omg get a grip theres people dying in the world ðŸ˜‚ allow ur fuckin snap streak ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[69% in an essay!!! What more did I need to do for that 1 mark ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegHindsRobinsX delete ur cookies or make a new account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I honestly outdo myself likeee taking a job that starts at 8 on a Saturday x are u ok in the head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umm just the latter really https://t.co/6MV90BfDfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannishort hope u had a lush bday boo sorry I couldn't make it xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg I wouldn't throw a hula hoop for that mess if I were them https://t.co/CIsEyUOmIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are people telling Facebook they're gna commit can u tell ur councillor orrrr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>