<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@dedbutdrmng @whimworm They could do a crossover with National Velvet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whimworm @dedbutdrmng Shire horses don't have tricks to deal with stairs - unlike daleks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Patrons have spoken. This weekend my very first story will be in my next Patreon thingie along with its backstory https://t.co/ogvsSrSwU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorOcampo Precisely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling If you ever visit Canberra and need a coffee from another writer, I will make you one, as thanks for the glory of that exchange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This helps show the difference between what's happening in the US and what needs to happen in the US. https://t.co/mPBvR1TYXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NITV @AnitaHeiss This man is one of my personal heroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staticsan Right now, in my fridge there's a vegie curry, much pasta sauce, fruit compote, pickled mushrooms and home made chocs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staticsan It means I have too much food. I was ill for so long, I'd forgotten and now i have too much food, always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staticsan My autopilot ends up in food cooked. I go in to get a coffee or wash dishes and more food is cooked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorOcampo With knitting needles. We need a Doctor who knits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Airstrip_0ne If I share it, they get to judge. This is fair, for stories are for readers, not writers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I give my Patreon people my very first ever published story, in all its ordinariness? They deserve better, but that's not the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridgeman_Books The bok chapter is all done. The course is always fun to teach. The rest... it all depends! It's a strange Thrones year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridgeman_Books I'm doing a re-watch for my year looks a bit Game of Thrones ish (an article I've written, a course I'm teaching etc)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MerriamWebster People have been reading the news today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matociquala Either that, or they're using a not-real-example as a smokescreen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Dog talks to those outside Australia: https://t.co/9wdUliXv4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark If I can help, then let me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark I can't do cute, but if I can help in talking, ring me. I have this strange past...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyDangerOz When someone doe something like this, the real show's elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And more reading: https://t.co/6FRvuDkpy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reading: https://t.co/PJDZlzpuUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustFiction This will never be me. I predict it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillianPolack @_thisisourdream Thank you for the RT (BTW, very auspicious date of birth - only the select few share in it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melkettle @WritersCentreAU Mozzies are evil. We need a mozzie army for our enemies. Except we have no enemies, just the mozzies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WritersCentreAU @melkettle Drown that mozzie in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillianPolack @jeannette_ng Thank you for the RT :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmjgardiner It's a lot of fun. I change the actual periods taught to meet the specific interests of students, which keeps it fresh for me,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melkettle @WritersCentreAU If you liquefy enough salt, you can put up an "Inland Sea" sign and sell tickets to tourists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillianPolack @kmjgardiner Thank you for the RT :) - I'll see you at the HNSA, I hope!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WritersCentreAU In Canberra it's so hot and sticky that if I pour sugar into a pile it'll turn into toffee right there on my kitchen bench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliettedb I could do a basic workshop for @worldcon75 with a bit of help from locals to source taste-stuff. If people wanted it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliettedb My students will get cook-at-home recipes and group tastings (only if they want! they almost always want...).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @jolantru Thank you for the RT :). This one looks as if it might actually go ahead. After last year, I wondered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't I ever remember to say that my food history course isn't specifically for writers, just useful to them? https://t.co/YQSLVDH924]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taste history &amp; argue about its flavours. Writers who asked me about food history for worldbuilding, this is it! https://t.co/YQSLVDH924]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only a few more places left in my ANU evening course about writing novels (and editing them, and marketing them!): https://t.co/Qmb7c8aBAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amisamileandme That's a very concise and almost attainable schedule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chadwickauthor I was impressed they let the ad run, given someone like me was sure to see it and misinterpret :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm putting together my reading from last year, for my Ditmar nominations and I read almost no Australian short fiction! This is not good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just received an ad telling me of the great new holidays available in the USA. "Terms and conditions apply."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm taking refuge in books tonight. Georgian books. My friends on Patreon will find out what this is about next weekend, all going well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dedbutdrmng I'm being beaten at the typo stakes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Turnbull is more informative right now on what isn't part of his job than what is. Leadership belongs in one of those two categories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseLemberg wise child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMakereti This is excellent news :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliettedb Also, Alma Alexander's (and twitter didn't force a link on me there!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKooriWoman I love it that you actively support freedom of speech not being freedom to hurt. I'm sorry it's family, though. That sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randomisalex She would've emailed you to say your nom of Paul came through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is true of so many critical issues,. We lack leadership, common sense, humanity and dignity. https://t.co/6qQPsWqcBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ann_leckie Supporting industry groups and special interest groups also helps, for one of the problems the US faces is big money arguing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseLemberg Thinking of you!! And worried for so many of my friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bogiperson Am thinking of you. If I can help, let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennybel75 Thank you! And the trivium one is fine. And we *so* need to catch up!! If you're likely to be in my vicinity sometime hoy me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randomisalex https://t.co/HhqBlCWIvh It's this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennybel75 If it's low in saturated fat, I'd love it - thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DUFF is open for voting! Help send the marvellous @PrinceJvstin  (Paul Weimer, of @SkiffyandFanty ) to Continuum!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randomisalex Lucy H. (who made the DUFF announcement). If you have trouble getting through to her, let me know and I'll email her privately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse It's a terrifying mess. Keep doing what you can, when you can - every bit helps, even if it doesn't feel that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliettedb My history side produces quite different experiences to my SF side. I'm very lucky to have both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrinceJvstin Thank you for the RT, kind sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in some amazing company in September: https://t.co/8TI0XUuptm Phryne Fisher fans, please note.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark It's hard, though. One of the things I've done over the years is teach people not to self-reject. I can't seem to teach myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_sales Check the NF&amp;SA online. If they have it, I can get it for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark Too often those who speak up are already-seen folks who see a gap, or majority culture folks who miss what's happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark An important thing is how many of us assess ourselves and step back, to let others in. It's something I've seen. A bit mixed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark I keep on thinking "I'm not marginalised" - when I am, but there are others who are more disadvantaged. I'll have a think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_sales I need to find out from you what Aussie stuff you have, for I live near the National Film &amp; Sound Archive and they have a shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark it's my pleasure. I don't know if I've got anything to submit to the antho, but I so want to see it see light of day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the whole story... https://t.co/y0FzATnMrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennybel75 That looks so yummy! My mind can't take it in cos my place smells of the pasta sauce I've been making]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_sales Wonderful! (including the cat)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasefranks @starrybryte @continuum_con is so going to rock!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visual storytelling - an online masterclass with Jason Franks (read his Sixsmiths!): https://t.co/cyMaVFL3sU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse It did some good - some people are prepared. Without the warnings, there would be weeks of stunned silence. Dangerous weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are good things. The New Year is one of them. My singing is not. Have someone singing for me: https://t.co/K3QBIfdlWt 
Gong Xi Fa Cai!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something cheering (thanks Sharyn!): https://t.co/JFQl3ONBeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse Suddenly those 20 years of activism weren't wasted. I'd rather they had been.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse I seem to spend a lot of my recreational time teaching people the basics of political action these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse No-one should hurt. Not even kids who threw stones at me or  adults who lost me my APS career because I'm Jewish. No-one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse This is where being Jewish in a country where we're a minority is handy. I know a lot of useful things, from experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse All we can all do now is continue to fight &amp; to make sure other people are OK. Get through the mess as intact as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse The theory was fine - but the reality of it hurts so many people, every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jendowli It's going to significantly interfere with US business. As it did last time. And reduce tourism to the US. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKooriWoman Oh, damn. I hope you reach the actual debt-free stage SOON. I'll party online with you when that happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jendowli US visas used to be such a pain to get, so this is a return to old ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffvandermeer I only read up to the first bracket. Then I skipped to the second line. (I blame the heat wave.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancinghorse He doesn't care about the violence, does he? What a  piece of work is that man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKooriWoman That's wonderful!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just going to put this one up here (she's no relation, for those who are curious): https://t.co/MbJkUe5V2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daggyvamp @tintinaus Death in fiction can (only sometimes) be, a type of exorcism. I don't really want to exorcise my friends..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tintinaus @daggyvamp In fact, any number of people who want to be forgettable non-entities can donate to GUFF and I'll make a list...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tintinaus @daggyvamp That'd be a specific kind of novel. I'd love to see if there were any takers to be forgettable non-entities in novels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all my friends who knit, Icelandic wool indiegogo: https://t.co/HhnZAwbZ79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tintinaus @daggyvamp Maybe. Or maybe I'll kill of people who annoy me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tintinaus @daggyvamp That sounds like a hint!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote! Help choose the Australasian delegate for @worldcon75 in Helsinki! https://t.co/p7lCvEFzmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark It's the only way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enoughsnark Very oddly, my scholarly book is easier to read than my fiction. What does this say about me? I possibly don't want to know.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>