<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall hmm, wasn't he adamant that he didn't want an electorate seat but to aim for 5%?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flash as MC in rochelle_goodrick #sparklesaddedforeffect #favouritedress https://t.co/90DDBKFe2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terrified dog pushed into the water for a film, a dog SHOT and killed in Auckland. WTF is actually wrong with people?! #mansbestfriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @NZStuff this 'cheat day' article's description of 5:2 is completely arse about face https://t.co/An79u07IWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shhh don't tell too many people. https://t.co/jsqv5NuE1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Batt @danozzi @VICE fuchsia fuhrer - I love that description!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 ...impact than a hard nosed IV. It's not how you get people interested in issues that matters, it's getting them interested at all #rpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For everyone bagging the @TheProject_NZ - think about the role of political satire in US politics. Well executed comedy can have more .. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rose_Matafeo Rose! That's incredible. Go you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregbie yeah. We came down to visit. So lovely, but alas is town summer forgot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When little girls attack #patientpup #loveshislittlefriends https://t.co/lJPRMqYbgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt I'm here and can confirm, it is! One of the best places to go to the races, so relaxed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 you were glorious/shit/magical/eye-opening/etc. Here's to the adventurous path ahead #2017… https://t.co/iQUIWYCUGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeeFaerie @TheEndisNaenae also ❤ 'We’ve given our kids a sh*t sandwich. Let’s not criticise their pickiness for wanting the crusts cut off']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what I found at the Bach we are staying at this year @sirmadbutcher https://t.co/udIUhgpJ8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Auckland taxi companies - do any of you transport dogs? (With their humans) @Akl_Co_Op_Taxis @Uber_NZ or anyone else??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerreMcIvor @SamHayes_ lovely to see you too x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerreMcIvor oh hush your mouth. You would look fab and then we'd just need to recruit a redhead to be Charlie's angels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rico got his friend velcrogriffon a Christmas present... he looks happy about it...… https://t.co/YhgZxaza42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisGlass I'm worried I have about 4 different types after reading that list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimberleeDowns yes please! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a little out of the loop, so just catching up. Excellent news @KimberleeDowns you will be beyond fabulous xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you take the issues seriously, as the ranking of the women's minister suggests, then just own the term! https://t.co/dsPc5s5F9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janikaterellen yes. And the streets are clean in those areas... out west, seems like no one's done a wee joosh up for months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmckinnel @toby_etc wouldn't duterte execute him on the spot? I mean, drugs and all that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wixtweet totally fine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the drive time to the airport was sweet as!! ...now, about the southern motorway...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, um, how many hours should I allow to get to the airport for a pickup at 5pm today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 @wallacelchapman omg what a clever idea... now to get a politician not to nix it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivvyAllison @LeilaniJM really?! Keep me updated please!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaniJM can i add 'and cure snoring' cos if we can man to the moon, surely that's a cinch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie anything specific?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie a bit of 'better the devil you know' perhaps, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonystevens1 we've just put in an outdoor fireplace, but I haven't yet let Dan put in that pizza oven! Yes was just the ticket :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antonystevens1 @jamieoliver thought you'd be using that pizza oven!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alisonmau @NatashaUtting @Anika_Moa how good are those outfits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealvw I think I'd like your wife!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rhybar pretty conservatively. But then, it was about -1° outside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At dinner next to posh young English couple arguing about him wanting to change how she dresses. So far, resisting urge to tell her to RUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallacelchapman @benhurleycom ..thousands before we bought 3years ago. Real estate agents lead you astray as to $ to get more in room, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallacelchapman @benhurleycom for first time buyers it's another cost - all the inspections before you even know if you'll win. We wasted..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallacelchapman hallelujah if that's true. Hardest way to buy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prost! Gluhwein at the Berlin Christmas markets #germany #berlin #ruggedup #drinktowarmup https://t.co/TtWD2af2Yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got one hand in my pocket... and the other one is taking a bathroom selfie. Dress by the… https://t.co/9qxFJZTDTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bonzobuck I'm all over it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson top-notch photo-ing Kim!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilly day in the Scottish borders, imagine the temp in the highlands! #shoppingforwarmerclothes… https://t.co/fjw8oDUHLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's @womansdaynz (that's my mug) https://t.co/QPCff0fYQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roddrury @Xero you're a good man and you run your company to your principles. The world is not completely f'ed after all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson idk what that means, unless cleaning more bathroom basins constitutes really 'living']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know i should prob be tweeting about politics but... recommendations for great holiday reading please??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeepingMum that's a great gig dita! All the very best xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anika_Moa great advice! Haha thank you x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommendations for the best place to stay in Paris please? Want to be close but don't want to remortgage house #lazyweb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hair-raising whirlwind trip to Welly #wellingtononagoodday #windycity https://t.co/cHqEatV0eL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson my fluffy monster came home with his fur FULL of SLUGS. And that was the last straw. Barber here you come kitty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson where did you get that done? Or did you risk life and limb and do it yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pennypink kind words, thank you very much. I was fond of that line, too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plumlovely1 haha I see what you did there, and I like it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewDickson13 thanks very much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlejane26 why thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reckon @lilyallen is a total gem. If only more celebs cared about more than never repeating the same outfit https://t.co/YWh1CwaWvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dallasgurney and it's tucked in! Good luck with your future ventures Dallas, I've no doubt they'll be successful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonmillsnz yep cards through the front door, agents knocking on the door, letters citing specific buyers by name. Leave me alone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@come_for_t really, and it comes addressed to you personally?? I'd be asking where they got those details!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekHelliwell that's interesting. I presume they charge for access to that? So much data collected about you you'd never know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samiamnz1 @MarkCrysell omg really?! I suppose that's in the fine print I didn't read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsKateMcD that's fascinating! Can only agents access this stuff??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillTaylorNZ @paulbrislen we are in process of forming one so I wonder who the letters will come addressed to next, the trustees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkCrysell oops typo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen I feel like ringing them and demanding to know! It's my information afterall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delphijunkie that does feel icky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen yes except I'm not on the electoral role. I'm on the unpublished after a bit of a stalker incident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkCrysell yes except I'm not on the electoral role. I'm on the unpublished after a bit of a stalker incident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else get incessant letters from real estate agents imploring them to sell? Where are they getting my details from?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLetele @Alisonmau you did great! And you're right, that teen ride operator is now a victim too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkJamesDye argh, and I am 20 bucks down!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quite revealing and explains a lot https://t.co/Ame4LDUHnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NapierinFrame had to work today, otherwise I'd have taken HB anniversary off in solidarity with my home town!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been on the motorway for an hour and 20mins... and just reached Manukau. #Auckland  #wheredreamsaremade #anddriversgoinsane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pollybarach it is outside of auckland, was wondering if that was jacking up price but evidently not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved this little post script at the end of every @HuffingtonPost article on the election. Addendum: he's a 70yea… https://t.co/pI9rJ50fR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can people who've done this wedding thing before tell me what's reasonable to pay for bouquets for me +bmaids? Quote seems so high!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lacey_Wilson @BreakfastSam @emirates we look so confused!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simonshealth That's very kind, thank you. I've finally figured out which buttons to press, or more importantly which ones NOT to press!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were a total hit on Graham Norton @TwoPaddocks !! #ownedit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selfless and inspirational NZer who cared about others until the very end. RIP Helen. NZ needs more like you https://t.co/XdTY3ThDLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ @RadioLIVENZ and the definition of 'affordable' keeps shifting as it's %of median, so makes sense 2developers to delay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simonshealth just filling in, but it's fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wrigglemania @JonoAndBen I think googling 'how many more fucking debates' would prob get you some weeeeird politician porn or something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie looks like a pretty special experience. (Not a total priss yo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthWW is that his own personal tanning bed?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenson_kurt neither are amazing, but yes, I do think she's far better than him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How stupid is our country? Asks Trump. Stupid enough to consider you as the answer to their problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I used those losses to not pay tax.. but so did those other rich guys (who aren't standing for president) #trumpisms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie jeez why don't you warn me when you're going to need a tripod carrier. I'm semi qualified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesAdank1 @SundayStarTimes found it, I was looking for it on the app https://t.co/IhLrouuu1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesAdank1 @SundayStarTimes I've been looking for it but haven't found it yet. Thank you though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie @AceMcWicked the germophobe in me thinks both options fairly unsanitary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianchristie @AceMcWicked an ak bar owner who'd just done a refurb proudly told me about the cocaine shelf they put in loos for patrons]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>