<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EIFantasmita Geis is decent as well. Good passing range and rather intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EIFantasmita yea I think Meyer is sorta overrated but might still have a half decent career. Embolo depends on how he recovers from injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AneilSaini @dries_mertens14 thanks bro can't wait for the inform card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Addyylaide @Arsenal feds gonna come knocking down your door soon ffs you grassed yourself bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanWalsh_97 you're a good man Sean Walsh. Great article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane I can't with these mans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eggysalsa Agree with Sessegnon, but KWP is capable of playing at LB despite being a more gifted RB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WonderSpurs @Travis_THFC @bxstock you took a breathe and that was enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Travis_THFC @bxstock I do 100% but it's not the same as the original tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WonderSpurs @Travis_THFC @bxstock who asked you to talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Travis_THFC @bxstock no he was saying that goal tallies shouldn't count penalties in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Travis_THFC @bxstock not really but that's why we have this stat called open play goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Travis_THFC @bxstock because a penalty is still a goal mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane @SpursOfficial how tf he get 11% already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cyrus_Sans @SpursOfficial I am using this in the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommiddletonr Yep he loves to play it safe every single time. It's alright against big teams but so so frustrating against teams like Boro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poch bringing Janssen on with less than a minute left lmaooooo where's the respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sissoko gets the ball, Sissoko ruins the attack. Rinse and repeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winsky coming on about 86 minutes too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robvfour @SeanWalsh_97 good villain him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanWalsh_97 there is no hyphen in lowkey get hip nerd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sicolol @gunnerpunner In the league maybe, but we had one vs Wycombe on Jan 28th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romanbogo damn I should've known better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane They'd probably say Dembele dived or some shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or when Neil Taylor kicked Walker straight in his face and didn't even get a warning? https://t.co/R7aVQuCspz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were these rival fans complaining about us paying the refs when Rodwell tried to break Dembele's legs and walked away without a red?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare we get rightfully deserved penalties https://t.co/kRsqiGIyyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Poch keeping up the tradition of never making subs before the 60th minute even if we're playing crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cyrus_Sans they've got two Dembele's also, so unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got Dortmund fans raving about Ousmane Dembele and Spurs fans raving about Mousa Dembele on my timeline. Very confusing stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CageTheBrenton been told it's true but there is potential he will be sold before next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do we have to do this why can't things just be easy for once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CageTheBrenton yup it represents our formation cause he's always behind them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@king26ledley he's shown signs of being good at it but I think play at CB has hindered his progression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRaylen yup would've sent him back to Barca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valdes lucky that Dier didn't see that, nobody touches Dele on his watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toby Alderweireld long balls give me life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho not even the best Portuguese manager in the league anymore, the main guy Marco Silva much much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane yep apart from Winks you can't rely on anyone to come on and have a positive impact. Meanwhile LFC have Studge on the bench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane @SpursOfficial replace Onomah and Sissoko with Edwards and Lamela and I think that'd be our ideal team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adama Traore vs Ben Davies should be fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpursOfficial no Edwards, sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PochPhiIosophy what a day bro, put it in the history books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PochPhiIosophy it's AGUEROOOOOOOO all over again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkothfc your ruse has backfired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Travis_THFC I expect greatness kiddo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlieEdwardz untradebale but I don't think I'd even want to sell him if I could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajesticMesut unlucky bro, you get any of the other decent OTW's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlieEdwardz nah it was more like this bro https://t.co/M8TUAdQwkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajesticMesut keep trying fella you'll get there eventually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NinjaSkrteI this was my 7th try, I got Renato also. Unsure if I should keep trying to get Kante, Dembele or Higuain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFC_DT untradebale, couldn't be bothered adding IF's in the traceable SBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaMastaAssassin best pull I've ever had probably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VIPswiiift only took about 7 attempts buzzing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY FUCKING BOYYYYYYY https://t.co/Vx8EBr8GWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Addyylaide the whole concept of freedom of speech has been warped by the right to justify hate speech IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Addyylaide It's just a lack of sympathy I suppose, plus it's easy to get RT's by doing that shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Addyylaide The thing is, they don't really care about that person's health, they just want to shame them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcdevin even caitlyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BugEyedFuck fighting anyone who votes kylie jenner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkothfc they probably will but atm theyre both cheap so you might as well trade them and try to get the better ones like Higuain or Pogba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkothfc but Sane and Gaitan are both pretty cheap I think, should trade them and try to get Pogba/Kante]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkothfc think you need to go outside virgin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephonHewitt been a patriots fan since day 1 bro lets get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arsenal89_Mo I did that on purpose lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrdinaryLiLi alternative facts if you will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane Yup they're just trying to get clicks and know using Erik's name is an easy way to get them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamela has said multiple times that he's happy at the club but the mainstream media keep making fake news about him leaving. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VIPswiiift he's connecting with the kids which will help build a bond and make teaching easier. That's his job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VIPswiiift ....... he's a teacher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning You can tell he's got all the talent, he's just inconsistent with delivering on it. I think he'll boss it next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpursOfficial can he play leftback cause he's probably better than davies going forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unbreelScenes Oh definitely but I don't think it's a valid excuse when there's other issues (Aboriginal, foreign policy) he's slacking on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unbreelScenes I feel the exact same. He has so much potential to do good but his lack of action on so many fronts is frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(and yes this account has become dedicated to Simpsons memes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRaylen Yep true. You've got guys like Jordan and Magic for the 90's and then Ronaldinho, Federer, Kobe etc for early 2000's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTTactics Same. Got maybe 2 or 3 more years until he starts slowing down I'd think but then again it is Messi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRaylen it's crazy cause there's probably never gonna be anyone like him. Feel the same way about Bolt and Serena Williams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PLambo14 trash Son is better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheenKL sheen I will fight you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you ever just sit back and think about how grateful we are to live at a time where we can watch Lionel Messi every week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BugEyedFuck it's a blessing in disguise trust me, gotta weed them out somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdcowled Terio is a fucking genius, his writing/dialogue is like poetry. I'm all for him helping Ben and Geoff on The Batman script.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane what the hell is wrong with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THFCRye it is the worst of the worst without a doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe they're making a Big Bang Theory spinoff. The world has truly gone to shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkothfc I'm not even a liberal wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_tbeck not really crying mate just saying he should've been sent off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane True. He's not good against teams that play deep especially, needs space to run into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTTactics Dembele-Wanyama is just so dull and they circulate the ball poorly. Think Winks should've been in there for Wanyama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane yea he did his job but I don't think he was necessarily needed vs Sunderland. Would've liked to have seen Winks start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously who gassed Wanyama and Davies to be shooting from 25 yards out in a 0-0 match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime Davies plays it makes me appreciate Danny Rose even more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WonderSpurs technical ability wise, absolutely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsleyyMane the guy is pure trash man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Sissoko has touched the ball 3 times and fucked it up every single one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnreaIvan didn't even notice my bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tristan71 Dier scored one at the Euros and Walker used to be good at them, other than that idk. Still should give someone else a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnreaIvan christ I cba to figure that one out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bxstock @Asterweireld need big Vic to cock slap him]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>