<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @KellyannePolls whining? After all lies she's told in interviews?? Blustering, aggressive, insidious person. Go… https://t.co/QdSspw2VE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder Video could not be played.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "I'm bringing ALL YOUR JOBS BACK! If companies are making goods overseas, I'll TAX them." #Trump goods made overseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing @POTUS does would surprise me, including creating a 'so-called terrorist event' to scare people. He is deme… https://t.co/DKV3eD2X2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS has just signed an Executive Order about me. https://t.co/ymG0fBqck6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump - as long as U &amp; @jaredkushner R supporting your demented, evil father, UR brands will be called out 4… https://t.co/U0EVk4RoLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, see his hair colour here - it's grey. What do you want to bet it will be YELLOW again when he returns on Monday… https://t.co/Sghbc2lO54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never watch @KellyannePolls on any channel ever again. She has proven that she is incapable of rational dialogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldtrump @POTUS NO ONE WANTS YOU. https://t.co/vBppruj9uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissamccarthy you are a brilliant comedien and actor!!!! Thank you @SNL for this outstanding show! https://t.co/GFMuS1IFaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but #US citizens know better, don't they? https://t.co/y2bYgfHPsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian here: My Dear #US Friends - You've elected a Madman. PERIOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk - this is what your president Trump has already done to the environment. Shame on you. https://t.co/aRZ1uEEIg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonMartinCTV What on earth are you doing interviewing Ann Coulter? Until you stop, I won't be watching your show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kady I agree about Lisa Raitt. She really stood out tonight. Also, Chong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk You've completely lost me. I thought you were a climate hero. Now, after the damage @POTUS has already do… https://t.co/cyrcts9gMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk The ONLY reason @POTUS wants you on committee is to show you off. He won't listen to a word you say if it… https://t.co/zxFu04sN39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls lied from day one for @realDonaldTrump @POTUS. Bowling Green Massacre was just the worst lately. I… https://t.co/latyAb2Fm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump - hair growing medicine can generate sexual dysfunction, depression, thoughts of suicide. https://t.co/fLftTJCqCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, @RonaAmbrose also has BILLIONAIRE friends who provide vacations in tropical places. https://t.co/1GvD8RszMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS - never doubted there was impotence. Melania is probably grateful. https://t.co/wWqWpX2eKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence is just as EVIL as @realDonaldTrump when it comes to women's rights. https://t.co/zmG0W3A0iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No legitimate journalists/members of media should be attending White House Correspondents' Dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is classic abusive behaviour/strategy. You see it in @POTUS, all his people, abusers of wives, children, cults… https://t.co/Zu9sCPhXlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems @POTUS has ordered @KellyannePolls to MAKE THE MEDIA SHOW HIM SOME RESPECT! When stops lying, creating chaos. Nah, it'll never happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Vancouver....it snows. https://t.co/EMmCnQkEOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe UAE is on Trump's list because he has business there. https://t.co/DWQCVeXF94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's hair is looking greyer. What do you want to bet it will be bright yellow again after his trip to Mar-A-Lago?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can safely bet that PUTIN didn't turn off his recorder. https://t.co/e0lMq0aHQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCS &amp; CBCF have become one: Donation drop forces merger of Canada's largest cancer charities /via @globeandmail https://t.co/n5p0M7RuMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvlis is dangerous man who was fully endorsed by @Kellieleitch until yesterday. Too late @KellieLeitch. You'… https://t.co/OBHJikeB1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile on BC's Sunshine Coast....it's snowing - Alot!! https://t.co/DZLDQCRj8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls invented 'BowlingGreen Massacre' - it NEVER happened. She has completely lost her mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NickKouvalis, who was (and I say that skeptically) campaign manager for @KellieLeitch - used that word to describe… https://t.co/HjIWqxZCVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Nordstrom dumps the #IvankaTrump brand over weak sales https://t.co/QmpOjaHRUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DICTATOR threatening university. https://t.co/VwEAX9z0Ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not definitively. Musk's market is rich folks like Trump. https://t.co/NwFGD3jVxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This HATE Monger says he's resigned @KellieLeitch's campaign. Kouvalis is a TRUMP Clone whose insidious thoughts/ac… https://t.co/Nq9PlIfT2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe this 4 1 minute. @NickKouvalis will be stealthily working behind  scenes for @KellieLeitch &amp;… https://t.co/Z3Ol9tRLwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCurrentCBC BRILLIANT SHOW Feb. 2. Three of the most compelling stories of our time - David Frum on Trump, Islamaphobia in Canada, PTSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DavidFrum: READ THIS NOW - it's long, brilliantly written &amp; is coming true: How to Build an Autocracy https://t.co/eBBj6Ezyzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These #Trump appointments are just the beginning. Wait until they start doing their dirty work. Then the penny will drop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvalis is a #Bannon clone. Just as dangerous. @christyclarkbc is using him for her BC ""Liberal"" campaign.… https://t.co/2NbeGrE3Yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvalis is @kellieLeitch's campaign manager. And she says she's not a racist. She of the proposed… https://t.co/ltupFbS0Cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the vets &amp; active service troops who voted for @realDonaldTrump @POTUS are taking in his war mongering threats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know, I know, Easterners will laugh at us on BC's southcoast. We're just not used to snow at all. However, I do h… https://t.co/q7tQd7eXwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running around behind @realDonaldTrump @POTUS sweeping up his S*&amp;t!! https://t.co/gyIku4OIMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear #UK &amp; World Friends, please Retweet. @KeithOlbermann is one of the sane journalists in #US. He has consistentl… https://t.co/I6ixxQR0Rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My PRIORITY ISSUES Worldwide - Climate Change &amp; Protection of Women's Rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If U notice any BOTS or Fake accounts on my timeline, please let me know so I can BLOCK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Savings Accounts are only helpful if you make a lot of money. When you have to pay a premium each month, you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraMiers @abrams_doug How did you figure this out? I'd love to check my Twitter followers and those I'm following.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieLeitch proposed the #BarbaricPracticesHotline. PERIOD. https://t.co/hyEuxrxqPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe charities that rely on generous public donations should NOT hold any  event at a Trump facility. https://t.co/xy2kiN5l9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested 2 see how the #US does with unilateral trade negotiations now that Trump is turning country into a racist, misogynist hell hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also looks like the #US is only safe for white supremacists, women haters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like people around the world will be BOYCOTTING #US products in their own countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this about how #Iceland WOMEN took control. https://t.co/YqlHOtCn1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing to me that when I was in Mexico, so many of the #Americans I met weren't concerned about Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke to an ex-pat Ukrainian, who informed me that things there are NOT black &amp; white re: preferences 4 belonging to Russia or EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will NEVER vote CPC after what they did to #Canada under #StephenHarper. Especially now that Trump is in #US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was never an issue for me really. I voted #Liberal to get rid of #StephenHarper &amp; #CPCCronies. That was my top… https://t.co/QwB16oleDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is heartening. Please read &amp; Retweet. People can &amp; do make a difference with their actions. https://t.co/tLRUqNaRCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No legitimate CHARITY that relies on public support should hold their fundraising events at ANY TRUMP PROPERTY. https://t.co/nrUH3NBDqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieLeitch's office. https://t.co/Hbb4sFGorp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No LOSS whatsoever to anyone. https://t.co/EqLGMixoZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree @Jackstar009. I have a responsibility to get to know them and appreciate them. https://t.co/RwvIgI5DVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palm Beach braces for Trump protest during weekend visit https://t.co/75GHtK2EbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I'm #Canadian. The Quebec City shooter is a white, Canadian male, French decent, who is pro-Trump, misogynist. No Moroccan!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Vancouverites - BEWARE strange man on bus/skytrain. How to report. https://t.co/btz296Q8Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember the Anita Hill hearings. The Republicans were BRUTAL to her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughing at this. CNN was enormously responsible for Trump winning the election by having all his talking heads on… https://t.co/UM5YsUj8RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourism visits to #US are already suffering. People don't want 2 be in an unsafe country where everyone carries gun… https://t.co/nfqzojc8gQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the culture of hate toward Muslims, don’t forget Made-in-Canada political contributions /via @globeandmail https://t.co/XJ7pEIzOmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a SHOCK EVENT? Read this please. It's a major event designed to pit people against each other, cause... https://t.co/oWfUGHxv0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone watching #TheYoungPope? Parallels with @realDonaldtrump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLucksDS @jfreewright @CBCNews @SheWhoVotes I'm fully aware that he used it as an opp. to decry Muslims and I am disgusted &amp; appalled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfreewright @SheWhoVotes As much as I HATE Trump, he did call the Canadian PM this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casualcactii The whole world of sane people is with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this appropriately edited version of @KellieLeitch's statement on Muslim killings. She has directly contribute… https://t.co/5EXPiIKPqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this letter from The World to Trump. https://t.co/rSz2ukAxfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS knows better than 2 take on #LGBTQ folks. LGBTQ movement is strong, will B joined by Women, Environmental protectors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieLeitch - HYPOCRITE. https://t.co/phxRDZkpsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at his eyes - https://t.co/A2MUyxtfJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REALLY? Thru" US Airspace? https://t.co/TKYVoRhQe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s National Security Advisor Met with the Head of Austrian Neo-Nazi Party https://t.co/ffjYx5keth via @TeenVogue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go away! No one believes you. https://t.co/WtbLdtAEKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calxandr Your profile photo looks like you're smirking - which is exactly how I believe your brain works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calxandr is old CPC MP who recommended 'THE CULTURAL BARBARIC PRACTICES HOTLINE' along with @KellieLeitch. Speaking out of edge of mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Crony Cabinet May Look Strong, But They Are Scared https://t.co/vVntnujINn via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear #US Friends - PLEASE RETWEET: 
Sole #Quebec shooter at Quebec City Mosque is a white, #Trump-loving, anti-immigration Canadian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About #StopPresidentBannon... https://t.co/mCqH4YPMSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About #StopPresidentBannon..... https://t.co/gNdsQcH9Wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS @seanspicer #Quebec shooter was #CaucasianCanadian who likes Trump. Not a justification for… https://t.co/ugZEUT33ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee I agree. I think I got sucked in by a few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @jaredkushner posted photo of themselves on weekend at Gala, Gala doo, while country protesting Muslim… https://t.co/4mAWtszge1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask him why #Bannon is on the committee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in #Canada....we declare solidarity with people of ALL Faiths. https://t.co/71wTSE6J3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While #Canadians mourn killing of #Muslim people last night, @realDonaldTrump @POTUS defends his actions to #BAN #Muslims - kids &amp; grandmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoGOPNo @barbaraward235 He's not the president. #Bannon is.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>