<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In summary:
@TuataraBrew &amp; @panheadbrewery are doing it one way
@Garage_Project going another
No matter what, just keep doing it #Beersies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz Bizarre eh? But since he's pissed off about it lets start.....  #SleepingIn  #50Bucks etc etc etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_voter yet these clowns campaigned against the flag change and all the self-identity discussion that went with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aotearoaxi @Sportsfreakconz Injuries have done that to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aotearoaxi @Sportsfreakconz If both healthy whos the first option - Lockie or Milne?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aotearoaxi @Sportsfreakconz Such a bad thing he doesnt carry on like Steyn, Sharma, or any of the Aussies   #NotReally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @aotearoaxi Definitely not. Thats further up the order. Its topical, but we shouldnt be relying on them for runs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aotearoaxi @Sportsfreakconz Agree. He just shouldnt be batting ahead of Wags if the latter is playing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher @Sportsfreakconz Hopefully I havent stolen your story lines!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see that now he's made his choice the "comedian" for hire has decided he needs a Lizziesque profile too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps we could just send Paddy to find out? https://t.co/sc0IymTkWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz "Them' at it again.... https://t.co/jm9cDx0Wj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girvana There's a thing somewhere that lets you set key words to filter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ @TuataraBrew a capital injection from the big boys hasnt ruined Emersons or Panhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the reactions to @TuataraBrew 's announcement today..... Sheesh.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly @KloppGoff exactly!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly @KloppGoff cripes. I drink them all. Does that make me bad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Head_Weasel @GordMacey terrorism is just that. This is different to the portrayal of the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly @KloppGoff nothing has changed yet with either of those]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly @KloppGoff I'd like to know if Parrotdog for one as another in the WCC area were ever asked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KloppGoff @SmithyInWelly all the things to have made it happen are there. GP are great but this arvo has a bitchiness to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly neither am I, or @KloppGoff. But it's a talking point if that's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly if capital from a corporate is bad... Wonder how he'd react if Red Bull bought the Nix of Welnix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punters treated alot more like inmates than paying clients https://t.co/5NvUmj4RnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewvoerman @Sportsfreakconz @NiallGunner at the very least breeds inconsistent application of the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @EricCrampton not a top RW, but it's utterly abhorrent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @Nakiman who was the clown who thought an afternoon k/o in Adelaide, in January, was going to be fine....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In predictable Piers being a fucktard (again) news.... https://t.co/ELm8iJU0iH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KloppGoff @Sportsfreakconz @ShaneHarmon @kiwibardy Yep. Terrific from a business perspective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @ShaneHarmon @KloppGoff @kiwibardy but they'd be beyond bloody barking mad to do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @ShaneHarmon @KloppGoff @kiwibardy Agreed. But all it needs is a few new people changing the owners direction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @ShaneHarmon @KloppGoff @kiwibardy as long as they don't mess things around. Which is always possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneHarmon @KloppGoff @kiwibardy @Sportsfreakconz nailed it once again Shane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_voter hopefully they leave it alone. Like Lion has with Panhead so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therockfm hey team. What time and where for the GnR giveaways in Welly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tamcramer @bilko08 is that the only Sutton United shirt in New Zealand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kiwigolfer65 @BrianAshby2 perhaps @JamieWall2 can provide some confirmation of that too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz wait for Arsene to complain about Sutton's artificial pitch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad misstep this morning @pmbillenglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nz_voter or he's treating everyone as dumbasses. Which is endearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrontRowGrunt @mikechron @RugbyNZ_ under this system only teams 7 &amp; 8 definitely can't host a semifinals. It's much clearer IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one hit these like Scholes did https://t.co/JtR8IEoRZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonobasile @coltheman1 if that's a highlight I'd hate to see what a disaster is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikechron @RugbyNZ_ @FrontRowGrunt correct. If 8th and 5th win then 5th hosts. Forget the order the semis teams are laid out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortflyslip that was the nearest comp I could think of. Though a hobbled Cairns a better bet than Hazelwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortflyslip Somewhat different circumstances though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flightradar24 an irregular visitor to an Air Force base... https://t.co/N0DvYzQXTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marcus Stoinis has just played one of the greatest ODI innings in history. Lets not forget that. Doesnt deserve really to lose #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OUT!!!!    What. A. Game!!!  #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top of the pad #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZCricketMuseum In that case.... then it is an age!  Cheers again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZCricketMuseum OK.... that one slipped my mind. Seems like its been an age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We dont have a clue how to deal with this.... #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for mine there is only one person who can be considered for MotM in this one; win or lose. Stoinis has dominated this #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he absolutely believes that he can still win this #rpt #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats one very classy hundred from Marcus Stoinis #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher @sillymidoff another pesky 'strayan by the looks!  He has a blinder today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starc DID NOT need to do that.... not with Stoinis on fire at the other end. But Im not complaining in the slightest #OneToGo #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely poor hurdling technique @Sportsfreakconz @SWTGallagher https://t.co/8sMDZv1Kxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZCricketMuseum Last time an NZ keeper had two stumpings in an ODI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santner uses Cummins' aggressiveness against him beautifully. 8 down, 2 to get #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's in more pain right now? The streaker or @TheACCnz #HeadGrot Lane after getting the snip?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruggerblogger @sumostevenson thats closer.... but this from @JamieWall2 is even closer to the truth https://t.co/K9iVRFY57j esp last paras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruggerblogger Im not sure the 10s has near the same appeal TBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was he really making a beeline for @TheACCnz caravan? https://t.co/ESPinmlzA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shortflyslip Not sure Geoff Hurst is involved in this match Andrew ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ @stevemcmillan5 although the whole 'Turkey as bulwark against Russian aggression' might be a bit iffy at present]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ @stevemcmillan5 and a major recipient of US military hardware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ @stevemcmillan5 and seemingly not those that the Trump empire has business interests in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a team of players supposedly raised on hard fast decks facing quicks the Aussies arent liking what Lockie is dishing up at them #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf because he, and Labour, can't manage even form of consistency on issues viewed in parallel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewvoerman @BenJStrang Aside from Vegas and Dubai they all have the capacity within the main stadium. Standards everywhere going up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_miller_nz @Sportsfreakconz @heyxie And he really does hate that nickname. Its not of his doing, but still fun to wind up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenJStrang @andrewvoerman and there has been comments raised about that. Is that adequate for a codes premier global comp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenJStrang @andrewvoerman Does stadium have quality facilities to support 16 teams and all their gear? Westpac barely does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenJStrang @andrewvoerman Not opposed to the idea. But scratch the surface &amp; the questions come up. Also no series leg in South America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenJStrang @andrewvoerman Next thing - facilities. Up to scratch?  Then fitting it to the schedule given WR 'pairs' events. Heat a factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ Congrats again team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDIT: And goodbye Shaun Marsh.....  #NZvAUS   #RightBrotherThisTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenJStrang @andrewvoerman Now can Fiji afford the WR fee to host it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MellyEason Haha!!! Both the same!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 @Sportsfreakconz Clearly written with their off hand too #Classy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall Yep. read the @ffa release. Player welfare my arse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall So is @FFA calling Greeny etc liars for saying that they did?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALeague @FFA #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrssurge Like I said... make of it what you will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roonsopo That was just where the ball hit the deck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that noise definitely didnt come from anywhere else! #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish send your proposal to NZ Rugby then. And best of luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish I know you are. Would the Blues get this sort of crowd? Doubt it. are the Nines sold out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish Aucklanders are more generally more apathetic than the rest of the country. Would another event change that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KloppGoff @SWTGallagher @Sportsfreakconz Our part-timer is better than their part-timer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz there is that. Plus Aussie haven't batted well there in most recent digs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsaymouat in a roundabout way yes. But it's  the OTT response to previous things plus all the wowsers etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz How many short you reckon? 20? 30?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's greatest #11 #LovelyTrenty #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish I think @ShaneHarmon nailed it when he said we have to look at how we treat sevens as a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish which WR is highly unlikely to go too given they group the tournaments. Auckland maybe, but would the apathy be different? 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamthehamish the argument for Dunedin is based on O-week. Think that alone isn't alarm bells? Plus it would mean changing schedule... 1/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the #NoShitSherlock files... https://t.co/GQaVrJYu78]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>