<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivanplis @goyal_abhi A great event to run into great people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunter S Thompson: "like lust or malaria… once you've seen one of your own kind standing next to the president… life will never be the same"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump expels experts from government, opportunistic anti-expertise experts emerge to take their place. In that regard, business as usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, @nntaleb showed how antifragile he was by blocking me within a minute of me sending this tweet, thereby taking… https://t.co/reNF6cnYL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American dream: building several careers on basic statistics with an edgy framing and keen awareness of which side… https://t.co/Vgk2KSWO6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sic semper tyrannis https://t.co/vsWcXqpdUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the many reasons that today is a great day to listen to The Monitor by @TitusAndronicus:… https://t.co/hne4fu82Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barefoot_Econ @brianklaas @nytimes Maybe, only if it works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese medicine is driving a rise in donkey slaughter, also depriving global impoverished commutes of pack animals https://t.co/HJLlktRzvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyberattack disabled 70% of DC police CCTV cameras before the inauguration, the entire network had to be reinstalled
https://t.co/uYOSyMgvaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we're going to ban the Quebecois from entering the United States to protect American Muslims, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're unsure where this leads, German police raid far-right group planning attacks on police, refugees, and Jews https://t.co/ro86nZ7yiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you debate the ethics of punching Nazis, UW College Republicans defend shooting a protestor at their event: https://t.co/f8w9F00qmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians talk like we just let Syrians in when it really takes years and more security checks than other refugees https://t.co/FfFZcbDqLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpundit I left out the part about the knife fights: https://t.co/2UrW0Jyh02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pato, Argentina's national sport, is like horseback quidditch, originally played with a live duck, and outlawed due to high player mortality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you think you were getting paid for your goddamn silly art? No, Ralph. You were getting paid to smash windows."… https://t.co/ticJqwHzU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunter Thompson: "in the name of art…you could draw queer pictures of the prime minister… but your own son shouldn’t want to smash windows?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As if we had all been plunged into a dream… We move like gazelles or the way gazelles move in a tiger's dream." Bolaño, By Night in Chile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU task force: “highly likely” Russia will try to influence French, Dutch, and German election “as it did in the US” https://t.co/k4nnPeovzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alymaybe @AthertonKD Much harder to delete a tattoo though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While we're debating whether it's OK to punch Nazis, Russian parliament is on track to make it OK to punch women https://t.co/MAPyZjCVqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeRodeheffer That was Sullivan Street Bakery on West 47th Street, I passed through Manhattan for a few hours ear… https://t.co/cRzyaXkVi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York has decided that by now, it's more effective to write feminist graffiti in Russian: "Women's rights are hu… https://t.co/XJzVya2jDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beating the Fascists argues research shows "preparedness of anti-fascists to use violence was not only historically… https://t.co/AeKFMKIPy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A literature review for those taking an academic approach to the Nazi punching question https://t.co/A2NhCMW9sR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tellmemo Living the dream, more or less. How have you been?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having seen the opiod epidemic as a cop, @nselby experienced it as a pain patient. His account is well worth a read.
https://t.co/XNGIpEvMfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horses of the world, unite! https://t.co/Ru2UX52nES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a recent survey, roughly as many Americans wanted to keep or expand the Affordable Care Act as repeal it:… https://t.co/0HtrsDdpPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police more often believe we've achieved racial equality, but the disparity between black and white officers is lar… https://t.co/H3TTIXvZ1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socialist Jim Cannon on World Peace Council: "professional fellow travelers…steered…by hard-faced jockeys from the Stalinist riding stables"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United Arab Emirates outlawed keeping wild animals like lions and tigers as pets, and even dogs need new permits https://t.co/RYfZiKawp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've come to realize that just like you can be rich in more than just money, you can also be nouveau riche in travel, experience, time, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Racially infused, conservative-populist movements gaining ground in both America and Europe" embrace Putin's Russia https://t.co/nOv0KnPywq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jewish Defense League won’t oppose Montana's anti-Jewish march led by a neo-Nazi due to white nationalist sympathies https://t.co/QDMqScw9YE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West shouldn't "contribute to [Putin's] mythmaking…stop building him up by portraying him as a virtual supervillain" https://t.co/BWzbcRAhHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True, lots of people who don't live in DC will love us disrupting our diplomacy: primarily those in countries with… https://t.co/XsCfCE5XXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Holman Rule to threaten civil servants with a $1 salary was previously revived to fight wild horse conservation https://t.co/oqtTj1wLEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to clear up any ambiguity: https://t.co/WlxcoPgHsL https://t.co/x6QTTvAky6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if a vile and possibly racially motivated crime against a white man made people empathize rather than keep score and justify racism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Kevin McCauley's Russian Influence Campaigns against the West: From the Cold War to Putin https://t.co/XNsbiSElCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Soviets created front groups targeting specific groups such as students and youth, women…causes such as peace, disarmerment or antifacsism"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Münzenberg led Soviet fronts he called Innocents' Clubs til Stalin condemned him for treason like other antifascists https://t.co/jluYKxirqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lithuanian intelligence…[say] cyber attacks have moved from being mainly financial crimes to more political spying" https://t.co/buTVeSCIeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China promising to shut down its ivory trade in 2017 "could be the pivotal turning point that brings elephants back" https://t.co/aH4ElROHZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidence shows forcing real names online doesn't improve behavior, it only worsens discrimination and harassment https://t.co/P3GsfjAUXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that Assange is the Right's unbiased authority, how does it feel about his Iraq leaks and war crimes accusations?https://t.co/mh0yHErRa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At an elementary school in Northeast DC, children hang up their wishes for the new year https://t.co/iSV76URtKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmathews @DaveedGR Was this him? https://t.co/LORV0nXP4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCauley's Russian Influence Campaigns against the West shows front groups were stunningly effective under Stalin until gutted by his purges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Agromahdi123 I assume @peterwsinger means CrowdStrike, FireEye, Palo Alto Networks, Kaspersky Lab, and Fidelis: https://t.co/AeRcd35cC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Agromahdi123 @peterwsinger Right, that's the problem. That article and others like it suggest only the government is making these claims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Russian Influence Campaigns against the West, on Wili Munzenberg, the "Comintern's premier front organizer," m… https://t.co/3lrns0KPF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Civil War pitted brother against brother, bear against bear https://t.co/EecNh4HY8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was on VCU's campus two minutes but a woman in an Easter Bunny onesie asked me where to find a Chick-fil-A so I've had the full experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samratner After the vote, the Museum shows a short film meant to firmly convince visitors that the Civil War was definitely about slavery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since opening, Richmond's Civil War Museum at Historic Tredegar let visitors to vote on what they think caused the… https://t.co/lf06N9kRIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me at the start of 2016 vs. me at the end of 2016 https://t.co/JcJa09BzIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlSchreck Like when Russia banned American adoptions in response to the Magnitsky Act, children are once again the victims of retaliation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacking's the focus because it's closest to a smoking gun but it isn't the only or even most significant form of Russian political influence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an attempt to redeem the last days of 2016, a new species of dwarf lemur, Cheirogaleus shethi, was just describe… https://t.co/4YAYc2hdIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More blackouts in Ukraine that are almost certainly the result of cyber attacks https://t.co/0qcUvScdbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Hungary, "Russian military intelligence officers… staged regular mock combat exercises… with neo-Nazi activists"
https://t.co/RRm0Wpu4Zh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While praising Trump, Assange claims WikiLeaks doesn't need to criticize Putin since Russia already has a free pres… https://t.co/8npmuNM39K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Llamakah, the festival of ungulights https://t.co/aUXfxCSHgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was lucky to get a signed copy when American Ulysses launched. Much of what made Grant noteworthy had previously… https://t.co/UqBM5iWIj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World War II Mexican anti-Nazi poster https://t.co/SlLZBuMsxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Species moved from wild to tame multiple times… human agency played a far smaller role than previously believed" https://t.co/cPyVGffVYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limusaurus lost all its teeth and became an herbivore in adulthood to avoid competing with its omnivorous offspring: https://t.co/WZwqHN7DyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian propaganda has grown frighteningly effective: https://t.co/2whday98MA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flynn's company partnered with "a man once convicted of trying to sell stolen biotech material to the Russian KGB" https://t.co/0A5tVcHmvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who noticed that Rogue One was For Whom The Bell Tolls in space?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When analyzing Russian political influence, remember Soviet reflexive control that drove targets to unwittingly make predetermined decisions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only did Johnny Cash write poetic lyrics, he also wrote poetry. Here's his California Poem:… https://t.co/DvXCJ2rskQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poem about the zombie apocalypse inspired by bad traffic: https://t.co/y6vy9al8v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since most of its neurons are in its tentacles, "consciousness experienced by an octopus… is wholly alien to humans" https://t.co/OMlVlGbFb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dhnexon Maybe I'm being generous but I read the original article not as "don't teach Classics or Western Civ," just "careful how it's used"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flood of white supremacy in the replies disproves Douthat's strawman about racists leveraging Classics being a… https://t.co/PEwLKczkx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines' president on abusing drugs despite his drug war: “Fools, I just made up that story and you believed it” https://t.co/jb0XFH9i2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunter S. Thompson's political commentary resonates once again and his Hell's Angels previewed our political climate https://t.co/wn4H9IfuLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donachaidh No, DC, so duck hearts must just be hot right now. But I've just read a good book on Oakland, Bullies, and want to check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donachaidh Wait, I ALSO just had duck hearts. Were we at the same restaurant at the same time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeRodeheffer that's a quagmire for sure, but unfortunately too relevant and high stakes to be tedious these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything more tedious than otherwise smart thinkers who grew up without the Internet discussing what it does to Kids These Days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad Obama shifted "Russian interference" from hacking to foreign influence infiltrating partisan news already just a shade from propaganda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having been exposed to elite lifters, every time a politician says "400 pound hacker," I think "that's not even that big, to be honest"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you were wondering, Rudolph can snatch 140 kilos but Santa can deadlift 650 pounds: https://t.co/dCS0EpvbAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AthertonKD Given the administration's Twitter presence, journalists should also edit their bios with "RTs ≠ endorsements of nuclear war"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member of Trump's USDA transition team ran an organization that "seems to exist mainly to troll the Humane Society" https://t.co/1JD0BKX0W6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entire Bunker Hill, Indiana, police force quit over being asked to "do illegal, unethical, and immoral things" https://t.co/jrfEVJFmaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What surprises me most about Politico firing @juliaioffe is that I really expected Breitbart to be the new administration's state-run media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Eight Ways to Avoid Getting Shanked by Other Weightlifters" like don't walk in front of someone preparing to lift https://t.co/bVt80ymwyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep a hand on your wallet when somebody says they know how Russia "thinks." If they start calling Russia "she," you've already been robbed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nationalist anti-corruption activist and vocal Putin critic Navalny plans to run for president - will he be allowed?
https://t.co/NP8yVT1Dgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're no match for the GRU's brilliant active measures! If we studied the KGB, we'd turn on 2 factor authentication… https://t.co/7GHhIGESjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From “Please Bury Me in This” by Allison Benis White: https://t.co/4M5ycNJNGf https://t.co/YCw2MujWTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am still waiting for the right words to explain myself to you…
Or maybe emptiness is a form of listening.
Maybe I am just listening."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When strong evidence of foreign intelligence influence in US politics is answered with false flag conspiracies, middle ground isn't moderate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Context for claims Exxon CEO and Putin ally Tillerson is a reasonable SecState because Gates and Rice suggested him… https://t.co/5N2KjE1UVh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>