<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson I was all set to jump in with the three-count but he was back on his feet almost instantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson He jumped off the sofa towards her and she half-caught him but he deflected off her and landed on his back. He was loving it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation between @IslaRamsay and 4 y/o nephew:

"Auntie Isla, are you from the olden days?"

"No! I'm 29!"

"So you're from these days?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Used to hate when Fed won all the time but can't begrudge him that one. Feel for Rafa. Another epic battle in a legendary rivalry. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday I saw my girlfriend's mum pay homage to WWF wrestler D'lo Brown by executing a near-textbook Sky High on her 4-year old grandson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you turn up to the #AusOpen final and you're wearing the same shorts, socks and shoes as e… https://t.co/85IbMGNtDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desperate times for LL Cool J having to audition on #TheVoice. https://t.co/CrjsFpie1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another #T2trainspotting observation. Of the various Hibee cameos, I have to say I was most impressed by @jmcginn7 as Begbie's son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There we have it. And that's science speaking. You can't argue with science. #baldtruth https://t.co/gQ8uIQMtjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in the Morgan household, Piers is watching #GrahamNorton. https://t.co/Vfp6TCtTaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze Yeah we re-watched the first a few days ago as well. Definitely adds to the sense of nostalgia in T2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, to sum up... @T2Trainspotting #DannyBoyle @mcgregor_ewan @robertcarlyle_ @jonnyjlm #EwenBremner https://t.co/bzm0hoRetf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole soundtrack was fantastic actually. "Silk" by Wolf Alice is an absolute tune. #T2trainspotting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved the nostalgia of it: the bits lifted directly from the books, the opening chords of Born Slippy echoing periodically. #T2trainspotting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a smidgeon of fear heading to see #T2trainspotting that it wouldn't live up to the hype. Fear very much alleviated - it's sensational.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happy hunting ground". 😂 Sure we've got a similar record at Parkhead. By that logic, Celtic will be quaking in the… https://t.co/4qY7RuJbS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamBain87 Yeah but think of all the kids films you'll get to see in the years to come. Congrats btw! Absolute spit of you. 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamBain87 1. Collateral Beauty, 2. A Monster Calls, 3. La La Land, 4. Rogue One. For my 140 character reviews, please see previous tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Film five of 2017: #ManchesterByTheSea. Liked it, but it was the sort of sombre slow-burner I doubt I'd sit through again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here, anyone else remember that time @piersmorgan got absolutely pied by Ewan McGregor then spent days greetin' and tweeting about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @mcgregor_ewan Run along to Papa Donald. He'll kiss it better for you, "Champ".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's no C.J. Cregg, that's for sure. https://t.co/8navsLUW3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson The innocence of youth. I'd trade her mindset for my own in a heartbeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get some of the ridicule towards Van Basten, but a dislike (or ignorance) of other sports is a lame argument against reform in football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect excuse to unearth my favourite clip of Patrick Stewart having a laugh and not taking himself too seriously. https://t.co/mvZQDbmQU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this has made my year. https://t.co/wGPQxIbnNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray @Follow_Follow_ So you address refereeing standards. Collum's flaws as a ref aren't synonymous with flaws of sin bins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sked21 No need for an orange card though. Ten minute sin bin for a yellow card would suffice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sked21 The sin bin idea is the only one I'm on board with. Would cut out cynical fouls and players "taking one for the team".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a time when Hollywood chucks 💵 at tired, repetitive franchises like Fast &amp; Furious, it's great that #StarWars remains fresh and original.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved #RogueOne. Plenty callbacks for the diehard fan without turning it into a Star Wars tribute film. A gripping chapter in its own right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second solo lunch in a row. @GregorSwanson @joaqpheonix https://t.co/YTWiEVO51A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No @GregorSwanson or @joaqpheonix at work today. Sitting on my lunch like... https://t.co/UHFP1bggxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson @joaqpheonix @tagropemag Sons of Anarchy meets Some Mothers Do 'Ave 'Em. Brilliant find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Andy Carroll goal from yesterday should be worth at least double. Five points doesn't do it justice.… https://t.co/HNuJ7yjdWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe a little dated, considering it was published over 20 years ago, but an interesting snapshot in time nonetheless. Worth a read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished Football Against the Enemy by @KuperSimon. An absorbing study of football's close relationship with politics around the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you find out Channel 4 are bringing back #TheCrystalMaze. https://t.co/FBZa3QW6L0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything Gosling can't turn his hand to? Serious, comical, musical. Almost as versatile as Barry. #LaLaLand https://t.co/lTtWcrt3VD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More cinema. #LaLaLand: a classy modern-day nod to 50s-era musicals. Reminded me of the Gene Kelly films we watched in Standard Grade music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze Experience our defence is crying out for and will help youngsters like Souttar immeasurably. Hard to draw negatives from this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second cinema trip of 2017: #AMonsterCalls. If this gut-wrenchingly honest portrayal of grief doesn't make you cry, then you're dead inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this and thought it might have been because you'd run out of Applewood Smoked Cheddar, @MichaelLiness. Relieved… https://t.co/tNogZfe8wO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary Barlow pitching #LetItShine to the BBC. https://t.co/2BkxkuMU6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Mika performance on #Pointless was like one of those random Conway Twitty interludes on Family Guy. Very bizarre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not paid much attention to Scottish lower league football the past couple of years but this Dundee Utd team is honking. How are they second?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in Scotland, we have a national team manager who doesn't seem to recognise who our best players are in almost every position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over-hyping players and piling this kind of pressure on them at such an early stage in their careers is so quintess… https://t.co/P7AAMCzn27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson I like Will Smith but his ratio of good films to bad ones isn't great. This one tips the balance back in his favour slightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson I'd say so. It's a very emotional film but some of the lines were a bit cheesy. Smith's very good in it though, to be fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First cinema trip of 2017: #CollateralBeauty. On the Will Smith scale, it was neither "After Earth bad", nor "Seven Pounds good". 6.5/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 can shove its healthy diets and detox plans. I discovered this the other day and it's pretty much made life in… https://t.co/RQh88GnVhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take it this means all the bloaters who retire to Benidorm will be given Spanish lessons before they go? https://t.co/rFqgxrK3mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting to one side the fact he'd be a good acquisition, I mainly want this to happen for the delicious seethe it'l… https://t.co/ITFvur0vfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson We saw it the other week and enjoyed it. Hanks is a safe pair of hands. 7/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must be rough being a member of the Mitchell clan. #Eastenders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel for the next generation. In 2016 we've mourned some absolute icons. In 50 years they'll be left to mourn a few Kardashians and Dappy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than Clarkson and Hammond are the knuckle-draggers in the studio audience applauding their chronic brand of "banter".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If nothing else, this Richard Hammond episode offers a perfect excuse to watch my favourite 15 mins of standup ever. https://t.co/NfH1eDXSdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson My guess is he'll rate Scott Bain's performance quite highly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson Defence aside, they seemingly played some of the best stuff they've played in ages. Confident he'll get results soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson I know you're just fishing, but that should really read "Hearts defence 🙈".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never a penalty. No contact from Samson. Rooney cons the ref by clipping his own leg. But Jamie Walker's the only diver in this league, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact, the complete lack of peanut butter representation across all the big Xmas sweet tubs, in this day and age, is an injustice IMHO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nestle would do well to bin either the toffee penny or toffee finger from Quality Street and get some peanut butter in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope Courtney's interview with Claude involves him being slapped about then dangled out the window by his stupid pink tie. #TheApprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news @IslaRamsay! https://t.co/Db1DeEalUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsadler87 Thought you were allergic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze His rage was absolutely delicious. I love how upset Cathro is making people without having said anything inflammatory himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lesleym1987 I've actually enjoyed this year more than last year. That might have more to do with the sweepstake we've had at work though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably the worst final five #TheApprentice has ever coughed up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss you bbz. @jdob78 #TheApprentice https://t.co/3RhfHlGP8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze Disagree entirely re the haircut. I say grow it longer! The old boys network with their short back and sides will be hating it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFBorthwick Never understood the Biffy Clyro hype. Embarrassingly over-rated. Far better Scottish bands out there, Admiral Fallow for one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson Amazing! A Swanson family conference about food. You must've been in your element. 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved a UCI trip as a kid. Also have fond memories of the Odeon, sneaking into films I was too young for. #thuglife https://t.co/qIgSfnBabg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson Lies. Nobody denied it. We simply pointed out that it didn't make a difference, she's still hot and you have high standards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sforrest86 Scottish football is run by a private members club with no transparency. Unless that changes, Pot 6 obscurity beckons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sforrest86 To be honest, I've become so apathetic about the national team that yesterday's news barely registered with me. I'm past caring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sforrest86 Exactly. I could "do my best" if put in charge of the national team. Doesn't make me the ideal candidate for the job though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking days off work to wait for IKEA deliveries to arrive. https://t.co/LQrHi5ShSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFBorthwick I did #solocinema earlier today for the first time. Massively underrated. Doesn't deserve the social stigma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagle Royal Rumble kicking off on #planetearth2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toasting @clobster7's last night as a free man with the #ENGSCO game and a tasty Polish brew. A wee throwback to th… https://t.co/xNG4zGLodD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuMq1 Tried to mix it up as best as possible. Think they'd do a job. https://t.co/kG0X6q8Cbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicholas may be a massive welt, but this is the glaring reality of it all. I'd probably pick all of our keepers ahe… https://t.co/xzJKBDd5LS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuMq1 Hard to imagine Brexit or President Trump happening in an age without widespread social media. Maybe a sign of things to come?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect song choice by @OC on @absoluteradio this morning. "Mad World" by Tears for Fears. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only went to see #AStreetCatNamedBob because we missed The Accountant. Glad we did in the end. A nice uplifting film for a Sunday afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze He's a talented but infuriating player to watch. Has a chronic fear of shooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ComeOnAndy https://t.co/6SNM0kbfl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah well, another work sweepstake I've been papped out of. Farewell @jdob78! You were a gentleman from start to finish. #TheApprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JD on #TheApprentice tonight. https://t.co/klQybJXZ3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise One Direction had qualified for the Champions League. #UCL #THFC https://t.co/hUWfbUEoiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorSwanson Not guilty. I was also handed said Jelly Babies and settled for a green one myself. Won't be tarred with that manky brush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left with all the foamy ones in a matter of minutes. Shan Haribo etiquette from @IslaRamsay. https://t.co/KJOi2PPX7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsadler87 @IslaRamsay was definitely greetin' though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelsadler87 It didn't quite move me to tears but I was pretty chuffed for both of them. Great ending to a captivating series. #Hunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless Brown stumbled into Jeff Goldblum's telepod from The Fly with Xavi and Paul Scholes, this really isn't as "m… https://t.co/08sUptBeOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a harrowing way to go to sleep. "And the moral of my story? Death can come when you least expect it. Sweet dre… https://t.co/FMnPKixf38]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>