<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiksRedGuard "coming together" - rubbish. The country is more divided than I can ever remember]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoorAjaj shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majorwilf @rawlimark surely space for a submarine there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiksRedGuard @bambula wow, barely recognisable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music @RichardHawley great start to the day, best song EVER - Hawley's "The Ocean"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark in Scotland we have 50 words for rain and we describe it in its angle from horizontal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark apparently ours is extremely changeable and localised so, erm, more interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterwalker99 Nicholas Cage would turn me Trump ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seankgn32 @WingsScotland fortunately we elected her for her policies and leadership skills. Still, shame we don't have a pin up like May]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark @MetroUK they could introduce a Happy Clappy meal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't believe my luck doing Scot:lands today and seeing @jamthrawn. Also Tannahil themed and me a Paisley buddy. Happy New Year indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark sounds ace, hope you had a great day xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipstout no it's never too early when a timelord is involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETimsNet @Stan_And_Ollie snap! That's what got too. Can't wait to watch it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark I started in Edinburgh but you're correct - it's been blown to Aberdeen which is now in Norway ðŸ’¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark merry Christmas my funny friends. Big mwah to you. Much love back xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark shocked! Where is the â¤ï¸??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark is that a compliment or an insult ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark it's ok Sam I know you've been preoccupied since I moved in, er, 2001 ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark lol you two! Yep Edinburgh Sam - lovely at this time of year ðŸŒ§âš¡ï¸ðŸ’¨â›ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdoleman @AllieHBNews guess it's only natural to die with 6 bullets in you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinistryBrexit but unfortunately not ðŸ‡«ðŸ‡·ðŸ‡³ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡¨ðŸ‡¿ðŸ‡­ðŸ‡·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark gotta be prepared- them being away could be an elaborate hoax to catch you out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heraldscotland Christmas means Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinShovel @RiksRedGuard @guardian it's more The Hooded Claw imho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 @theJeremyVine incidentally that's just as true of Scottish Independence #indyref2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiksRedGuard @guardian hell that would fund a week of post brexit NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ian4UKIP @theJeremyVine "Lycra clad plonkers" may suggest some unconscious bias here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeheenan @AngrySalmond follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telegraph @Pmacgiollabhain @TelegraphNews that's her job. She made her preference clear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inneslaing a hoof in the nuts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music @LizKershawDJ @MGStephenson Martin Stephenson absolute legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theJeremyVine I'm sure Harry's dad will be proud. Although Prince Charles won't be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScoWorstDrivers considerate to cars, inconsiderate to people with prams. Drylaw. https://t.co/w3BaHv4k1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukehowardtri shocker but unfortunately not uncommon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjust67 @TheClumpany @Daily_Record the rest of the SPL must have forgotten to read this script]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMcKelvie @owen_g @guardian greedy, corrupt, unsportsmanlike, uncompetitive, undeserving. Has turned me off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD @rawlimark maybe you could try Bob Marley's spliff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant result for Dideriksen at #UCIDoha2016. Shame the ceremony crowd was reminiscent of a club hill climb event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GildedpumpkinMD did @rawlimark photoshop out your straw?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weaselpopper @rawlimark the Sun don't see the irony of "treats women like dirt" headline beside photo on left?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artisannes @theJeremyVine @NicolaSturgeon @guardian always go for the gag ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theJeremyVine @NicolaSturgeon @guardian as a Scot I don't dodge my license fee to be insulted like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pavbryan the other riders faces ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willwrite4cake I'm with you on Paddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PickardJE @WingsScotland @MediaChris presumably the Scots can put the brexiteers in the tower too for acting against our will?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music good man Simon, outstanding album and you chose the best track. #CocteauTwins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music whoever that bloke is talking about Cocteau Twins, Head Over Heels he's my new best mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark wtf are wire firepeople - they sound amazing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark that's what our sparrows look like in Scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark could be Nessie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyclingEurope @WeAreCyclingUK if only there was a way for drivers to become cyclists...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoPlattTweets @koozers wow head like a microphone ðŸŽ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipstout gutted, mine is in hifi hospital with a broken arm ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamSpiers nice to see Danny McGrain is still getting out and about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark same old sun every day. But what happens in that pub - chaos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoPlattTweets that's me hearing about GBBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark but at what ISO?  I need to know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark @jointhebreed are those your spare tyres Mark?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark no help offered there either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark reminds me of Kevin Carter's famous photo - wonder if that's what the togs thought https://t.co/1ToBiReAp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark wasn't aware of the media scrum Mark, that's disturbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark yes sad but you could argue that taking this photo has had more impact on public awareness than anything else has]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewJacklin @rawlimark classic Bond villain shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling so true. Read any internet forum and see how quickly any civil question descends into personal abuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pmacgiollabhain fortunately for him lions don't use money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshall_kappel cracking profile pic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark @MetroUK what he said didn't imply anything about who's role it is. Jumping to conclusions. Wanting to be offended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willwrite4cake @BBCScotlandNews remember the Scottish news comes straight after the uk news so always has a Scottish slant (naturally)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScalareSorpasso beast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Rio2016 awesome women's pursuit. And @_katiearchibald should be a household name here in Scotland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Rio2016 Noooo! This is what a derny looks like! https://t.co/lSZTgZByRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark the transit van?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewAwhouston release the lions and there's good sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewAwhouston #toffsonhorses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoPlattTweets morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipstout toffs on horses. Sport?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosiemay9900 @JoPlattTweets @nicktwinney @tuna_lucy ah I miss the psychoactive drug period of daytime TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoPlattTweets ha, remember it well. In Scotland we had to wait a few weeks until the English schools were off then holiday TV started ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark this it? https://t.co/9MtSH889Hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomsonHolidays some relaxing, some Tui tours and some exploring of this beautiful island. Bliss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomsonHolidays how's that for attention to detail at Lindos View, Rhodes? https://t.co/pIgk1Q0s80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyclingEurope where is this Andrew? Beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark try the auto setting. I think that must be for cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark so disappointed. After Ronaldo spoke to that moth I was waiting on the giant Eagles to arrive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark if only he had the sparkling personality and dazzling skills of, er, Tim Henman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewAwhouston I can see neither a Raven nor flock of seagulls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewAwhouston always the sun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark get me one, my old xpro1 is long in the tooth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark have you finally come round to Fuji?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjohngalloway @philipstout @Nigel_Farage @V_Andriukaitis hint: it's not the racist liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjohngalloway @philipstout @Nigel_Farage @V_Andriukaitis I know who I'd rather represent me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian ashamed and embarrassed to have him speak there purportedly in my name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark being returned from Britain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnLamont hear hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWYweddings we do! No special reason just full of the joys of summer (rain stopped and double figures!) xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWYweddings morning Sam, well done and I hope it was useful. All good here - feeling funky ðŸ˜œ xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrvineWelsh @alexmassie good article. Why suspend campaigning? Is it because they know well that  it's divisive, inflammatory, aggressive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawlimark the little one is still showing its rubber band from the catapult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclist 4 bar heater]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>