<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@genetics1999 @evanescence @AmyLeeEV Pretty sweet. Was it vinyl or CD collection as I can't remember?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @TheJoeStorm @TokyoHiro_SKUNX @Halestorm Wow I'm really impressed. And does Joe really have that tattoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @TheJoeStorm @TokyoHiro_SKUNX @Halestorm That looks so badass. How long did it take to put together?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnaLeneeShow Lovely selfie. Sweet shades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennoVonMarie Right on thx for the follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnaLeneeShow It's ok as you're a very busy woman but just want to say hey hope yur week has been rad so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jetjaguar67 Got to be for me PlayStation and Nintendo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 1st of the month peeps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabbathCostello @DIAMANTEband @YouTube Ha this interview was fun. Soon enough Dia will get her opportunity to tour internationally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE Have had a few of those nights in the past. Freaky dreams of sudden drops from an insane height.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE Any really trippy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns Jealously is ugly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns Why would someone bully u? You're cute. As long as you'r not offended then yeah do yur thing as I mentioned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieDunn93 Could mean something else entirely lol. Katie needs her coffee now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE That's terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns Then keep it going. Keep doing yur thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelleFoley Seen every episode and #HolyFoley is a fantastic show. We get hysterical moments to emotional tender moments. Loved it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieDunn93 @TotalEmmalution All I can say is right on. That's got to put a smile on her face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE Hopefully not. It sux you're feeling so ill that u may have to go to hospital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns You concerned if someone says anything over the top or perhaps disrespectful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE I'm glad to hear it. The positive vibes truly helped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns What's the whole Curious Cat thing? I'm confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd is rowdy &amp; making the #ListOfJericho on @IAmJericho #TIJ live in Toronto w/ best friend @FightOwensFight The greatest creation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns Thx. I'll need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns Can't complain too much. Heading over to Uni to sort some stuff out tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleySinns How are things mate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmNotRhanda @Michael47198999 @genetics1999 @_Mz_Hyde_ @LZZYHALE Adorable. Have my cat sitting above me right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at those abs @MissCaliCarter Looking absolutely stunning. https://t.co/ruYSRLIUW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher @HeidiTheButcher @carlaharvey That's so cool. Both are still right up there to who I want to meet. Such lovely people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xXEvilMidgetXx @lycrymosa @DevilskinNZ I'm pretty stoked for them. U both got to know them &amp; it was great to chat w/ them after Sydney show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AugustAmesxxx Always a plus. Canadians rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5FDPChrisKael @BaconBarLV Ok this shit needs to be brought to Australia. Of course our beer is already pretty great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AugustAmesxxx Looking very beautiful. Lovely selfie to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetalheadAussie Not having much luck getting my tweets scrolled in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't which reference by @mauroranallo I got a kick out of between Big Sean and South Park. Both were great as was both #SDLive &amp; #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher How is with job finding for u? Have u heard back from anyone of a potential job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetalheadAussie Actually saw his tweet scroll on Talking Smack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher And I'm happy you're so happy with yur girlfriend. I just want to earn enough to go to more rockshows lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher As for me life has been meh being broke isn't really fun. Went to my 1st job interview and was so nervous I couldn't sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher Ooh that's great to hear. Very happy for u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaigeTheButcher Been a while so how are things? Life treating you well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicajaymes Looking mighty rad with the sweet shades. Hopefully the therapy takes yur mind off the pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicajaymes At least you're still getting around doing everyday things. You look amazing by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TanyaTate Oooh those look delicious ðŸ˜‹ U make them yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was great once again @mauroranallo calling 3 great hrs of action with #SDLive &amp; #205Live Now you'll call yur 1st Chamber match I can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoltanBathory @jamesmcgowan It's just better to accept defeat rather than delete and run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DIAMANTEband If you were to tour with @HeidiTheButcher @StefwithanfCOTW @Mixiofficial all collectively... I think it will happen eventually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DIAMANTEband So many to say. @itsdorothysucka and yourself would be a rad pair I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madison420Ivy Ok I want to hang with you if you're chowing down donuts while we watch DBZ. Damn looking at them makes me hungry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityoftheWeak @StefwithanfCOTW this looks so awesome. Too bad I'm broke ðŸ˜ž Really dig the design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DIAMANTEband ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ Looking very lovely in this outfit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyOrton is in a prime position after winning the Royal Rumble. Beware of the Viper #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome the Viper to #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to Naomi and Alexa Bliss have a fantastic match for the Women's championship at #EliminationChamber #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalEmmalution @NaomiWWE This tweet just scrolled along #TalkingSmack ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see @NaomiWWE who brings such a positive attitude. She is on a roll. #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EliminationChamber is barbaric. The 6 men will endure such punishment #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tag Team Turmoil at #EliminationChamber what an opportunity for the #SDLive tag division #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't deny Cena is one hard worker. Winning his 16th championship and learning Mandarin #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome champions #AmericanAlpha to #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yes Cena and Styles stole the show at Rumble #TalkingSmack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An amazing tag team main event on #205Live but Noam Dar won't think so after Neville left him high and dry #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome back to #TalkingSmack @WWEDanielBryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This should be an excellent tag team match. Such contrast of styles between Gallagher, Alexander, Dar and Neville #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashanyao @LZZYHALE Hopefully you're starting to feel much better now. Rest well mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knockers7of9 @buss02_megan @LZZYHALE Finding out who u are is the ultimate journey we all are on. We all will find our way and our purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neville is the king but Alice Fox is no baggage #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE Well if u enjoy being with a woman it shouldn't be deterred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really learning more about Tozawa thanks to @mrbriankendrick knowledge #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited for the debut @TozawaAkira He is so awesome. #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet! The Man With The Plan @mrbriankendrick is here. Can't wait to hear his thoughts on the debut of @TozawaAkira #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Mz_Hyde_ One more sleep to go until u see TPR ðŸ™Œ Have a great time and enjoy if u do mingling with Taylor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unfortunate that @GottaGetSwann injured his ankle but he'll bounce back. #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE Oh well if u can open his eyes u can help him understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Nese might be the most dangerous man in the cruiserweight division #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE That sounds ridiculous. This is coming from someone who hasn't had a relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE If I may leave my two cents, u may have to end things if you're not accepted for who u are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE Yur welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buss02_megan @Knockers7of9 @LZZYHALE Happy belated birthday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SDLive was fantastic as usual but now bring on #205Live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Mz_Hyde_ @LorenitaEV LOL can't blame u for not being able to sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baron Corbin will be the most dangerous come #EliminationChamber in my opinion. A real dark horse to win the WWE championship #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As expected back and forth between Ambrose and Styles. This match isn't disappointing at all #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garyfair73 @LZZYHALE @SoFckUrRulesMan @genetics1999 Awww. I'm such a sucker for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stitcheddrummer That's amazing footage of yur show from Atlanta. Everyone looks to be having so much fun which is obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tamachick @TheDeadDeads  @MMTortuga @helladeadxx @tishimon @betty_dead That would be awesome. Covering some Slipknot is wat I want to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LZZYHALE @TheScaryDuck I know for a fact all of this warms that big heart of yurs. Must feel tremendous of how influential u are #TheRealMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miz is providing such an insight in this match between Styles and Ambrose concerning #EliminationChamber #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genetics1999 @LZZYHALE @Lndsz202 Gotten to know some great people in this community on here. You're all are awesome people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LZZYHALE @Uglybassmike I would never expect that. Was this when u were learning music before starting Halestorm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor @WWEDanielBryan lost his cool as now we have Nikki and Natalya at #EliminationChamber to settle their issues once and for all #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That escalated quickly with that Open Challenge by Alpha. All the #SDLive tag teams really want to establish as the premier team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmNotRhanda @Lndsz202 @LZZYHALE Mhmm. I've learned quite a bit about myself thanks to u guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlamoDeadXX @LZZYHALE Well definitely not with me. And I appreciate that you're straight up. I much prefer brutal honesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genetics1999 @buss02_megan @LZZYHALE Well all of us aren't fake. We all say wat u see is wat u get. We accept who we are &amp; are proud of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LZZYHALE @Lndsz202 And that's the truth. In the end love will conquer hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlamoDeadXX @LZZYHALE Well not people like us who are real. We are straight up with each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lndsz202 @LZZYHALE No problem. I'm here to bring positivity. I follow Lzzy's example with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlamoDeadXX @LZZYHALE I dislike people who are two-faced. They are toxic. Once u remove them u feel better off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That makes two straight victories over Alexa for Naomi. Future title shot I think is in order #SDLive]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>