<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E I already said the truth , darling 100% attested https://t.co/NcroOn9jg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xleeseungri the clouds, the birds, the sky? ok just joking, nothing much here. How's there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dxllicnce really? okay, yeah sure theres some cool place around, should we go now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANGELL1C no its not, i like your name instead. giggles. I havent mentioned it yet but nice to meet you, eiryls!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah I'm trying to be nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shesaphrodite of course. Anyway, whats up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk (she chuckles along with her) not bad, perhaps you've burned lots of calories too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANGELL1C haha. Okay, eirlys? I dont think I pronounce it right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daydrcm the same goes to you too, Yvette. Are you perhaps, french? Your name sounds like one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shesaphrodite is it? How is that? Hello lily!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU aw okay, land safe in the dream land!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey angel &lt;3 https://t.co/TZbvImjVTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dxllicnce yes, totally. your treat? (she chuckles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk oh it is better, at least you were being athletic. (she chuckles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dreamt my life was narrated by liam neeson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daydrcm thank you for the compliment! (A soft smile blooms on her face) hi, I'm aurora.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dxllicnce Pleasure is all mine. (She smiles slightly) hm.. caffeine i guess, why is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_DARTHV4DER but He is nowhere to be found : (]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk my day? Idk what to tell- i basically did  nothing the whole day... lets talk about yours insted?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E you mean 1000000000000% ??? Yes exactlyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dxllicnce Cool, hello Alex. I'm aurora. Does this mean we're friends now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_DARTHV4DER I'm awakened already, so he's not coming 😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@053KG amen to that. Not hating tho, but he pisses me off sometimes 😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@053KG no no, I wasn't intending to delete it lol ok lets skip on it. Great idea, burning him down would be wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@053KG gasps. Ok my previous tweet just poof missing- Oh you can call me Rory, for short. Aw me too, lets burn something 🔥🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E On a scale of Im Jinah to Megan Fox how pretty Aurora is? https://t.co/mQpZj2j5Ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_DARTHV4DER Hi megan there 💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my gawd thanks https://t.co/6D6t0lKRRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have two puppies already but if he wants to raise another one i'd be joyful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU boredom never stop to strikes. Well, i just finished all my work, i'm heading to rest now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll make it short, I need friends. Help me out? @freelancerpers @englishrpers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are in ghostbusters outfits-- https://t.co/g3WvLNUSHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a very bad "conversationator"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk just getting some rest here. what bout you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yup good morning pretty. what's up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearBelIe now befriend with meee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk then it is late. Well save your energy for today, okay~ likewise, dear alin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk but here you are still replying to my tweet! Or its not that late there now? Sure, thanks for reminding darling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MACARUIN yeaas accompany me bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E (she thinks hard). errr no idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a dead town everywhere I go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yup. you can take it with you if you want. chuckles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glittery face ✨✨ https://t.co/tBV3j7ZIpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU you're lucky, i got potato chips. Slides out a sack of potato chips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yeah sometimes. If you did, i'd share some of mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU do you eat late night snack?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU i feel you~ girl, maybe you should find something to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yes i have~ yeah? So You dont wanna sleep but got nothing to do either, like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll go and do rush hour marathon and prolly fall asleep, again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yeah, i went to look for my favorite chicken but its late already, they're closed. Instead i bought snacks- Good, I'm chilling here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arrowdownx same just like you or other people, i guess? I'm sorry i dont seem to get your question...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk ikr, i do that sometimes too- hahaha. Yeah, i became such a lazy bum today. Ah okay, dont be late to eat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yeah, sadly I didn't get my food. Lol. How's your evening so far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arrowdownx yeah? i'm pretty much the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU i'm just about to prepare myself now, i'm going out for dinner. how bout yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk such a long day, today? that's quite a long sleep. I just woke up too, getting ready for dinner now. have you eaten?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindcrcella and much more love from me 💕💕💕💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk yup. Aw, how's your rest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E you're taken???? By who???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindcrcella thank you 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindcrcella hello, do you followback?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to create another thread but again hey lazy : - )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arrowdownx hello there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm hungry too babe 

And you made me hungrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk my day's started off well, its hasn't ended yet but i'm already tired. Lol. How bout yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came in and saw so many foodporn flooding my TL, 

stepping outta twitter again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearBelIe you're the first ever who recognize it, i guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenteamiIk great to find another vanilla buddy! chuckles softly. Thanks dear, and likewise. smiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E y u no take him instead gavin, no thank you, im good being solo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pe2achy yes, I know that already~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you desperately want to read a book but you got no money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pe2achy dear , if you do that there will be no breakfast for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E JUST NO NO HES NOT HONEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E THIS IS NO HONEY NOOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New unni? Are you talking to me gavin? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU yeah, i'm the same here apparently. Physically mentally tired. Why dont you rest, love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veIvetvintage im sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veIvetvintage and lame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I'm over sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pe2achy child, find your mommy a daddy please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E wHATS WITH THE GIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fleursys is it? Somebody said it reminds her of Dory lol. Aw yes, i've never seen the aurora lights tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fleursys it stuck? All this long, since you were kid? Well i cant even remember what my teacher said yesterday in class haha. +]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G0NGZHU hi love, whats the news?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@polayrize I'm feeling awesome tho today was shitty,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E who? Me? No im not https://t.co/6wqGPrEU5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(throws herself onto the couch and groans) i'm done dealing with these people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my college has not even started yet I'm already tired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E i think you better mark a line between your eyebrows and the stray hair that you wanna pluck(?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E well... what else.. ehm do you trim, pluck, or shave your eyebrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pe2achy (emits another chuckle)   Okay, you're sweet. I like sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fleursys my name is aurora, but people often call me rory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fleursys I don't know much about flowers though i always want to learn about them, it's really glad to meet you kurai. As you already know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E it's uh a gel to keep your eyebrows in shape, i think it is applied after you groom your eyebrows(?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@101jpeg well, you're the first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTTOKH4E so... this is what i do: i dont use brow gel...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SADISTICSANA good for you bae, enjoy the rest of your day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pe2achy (she chuckles softly) you ask breakfast to your momma, honey boo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fleursys that is very sweet. I like the flower you just mentioned, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@101jpeg yeah, but that does not happen in my reality, Love's what we feel inside]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>