<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sjbrophy good one. might do the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like so little, but it is the very least thing I can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started with the Taoiseach. Will do more on my lunch break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm writing to my political representatives today. We need to stand up for human rights and our fellow human beings. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed this petition to @EndaKennyTD to take a stand  https://t.co/VEmctYn3Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neasaconneally the worst is people affirming it won't effect the illegal Irish. Phew tg it's a racist law!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BittrScrptReadr spent the days after the election result saying 'I know too much.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BittrScrptReadr all my expertise in the area tells me we could be even more epically fucked than those opinion pieces think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this morning I decided @mcgregor_ewan was cool enough for me to follow. I'm sure it's the crowning moment of his life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifecasey13 silly is usually a plus for me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifecasey13 it's very silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sorry for those of you who have to see this film without my witty commentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a lot of great, worthy films out this week, so I made sure I went to see xXx: the return of Xander Cage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its very hard to steal chocolate and run away without it melting in your hand.... I mean..... nothing...  😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm moving the same week as the Obamas. Coincidence?

Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neasaconneally the difference between protected and unprotected sex always cracks me up icon-wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last chance to clean the place I'm moving out of and there's a major power outage #cleaninginthedark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieloftus one time I got up when they called 'Marie', saying 'my name is actually Máire' ... nope they meant Marie. Morto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahthemoose I remember you seemed to have a constant grind and tough living situation. Glad you're doing ok now 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying down is great all the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@301N I'm sticking with Luke Cage for the moment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just bitter because I've been carrying heavy things instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not watching #Sherlock but I'm relieved to see you all have opinions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew sitting down was a mistake but when you move an armchair you are legally obliged to sit in it #Idontmaketherules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrokenBiros I know right??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Tabletop Gaming Taught Me About Feminist Fitness, Inclusiveness, and Body Image (Guest Post) https://t.co/4PqTWodMsT via @SamJaneB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am woman, see me hold my breath repeatedly to try and stop hiccuping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have consistent style envy of @octaviaspencer. One time I scrolled through her IMDb pics to just bask in her fabulousness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pulled a twisty muscle in my back that's hard to put a hot water bottle on without painful twisting #biology #movingproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nephew (explaining): and if the cow tries to get out, the metal detector will go off
Mam: what metal would a cow have?
N: a gun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyCClarke I'm watching and thinking 'well they wouldn't have danced like that' and then 🙄 at myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pride and Prejudice and Zombies is historically inaccurate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But dad prefers cards with terrible puns and fart jokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record I'm into the non gendering of things - always annoyed at the lack of Star Wars cards for mothers, daughters and aunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I've found the birthday card that would impress my dad the least ... I'm fighting the urge to buy it! https://t.co/3Me6wNYEqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm probably more likely to run an evil lab than do parkour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh because that's how boring it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have I fixated on how I'd run my evil lab?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not have an open menu in my canteen as I would be paralysed by indecision daily. Also I bet everything tastes of celery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had an evil lab I would Ikea the shit out of it. There'd be cushions and curtains. Who said being evil means you can't be homey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a pretty good ad for the game but a pretty boring film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have thoughts about Assassins Creed: The Movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@301N it allows two screens at a time. My parents hog the two screens... as they watch different things in different rooms!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The feckers keep locking me out of it. In retrospect I wish I'd tied up their phoneline more as a teenager as preemptive revenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have few regrets but one of them is definitely giving my parents access to my Netflix account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This getting up in the dark is for suckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, to close the winter festivities, the traditional night of lying in bed awake worrying about not getting enough sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scriblit "on a huge pile of money with many beautiful ladies"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scriblit all my Arnie impressions are  actually Rainier Wolfcastle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god it's the annual resetting of the alarm clock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have to put my bin out tonight, then you should all have to as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn penguin classic I think (I've just packed it in a box due to moving) it cost me £1 at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn I had it hidden in my work intray and I would sneak read it when the office was empty for 5 mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn I really love that book. Once I got into it, it was unputdownable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year. Here's hoping we don't look back on 2016 as a happier time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm currently halfway through the Princess Diarist. I suspect every time she makes me laugh I'll have a little cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was young I idolised Carrie Fisher. As we both got older my admiration only grew. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thunderstormbun the whole group laughed at your comment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power of lip balm in battle #DnD https://t.co/cws4d2wG5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas day pic story: Dog climbs to top of unstable cushion pile, pile collapses, dog falls, digs herself out. https://t.co/vqi1qEgjyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiller just don't try and move to dublin - there's no housing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAwkward my dad nearly opened up a decades old conflict by offering me sprouts today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas all. On the way to dinner at my brothers. He has threatened no turkey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took a large box and a pouch with about 6 to spare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was slightly worried I wouldn't have enough maltesers https://t.co/ujg1OCYyIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have packed one box  #yesitsanothermove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok this is my favourite Christmas tree of the year @TCD_Chemistry https://t.co/IVyu7oIBPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took both of these photos in my neighbourhood on different roads, but like what is happening?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eventually I'll have enough of these for my 'Teddy Bears Exposed' photo exhibition. https://t.co/KXYuvqxYgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got up early to collect an enormous roll of bubble wrap, so now I'm watching uncle buck as a reward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's #dnd Christmas party will be a hastily prepared homebrew with far to many Christmas puns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't decide what to drink but it turns out southern comfort and disaronno is a magical combination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have such a vivid recollection of that night. Also out at a work party and walked home in torrential rain  https://t.co/Cs635kZuRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to open a window #fiercemild]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a lot on my mind right now. Admittedly some of it is trying to breed a Christmas Monster in a game https://t.co/ih7WiVBKVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm only ever momentarily pretending to be an adult. But like that's everyone, right? Right? .... right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto no, "Last Holiday" with Queen Latifah, and lazy punctuation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_tayto confession: I just watched last holiday and enjoyed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ladies D&amp;D group is currently obsessed with @SingingMonsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifecasey13 too late!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like all of Twitter to believe that we did not eat the out of date biscuits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought these today! I expected better @marksandspencer #birthdayruined https://t.co/q9PomkaG8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode 41: NaNoWriMo past the half way point https://t.co/qpXyZwBAOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that my niece is 4 I think she might be a super villain. And that her interest in minions is really about their labour force potential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when my nephew was 4, I thought that his ideal job might be working in a food truck at a building site - cooking, diggers, things on wheels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intro to Wine, Women &amp; Westeros hurt my heart. I remember when we had hope! It's still great though! @JenniferCheek @thatbetsylady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mental state can probably be tracked by Netflix based on when I watch Arthur Christmas and the Curse of the Wererabbit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have an episode of @IrishWritersPod waiting to be edited on my laptop. I hope to get round to it soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Post: A post-election guide to changing hearts and minds https://t.co/mNAqFEWMo8 via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the actual fuck world? I'd like to say we had a good run but I feel we never really gave being cool to each other a proper try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So which sign of the apocalypse is freezing fog? I've been distracted this week and I've lost track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took the day off to make this. Worth it! https://t.co/VXKkzy1wdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just noticed the Winchester brothers wear a lot of lip gloss. I bet Dean's is cherry flavoured #supernatural]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jowrotethis the bugle made me laugh in my despair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatKateDoes kinda worried that that makes me vintage as well. And I am still young... or at least not grown up yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just realised that today I'm wearing a skirt I bought in the 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long overdue cinema day @cineworld: Dr Strange and Arrival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may look like I wasted today but I also built a car ... well most of it https://t.co/4MzdsG1vaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and to @FocusIreland because its cold outside and we have a homelessness crisis https://t.co/HXbiUzoxqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got some cash as a birthday present, I'm donating to the World Food Programme today https://t.co/qpGXby7jxK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>