<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WecopsCaroline @skicrampons sorry, was being (trying to be) ironic. Point being it may be a blind spot in inspections. No doubt it's real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_hamilton_ @narcomania pretty sure I've read evidence for demise of crack in 80s/90s US linked to younger gen seeing devastating impact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wiggett_ie @skicrampons but can count intel, inc quality (grading)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obbsie @skicrampons &gt; had earned. Trident raided his mothers house - cue angry calls to borough, who were unsighted #siloworking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obbsie @skicrampons eg borough not told abt firearm recoveries or Trident ops. One case of latter involved gang member whose trust borough&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obbsie @skicrampons experience of BIU I sat in 2011/12: Trident didn't proactively share their intel or tell borough what they were up to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; lots of outrage about the £50 fine, not much said about the 18 month community order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am curious: how does this compare to a typical sanction for criminal damage to a motor vehicle? https://t.co/ByVr9Sud2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know the #policeworkforce is ageing? Take 5 mins to read this look at data. What implications did I miss? https://t.co/8surkokXE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nca_lynneowens would be interested to know more abt reasons behind SE picture - exporting older officers? @the_police_fdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skicrampons don't remember reading that in any inspection reports (or did I miss it?) #efficiency #effectiveness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHesky might be of interest https://t.co/MtebrE5bfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which I join the dots in the #policeworkforce data I started looking at and was tweeting about the other day https://t.co/MtebrE5bfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizmead867 @ktbg1 @TrngDesign I'd imagine that requires leaders who are confident enough to admit their mistakes to set the tone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktbg1 @TrngDesign &gt; I can't see the police service being able to make the changes unilaterally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktbg1 @TrngDesign I'm not aware of any evidence that the IPCC and Home Office buy in to the 'learn not blame' agenda, and if they don't &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ktbg1 plus a duty of candour and much better #nearmiss reporting and analysis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ktbg1 including a commitment to robust process and outcome monitoring to identify harms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ktbg1 I'd suggest with the support of suitably qualified #ethical (and legal) support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sean__Butcher thanks Sean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkquinton @levinwheller in case of interest https://t.co/MtebrE5bfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJonnyBugg I've joined the dots and added some more detail #policeworkforce https://t.co/MtebrEmMEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Peter_Kirkham my blog (just published) has a lot more detail Peter https://t.co/MtebrEmMEk #policeworkforce @BluelightInfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iofiv blog up - chart I had in mind is this one https://t.co/MtebrEmMEk https://t.co/MmscX2RWAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_C_Holmes very best wishes for the new role Lucy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflects a conversation I had recently abt how there is now less proactivity, fewer CHIS sources, fewer analysts, l… https://t.co/tqjimmdhx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tompeck have you seen https://t.co/WSgrF2J80C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet below arrived in my timeline a few tweets above this one https://t.co/WSgrF2J80C https://t.co/vzxWHUm1Fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bodywornvideo - now in schools https://t.co/cHyaSj4dDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyhillunak really interesting - great stuff. Did you have a prior connection to Iceland? @efrogwraig @wiggett_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cate_a_moore Q is whether at an aggregate level it's a reasonable relative proxy measure for those other harms @gingefather @wiggett_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iofiv nice chart to follow tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iofiv pass go and collect £200.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; blog on all of this to follow, hopefully tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; more #policeworkforce - here the 2016 age profile of police officers in E&amp;W (43 + BTP), ranked by % over 40yrs, t… https://t.co/rzAPXMwTOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeDeeDubya Is it to prove credibility, establish hierarchy, more of a conversational ice breaker...? @AndreasThinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeDeeDubya As it would be in many professions. Not sure that addresses the Q why police officer so overt in discussing it @AndreasThinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SgtJDS in general a risk of "caught on camera or it didn't happen" @NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; youngest workforces seen almost exclusively in the SE, v loosely speaking hints age increases w distance from London. Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline &gt; may be what it does to trust when #bodywornvideo not present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline my take: #bodywornvideo a fix for fragile trust when it's your word against mine. In many ways key Q &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_criminologist @WecopsCaroline *showed*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_criminologist Alex, any thoughts on why the MPS RCT show so little impact? @WecopsCaroline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline someone put it well: we've got a better sense of the Qs to ask, not all the answers #bodywornvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline that's not a definitive summary BTW, and there are lots of issues still to be worked out &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline fewer complaints, signs of increased (recording of?) assaults on officers, reducns in some use of force]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanConstable @WecopsCaroline there are of course now an increasing number of studies that should be considered alongside the MPS one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@pwneyroud given the scale of the change you'd think so... @CollegeofPolice @pkquinton @levinwheller might know #prechargebail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GazTheJourno But you can't just go into a shop and buy a realistic imitation, which you could previously @CWexlerPERF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GazTheJourno you are of course correct, in limited circs - and I provided a link for the full detail @CWexlerPERF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WecopsCaroline &gt; namely cld the MPS afford not to implement #bodywornvideo - esp as everyone else does &amp; force can show transparency?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WecopsCaroline I heard rumours about trial implementation issues, which may have complicated things. There's a broader political point &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WecopsCaroline I would refer you to @_criminologist who knows more about #bodywornvideo than I do, but yes you are right to ask the Q &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctmccartney good question - I would imagine that is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigbyHowis same issues in South Australia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigbyHowis don't know the answer to that - though increasing number now graduates. Main point: rel few recruits, existing workforce ageing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelDawson3 Supt single authorisation up to 3 months, Magistrate thereafter. This quite helpful https://t.co/uFlsIrnqip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigbyHowis Main factors: austerity &amp; related recruitment freezes, plus changes to pension schemes mean many have to work longer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigbyHowis no redundancies of police officers, apart from small number with more than 30 yrs service. &gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peter_kirkham yes, I'm not complaining - just explaining my perspective, has never been abt pension @from_paddington @ianhesky @tiredsgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexJTRay implication seemed to be it was already evidenced - I imagine some actuaries out there have the data]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; Got me wondering abt legal liabilities for police employers if known to be so harmful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; due, frankly, to reduced life expectancy. That was under the 30yr scheme - implications of 40+yr career?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An aside: conversation few yrs ago w fomer snr police finance person. Said cops doing career shifts/response shld take pension commutation &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChristinaC_gl rather proves my point: everything through the pension lens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetPoliceSuper thanks Paul. (Hope the new-ish role going well BTW)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Kirkham I say that having several small pension pots fr different jobs and expect to work to 70 @TiredSgt @from_Paddington @IanHesky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Kirkham it's always seemed to me to go beyond that though @TiredSgt @from_Paddington @IanHesky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexJTRay so what's the explanation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHesky thanks Ian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreasThinks yes indeed - but why is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyhillunak I've done many jobs, have rel little pension accumulated and expect to work til I'm 70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiredsgt wld be interested to know to what extent you feel bound by pension to stay, in spite of personal toll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiredsgt in same way I've researched eg gun crime, drug mkts, even chief off misconduct - never done any of those either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiredsgt apologies, brevity of 140chars - didn't mean to sound flippant. I've not been there &amp; done it, but try to understand nevertheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roysmithpolice @trojandelta have seen the same thing w officers sharing office w pol staff who were being made redundant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiredsgt that's a fair challenge - &amp; I get the demands of response. But I've experienced it w all ranks/roles. @from_paddington @ianhesky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;&gt; 'A watched pot never boils' comes to mind. Relevance to the question of morale?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I've ever encountered a profession as preoccupied with retirement dates as policing https://t.co/bqQaZcueyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;&gt; this piece on educating youths about #sexting ethics raises some interesting points - a v different approach https://t.co/MHe4yinY4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuine Q: do they not already know this? https://t.co/glL57OihTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuxUnitME4 That wld imply its by design, rarther than forces not recruiting &amp; older officer not leaving due to pensions etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; perhaps the key point to take away is the ageing population of PCs #policeworkforce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; Same data but using actual totals rather than percentages #policeworkforce https://t.co/Na8IHHwhqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This chart tells such an interesting story - how the age profile of police officers has changed 2007-16, by rank… https://t.co/ZalVV3ICpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyHarle1968 @RoamingRoyston recruitment freezes. Data from the Home Office https://t.co/DInepRzRHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IanHesky don't recall the detail - but am I correct that the older officers locked in to staying by pension arrangements?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wiggett_IE @IanHesky for info https://t.co/B0RDnd5LUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;&gt; here's the underlying data #policeworkforce https://t.co/P626TvJ03X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, police officers don't get younger every year - quite the opposite in fact. #policeworkforce https://t.co/BEULRJo3TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHesky the definitions of #policeleavers https://t.co/O64avwMWmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; #policeleaver data definitions from the User Guide https://t.co/qQtvb8ur77 https://t.co/F28NgFhoHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IanHesky to add: striking that 'normal retirement' by some margin the main exit route for police officers #policeleavers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IanHesky Looking @ police staff my guess some counted under dismissed (see 2010-13). Maybe voluntary redundancy = resigned? #policeleavers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gingefather issue is whether those cases that are prosecuted and receive a sanction are representative @cate_a_moore @Wiggett_IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHesky worth saying that the transferees won't have left policing, but are part of the churn nonetheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gingefather why lop sided? @Wiggett_IE @cate_a_moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CCLeicsPolice @CmdrChrisGreany @cate_a_moore @Wiggett_IE to note the rationale https://t.co/CyJGXodexf https://t.co/JZWF5768Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; the source for that was a serving CC, expressing concern abt the implications for leadership of the service; seen as consequence of PCCs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With news of a cple of chief constable retirements am reminded of something I heard recently: avg CC tenure now only around 2 yrs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>