<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 ...no. I think if I dropped a deuce in the sensory deprivation tank I might not be invited back to the spa. Just a hunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a float session followed by a massage to make you just never want to do anything else ever again. #LazySunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eden_Eats This is true. Meanwhile, I have to answer a skill-testing question to win a free small fries in McDonald's Monopoly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what if Beyoncé's eating for three? I can do that without even getting knocked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's too short for [blank].

*nudges life* PSST. THAT'S YOUR CUE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW someone replies to my email and actually spells my name right. https://t.co/LfMldXfgzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrLXC And if they weren't scented, GTFO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrLXC Thank god for Super Smash Bros. for the WiiU - finally being allowed to beat the tar out of that little smirking bastard was bliss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office phone system still down. This may be the greatest start to a February of my entire life. #socialanxiety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I envy gaming consoles. I wish I could get away with just buggering off and updating for two hours any time someone asks me to do something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT guy broke all our phones.

As someone who hates talking on the phone with 10,000 nuances of fiery loathing, I say give the man a raise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sorry to keep bothering you!"

No you're not. If you were actually sorry, you'd STOP.
#ThingsICantReplyInBusinessEmails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a big fan of unsolicited dick pics so if you all could just stop posting photos of Trump to social media, that would be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadRealtyPhotos I'm not even going to swat that fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a word for the kind of laziness where you end up going to more trouble trying not to go to any trouble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My coworker just searched her entire desk for a single blank sheet of paper to print on rather than opening a ream to refill the copier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I realized people here would probably sooner just take the poster down and print over it than actually follow its instructions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've given serious thought to putting up a poster with instructions on how to reload the office printer with paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: *picking up greasy takeout in a hoodie and pajama pants*
Cashier: Any plans for the evening?
Me: https://t.co/9LeKDIJW28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pearls of wisdom are usually more like polished turds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just pretend the next four years are Opposite Day and we'll all get through this somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 They're just so soft and convenient and THERE, y'know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG OMG OMG

WORK DAY PLEASE GO FASTER I HAVE VIDEO GAMES TO PLAY https://t.co/GfRY55og1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 ...yeah this has been me more times than I ought to admit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RageMichelle I dunno, it would sure cut down on the amount of annoying neighbors I have to deal with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to Trump for figuring out how to travel back in time, but do you have to take the whole country with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OscarNoms are making me want to watch Arrival again while simultaneously seeking out vengeance for Amy Adams' lack of nomination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is depressing today so I think I'll go get myself the largest mug of hot chocolate locally available to help ease the heartache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RageMichelle Pictured at right: There's Something About Mary, The Early Years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it too late to take #InaugurationDay off work as bereavement leave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#InaugurationDay https://t.co/CruUJTeiDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DadandBuried That's way too long a trip. I'm headed for Venus, myself. I hear those poison clouds are a breath of fresh air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letters to my miscellaneous anatomy. https://t.co/ovss1FWa8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent all day yesterday avoiding my boss because she was sick.
Coworker kicked today off by having a coughing fit at my desk.

Pray for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client brought in giant tray of mochi as gift to the office.
Only one here who likes mochi = me.
Will power breaking down in 3...2...1...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Rose by any other name would still have let a Jack by any other name freeze in the water because she can't share a friggin' floating door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not secretly adopting a dog and sneaking it into my apartment building is the hardest part of my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*wants to like tweet but can't on principle because of typo*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrot_rewards Everything's looking good now, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've walked 10km today but @carrot_rewards is down so all you have to show for it is your own stupid sense o… https://t.co/clvYB3PyE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrot_rewards pretty please fix your app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My husband just said the seven sexiest words in the English language:

"Those pants make your ass look good."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who invents the technology to finally stop me from accidentally biting the inside of my mouth can have all my money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hey, Twitter.
Been a while.
So. Is the world still awful?

...silly question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: ...Sincerely, Jane Doe
Every email response ever: Hi Jaiyyne, I got your email and...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about changing my name to Adele Dazeem at work because apparently no one I correspond with is ever going to spell it right anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My New Year's resolution is to not accidentally write 2016 on anything, because apparently I believe in doing the impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And no one gave it an award, it just decided to walk up on stage and grab one anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 is like an actor who refuses to wrap up their goddamn Oscar speech, only instead of thanking people it's just killing them all off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2:30am Christmas morning. Eating boozy chocolates and watching Hogfather.

This beats being a kid waiting for Santa any day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized I wore a white shirt to work during holiday chocolate season. This will almost certainly prove to have been a mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateWhineHall I didn't know you worked at Starbucks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trek the Wars, or "When 2016 gives you lemons, make eggnog with Jean-Luc Picard and a Wookiee." https://t.co/YwNFcFmrym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you go to get a hot cocoa from the coffee machine but it's almost out of mix so what you actually get resembles… https://t.co/F4l4bCOEVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fond memories of Nintendo tits and the days before "unknown search terms". | You sick bastards. https://t.co/n8qiRhZjZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton Best of both worlds: https://t.co/SrjCRiMnUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dduane I can just hear Nita Callahan grumbling about people who insist on adding seeds to perfectly good cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the anagrams for "Christmas" is "Mr. Shit Sac" and long story short I now have a new favorite nickname for Santa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be a lot less eager to leave work every day if my cubicle had heated seats like my car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stranger things. https://t.co/Uf4tZIX0oU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sincere thanks to all the kind drivers who offered rides to those of us stranded at bus stations this morning thanks to #bcstorm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything I've consumed so far today has contained some form of chocolate.

Some dreams DO come true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A plague on the Nut house. https://t.co/BSj2ufk5KC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what evil looks like, kids. https://t.co/sAdDDI9KOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a Christmas card covered in black glitter from someone so now I have to write back and ask what I did to piss them off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*somebody sneezes in the general direction of my blog*

WordPress: Your stats are booming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just burnt my lip on my hot chocolate and also there's a tickle in my throat.
My first world problem game is strong today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step 1: Store thing in place where you "won't be able to miss it!"
Step 2: Smugness.
*later*
Step 3: Can't find thing. Panic.
- me, always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LolaDLaval @AlbertaAltruist Derrick beat me to the proper response, so here's this inferior offering: https://t.co/bevVzpfNtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't stepped on a scale in a while because I figure any more disappointment and 2016 is just going to spontaneously implode on itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ugh. Don't you find it too hot in here?" he asked, looking directly at me shivering in my three layers of sweaters without a hint of irony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May your Xmas be as merry and bright as the fire I started using your 5-page bragfest of a holiday letter as kindling. #BackHandedXmasWishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning the moon hit my eye like a big pizza pie, and now I'm hungry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt OOOOO-klahoma where the guilt comes tripping down the plain...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breliloquy That's the route I took. 5/5 would be doped up out of my skull again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breliloquy @YaAverageJoe Really not that awful. I lived in mortal fear of getting mine out but it's so much better with them gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, all these Star Wars re-release changes are getting ridiculous. @SmoshGames @TheJovenshire https://t.co/LAd8bbwMnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year was shit enough the first time around and now you're trying to make me relive it?

You sadistic fucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how Facebook doesn't give you the option to report their "Year in Review 2016" TL spamming as harassment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Year's not over yet. I've got time to kill off a few more notable people before the holidays." - 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOMGSpot 'scuse me while I just stalk your TL for the next few days and heart every goddamn tweet because KITTIES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me watching #YouTubeRewind. https://t.co/CtXO7sVB7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGFunkyKing I'm taking this as a sign that I need to go roundhouse kick all those goddamn defective snowflakes into confetti.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tis the season to bottle up my silent rage at all the store windows full of anatomically incorrect 8-sided snowflakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaraWilson Just start responding to everything they say with "It's a Festivus miracle!" and they'll leave you be soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 has been a crap sandwich and TIME making Trump their Person of the Year is just the soggy pickle on top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squaredbyrd @suzdal92 I came close. Spent a good minute just staring in disbelief at the carnage, wondering what I'd done to deserve this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 @squaredbyrd Thanks for the trip down memory lane to that time I tripped up the stairs holding a salted caramel mocha. RIP mocha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't put on and removed so many articles of clothing in so short a time span since my theatre days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to my coworker on somehow managing to program the office thermostat with the extreme temperature fluctuations of a menopausal woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breliloquy "Oh dear. I'm sorry, but we're going to have to go with someone with less experience."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first mistake was bringing an entire package of chocolate-covered gingerbread cookies to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGFunkyKing Send bourbon, then we'll talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing gets a lady's attention quite like having a clump of wet snow fall off a roof and directly into her cleavage. Ask me how I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I've done today:

-gone to work
-spent all morning looking out window at pretty snow and tweeting about dicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 The imperative one. Managing to hide a giant trouser snake in some of the stuff I wore in high school would have been impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 Little did my classmates know, when I wrote "HAGS" in their yearbooks it actually stood for "Have a giant stiffy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 At least, it will once I get home and write it in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 If you look at my high school yearbook, it says I was voted, "Most likely to inspire idle remarks about dicks."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzdal92 I have zero regrets about deleting my original reply because this is so much better out of context.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>