<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My aunt asked LePage if the ACA would be repealed. He predicted that the GOP won't have the "courage" to repeal.… https://t.co/j8FKiw1CyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HHS nominee Tom Price bought biomedical stock at a 12% discount after special invite https://t.co/8C6zQKrm6m via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ImWithHer https://t.co/aQ53u0fKgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 days in and we already have a Saturday Night Massacre https://t.co/VClxcPs7vP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reminder that Paul Ryan, Mitch McConnell &amp; their fellow Congressional Republicans suck too https://t.co/4MuLkwJyfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Dave Brat: 'The women are in my grill no matter where I go' https://t.co/BvCmPeokce via @richmonddotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bellatrix Lestrange of the Trump Administration https://t.co/JTfrVRDTgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump’s tax plan could save his family’s businesses millions of dollars.    https://t.co/ojbDRenqqd via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impact of taking it to the streets. https://t.co/mHJ4Jzttf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is her ninth full day as Counselor to the President.... https://t.co/8gJp8fMozq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: Senate Republicans are at a Koch retreat right now. https://t.co/kLTTBuplUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delete that app https://t.co/AnemtDUcgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats have the power to stop Trump. All they have to do is use it. https://t.co/hucJWyYzdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees Detained at U.S. Airports, Prompting Legal Challenges to Trump’s Immigration Order https://t.co/mqALN0ujy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lexington health care advocates call on Congress to keep Affordable Care Act https://t.co/m4zhe36brf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind closed doors, Republican lawmakers fret about how to repeal Obamacare https://t.co/IXyYzfQtWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Gore revives climate summit the CDC abruptly canceled https://t.co/OXyT5MvP4i via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus tour and 'blackout' rally for ACA ahead of Trump visit to Philly https://t.co/oQiCSOOwZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just asked a philly cop how many people they estimate are here. He had the perfect answer "a lot of people." https://t.co/M7ymFIS6j3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 7 of the trump administration #ResistanceInPhilly #savemycare https://t.co/WNb2l1nlju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald trumps first visit out of dc as president #ResistanceInPhilly #savemycare https://t.co/wkeAF1weyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drepurse @jrovner @RM_Patterson we're at Thomas pain plaza. Thousands here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philly resists! #savemycare #fightingforourlives https://t.co/SZdIQ6c8fX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the billionaire class hasn't learned anything https://t.co/yBfiOjcdtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just 15% of primary care doctors want ACA repealed, survey finds https://t.co/YQx1MljG4d via @phillyhealthsci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's golfer Euro friend illegally tried to vote in Florida and was barred. Trump: millions of illegals stole the popular vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are You Not Washing Your Hair Enough? https://t.co/OrLXrBJp6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tTe latest reminder that elections really do matter: Trump expected to sign executive actions to advance KXL, DAPL https://t.co/4A153MvHFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US investigating Flynn calls with Russian diplomat https://t.co/UbpJTja9ZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As GOP pushes repeal, Obamacare has never been more popular https://t.co/T2fIZm694X via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Trump labor pick Andrew Puzder has voiced second thoughts about nomination @CNNPolitics https://t.co/MVpTqdMcMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear Spurs Support for Health Law as Republicans Work to Repeal It https://t.co/Zpmw2qPPgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obamacare repeal would give 400 super-rich U.S. households a giant tax cut, new report says https://t.co/FIF8PtWSsm via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cross-country bus tour aims to help save the endangered Affordable Care Act https://t.co/yrPkSguYD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a mobile alert says it all https://t.co/8bA7hCGkiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Gov Baker warns GOP against a "cut and run" approach on health care https://t.co/7UaCn8HxlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of going after Trump's conflicts of interests, Chaffetz is going after... the federal ethics watchdog?? https://t.co/NdHwr3amsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hoping this is ~fake news~ https://t.co/7K6c6SvUUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obamacare repeal would give 400 super-rich U.S. households a giant tax cut, new report says https://t.co/FIF8PtWSsm via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super-PAC launches effort attacking Trump for potential conflicts of interest https://t.co/Ye7y5szWyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In State Department Visit, Clinton Invokes Berlin Wall to Warn of Threats to Democracy https://t.co/f4kt2hbmn2 via @WSJPolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reason #1000 to love the Obamas. https://t.co/txX1lJY92I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Day 1, Trump will  violate the Constitution's ban on profiting off foreign governments. Conflicts of interest co… https://t.co/TUKT3iPem7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; Sessions on Trump violating the Emoluments Clause... Haven't looked into it https://t.co/vFnCYNLqVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions on Russia.. Haven't researched it
Sessions on Trump conflicts of interest... Haven't researched it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next four years... https://t.co/paeMDN2vmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And she's about to be our Deputy National Security advisor --&gt; https://t.co/Xn7UKlphlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile on Earth 2, a very different AG hearing is happening: https://t.co/JXJhKqrLHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In our so-called post-truth times, @alfranken just showed the value of a simple fact check. The truth matters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@alfranken, one of only non-lawyers on Judiciary, right now doing amazing job of cutting through legalese &amp; exposing Sessions' false claims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not watching, tune in: .@alfranken is taking apart--piece by piece--Sessions' claims about his civil rights record as US Attorney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOSTILE ENVIRONMENT: Fox News Settled Sexual Harassment Allegations Against Bill O’Reilly, Documents Show https://t.co/69ig1Aq3sH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whitehouse: Did you ever chant "Lock Her Up"?
Sessions: "No I did not... I think"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Sessions had more to say about online gambling (Sheldon Adelson's pet issue) than Russia hacking an American election. Really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big win for American democracy! https://t.co/G5i4R99UiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ExxonMobil and Iran did business under Secretary of State nominee Tillerson https://t.co/25BxI545Ga via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In DNC race, Ellison opts for bridge building over bomb throwing https://t.co/EWQYTrMmw2 via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Russia with love https://t.co/ulHY9gCRMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 1,100 law school professors nationwide oppose Sessions’s nomination as attorney general https://t.co/I1keVvKOW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg she's running in 2020. https://t.co/SNjrAxdQP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth ---&gt; https://t.co/1OXf4DWrKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why subscribing to @newyorker is worth it: https://t.co/MZHbIvS3M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:( 2016 strikes again: 

'Star Wars' actress Carrie Fisher has died at 60 https://t.co/Jaq09CX6TY via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump protesters plan to open 'movement house' in Washington DC https://t.co/a4FT8i1iR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read: @lisamascaro's piece on Harry Reid &amp; Michael Heizer in a place they both love: the Nevada desert https://t.co/FXB9ZS80Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump donors already using the transition to help their companies. Only set to get worse after Jan 20. https://t.co/JQEt7DTloG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Sessions think the police should be able to legally rob you? https://t.co/kI50kiPB6F via @DCExaminer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: The Richest Administration In History Just Got Richer https://t.co/33AYCGP5Iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA Today Analysis: Some big donors win big Trump roles https://t.co/FzTYozHNff via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He still hasn't had a press conference since this summer.... https://t.co/MQVNOkzp0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gross! https://t.co/MQVNOkzp0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is too good. 

NYT: When Donald Trump Partied With Richard Nixon https://t.co/reoHHUU48T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rex Tillerson's ExxonMobil helped defeat Russia sanctions bill https://t.co/pgYndh6FNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GinaEPA:  Any attempt to scrap climate rules must be scientifically justified under Clean Air Act https://t.co/sIvqxNqbuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leak reveals Rex Tillerson is director of Bahamas-based US-Russian oil company https://t.co/Br2dRkIM3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the latest example of the GOP defying the will of the voters. https://t.co/FG399ohcaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to know I'm not the only one in DC who uses wicked https://t.co/JC0v06mvrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI backs CIA view that Russia intervened to help Trump win election https://t.co/miFJ2S84fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Trumps cash in at the White House? The answer is yes. https://t.co/4WnP86KqaN via @BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palantir CEO at Trump-tech summit raises red flags https://t.co/MRVPEvmHRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rex Tillerson shared stage at 2014 Russian conference with official under U.S. sanctions https://t.co/6Li9cNI2ZB via @CNNMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Podesta: Something is deeply broken at the FBI https://t.co/lkqFZ5Bd4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rex Tillerson’s potentially huge conflict of interest over Russia and oil, explained https://t.co/zFMFIwQTxj via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@llerer &amp; and @jpaceDC on Trump's cabinet: "wealthy, white, male-dominated and business-minded." https://t.co/NGXdKTqZvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait This too: https://t.co/Br8FXUjaFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘California will launch its own damn satellite' Gov. Moonbeam is back--and ready to fight:https://t.co/G3W0ii9jl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House suggests Putin was involved in US hacking   https://t.co/kOEUXMjg8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So basically the Kremlin + Fox are running foreign policy now 
Monica Crowley to Join Trump’s Nat'l Security Council https://t.co/kRvtj5yDFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson said "I have a very close relationship with Putin" and said he was not qualified to serve in government. https://t.co/6PSt1mR4oD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NH Union Leader: Shaheen questions whether Trump national security adviser pick should get secret clearance  https://t.co/zbOmQVjeYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twist on controversial 'Professor Watchlist’: Notre Dame academics want their names added https://t.co/mGOKFupe3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENDORSE: Gregory Downs, Eric Foner and Kate Masur on why we need a national monument to Reconstruction https://t.co/Lz7NUUT2bU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awesome:

How are millennials coping with a Trump presidency? They're running for public office. https://t.co/ljGAfUoilB via @Mic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm rooting for you girl! https://t.co/cfBl9GpS4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists are frantically copying U.S. climate data, fearing it might vanish under Trump https://t.co/FSW9QETkuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something we should all worry about: Don Jr.--who is supposedly running the Trump org--is intimately involved in ch… https://t.co/w8d8gxrJXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's fine https://t.co/PdgkViPfLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINGERS CROSSED https://t.co/ZTEedgeSLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this thread ---&gt; https://t.co/8VETl7iQVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[**Press conferences about his MANY conflicts of interest https://t.co/bSJlsZ6QyH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>