<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel We called it Butts Up in Alberta Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnionSportsGuy @joerogan @rickyred09 They're shooting near the tigers to scare them off. Almost looks like sandbags at one point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_McDaniel16 Best 4th Quarter Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxStrunk @EASPORTSFIFA I don't think it's just you. I can't connect to Battlefield on PS4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell Yeeeeesssss. Scrappy white receiver? Perfect for the Pats. But will Bill take a WR in the 1st?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMitchellPM You should throw your name into the hat. It can't get worse can it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomsegura On your tour dates you have Calgary spelt as 'Calgray'. Leads me to belive @ChristinaP is the personality champ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMitchellPM Jesus, this is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nottjmiller @cashinginwithtj @CashLevy Shepard's Pie. Delicious Englishman's dish? Or a delicious dish of Englishman? #maskers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nottjmiller @cashinginwithtj @CashLevy Shepard's Pie. Delicious Englishman's dish? Or a delicious dish of Englishman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dabnorfish @AesopRockWins That's like them blatantly trying to screw their customers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell How do you feel about another player named Mitchell wearing 19?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell Freelance photographer's are this generations actors. There's a dime a dozen because everyone thinks they can do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StampMachine You can google maps Area 51. https://t.co/Dn0v9EWUAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanLaralive Awesome show tonight. How long are you in town for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko Any plans for Planet of the Apes from the newer films? Gotta have Caesar and Maurice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjayoakerson Hearing you talk about anxiety on @joerogan has really made me feel better about my own and that I'm not alone. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko Any plans for Caesar and Maurice from the new Planet of the Apes franchise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeReiss How many post season yards did Wes have with the Pats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 You're a Calgarian now and that will not be tolerated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate my bloody car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 Your life sounds like an episode of a sitcom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanETID The Nice Guys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sent a package to New Zealand and it arrived 5 days later. Very impressed @canadapostcorp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AesopRockWins Do you know what time you fine lads will be hitting the stage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @TofinoBrewCo for bringing your lager back to the mainland. Best Christmas present I could've asked for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 @ScottFisherPM He's retiring? All the best Scott. Does that mean you're taking over the Stamps beat full time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lemarvelous23 This is actually pretty low considering I remember paying 1.40-1.50 a year ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AesopRockWins Wanna watch mine? It's only 5 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Goldbergs is a fun show with the worst theme song ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AesopRockWins @jennruhl My bad I got carried away. Apologies to you both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennruhl @AesopRockWins Why don't you chill the fuck out? It's not his fault, stop blaming him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 I've been at a Christmas party. In 140 letters or less why did it turn out so well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StampMachine The irony is thick especially with what he's wearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 Get a chance to watch it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 https://t.co/B7EJVV9iku Password is Victoria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 Hey Nik, would you be interested in watching a short film I made. Just trying to see what the public thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 @SheaSerrano But he went platinum without any singles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnePerfectShot Simply put, did you enjoy it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmaver6 When the depression from the loss ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6BONECRUSHER3 it's either an extension which makes my heart sing or you're going to the NFL which makes my heart break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_McDaniel16 are you saying you don't want to come back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 Not at all, you were awesome. I there's a way I can let the guys upstairs to keep you on this beat let me know. #Danny2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 It was a fun ride, albeit frustrating. You'll be with us next year I hope?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexsingleton43 Should've got Most Valuable Canadian regardless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_McDaniel16 Now we know how the Seahawks felt. Should've given it to Messam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 The Stamps have so much to be ashamed of. No excuses just results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should've given it to @JMessam this has been a travesty @calstampeders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricDionRogers Shoulder, but I didn't see what happened and no one is saying anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 No one can. This is heartbreaking. They said they weren't going to over confident but they don't look prepared at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 What even happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I predict that #TeamShaw #BoLeviMitchell will hoist the #GreyCup. What about you? https://t.co/gwJVIrMhXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell You said you were going to watch movies, could you check out my shot? Password: Victoria https://t.co/B7EJVV9iku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tfcnation07 @MinCanadaFA So you have something in common with him then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 I thought the Grey Cup was tomorrow? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel @kelsblackerby @VAMNit Surely you mean uncanine-y.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMitchellPM I almost stupidly asked who's rings those were. Now I'm just stupidly pointing it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMessam winning just crashed the @CFL Feed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONGRATS @6BONECRUSHER3!!! Absolutely deserved. And damn you clean up nicely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calstampeders @SincerelyToot Damn Toot that suit is lit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeDoctor I may or may not have used this shot as influence for one of my own. https://t.co/I2u2vfFHt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel What's your team Lin? I'm guessing Giants or Jets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel I'm surprised Canada's so late to the party https://t.co/1t0tmX5oYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@protodenNIS @6BONECRUSHER3 Juwan Simpson broke it when we won in 2014. It's not the most sturdy trophy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GoodLuckStamps Go be the Champions I know you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 It's only that big when they build the bleachers for the Grey Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Wall30 wearing 31 scores a pick six to bring the game to 31 points. #ThanksMylan @calstampeders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 News on Finch? I'm just wondering why Durant is returning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjayvegas @RealGDT @LACMA There's a del Toro doppleganger that was there as well it looks like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 of this whole empire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight, I wrote two pages of dialogue about whether or not a hot dog was a sandwich. This is art folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCLions I really want to go to the game tomorrow but can't afford a ticket. Help a @CFL fan out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 Were you one of these questions? https://t.co/yjkCv8iOsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFL @Shaw_CFL We got a lot of DDs on the team but that isn't one of them. I think you mean Derek Dennis @6BONECRUSHER3 Future MOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMorley62 Yet our dollar dropped a whole cent in 4 hours because of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing Trump did was tank the Canadian dollar a cent in 4 hours. Thanks a lot, the future's going to be swell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This season of South Park has gotten out of hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshdrozda The people chose those candidates unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 Calgary or Montreal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell How long till you can apply for dual citizenship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6BONECRUSHER3 How about a new ring?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randychevrier The only place in Canada that thinks our country is going in the wrong direction is the prairies. This doesn't compare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_McDaniel16 Wikipedia was sadly bare for such a great receiver so I updated it. But can someone with more knowledge upload a picture @CFL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @calstampeders Our leading receiver needs a picture for his wikipedia page. @_McDaniel16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell @Greg_Wilson15 You know it's the bye week when Bo starts trolling his receivers. #IsItNov20Yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 What they did with the original was combine it into 2 hour Documentary and included new footage. They may do it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 gets stripped by @Mr_Raymond25. Gotta love the two former @calstampeders ballin' hard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@df_sacks @calstampeders @packers @NHLFlames It's still a little jarring to see green in all that red ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricDionRogers @_McDaniel16 Just adding fuel to the fire that is your basketball rivalry. https://t.co/bZd7a4WqxQ Brutal airball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsOn770 @DebStrickland65 I agree with Jock. @humbled_roy has been incredible and given our ST unit a completely different look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 Still look good in red and white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greecebaII @ScottMitchellPM Jags would die in Calgary. The cold would destroy them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMitchellPM Not going to be anywhere near as historic as yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The older I get the more disgusting I think ketchup is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMitchellPM Please tweet more about the CFL going into the playoffs. We miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calstampeders @StampMachine @BoLeviMitchell @TD_Canada Where's Bo's beard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikel18 At least with Cardinals they had Wagner coming in hot, would've rattled the best guy. Seahawks? No excuse. Just incompetence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 If it still isn't working the stamps app is updating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 This is true. I won't be surprised if the oline gels better for the rest of the game with Lavertu out. Wilson seemed better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyAustin_9 he's only missed two passes. Granted those could've been caught.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>