<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya'll will hear someone say something negative about me and believe it like it came out my mouth ðŸ˜‚
I ain't know... https://t.co/7HH09SfjoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since y'all niggas know everything, which one of you my husband ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what else I'll have when I'm 35? My own businesses ðŸ˜´
I'm leveling up https://t.co/0fOHapv6lE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angelo Fisher ðŸ’• you so cute to me lol ðŸ˜­ 
I ain't have days off this week but I'm going to see you (.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put this if I was older everyone at work would of been all on but since they heard my age they just stare ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It breaks me down when we're not in good terms my love ðŸ˜”
I want this to work so bad that it hurts me...
Cause I know you don't deserve me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who got a rich old grandpa https://t.co/MHeHaqXkmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So which one? https://t.co/gmuCMGIcIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use to do this ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/1LsHlI6a7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This me af lmao https://t.co/IGB0wku5hV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ I mean he ight https://t.co/4dHQ4W7IMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda want to go to my coworkers party but then again no :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to do what to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm tryna Kim K this bitch, lights camera action" ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have a1 nudes but you single so you admire your naked body in private ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay this one funny https://t.co/suLoU1NtNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ain't having fun if you ain't having funds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimberly Rosales is my profile but only add me if I know your ugly ass I'm off this one too many lurking ass bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew that nigga liked me he always waved at my parents tryna be extra friendly uhhhh noooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why they asking my older brother if they can text me at work wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be too freaky for your taste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the new car you'd think I sold drugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need it way more than just one time. 
If the neighbors hate the noise they can call that one time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video call? Even if I sound gross :( lol I'm cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy at work says I'm cheating on him because I'm talking to someone else...
Hold up! Bitch when I say we was together???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone with a license need a job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My bitch ordered 100 wings man she lucky I love her or I would of declined lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im ordering my pizza online so when I get home this shit better be there and ready or imma kill someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give credit where credit is due &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They fine af https://t.co/HmfLyBD1Ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me ('x bitch pay me https://t.co/HMWQT4noF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most don't even last that long wtf https://t.co/pKqnv87src]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You all don't know nothing about this. https://t.co/49PiYRBcQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angelo Fisher https://t.co/xQD6UbTxFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you get rid of a cold?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son so cute &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate today -.-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im not feeling work I'm sick af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao okay I think it's time to sleep https://t.co/YezFygfhmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My throat hurts so bad :/ 
Being sick sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's up â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't trust these hoes, no ðŸ‘Ž
That's what my family told me
He gonna love me, he gon support me 
He gotta hand it over ðŸ’°ðŸ’°ðŸ’°ðŸ’°ðŸ’°ðŸ‘ŒðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JR PATTON " GOTTA BE MORE CAREFUL " Produced By O https://t.co/Mx0JSUrdqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm crying ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/PE7QDIkiDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've only been talking for three years.... get to know me first before we start dating dang ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jordan Alexander Rosales why you leave me with this weird ass cat LMAO 
PS I fed him Cheetos https://t.co/FPXzAFHtUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This photographer was tryna get me to take grimey ass pictures I was like bitch if you don't get it together and act professional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/2t2vbUG7qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tbh? 
I'm being blunt too so dont even like it if you not tryna fuck cause ima let you know... 
If you ugly ima let you know lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pass me
Bitch, you can't fucking have me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all hear him? &lt;3 this babe https://t.co/vA79Ihl3Ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ex he wants some closure 
But I just act like I don't know him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's yours it's all yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I'm feeling ... https://t.co/ZxMz60Pnud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was talking about this smh https://t.co/LJUKDHjCOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said "you the finest walking around and they still don't know how to treat you right... I hate that." Mannnnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets do something? &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.... See I don't break up
I break dishes 
And pictures 
And door off with hinges 
And necks off of bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmu I'm off at 6 :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to get it together I want to get it on my own and hope you match up or catch up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No days off :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm too goofy to be with someone who's serious all the time ðŸ‘Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before that I need some ðŸ”¥ðŸ˜‚ 
So I can pass out rq lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you really fw me add me ðŸ‘‰ Kimberly Rosales ðŸ‘ˆ 

This profile got to many people just watching my every move and some negative ass mf's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be just a pretty face I got much more than just that to offer the world. 
My brain functions quite well.... https://t.co/bLazO7gqjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my boss makes a quater mil ðŸ˜­ 
I sat and talked to him and I already got one person down to work with me and my... https://t.co/r0o8QuXc5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I got shooters but I don't even call them cause I'm a shooter"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm deactivating cause fuck this ðŸ‘Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ this dude walking on sticks https://t.co/qH45XuwTwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just been staying busy... 
But I guess I'll let the work speak for me 
I'll be sure to let ya'll see 
I got new things coming â¤ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You come over at 2 am issa sex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing is idc if you don't like me ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a blood orange ðŸ˜‚ ya tards https://t.co/oANiSWQ6wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angelo Fisher https://t.co/UiUKO2aD3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap chat @ CurrencyKim https://t.co/gXsCh0vPty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I wanted to use someone else's pictures I would of chose a prettier female wtf ðŸ˜‚
How am I gonna steal pics of my ugly ass ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be in the mix idk how ya'll do it ðŸ˜­ 
I hate people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finesse game strong so I flex that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be giving me advice when you been in the same spot for years... Get out my way p ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, I ain't with that friendly shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inbox? ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use you want you hella bad but I don't now ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fuck you so long that I'm fucking my bread up"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's my baby ðŸ˜­â¤â¤â¤ https://t.co/I70MtjhIiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess the neighbors think I'm selling dope...

Well mf I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can have the nigga I just want him for the presidents ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got off work and they want me to go to a dinner like I didn't just waste all my energy ðŸ˜‚
Fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ain't no police, I don't cuff shit...
Only time I fw him... when I'm fucking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom over here reminding me that I use to sing in front of cameras when I was little lmao hope they never show that to no one ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe Donald Trump can build your pussy walls, that shit knocked all the way off"
Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I told him I had to leave in a few I wasn't kidding lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ol' dude payed me 50 to talk for like 2 seconds lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tbh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sick to my stomach :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm already tired of work lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can have a hustle contest ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to get that "Swear2God" dick ðŸ†ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I make time for you I must really care. I started working two jobs and I have to make some time for rest and... https://t.co/2b7nA87mk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so fluffy! ðŸ˜­â¤ https://t.co/4veXXL0YVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was one in specific he  a cute ass brace face just know he already mine I'm taken  v.v]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>