<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The little-known bureaucrats who are cashing in multi-million-dollar pay cheques. Why? This is outrageous.  https://t.co/7bElQozibB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On refugees, Trump and Turnbull compete in a race to the bottom | Oliver Laughland | Opinion | The Guardian https://t.co/inH2M7QkDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Guardian view on Donald Trump’s anti-Muslim orders: not in our name | Editorial | Opinion | The Guardian.  https://t.co/EyjSUApEVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Although we are alive, we are dead inside': Refugees despair at on-off US resettlement deal. R u listening Malcolm? https://t.co/DBYM2Cg5Fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeting cancer drugs to reduce side effects https://t.co/xdBlv1ALv8 via @RadioNational. But Turnbull chooses to fund coal mines instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm climate change is real, if we must pay more 4 electricity to protect future generations, so be it. #grandchildren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Morrison blustering, swearing, rude - sounding more like Trump everyday. He must be desperate. @RNBreakfast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No @TurnbullMalcolm you're just beholden to big business, coal industry, IPA, Murdoch &amp; Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think @TurnbullMalcolm appreciates in depth questioning from Stan Grant. Compared with Leigh Sales who gives him an easy run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The women of NSW deserve better than a minister who is 'personally pro-life'.   https://t.co/j3E0n1JV8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our society is fraying. The problem starts with our political leaders. Well said Ross Gittens. https://t.co/9wbhngimF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can  @GChristensenMP tell me exactly when Australia was great? I'm female, almost 70, 5th generation, &amp; I can tell him it was never great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think so Malcolm. Israel's disgraceful treatment of Palestinians must not be rewarded. https://t.co/v0771Gcz2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Give me your tired, your poor / Your huddled masses yearning to breathe free." Has Trump read these Famous words from Statue of Liberty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/TU44837iqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacist threatened to shoot up Central Coast shopping centre  https://t.co/E3NCRJN2XC via @smh. Any comments @PaulineHansonOz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suggest all sportspeople, actors, singers, bands, in fact all celebrities boycott USA. #boycottUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Switzer is so inauthentic, sounds likes he's talking to bunch of kindergarten children. Big mistake Michelle Guthrie. Missing @GreenJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnewsAdelaide Did you know about Survival Day celebrations at Semaphore today? It should have been reported.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Jan seems the right date for Australia Day celebrations, includes all states then. 26 Jan only applies to NSW https://t.co/kFTvEdqAlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great turnout at Survival Day in Semaphore #changethedate https://t.co/xIbvf2gpXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshall_steven where are the women? https://t.co/JLwCQNJsfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To understand Trump, we should look to the tyrants of Ancient Rome.  https://t.co/LjN4SdoF9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the women? Australia Day honours list dominated by men (again). Who decides these awards?  https://t.co/vRIgvDYa2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survival Day 2017. Great alternative to Australia Day, I'll be going. https://t.co/gu1fswWCdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twiggy Forrest is a candidate for Australian of the Year! I'm shocked and appalled.I'd like to hear the opinion of indigenous people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busting Black Myths: The Truth About Our First Peoples - New Matilda. We need to rethink Australia Day. https://t.co/ajDqYmU4IF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone Is Photoshopping Trump’s Face On The Queen, The Results Are Scary | Bored Panda. Something to cheer us up. https://t.co/krw35VfzS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb @RadioNational we listen to RN &amp; local ABC everyday. But also FIP radio from Paris through the Sonos, its eclectic &amp; fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioNational When will new season start? I'm becoming tired &amp; bored with continual repeats. Often that afternoon or next day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actress Ashley Judd became the breakout star of the Women's March on Washington. Wow, look out Trump et al. https://t.co/49zoXKyOuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Donna Buang | Visit Melbourne's Yarra Valley - Official Site @ashleyfwalsh  https://t.co/O5MlOe7vkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QMS Media: Reinstate the Cranbourne billboard! https://t.co/rcFrm1ILaR via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you think things can't get any more bizarre, it does. Where &amp; when will it all end? https://t.co/MoqNukWVI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lWC14CT0zD | What I don't understand is how she becomes a millionaire using unemployed people!  https://t.co/qnJBUv9hWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Robeson also sang to a group of wharfies in Port Adelaide in 1960. It was to thank them for their support. An… https://t.co/LP56cUHkDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @sussanley becomes the sacrificial lamb for @JulieBishopMP @StevenCiobo @PeterDutton_MP et al.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN Thanks Noely, that's pretty clear. I don't think most pollies are actually stupid so they must be dishonest &amp; deceitful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickle_ems Hi Emma, glad you found us, we couldn't remember your Twitter tag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's scary, hope you get a positive result from @Cityof PAE https://t.co/ArieVBpGW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done ABC, got rid of QI and replaced with Antiques Roadshow. It can't get better than this. #sarcasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The case for despair is made. Now let’s start to get out of the mess we’re in | George Monbiot | Opinion https://t.co/60JdYewRko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hygge: A heart-warming lesson from Denmark - BBC News. A great idea in these trying times.  https://t.co/XwXUilZGJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s parting shot at Netanyahu is a futile gesture | Simon Tisdall | Opinion | The Guardian. Why didn't Obama act https://t.co/BtGUkZ38F8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No country with a McDonald’s can remain a democracy | George Monbiot | Opinion | The Guardian https://t.co/YKQwF8cimm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of attacking pensioners @cporter how about taxing the rich who pay little or no tax. https://t.co/N66JR1Guqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cporter has obviously never had to contact Centrelink online, by phone or in person. No sympathy for ppl who have… https://t.co/eofzL4aZpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know Gustav Weindorfer &amp; his wife Kate spent their honeymoon on Mt Roland in 1906? Collecting botanic speci… https://t.co/0jpryxG525]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deli-plomacy: New York's famous Katz's Deli bemoans loss of Carnegie rival. Best pastrami sandwich &amp; cheesecake. https://t.co/SbmvxV7Ufj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnewsAdelaide Why no report on car accident in Port Adelaide today? Not important enough?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why sacking Peter Dutton should be at the top of Australia's list of New Year's resolutions. #SackDutton  https://t.co/zntZlCXYzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Attenborough's Great Barrier Reef :World's largest living structure and we're destroying it @GregHuntMP  https://t.co/6cede2bKmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of trolls &amp; severely disturbed people out there Mariam. Ignore and shine on, you have lots of supporters. https://t.co/iK6jPLU27D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 20 years time when my grandchildren are suffering the effects of climate change, will @TurnbullMalcolm et al be held responsible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glen Murcutt not only designs beautiful houses, he is inspirational &amp; positive in giving his all to the Newport mosque. #spiritofplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NITV Motorkite Dreaming is great fun, meeting wonderful people with great stories. Well done all of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The victory at Standing Rock could mark a turning point. A victory for people power. https://t.co/k5cnjO48Ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$1b of taxpayers' money could be used to prop up the #Adani Reef-killing coal mine. Stop it now: https://t.co/jIb6Ij9wzg via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White, working class men have nothing to fear but other white men. Great article. https://t.co/oXqCLVmRjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointed in reaction of ALP to protestors today, surely in a democracy we have the right to protest @billshortenmp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As nationalism is weaponised, Australia desperately needs to embrace inclusive patriotism. Yes, Katherine Murphy. https://t.co/oYEiPINHtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dutton's remarks on Lebanese Muslims risk 'creating terrorists of future'. "Milk is spilt, the damage is done" https://t.co/oj64SmNY0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exodus: Our Journey to Europe review – all you want is for these people to survive. Series on SBS now. A must watch. https://t.co/pIBbl9yAfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people racist? | Racism. It Stops With Me. @PeterDutton_MP should read this. "Only connect" https://t.co/Vv8DdTYQHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stand by @sarahinthesen8, @PeterDutton_MP is a racist &amp; bigot. #sackdutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile another public school struggles to meet ends. https://t.co/jU27eFj4Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia cannot have a healthy Great Barrier Reef and an expanding coal industry. Join the campaign: https://t.co/dY3p7eBaQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Go Back – To The Left – Medium https://t.co/ZnYdaxVncc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn’t just a photo of Ivanka Trump. It’s a middle finger to democracy. https://t.co/70I98o1eQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stan Grant: 'Can an Aborigine be a Smiths fan? I can be whatever I damn like'. A thoughtful piece on identity.  https://t.co/027xn8WPv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And didn't he walk out on the apology to Aboriginal people by Rudd? He is a seriously troubled man. https://t.co/QuOKoKhTfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you John Menadue - "the person most responsible for any immigration problems is John Howard". @PeterDutton_MP take note, you are wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are people David Miles, some are good some aren't. How dare you focus on immigrants and malign them. #TheDrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Fight for The Bight https://t.co/hmxk8oaWzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA will continue to stuff up Middle East just as they have supported Israel against Palestinians, they are not int… https://t.co/9BqaTymBog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A win for Trump was a win for bigotry. Here’s how we resist him. Don't normalise Trump, resist. https://t.co/wY8qiloAHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality journalism project: Switzer the Spectator - Crikey. He's replacing Jonathan Green on Sunday Extra. FFS. https://t.co/lRJxNM1HTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanley Tang &amp; the Black-throated Finch https://t.co/2GXpfDfzxP via @AusConservation. Adani threatens their habitat and future survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Professor Fiona Wood on grasping the nettle and not letting go https://t.co/poYN2TiZF7 via @RadioNational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s hard for me to leave Manus Island without justice: Behrouz Boochani on the US refugee deal. https://t.co/X1XQDPjQzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister for Immigration and Border Control - Honorable Peter Dutton: Help Omotayo and his family ... https://t.co/QtuMa9w2DY via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save the Bight from oil drilling  https://t.co/XhJChxz5P2 via @AustMarConsSoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deng Thiak Adut: Australia was 'a place that was as strange to me as Neptune may be to you'.  https://t.co/JEL0OaDGWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not allowing asylum seekers into Australia is vindictive, small minded &amp; vengeful. @PeterDutton_MP @TurnbullMalcolm where is your heart?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is no time to be diplomatic – we should not wish Donald Trump well.  https://t.co/ATjTJFySmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Gustav Weindorfer this area was made a National Park. https://t.co/7iKsPaT6zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was the Democrats' embrace of neoliberalism that won it for Trump https://t.co/gddDeMB1G6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The perils of democracy - » The Australian Independent Media Network. https://t.co/wOq12WbaGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump prevailed despite the cloud of sexual assault accusations over him. https://t.co/jClwmFh79G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love @NaomiAKlein - new advisory body to Trump on climate change - equivalent of IPA. Beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he mean the Whitlam years? If only. https://t.co/xl1T3babcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a sight, Trump's parents looking down on him. And god too. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders in Australia voting day is always on a Saturday. Works well. Ppl set up a BBQ &amp; schools may have a stall to raise money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian politicians barracking for Donald Trump? That's disturbing. https://t.co/VE8CPgxzCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admire Gillian Triggs, her excellent leadership on HRC deserves congratulations not criticism @TurnbullMalcolm. Recognise her achievements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal MP Russell Broadbent calls out George Christensen for anti-Islam remarks. Well done Russell. https://t.co/4JS476GzzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamVeiszadeh @antigone944 Yes, they live in a privileged world. No understanding of, or desire to know otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#australianstory Like the locals in Mingoola I think majority of Australians are open hearted &amp; want to help. Take note @PeterDutton_MP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed. https://t.co/2T1jzsFgsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious. I'd laugh except it's too serious. Where do these ppl come from? https://t.co/P3WmPweYu4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>