<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Men: always remember to use scotch tape to keep your ties in order. https://t.co/7Hpz2XTPgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iD4RO the "ProudBoy Group"? Yeesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC when did I ever defend the "authoritarian left"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC but you're right: we don't know his political affiliations yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC careful. You'll blow Chris's mind if you say anything positive about the CBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC and I would caution you against making silly and unfounded assumptions and egregious misrepresentations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC here you go. https://t.co/jlhCcev8TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poploser character flaw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @anniegirl1138 you can only be a centrist if you've voted CPC, apparently...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akaRCN pretty sure it's the WRP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @anniegirl1138 come on, Chris. Now you're just playing dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danaT8N @ChrisFordYYC how is it "disingenuous" when it's based in fact?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare they report things! https://t.co/VfzWN6GRYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC remind me again when someone from the "authoritarian left" shot up a mosque?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boehmerB which "ideological experiments" might that be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am shocked -- shocked! -- that something like this would happen at Vice Canada. (great work, @sdbcraig) https://t.co/3WpejmdleY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC the world isn't about false binaries. It's about complexity and nuance. But carry on, Mr. Centrist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always with the anonymous/pseudonymous accounts, these ones. https://t.co/OzFQgX9cy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @nationalpost can they overstep? Sure -- and the BC one is notorious for that. But they have value, IMO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @nationalpost Odd that it's always white guys who get the most animated about HRTs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC again, that's not how they work. You should read about them from someone other than Ezra Levant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC Tribunals can't "arrest" anyone. Please learn more about how they actually work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC yes, how dare our laws make accommodations for minorities! We should be more like America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC I suspect your disdain for the Charter comes from the fact that it was created by a Liberal government. So it goes, I suppose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC Do I really have to explain the relationship between HRCs and the Charter? You're channelling Ezra here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC I'm sorry, but you really don't understand what you're talking about here. At all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC of course it does. It's also not the only thing that matters -- something our constitution speaks to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC way to zero in on the things that really matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 "Weak tea"? It's widely regarded as the best constitutional document in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 And our Charter is very clear: all rights have limitations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 Not at all. Freedom of speech means freedom to offend. But it's worth questioning the intent behind it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 Freedom of speech allows for criticism. But when criticism strays into efforts to malign an entire culture? Bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 meanwhile, I'd point out that plenty of people from Muslim countries are fleeing religious extremism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 but people are free to believe whatever they want, provided they don't inflict it on others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 I think religion is just organized (and politicized) superstition, frankly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 here's where I'm at: as a secularist and atheist, I believe religion has no place in the public square.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 but yeah, maybe the secular humanist who believes in facts and good data really is the extremist in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 That's not really how it works. And we've been over this already -- you're not a centrist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandemrbs apology, schmology. They should retract and explain the error to their viewers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 and? I never said immigration was a frictionless or easy process. But it's a necessary one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 again, straw man. You asked about my beliefs, not this mythical far left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 "drown the west". Charming language. Read the pieces, Chris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 https://t.co/WjTj1pjlLu That's enough for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 Seriously? You must be able to see the difference between Canada and the former Yugoslavia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 plenty. Do you want the economic ones or the social ones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 Occam's Razor applies here: the CBC promotes diversity because it genuinely believes in its virtues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 and I certainly don't think the CBC is dog whistling anything to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 But no, I don't think all but the most aggressively Leninist parts of the left want to destroy our culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC of course I mind, even though that's an obvious straw man. But you didn't actually answer my question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 how, in this apparent view of the anti-western left, would immigration "fix" our culture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC you believe this? That the government of Canada is dog-whistling to an "anti-western left" when it promotes diversity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 uh huh. I'd suggest that's easy for you to say, but that'll probably trigger you, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 if it's a dog whistle, what is the subgroup it's targeting and what does it mean to them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 That's not what a dog whistle is. At all. 

And why is it "vapid"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 hey, you were the one who doesn't like the CBC narrative and said it was about promoting multiculturalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @QuirkyGirl69 you object to the support of diversity? Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC So, you have alt-right jargon, but no actual examples. Got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is all kinds of insane. https://t.co/e5ZT2tu7TG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC you'll note that Jesse Brown has actually spoken up for Ezra on that show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC examples, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC "vileness"? Such as?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @CANADALAND Jesse Brown has taken plenty of shots at the CBC. Plenty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC you sound like you're making excuses for their behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mforsis @eastsidedads seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmfaris I wish I knew. Appeals to decency clearly don't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realmarkwells @markusoff @omar_aok It won't be around for much longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so incredibly greasy. https://t.co/n0TxFHhIG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC Oh, come now. Remember Ezra's screed against the Roma?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC funny how it almost sounds like the Rebel is the CBC's fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC I'd suggest it's because paranoia and race-based fear mongering sells. But YMMV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC in any event, one promotes diversity, and the other attacks it. You tell me which is worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC That's exceedingly generous. I'd suggest you include anti-feminism, anti-immigrant, and anti-decency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ppreville @stevemaich @RobSilver who gather and amplify each other's rage and bigotries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC And what, in your opinion, is the Rebel's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaniParadis Old stock Canadian wisdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the one Democrats MUST keep an eye on. Public education is the bedrock of a civilized and decent society. https://t.co/h6DIN8HNG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC And what do you believe that agenda is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ppreville @stevemaich @RobSilver Or the ethical responsibilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ppreville @stevemaich @RobSilver Me neither. It's a heck of a question, actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC @Forbes Fair -- find me a Canadian or someone at the CBC who's said that and you might have something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC you actually believe that the CBC is a mirror of the Rebel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ppreville @stevemaich @RobSilver Of course. But free speech *has* limitations under the Charter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billdinYEG Dip your toes into the comments section. Browse some FB threads. Search Twitter. It's everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC when has anyone ever blamed Islamic extremism/violence on climate change? This is absurd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC You can dare to say it, but it's actually not true when it comes to where we live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC I'm sorry that you find it so upsetting that the CBC won't trade in the kind of Islamophobic coverage that others do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ppreville @stevemaich @RobSilver I don't think it means defending someone's right to propagate hate against a particular group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billdinYEG Seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC you're conflating Muslims with the alt-right, which is....interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC Why on earth would it have to do that? It's never run pieces about how we need to have compassion for ISIS/Al Qaeda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billdinYEG Official Canada, yes -- and thank goodness for that. Anti-Muslim sentiment still runs high in segments of the population.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC If we didn't have news organizations and politicians talking about it constantly? Sure. The headline fits the situation here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billdinYEG Let's hope we never get one (although there are too many people who are secretly hoping for exactly that).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevemaich @RobSilver it's definitely fraught. It's still worth doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC but if a Muslim shooter openly admired, say, OBL and ISIS? I'm sure they'd put that in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC again, you're evading. What was the story on March 16, 2016 related to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billdinYEG I don't see a lot of social media profile pics being shadowed with a CDN flag. I suspect we would if the parties were reversed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFordYYC Of course there is, but one's about someone who murdered six people recently and you won't tell me what the other is about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevemaich @RobSilver I think "says things that are demonstrably untrue and with malicious intent" meets that standard.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>