<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaTrioli @springsteen @frontiertouring love your work! I'm here too!! Bit breezy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCthedrum couldn't be further from where we need to be it's not cheaper power its sustainable energy we need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaOpp @umairh exactly no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlin_roper @MelTankardReist @CarolineNorma76 Great book - thanks so much for sharing your story!! Very inspiring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A letter to America from Leslie Knope, regarding Donald Trump https://t.co/QdaiTooy9e via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dialmformovies .... it's what??? true... WTF!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dialmformovies The USA election - what a surprise ending!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Becoming Ugly https://t.co/lQkxiVI8U0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyCole68 @JB_AU come to Melbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterfra @FinancialReview Heads up....neither do the rest of us!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwyres gawd get a pedicure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyfindlay thanks Carly for the moment to think about Stella - she is very missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelLiszewski @WestfieldAU please tell me that image is displayed at a Westfield where I shop with my 8yo granddaughter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AASW_The Hon. Daniel Andrews MP Premier of Victoria  launching Ending Family Violence Victoria's Plan for Change https://t.co/TmACB2AbfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darcstei @BevJohnst count the women to men ratio of each response - no surprises!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count the women to men ratio on each response- no surprises https://t.co/sCbGM7T1Oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyfindlay thanks Carly actually I am my daughter is now 31 and amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyfindlay I was 17 when I had my daughter I was ridiculed because of my age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mon_marsh what state are u in?im in Melbourne no passionfruit flowers yet on my vines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alyankovic donate them to Project Respect they'll be much appreciated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEDTalks tell that to the people trying to cure the common cold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuentinDempster @MikeCarlton01 and other countries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pontifex umm prostitution is a lot of things but not new!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewGuyMP Libs the only one point scoring off this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenjduckett good morning - any update on release of Quality &amp; Safety Review? I've been in Vietnam so not sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greens4Animals just returned from Vietnam Hoi An shocked by the amount of plastic along the beach and in sea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonChapman6 is it also free?? 😖 I'm in Vietnam at mo and it's also fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennylmackinnon that used to happen to me when collecting my son from JBHIFI very annoying m!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Project Respect raise money Run Melbourne 2016 https://t.co/Uh0zzPEhKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[90% women get PMS, scientist have started work but say hard to get $$, it's not a priority! Erectile dysfunction funded?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham 2017? Or 2016?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenjduckett thanks I'm looking forward to reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenjduckett hi Stephen when is the quality and safety review being released?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyMikakos that's wonderful news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb Great article, Seriously, don't ever be afraid of using the F-word, Hooray Feminists!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardTuffin thank goodness for the Greens!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T @AvalonAirportAU frustrating but more important that you are safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrBastianSeidel really? What do you drive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMeaganTyler very much adds to the discourse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWBC_Museum I've got that at home in my garden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amcunningham but would you want to live longer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieCurtis @PorkysLondon not in the chip form! Tell me you didn't eat all that meat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieCurtis @PorkysLondon where are your vegetables?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeHockey you're bored in that role, aren't you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ama_media I want to believe the AMA is acting on behalf of patients but it's hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant I work for org who support women to leave "industry", doing work on physical injuries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant R there any known damage 2 women's mouths and surrounding skin due to their "work" in sex industry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant okay just read ur other texts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant that's great, my experience in past when packages announced new fees were set by dentists using $$  quickly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant Really?? You must know different dentists than I do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant dentist need to not put their fees up to meet the gov dental scheme benefits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education official mishandled more than $6 million: IBAC -  https://t.co/z4jExH9AdG via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielAndrewsMP please  fund widening High &amp; Plenty Rd northern suburbs- they are gridlocked daily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant yet the cost to public remains high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OurCommunityAU @NFPdirectors Inspirational speech by Paul Ronalds CEO Save The Children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driven out of Mernda by two-hour traffic jams -  https://t.co/RSRPlyHZUW via @theage@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driven out of Mernda by two-hour traffic jams -  https://t.co/RSRPlyHZUW via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick45516481 @deanhepburn @BBCWorld And?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant that actually is a good pic, helpful even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliamedew won't you have to leave your telecommunication devices outside?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw movie Rams- very good, can recommend it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielAndrewsMP That is very sad, condolences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommunityCare this is fantastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant does include unlicensed? -remember city of Hume last year had 3 unregistered dentist clinic operating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant how's city of Hume look?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hertz to refund hundreds of customers it falsely accused of damaging rental cars -  https://t.co/44NTCMg3mN via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesTheo gawd don't eat that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHOICE And The ACCC Are Gunning For Thermomix (via @LifehackerAU) https://t.co/zoxu5Je5SW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrTrevorDines @Love_plants hi Trevor do you have ideas about how to make passion fruit fruit! I've tried a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcTennant I'm afraid you're going to have to explain further]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyMikakos thanks Jenny for fwding tweet about Project Respect much appreciated Cindy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinFoleyMP Can I please meet with you to discuss Project Respect in serious difficulties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBandt hello Adam can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexbhathal hi Alex can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieOwensMP Hello Julie can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorSiewert Hello Senator can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColMorrisDavis hello Col please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvvic hello can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hannahgadsby hi Hannah can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyMikakos Hello Minister can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 we support women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sandra_Sully Sandra can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosieBatty1 hello Rosie can you please retweet   Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femfreq hello please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaValenti hello Jessica can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren Hi Senator Warren can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evacox hello Ms Cox can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiaFreedman Hi Mia can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfessorsBlogg Hi Professor Can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionalander Hi Fiona can you please Retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraEmilyG Cassandra can you please Retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellensandell hi Ellen can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillHennessyMP Jill can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyDAmbrosioMP Lily can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacintaAllanMP Jacinta can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaGillardGPE Julia can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamanthaDunnMP Samantha can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WIREwomensinfo please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvrcv please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitzroyLegal can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 Fitzroy service supporting women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FatherBob Father Bob can you please retweet Save Project Respect https://t.co/thc1ZbR2m3 supports women]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>