<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanStern happy birthday Clyde and Pluto is still a planet and not a dwarf planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan as a Utd fan I hope so,  so that Arsenal keep losing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 I must try this out with Winston and see how he responds lol. Different politics to u but liked your way handling it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 Did he need the stamp?  Thought it got to you whether it had a stamp on it or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 @nzlabour @AndrewLittleMP who's Andrew little? Never seen him before on TV or in newspapers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Primetv_NZ @bbcdoctorwho thanks for the advance notice guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aggerscricket @henrymoeranBBC @Independent seriously? How gross is that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint since Trump took over you have been hysterical @MMFlint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan reason Utd pulled out of FA cup years ago was FA wanted Utd  to take part FIFA world club championship instead. Don't blame Utd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcdoctorwho perfectly cast as the War Doctor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 @geonet it felt stronger than 4.0 and I got no rumble but a sudden jolt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese you are trying to take on media as well..... and losing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgregor_ewan @piersmorgan stop being a idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker bet you still get stressed out watching them in Champions League?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @GMB cry us a river Piers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn another reason to get rid the useless trolley buses and get proper buses that work in all weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donttrythis @MythBusters the most pounded button in television history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK about time he got popped off. He did the same to many others now it's his turn. Hope it's painful for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraDSN ok thanks for info on getting out to you guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ricsalizzo I tried to stuff a parking ticket down the mouth of parking warden who was being obnoxious. Gave me great pleasure at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraDSN hi guys thinking coming to u in March. Do I have get a hire car out to see the radio dishes or is there tour bus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC @geonet working in the Opera house today didn't feel a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nafis_shehryar @JeremyClarkson it's on Amazon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan won't occur
                               Never occur
                               Never occur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan oh what a lucky boy you are, I really wanted Arsenal to loose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan maybe you should support a different team in future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn the buses have battery's that allow them to run so why not run them like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP how can she an artist if she has to lip synch. What's wrong with actually singing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese A pity that the play Fawlty Towers not coming to New Zealand now, was looking forward to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariahCarey it sounds like someone cannot sing anymore if she has to lip synch her own songs #mariahmeltdown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese are you still a touch sensitive about Palmerton North]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC who? Oh someone wanted Wellington first cycle lane to very conveniently be on the route she traveled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No I didn't feel the 5.5 earthquake I was supermarket at time and felt nothing #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DevlinLive ummm what day is it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan sooner 2016 is over the better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolynporco come New Zealand it's better than Australia and doesn't have snakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyClarkson Your English has improved lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraDSN tell Santa keep behind the hills in future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astroengine is it really 20 years. I remember when he came out to New Zealand and getting my copy of Cosmos signed by him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bladerunner @donttrythis @RyanGosling wow can't wait for the new #BladeRunner looks fab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentSpiner would Data be on the side the Empire or rebellion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan what's soft centered and melts by Christmas........ answer the Arsenal football team lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan where's Pele]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBoyed who's Bunny Walter's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithQuinn88 don't argue with Keith Quinn the man who's anything sporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz John Glenn is a hero and a legend for anyone who follow the space program. He will be missed. No more original Seven astronauts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz it's well known that Morgan is a cat hating socialist who belongs extreme left of the labour party. More like the communist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJamesMay it needs shrinking even further or is that not possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NewsNZ is Little sure he's not talking about the labour party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker that man is a born liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astroengine @GeorgeTakei I remember as a very young kid in England sitting on the knee of a black Santa and never thought it was different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buzzs_xtina @TheRealBuzz please tell Buzz,  Welcome to New Zealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz hey Buzz not the way one intends to come here but can i say Welcome to New Zealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite a jolt the earthquake the 5.7 #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 for first time ever I have to agree with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese RIP Manuel you were absolutely brilliant in Fawlty Towers. Will be sadly missed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NewsNZ define tourist please? I travel on a UK passport as a permanent nz resident so do I get called a tourist not on a nz passport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasinReserve @WgtnCC @NZCricketMuseum @cricketwgtn most unfortunate to find out at 6am when I was on my way to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FIFAcom re the poppies,  FIFA GO AND FUCK YOURSELVES........ thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @BrianJe02171746 who the fuck cares as long as Arsenal loses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiar territory for @piersmorgan losing to Mancherster United. You must be use to that feeling by now Pierys old boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @ChelwestFT oh dear, how sad.............. Never mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Buckingham Palace owned by the nation. So if it need to be updated then you update or see it burn like Windsor Castle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan like the old Top Gear you will get into trouble saying that..... even though I agree with you lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyMail @piersmorgan got to agree with @piersmorgan on this. Every single celebratie   seem to parade on TV crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN people are stupid. That was a free Democrat vote by the US voters and now they people don't want to accept democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn better get bailing then with the bucket guys lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton not good enough to play was you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyMailUK and this considered newsworthy by the Daily Mail? What a wasted space and time reporting this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton what's it like being a out work, unwanted and an unfit footballer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@exploreplanets remember when he came to New Zealand in about 86 and getting Cosmos signed by him at Carter Observatory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz please please please come to New Zealand I'm begging you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100 bugger New Zealand not on the list lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport ignore fifa and just do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan what a choice for America this election,  a criminal, a allege rapiest and third party candidate who has no idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroTerry yet again New Zealand misses out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz why you not coming to New Zealand Buzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ONENewsNZ Where's the next Tintin movie and whats happened to the Dam Busters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker @dm_electrical91 well put Gary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanStern @exploreplanets Damn right Pluto is and always has been a planet to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bbcfootball United finally showing what they are really capable off and good to see Rooney back on form again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton looks like you not be playing Rangers again? How u feel about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan loved her as Auntie Wainwright in Last of the Summer Wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not much choice the Americans in the up coming presidential elections,  a complete idiot (Trump) or a crook (Clinton) #USElections2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaSharapova no matter what you say the truth us you still a drugs cheat and still banned from playing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelegraphNews when he said arrogant felt sure he was talking about Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @DavidPoppops @SkySports @ThierryHenry Cantona was a far better player than Henry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @jacomus69 No no no we don't want him as England manager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @mmurraypolitics says a lot about Americans of all political backgrounds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcdoctorwho @BriggsNicholas exterminate!!!! A happy Dalek birthday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan as a Englishman can I say we don't NOT want Wenger as manager you can keep him at Arsenal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton @jackkenmare_ if you spent more time concentrating on playing than writing you might still be a Rangers player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP sooner trust the Dutch than the Ruskies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuff who?????? Never heard of her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @DannyShawBBC for once got to agree with Piers, leave Cliff alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @_BBCTopGear face it guys without Clarkson, Hammond and May  Top is SHIT bring them back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndyUSA shouldn't that read His own life!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBuzz why you not coming to New Zealand as well Buzz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattyMcLean it's always to early to watch Xmas movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSA we have take shoes going through your security but why in many airports there are no provisions for seating to put our shoes back!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>