<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@msleedy Yep. You might be angry about those things, but putting your focus to best use on one. Toblerone, I hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMotown Please let us know if you come. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanyasweeney Lovely chatting to you. Thanks for writing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneClear It's so ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3: who made you the issue police?  #whatabouteryispointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2: Whatabout all the other issues YOU didn't mention, whatabouterer? Gluten. The HSE. Animal rights. Rain.  #whatabouteryispointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1: People are capable of caring (and doing things about) more than one thing, even if they're not talking about it. #whatabouteryispointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMotown We are great, thank you. You over here any time soon? A face to face is long overdue xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whataboutery. Is. Pointless. https://t.co/EE80OgCXwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_maguire Mine is Christmas Day. My half birthday always gets overlooked. I feel you, man. Happy Half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urchinette @tanyasweeney Thanks lovely. Couple of years old now, but we'll take it xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raycop Oh jeez, I've no idea where I'm going... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beannachtaí na Féile oraibh! We all know she's a goddess. My piece (in English) "Brigid (Not Jones's) Diary" is on… https://t.co/myrSgEgsjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HerstoryIreland @TG4TV @RoisinTG4 Yippee! Maith na mná xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Ray! Need it myself. https://t.co/89IQZOgBDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We chatted to @tanyasweeney at the Indo about racism and that. It's in today. https://t.co/DDostm2vEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Those people don't have the moral high ground, they just have their own. But still they attempt to shame. https://t.co/cKNty114uG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunionsandphey @BeeNiBee @Independent_ie Oh thank goodness. Thank you xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaraRose @irishtatler Gwan you! Thanks so much for chatting to me x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hon, Karl Geary. Hope the book flies off the shelves. https://t.co/WMnGqcY5wK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionaBooks @Hodges_Figgis @HarvillSecker @vintagebooks @PenguinRandomIE Thanks for having us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mate Karl done wrote a book. Launches tonight. Excitement. https://t.co/WMnGqcY5wK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daytime_reverie In the greater scheme of things, it's an annoying queue, but only an annoying queue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlynnUSVisaLaw Also, I think we'll be forced to be complicit. I don't think it will go anywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlynnUSVisaLaw It'd be great if we could keep the parts that help people. But already someone was turned back here yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlynnUSVisaLaw It has advantages. Doesn't change that it makes us complicit in human rights breaches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daytime_reverie Me too. Given the alternative, don't even have to think about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomClonan @DrUmarAlQadri If he's going to go, he should make a statement. I sadly doubt he will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NursepollyRgn @BeeNiBee I hope with all my heart she's ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, please share. https://t.co/xyhClRMM5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NursepollyRgn @BeeNiBee What? My god, I didn't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funnydub You will be. Brilliant. Have fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funnydub You're going to be brilliant.Have a great shoot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickoshea I take days away from it. It's a lot, but too important to ignore. Honestly fine if people want to unfollow/ unfriend, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oceanclub @TheKavOfficial @unakavanagh @Twitter A couple of lads dog-piling me got removed, but they need stronger policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oceanclub @TheKavOfficial @unakavanagh @Twitter It's hard not to draw that conclusion. Racism seems perfectly fine to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKavOfficial @unakavanagh She's a wonderful person. And @Twitter needs to take this seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjayawardene Feeling sick seeing politicians let pandering trump the lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unakavanagh Give me a shout if you like xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unakavanagh Here if you need anything. Let me know what I can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP. #annlovett #onthisday https://t.co/gQUMstAtnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US preclearance is handy. Married to a US citizen, it makes my life easier. I like it. But I like human rights more. https://t.co/EA91N7ynKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI ...you're the one who wins. The trolls will do what they do anyway. Day by day, do what you need. You ROCK xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI I think it's a bit of both. Going off for a few days, coming back when you're up for it. But, even if you went completely...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arshimbo I reckon he'd be pretty pissed off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undocumented Irish will be fine, by the way. So long as they're Christian and white. But you know that, @EndaKennyTD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedtheWarrior86 Only if we met that happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incogellen Hope you're alright. Fuck their whinybaby noise ❤️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unloveablesteve I can see why people get disheartened. Totally understandable. But something's better than nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda Gerard, that gave me the laugh I sorely needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaraRose @AnaCosgrave @YouTube @ava We need to meet. And plan. Love you guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my @irishtatler piece for the March issue, I reflect on what Irishness means. Much as I'm doing today… https://t.co/BH0dpd9SzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 There's a protest organised for Thursday, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrantiaroma Yep. "Let our white kids in, g'wan." It's a pretty serious statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIGN THE FECKING THINGS ANYWAY. Don't let "it won't work" put you off. Try something. Do something. https://t.co/sROGAjhFaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was kind of sick of reading milennial-bashing pieces. So I wrote this. https://t.co/Eb5J6ODqXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Jobs" "the economy" "tradition" "I'm not affected" "racist policies are fine" "Nazis are quite sharp dressers, whe… https://t.co/X3Pg23cXqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you know he won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @EndaKennyTD That was some spectacle. And history will remember.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @EndaKennyTD Sadly, it's looking that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Enda should go and let Trump know what we think of his policies." But he won't. He won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewRalph7 But he won't, so that's moot. And I completely disagree - but disagreement's good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyLeJeune @EndaKennyTD Yes, I don't think it can even be dressed up as a shrewd business move. On a humanitarian level? Disaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @EndaKennyTD He will not be representing many if he goes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we all want to shift Aran jumper units, but FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...or how history will view us. Or him. Please do not go to the White House on March 17 @EndaKennyTD. Make Ireland proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think @EndaKennyTD has considered what cosying up to a fascist will do for Ireland's international reputation...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much fun, I want to do it all again tomorrow. Thanks for having me, @24HourPlaysDub. Well done everyone. Happy b… https://t.co/QuNJDVzf87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI @unakavanagh She sure does. She's incredible xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey everyone, some racists have been at @unakavanagh but she's a QUEEN. https://t.co/QSMHWWsH3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actors? Awake? On a Sunday? And already at @AbbeyTheatre? Must be #24hrdub Aaaargh! https://t.co/0bFmHbdtuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon and his frog babies. https://t.co/2cp2nffrrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rehearsing  for #24hrdub in just over 7 hours. 'Night, all. Peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CillianDaly @faduda @DonaldClarke63 @roisiningle Shine on, diamonds. Night night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CillianDaly @DonaldClarke63 @roisiningle Even if it seems futile, or silly, every obstruction or refusal to normalise is vital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CillianDaly @DonaldClarke63 @roisiningle Yes! There is always hope. So try mad ideas. They're not half as mad as what's happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisIsGreels @TrishByrne Email, letters, the lot. Whatever we can think of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @CillianDaly @roisiningle Either way, it's a great idea. We might have to operate beyond hope for a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @andrewmanganVO @roisiningle US, UK, Vatican - not an arse from beyond these shores goes unlicked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmanganVO @DonaldClarke63 @roisiningle It would be honourable and gutsy if he refused. I think he'll go. Love him to prove us wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @roisiningle I don't think he'll refuse. Dinner long since gone 'round here in that regard. I'll still ask him not to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrishByrne I'd grab onto even that like a liferaft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixiesisi @YouTube I know... too apt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Maybe people are going to go "You know what? What do you even do?" They're sick of the disconnect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane It can't be tackled til it's acknowledged. Hopefully that's what's happening now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Seeing that here, too. HSH, etc. There's a lesson in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Because, as you know, I'm about on my last nerve with that bullshit. Glad you feel a little better, my friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Wherever this ends, people are seeing it now. Most care. Hopefully an end to entitled, ignorant "wait and see"ers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane I never want to underestimate those sickos. But people are great, they really are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obstruction and protest are love. Calling out racism is love. Taking turns to keep on keeping on is love. This is g… https://t.co/SPqzYv60ov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairemsb @colmtobin You care. That's a brilliant thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love will get us through. Eventually. Meanwhile, love doesn't mean pretending this isn't happening, or letting it happen to others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colmtobin Burst into tears when I read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closer to home too. Please don't stand by. Speak up. Stand up. In whatever way you feel you can. It all counts. https://t.co/88DM4iQ5wW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI That's it. But we can't. Love to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm getting off here for a bit. Wishing you good health, good craic, and whatever is helping you through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A favour: please dig deeper. See what these lads are really about. It's easy to find. Not spin, not acceptable gloss but what they intend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just sad, lads. That's the truth of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The apologism. It's really quite strange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey, wait and see!" "Hear them out!" No thanks.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>