<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Weary from the state of the world. An evening of Netflix and distraction is required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to be back #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Sinks?! AND a heated towel rail?! This isn't 2007 lads. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The house looks stunning. Bravo @DermotBannon #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So why make it look like a Military Base? #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Dermot gets some free car insurance for the distress that was caused. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Dermot is walking around that kitchen like a child who misplaced their favourite stuffed animal. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dermot - 'I wear the orange jacket so shut up and do as I say' #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one of the best creeping windows I've ever seen. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TBH I think she should just be satisfied she can see out of the window at this stage. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't use Munster Joinery?! Betrayal. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pfffft. Certification. Who needs that. Certs are for losers. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness those beams look like they wouldn't hold up Robbie's notions never mind his house. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We may be living with this kitchen forever but we will bow to the will of the almighty Dermot and choose the one we despise #RoomToImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robbie - 'If I was to buy a car' *turns to camera* 'Which I would insure with AIG insurance' #RoomToImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. You know the yellow bowl we all keep on the counter for absolutely no fucking reason. #RoomToImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dermot - 'We're all in a much worse position'
Translation - 'We're fucked'
#RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're taking inspiration from shower gel now are we? Jaysus, easily know they don't use a bar of Dettol Soap in that house. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm beginning to wonder in Mr. Builder facilitated Robbie's accident #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how in order to get the utmost sympathy from the country they needed to show Robbie's struggles with making tea. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear that Ex-Boyfriend?! You too could have spent almost half a million on an absolute dump. #TheOneThatGotAway #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Dermot Bannon and the Lost Sewerage Drain'
Wow these Harry Potter remakes are getting worse and worse. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You done messed up Robbie. You done messed up. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Patricia wouldn't have been able to sign off on this shit show. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT'S HIS SON?! Did he have him when he was 4 years old?! #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By smashing that window Robbie managed to unleash some of his daily window cleaning frustrations #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ. I need to get into window cleaning. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?! We require money in order to exchange it for goods and services?! #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oi buddy. You're the one with no money. Don't you dare take this out on our beloved Dermot. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe he could donate his beard in order to raise money? #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The back of the house will be rebuilt with cardboard held up with hope and sticky tape because that's all you can afford. #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa wearing a high-vis jacket in the middle of a well lit cafe. Hmmmm #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QS Patricia has fled with her remaining nerve in tact for a life of polished concrete related therapy #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They said â‚¬180k and Dermot heard â‚¬500k #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipster Beard is optimistic. Or at least that's what he tells himself as he cries himself to sleep.  #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending 400k without being inside the house?! Celtic tiger is alive and well. #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus fucking Christ. https://t.co/inyS4pOvAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the world is gone to shit can we all appreciate the ray of sunshine that is Dermot Bannon re-entering our lives later? #RoomtoImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OGrianain22 Very. You'd love him. #Puntastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noooooooo.  Poor Pun Guy. I'd have definitely shifted him for the flour joke alone. #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love migrane so bad you can't stop throwing up. It's awesome. #alternativefact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just about sums it up. #fuckingwall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump isn't  the President of America. If I chose to believe it it has to be true. Right @KellyannePolls? #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When they go low we go high. Just need to hang onto that. #TrumpInauguration #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait for this rich white man to decide what's best for the average person. #TrumpInauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching the western world crumble in front of my eyes, but I made a good cup of tea so it's not all bad. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kteluvsmusic You will never quash my love!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting on my results like: #accaresults https://t.co/mCoe9KjQ15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad I watched it with @niamhhew though. Having a Doctor on hand for the post credits cardiac arrest was handy. #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SON OF A MOTHERFUCKING FUCK. #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean at the start I was like 'what?'. Then there were feels. Then there was stunned silence. #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spabreaks Need a refund as I've been charged twice for a December stay. Noone seems to be answering the phone. Very frustrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't be worse #2017in3words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's play a game of let's figure out what the fuck is going on when being forced to watch Fair City.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After that B-Batteries joke @bdunkelman never needs to think she's not funny. The reason that was spat on my laptop can confirm. #RTPodcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's post watershed. We can say ass in front of children right? #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE PARADE. Let the chaos commence. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kid is me looking at pizza. #LateLateToyShow https://t.co/9UMC2d5ftu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VR on the Toyshow. We've come a long way from Uncle Gaybo in the 90s. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timmy doesn't speak peasant #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instant Cameras. Teach them your hipster ways from a young age. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulpmcg I speak with love. I'm one meself shur. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell the Culchies it's not the 8th of December yet. They've no reason to be in the Big Schmoke #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This child doesn't seem like he was overly attached to his sheep. Should have worked a bit harder on her keepy uppys. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Sheep can't play football' - Late Late Show 2016 #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bull McCabe has arrived. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hon youngfella' #SomePairOfLungs #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though Irish children today need to broaden their horizons and choose heros other than the contents of the RTE Canteen. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan and Dermot in the same place. Be still my beating heart. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DERMOT BANNON ON THE TOY SHOW. THIS IS NOT A DRILL. #ToyShow #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare Thanks so much for the great service. â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare Everytime the Internet stops working I restart and it works for maybe an hour. Sometimes can happen 6+ times per day. Working now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare Internet coverage had been appalling. Had issues everyday for the last week and a bit. Just me or general problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally. Thanks for the assistance twitter! #HiddenBooksGame https://t.co/cafvcr7lSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait.....this means @IAmLindsayJones and @AH_Michael had sex. Gross. #LiterallyForTheKid #RTExtraLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cried a little bit. #CongratulationsMichaelAndLindsay https://t.co/1RgK60WhLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tradition continues. #RTExtraLife posters purchased. Amazing work and amazing stream as always!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we need a change. This is what we need to prevent. #repealthe8th https://t.co/0HuTEjsJyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaroadwatch Bus broken down on Patrick's St in Cork. Causing some issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Masshalogear Thanks!! ðŸ’•ðŸ’• https://t.co/XKq9JYRFme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Masshalogear My Life. https://t.co/ClqxcHy3wQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tried to do a simple multiplication without my calculator. I learned 2 things. 1. 4x5 is not 35 and 2. Accountancy may not be for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldi_Ireland What's gone down in Bishopstown? #UnintentionalRhyming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as it galls me to say it that was an excellent penalty. #DUBvMAYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Nick Pisa discuss with glee the murder of Maradeth Kercher is a sobering reminder of how fucked society is. #AmandaKnox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southern_mayers 'Before a downfall the heart is haughty,
but humility comes before honor' -Proverbs 18:12
#WednesdayWisdom #God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm come to the realisation that adulthood is a continuous cycle of buying whatever shower gel is on offer until you reach death. #adulting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And just like that the Google searches for 'Dampfnudel' skyrocketed. #GBBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niamhhew How dare Austerity Spice laugh at Mary. &gt;:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barenakedladies Why you no play Ireland? #ShutUpAndTakeMyMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just turned off new Top Gear in order to watch the old Top Gear Bolivia special for the 10th time. #SaysItAll #TopGear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll settle for paying .005% in tax. I mean it's only fair. #AppleTax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooooo....do I get to buy a yacht or.......#AppleTax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREAT BRITISH BAKE OFF IS LESS THAN 24 HOURS AWAY. THIS IS NOT A DRILL. #GBBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose none of you have said anything bad. @slackalicebeer said something silly &amp; apologised. In the immortal words of Elsa, Let it go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Necromancer ... what I decide to do with my body I will end this conversation here. I sincerely hope you have a plesant evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Necromancer @TwoWomenTravel I agree, twitter is not the place for a debate, &amp; as I will never agree that you should have a say on ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Necromancer @TwoWomenTravel No. It's not. 140 characters isn't enough to diagnose a mental illness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Necromancer 1. Abortion affects women far more than men. 2. My issue was your labelling of these women having no idea of their story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Necromancer @TwoWomenTravel  Also wish to state, I respect your point of view. Labelling people you've never met sociopaths is my issue]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>