<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it normal for a cat to be able to meow "hello" or should I get it put down asap??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did ryan gosling and rachel mcadams not end up together?? Absolute tragedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can people actually afford to go to New York?!? Even if I could afford the flight, I'd need a few grand just for shopping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine thinking geordie shore was all real and this being a shock to you ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤” https://t.co/Q5Z33gRLEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The replacement bus I'm on from Clapham is literally the bus from Harry Potter. I'm not getting home alive https://t.co/2gCxdp8evv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixUK can u make Gilmore girls available to download please ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan gosling is ok though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenFrancis this is your warning Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't say thanks when I let you cross at a pedestrian crossing, you better run fast over it because I will run you over x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False alarm everyone! He's been found safe and well. Thanks for all the help and support https://t.co/m7F0tE4TrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns no no you're getting it confused with the hole punch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone seen my stapler?? It looks kinda like this one. I need it. Reward for safe return https://t.co/j5oMWgrleM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I ask for a sewing machine for Christmas??? Most complex thing ever. Should've asked for a bloody pandora ring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My main concern is how the guy from rizzle kicks managed to get a role in rogue one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accidentally bought electric blue car mats and couldn't be bothered to send them back so I just spent an hour colouring them in with sharpie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revenant was mad. Only time I've ever wanted tom hardy to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns you 2 will never be me xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSpencer97 please witness this picture of kris and get slug flashbacks https://t.co/sIfA4nQ6jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UGGHelp @Hayleigh_Kay tweet this account Hayleigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missguided_help can you please reply to my dm. It's urgent!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaraaaTaylor memories of being round yours as kids!! https://t.co/dW2Lk07hda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little boy sitting in front of me on the train has got an x-wing toy in one hand and a hot dog in the other #respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No fucking chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Christmas cookies at work today and I am 100% more excited than the kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a pretty strong chance that im a fucking moron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coopukinsurance oh no I haven't actually, would they be able to help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How have I ended up paying more for my car insurance in my second year than my first ðŸ˜’@coopukinsurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite heartbreaking that I'm getting off at the next stop.. won't see the finished product]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no wifi on this train so I've watched a lady knit for a solid hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gemma and Baptiste to everyone when they find out Alice is actually still alive #themissing https://t.co/aR2yEqlcxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mare of a day ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally have an essay deadline but clearly I've got my priorities right https://t.co/Dk0jmJIzf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has shaving your stray eyebrow hairs become a thing?? That shit will grow back in 0.02 seconds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if I'm too stupid to understand black mirror or what but I don't get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toffee nut latte's are definitely the best thing ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like reading 400 lines of the wrong poem ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns @DeanMcKinney3 @BBC yeah he's so cute bless him!! I've got a feeling they'll kill him off :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish the workers are Starbucks would take the hint that when I say I want 1 pump of sugar syrup, I actually want 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man opposite me on the train is eating sushi and then washing it down with a pint of milk. It's gonna be a long hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@osBORNE2begreat @urbaneat Whsmith sell food?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the FUCK isn't university challenge on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They discontinued the only foundation that I have ever liked ðŸ˜Š ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little mix's new song is a full copy of @grl ugly heart just sayin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I see another youtuber do an 'Instagram baddie make up tutorial' I will vom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The host for only connect actually makes me sick she's so annoying ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My car won't start and my trains delayed.... If those killer clowns come at me, I'm not gonna stop them x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BenFrancis it wasn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save your money and don't see the girl on the train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I'll throw all my clothes on the floor then cry because all my clothes are on the floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that pisses me off the most about myself is that I'm a messy person but I hate mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNiDAYS_Help says no boohoo codes left?? Help pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get how lecturers can set 300+ pages of reading like I am a human being I am not a kindle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That gbbo episode got me hungry as f for chocolate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must act cool so she doesn't detect my dog obsession and move seats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEST TRAIN JOURNEY EVER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady on the train with a Labrador just asked to sit next to me and if I'm okay with dogs.... GIRL IS THAT A JOKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg my year 8 self would be buzzing https://t.co/L8BgUKed2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Windows 10 update has broken my entire laptop. Crashes every 5 seconds. Someone pls help. Preferably @BillGates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pulp fiction is one film I can watch a million times and never get bored of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't they just play nintendogs in their room quietly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister and her friend just pretended they locked themselves out of the house just to make a funny musicly video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Val is such a sweetheart. Lovely lady â¤ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns I'm not!!! The one decent coat is yours. 1 nice coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zara's coat selection this year is disappointing as f ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not my week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fully having a mental breakdown I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never get over the fact that there are people in this world who think the way they are is because of their STAR SIGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remembered bake off's on tonight!!!! Now I'm happy ðŸ¤“ðŸ¤“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanna and caleb ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ https://t.co/RmAnN2eOBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie just said that mcfly's best song is 'year 2000']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially when the main love interest is Matthew from downton abbey ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jane Austen period dramas are my weakness in life â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THORPEPARK give her a phat raise and a year supply of hair bands my G x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THORPEPARK her name was Miomi I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THORPEPARK big shout out to the girl working on the supplies till in the saw queue for giving me her hairband because I didn't have one â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2014, more people called their kid Khaleesi than Nadine ðŸ¤”#funfact #endangeredspecies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh they're not even the words lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOAHHHH I NEVER MEANT TO BREAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught a pikachu and then it froze and now it's gone :) love life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenSpencer97 @Hayleigh_Kay @GEO7GE wtf she is so banging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear everytime I turn up to work with no make up on, everyone asks if I'm ill or haven't slept #thanku #feelingconfident #lovemyself x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tina is the only one talking sense, actually love her now #loveisland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY IS ALEX EATING COLD BEANS OUT OF THE TIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns @LaurenSpencer97 @Hayleigh_Kay @LoveIslandUK wow did you just outsmart me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns @LaurenSpencer97 @Hayleigh_Kay @LoveIslandUK swear it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giorgiajenns @LoveIslandReact oh boy she's gonna knock his teeth out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is every road in Walton being redone!!!! My tyres are full of stones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why does everyone think they're a politician now ðŸ˜‚" um no it's called educating yourself in politics u moron read a frikin book for once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO COMES UP WITH THESE SUPERDRUG ADVERTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad idea that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who even invented toe rings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kady and Scott are actually a married couple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't seen the bee movie yet, I highly recommend to all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually so upset about Christina grimmie being shot wtf is wrong with people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I buy a lot of clothes for someone who wears the same outfit everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming to the pub when the FA cup final is on probs wasn't the best idea #onlygirlshere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me why I'm watching a documentary about people dying of cancer when I'm this menstrual??? I'm literally drowning in tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only bad thing about sunny weather is when people blast out their shit music in their gardens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met an old man out dog walking and he told me all of his favourite Oscar Wilde quotes.. Think I've found a new bestie]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>