<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe they thought he was illegally importing Fjords not manufactured in the US? https://t.co/3rWGgyYXRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenmangan Clearly he’s Madras hell about something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of @DonnaOneWater working for a fantastic cause. #mygirl https://t.co/qYwWyYT383]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8/10 of the UKs top export targets (63% of total) in Europe. Approx 120Bn GBP v 60 (US &amp; China). Perfect sense to upset that apple cart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if HMG have shares in printer consumable companies, because whole pages of solid grey in https://t.co/E3vMwGht17 is gonna cost….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden getting quite a lot of desperate sounding queries for public sector roles.  Not sure I trust the IR35 position though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themurdochtimes Giving a  subliminal middle finger to whoever it is on the other end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’d be more surprising if he were telling the truth, to be fair. https://t.co/wleok8YbMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t help feeling it’d be fun if the Rogue POTUS Staff account got a blue tick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m always a little astonished when I unmute a computer how many browser tabs seem to have autoplayed some shouty video in the background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, I seem to magically look at a clock at 13:37.  It’s quite literally the best time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure it’s time to implement some sort of written test before people are allowed to breathe… https://t.co/YCEIXZbX9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellhoward Enjoyed your gig in Windsor, thank you - sadly we have to let people from Slough come south of the M4 on Sundays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themurdochtimes The @Telegraph terms it a ‘fear of slopes’, a sentiment I’m sure Jeremy Clarkson identifies with…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To hear that Trump has a fear of slopes isn’t as surprising as you might think.  Just ask Jeremy Clarkson about his… https://t.co/Zs7bQ2S86u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know - we've isolated ourselves from the civilised world, so let's sell weapons to human rights abusers and not condemn refugee policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This round was firmly Team Redwing, until a Blackbird aerial assault. Collateral feline damage incurred by standing… https://t.co/DuuXFnfkME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The battle for the pyracantha berries between the Blackbird Militia and the Redwing Army continues with frequent sk… https://t.co/cn0Dj4NbNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hitch undergoing waterboarding under controlled conditions.  Still looks terrifying, still torture https://t.co/EmV3cuDEYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthaig1 Mostly because Piers is the only person on the face of the planet that thinks there is a debate in this context….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countryside (n): Killing Piers Morgan.  HT @stephenfry https://t.co/tGMZdkECEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure they know. https://t.co/eyQuKp79Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat indoors tonight half expecting a tweet from the tangoshitgibbon thanking all the women for coming out to support him today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crayfishx Indeed - curtailment and denigration of such freedoms (speech, expression, marching etc) are symptomatic of rising fascism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure a march can just be anti-Trump, rather than it needing to be against democracy. https://t.co/kMpjjrlMjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pegobry I know lots of folks who get good mileage out of mailchimp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cstross Dunno about talking to a computer, but it’s pretty cathartic having a shout at it when it misbehaves….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, indeed.  What has the European Convention on human rights ever done for us, eh? https://t.co/UqVYW1rQk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah - so it’s illegal funnelling of information when it goes to a mainstream news outlet rather than WikiLeaks.  Got… https://t.co/xcpP7tTqPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just set my running goal for 2017, and right now another 977 miles in 359 days looks achievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as bad as the idiotic idea of selling the Land Registry - https://t.co/HQDt5xst5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrzarquon I think you have a rather more pressing date with the future than we do - YOU WIN! Er, lose?  Something anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK, it would seem, is currently hell bent on fucking itself https://t.co/xGR4fM9NqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your chocolate bar uses an outmoded hashing algorithm. Must get out more. https://t.co/WPukeOIZ0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m reminded that free access to online publishing tools usually serves only to demonstrate an overwhelming need for proof readers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ho Yourself! https://t.co/6CdfqoNugd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful hand sanitizer moment from Robbie Williams there. Happy germ free 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should add, that it’s not exactly lightning fast either - although 20 years ago on dial up I’d be ecstatic with the throughput I’m getting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really?  Trusted? https://t.co/qXkBhk9pKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#brighteyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thusly did the turkey go into the oven.  This is the one day of the year I wish a domestic appliance had an API.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The latest advice from the British Turkey Information Service…” Wait - there’s a British Turkey Information Service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @OpenRightsGroup has an overview of the judgment, and it’s fun reading https://t.co/TUlrWqUqDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not looking forward to the UK losing access to the ECJ when it does stuff like this https://t.co/FLgqaQZE5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know about you but I'm feeling pretty tired right now. https://t.co/ZIIyHkOc6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens in Vegas, gets plastered all over the walls of the Internet. https://t.co/0jENIxiEW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what one could do with a billion stolen user accounts on a service nobody sensible has used for 10 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I guess we all learned that money follows power and vice versa. I say learned. Had reconfirmed. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of the BA cabin crew I’ve met recently seem terribly impressed with BA in any respect, let alone pay. https://t.co/Zs3jK0YMRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I suppose he does have significant experience of the legal system in the U.K. https://t.co/fom33p6hu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ripienaar We saw folk swimming in lake Windermere today. No fewer than 3 ambulances in attendance just in case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Warranty support is no longer available for Pebble watches.” is why the Sale of Goods Act was invented….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Donald Trump on winning what we all expect to be the last ever @time Person of the Year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it me, or is there a fashion for websites to display light body text on a light background for increased eye strain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, whenever I shout at a computer it does as it's bloody well told, so why not a human controlled remotely… https://t.co/d4Zm5QevJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though I’m sure there are plenty of children who would benefit from being employed to shimmy up the chimney of his… https://t.co/6CZ2KcWd2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m fascinated by Brexit being the will of the people SO WE MUST DO THIS, but more spending on the NHS and education? Not so much it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three bluebird days on the trot in Espace Killy.  This is not the December skiing I was expecting. https://t.co/qXv42a88kV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My understanding is that Playboy uses Drupal for their German site. https://t.co/stjQbsikAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By “bit non-plussed” I read ‘gave no fucks at all’ https://t.co/9ja1KI1Ane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thinly veiled agenda of owning all the communications is wearing thin.  If governments wanted solutions, they’d invest in education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullying is not a technology problem, Jeremy - it’s a cultural one. https://t.co/4VMvklNnEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I for one do not wish to be subject to different rules from those that govern the rest of us https://t.co/xmX4w7gIn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put much more eloquently than simply blaming it on the boogie. https://t.co/GFPzLQnVVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes, someone should think about the children.  Their parents.  Who should also be responsible about and for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many freedoms are taken away in a Daily Mail like shriek of “Won’t someone think of the children”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we have some liberal politicians at some point please - this current crop of moral absolutists are quite tiring. https://t.co/ANIq7nj2yB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope - definitely can’t think of any other tools with a kitcheny feel called, er, Chef https://t.co/zAoU5cWEmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tw2_d09r Ah, my first proper senior moment of the year.  As you were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tw2_d09r @heathrownoise What do you mean exempt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to next weekend with the @snowheads in Tignes https://t.co/W9W3xPzFFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Brexit means Brexit, then I'm sure that remoaning means a commitment to fact based political and economic decision making]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobwierdsma I expect you’re thinking of carbon monoxide https://t.co/wqPT1ROjAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobwierdsma @vicgreenaway @e73rock @takethatdarwin Actually, it’s dihydrogen monoxide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think that word means quite what you think it does...... https://t.co/0Yn0SWLtBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The drive towards full LED lighting turns out to have needed entirely new dimmer drivers to stop the infernal buzz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmgmoylan Read what she said - I don't hear a decision in the lecture https://t.co/SbNFoe6Vge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmgmoylan Sigh. Read back. There's a clear implication you don't like what the lawyer said abroad. Try harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how in all of this the political establishment is now blaming the lawyers. Especially ironic given how many of them came from the law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmgmoylan In principle sure. In practice your reasons seem to be that our independent judiciary aren't giving you what you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overall it's probably best to promote the independence of your Judiciary. Just saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iinavpov @cstross Hilarious if Govt argue that though - they'd want to win bad enough to make a European court rule in their favour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmgmoylan Which is exactly what happens. They're already political. Unless you want them apolitical in which… https://t.co/fOD1V2plp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cstross Only if they argue an Article 50 notification is revocable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullshit.  Would you stop politicians taking about politics?  Economists?  What other subject matter experts should… https://t.co/q9wEbM4nPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to a thing at the frontline club about Brexit. As expected. Nobody actually knows anything. Shrug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminhaines Thanks man - although I’ve not been at TR since April ;)  Still - now I’m out of contract again…..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck the Daily Mail https://t.co/jqfCeaVNDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try as I might, I cannot comprehend the palatial magnificence that 800M GBP of car park might deliver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite end of contract activity is completely resetting my Mac to factory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richburroughs I saw that and noted to myself what spectacular bullshit it is. What an utter fucktard Assange is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS THE YEAR OF LINUX ON THE DESKTOP!!!11!!!1 https://t.co/zOIJgklQ25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face like a beautiful yet aggressive angel that would kill you if she thought she’d still get fed. Stench like the… https://t.co/shgx8rwGVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syonist Yup - A weighted dB - the flight info comes straight from a USB ADS-B receiver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ripienaar Although seriously, that’s the reason to collect the data, because who believes gov’ts or airports about this shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ripienaar Not sure my cloud, er, loft based datacentre would be able to handle the load of the metrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enriching graphs in grafana with events and concomitant data from InfluxDB is pretty sweet https://t.co/j4hj7fz2dD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite things is being expected to know critical information without ever actually being told it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL JVM DNS caching behaviour is….. dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a messed up world, it’s a good thing the UK is part of a European political and trading un…  what’s that Dave?  Brexwhat?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>