<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The WH defends handcuffing a FIVE YEAR OLD BOY and seeks to justify it. #muslimban  https://t.co/wit6dtgzDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardHogen1 @RealChrisWick @Ziplok_ @BretBaier @realDonaldTrump It's a lie, spread via confirmation bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelton59P I meant a church in North America. We both know the west only cares about the west.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelton59P ISIS kill ten times as many Mulims as they do Christians. They are everyone's enemy; made by American foreign policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a government stops adhering to the law, something is very, very wrong. https://t.co/iYa6WO8r0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine the meltdown if someone had just shot dead six people in a Christian Church? Do Muslim deaths still mean anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation bias is one of Trump's biggest weapons. Challenge ignorance. It's time to stand up and be counted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just looked at who #DonaldTrump follows. Out of 41, all were his businesses, colleagues and family. And Piers Morgan. Donny needs a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireHammond He's great. Wouldn't change him for literally anyone. I find the key to all this is to have constantly low expectations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadhim Zawahi has to book a flight to America immediately and force this issue. It's time to stop tweeting and step up for what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadhimzahawi In solidarity for your fellow Muslims and for humanity, travel to the USA immediately and deal with what happens with dignity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireHammond I feel your pain.I am a Liverpool fan.Thank god for alternative facts because they say we're awesome with plenty to play for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireHammond I thought you were saying you were sad, but actually you mean a football team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenKing America is certainly expensive, but the maintenance ain't what it used to be...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, why bother with logic and reason when you can call someone a snowflake or an SJW instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hrtbps Well, with initials like NF, what would you expect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDMumford @Glinner Well, his initials are NF, after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blu_Collar_Man So incest and rape are fine then? Thanks for the clarity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blu_Collar_Man It's so easy to call them liberals. It stops you having to think about what is happening. This is wrong, wrong, wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The double-fault in our stars #FilmsForTennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft I said that the comparison is not factual. It compare apples with elephants and is evidence of nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Ah, I see. You are a paranoid xenophobe and stifled by extremist dogma. You are as bad as your boogey man and don't realise it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Straw man bullshit. Deranged laughing. You're terrible at this grown up discussion stuff. #impotent #brainless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft There is a gaoing chasm between accepting immigration and wanting the west to turn into, sigh, "a(sic) islamic ghetto".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Ha. SJW. When will you drop snowflake in? I know and love many muslim immigrants. They are gently and lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft It's not really factual, it is just playing with language to manipulate the easily manipulated. People like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft No, I don't know. What do you mean by it? I don't have that desire. That's mindless straw manning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft But I am demonstrably not that, or I would have proclaimed it. You have real understanding and processing issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Memes are the tactic of those who can't think for themselves. #impotent #brainless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hanahx36 Perhaps. Nevertheless, we still have an active role to play in using our resources responsibly. We must be responsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft I am actually a gamma male. My user name refers to something else. And as for cuckold? What does it even mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft I don't think I have, but even so, you admit you are guilty of what you accuse me of. You're not very bright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Attack the person instead of their views is what it means. And it is all you have ever done to me. I attack your views.#impotent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hanahx36 I am not about to dispute your beliefs, but it is up to us to sustain our resources. This is our responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft No, but just an opinion. Not the "truth". I don't worship any given demographic group. I just don't hate them either. #impotent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft You don't even know what ad hominen means. I believe you can indeed spew insults all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Intellectuals don't spread lies and spew meaningless personal insults. A lack of self-awreness fits you very well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft It's just childish white noise. Sub-playground taunting. You're completely impotent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibertarianBot Ha. It has to do this because the truth doesn't do it any favours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hanahx36 Are you saying that we are not the sustainers of our own resources?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Embarrassing, childlike nonsense. You are an intellectual and political no mark. You are irrelevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft British culture has not been torn apart by radical Muslims. That is indisputable. You are a purveyor of lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Name calling and lies. You spread lies in the hope of confirmation bias from simple-minded followers. You're disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReformLeft Well, that hasn't happened. If you are right, why do you tell lies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SupportDonald It's a global village, and your dickhead President is fucking it up for everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SupportDonald I'm sure there is a lot you don't understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #muslimban is the equivalent of Trump having a "kick me" sign on his back. The US are now the biggest target for ISIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seymourgomez @peddoc63 You know. As a Christian. WWJD? Would he fuck people's lives up for no good reason because he could?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seymourgomez @peddoc63 You're desperately reaching to avoid the topic. What do you make of this ban?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seymourgomez @peddoc63 More ad hominen rubbish. An arbitrary ban on a demographic group has nothing to do with the topic of abortions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandonrgates @BradReason I tend to agree. Progess and growth can be made here. You have to look hard though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seymourgomez @peddoc63 Brainless bs is just my preferred term for brainless bs. One can find association in any two disparate topics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandonrgates @BradReason I agree with that, but it seems unachievable to me. Would be interesting to see it happen, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandonrgates @realDonaldTrump @BradReason I can't see him being in the WH for long. Too many skeletons in the closet. And too petulant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandonrgates @BradReason Your energy might be better employed elsewhere is all I am saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seymourgomez @peddoc63 There is no logical association. They are two separate issues. You cite ad hominen, then insult me? Wow. #brainless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teresa May has basically said any country can fuck with basic human rights and she has no problem with it. #muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miguelcarvalhu Most of the agents of ISIS are citizens. Refugees are an easy target for bigoted idiots who hate what they don't understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miguelcarvalhu Never. You said it. How can you have less than never? European countries do that already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miguelcarvalhu Nah.It's an empty, racist, bigoted gesture to appeal to the populist idiot masses.When was the last time ISIS bombed the US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miguelcarvalhu How is this giving ISIS a harder time? This is exactly what they want. They thrive on division.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All decent people need to boycott everything to do with America. If Trumps wants isolation, let's give it to him. #muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miguelcarvalhu How on earth with it solve the issue? It will just increase tension and divide us more. It plays into the hands of ISIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peddoc63 What's more stupid? Comparing completely incomparable things or avoiding the issue with brainless bullshit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mascara of Zorro #cosmeticsamovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradReason @brandonrgates It seems unlikely to say the least. And is a waste of a lot of anti-Trump campaigners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandonrgates @BradReason That's not particularly constructive Brad, and hardly likely to lead to a fruitful debate, is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradReason I have no strong feelings about it,but I do wonder whether the states breaking up might benefit everyone. Or most of us, anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradReason Is that a joke or are you genuinely pissed at this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Udder Guys #MilkyMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The men who sterilise goats #MilkyMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt, that's a big loss. He'll be greatly missed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are extremist feminists doing Trump's work for him?

https://t.co/MS39KdrKzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote this writing. Not sure if that means I am a writer:

https://t.co/MS39KdrKzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald the idiot became the pres, and turned it into a circus.
Off we went with a trumpety trump, trump trump trump.

Needs some work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to get conversations going about, you know, stuff:

https://t.co/313zh3a0h9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has feminism lost its way? Please join in:

https://t.co/313zh3a0h9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to make sense of the World, a bit at a time. Help me!

https://t.co/313zh3a0h9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Feminism eat itself? @niume_official https://t.co/MS39KdrKzD #Niume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eminema Watson #RapACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Agreed. I despair, It isn't about what is right and what is wrong. People are entrenched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Accepted. The history of MRAs is very different. Has it ever been about equality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Of course. But it seems to be where social media is at. Name calling never leads to understanding or progression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin I will return with more tangible examples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin You are demonstrating that I need to do more reading. I very much appreciate the opportunity to expand my horizons. TY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin If feminism ceases to be about equality, then it has been perverted to become something else. And is utterly counter productive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin I would say, thanks for not calling me names and repeating SJW bullshit. Is hard to actually talk to someone here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Yes, but they are exceptional intellectuals. Most are far from that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Fair point. I believe it still remains the case. But that does suit my agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Sorry to be vague, but anything that is ultimately female supremacy nonsense and misandry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Thanks, I'll have a read!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Yes, I understand that, but we don't have to let them take over. Intellectuals are often out of touch and detached from reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Feminism is ostensibly a pursuit of equality. All those that lose sight of this do so because they have their own agendas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Yes, I get that, but I would argue that movements are defined by those with agendas, on all sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin Why do academics define the ideas of any given movement? Am interested to see examples though, Do you have links?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arovmorin @TylerPreston20 I can't. I can't sit here and defend every example of people who pervert the ideology. They're wrong, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoicAdvantage @Pesimist_Sense @SaltyLiberal @YouTube Yeah, that's onviously ridiculous. And means absolutely fuck all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook removed a video from my feed about Trump saying he would show his tax returns. Seems a bit Orwellian, wouldn't you say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dolphin_Radio_ You can't admit you and are wrong and you are projecting. You lack any vestige of self awareness to the point of parody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dolphin_Radio_ Ah fuck you, you argumentative prick. You had the chance to qualify your accusation or withdraw it. You did neither.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>