<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The burrito. https://t.co/SLZNLhJyZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steele131 Fuckin hell. Overachiever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't know #johnwick2 decided to go that route. I'm game though. https://t.co/BFDRPBLZ9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff Any idea where he left for? News said it's "off the books."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMikeSnyder My total came to $216]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving day for me. Never had movers before. I will have movers henceforth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most laughable name I keep seeing by fans for director of The Batman?

Tim Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmmireles93 I agree with the list and its order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm genuinely surprised. https://t.co/owlweHErzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more and more bad shit happening in my county, the less I'm caring about cape shit. And I'm fine with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never compromise. Not even in the face of Armageddon. https://t.co/8SMvfkNIiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I believe he's better at directing, this doesn't surprise me. The fan community is way too harsh. https://t.co/snk0soRyRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so fucking wrong. https://t.co/xRH6x8ELaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope all journalists sink their teeth into this. https://t.co/STN5XzK3a8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are some people constantly asking Snyder and Clay Enos when the JL trailer will drop? 

Stop being pathetic. Try patience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMikeSnyder Person was turning down our alley and they hit the gas instead of the brake apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMikeSnyder I know right? Lol. Luckily, we move out in two days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yuey_J4 Thanks man. Appreciate it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelTweaton Thanks brother. Luckily we move out in two days! Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunflowerJD A car hit our house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this just happened. Yeah that's my dads bed, the end he puts his head. Everyone's okay. https://t.co/OzRTyFuh9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TronVin_ Savitar I'm guessing? Well, it's the first speedster villain costume that isn't a leather copy of The Flash's costume.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TronVin_ Wtf is that shit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must say, @jaketapper is becoming a personal hero of mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish we could ban you from the country. https://t.co/uCAY6tki44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The governors who disagree with the #MuslimBan should mobilize the national guard and physically free the detainees at the airports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something something something...women can't lead movies...something something https://t.co/gar49Ggvp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ. Trump needs to be in jail. https://t.co/fJ3E0PtP67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope every country in the world bans US citizens from entering. That's the only way this will backfire enough to change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internment camps come next, folks. It's time to wake up.

#MuslimBan #donaldtrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've elected a moron. Among his other accurate titles. 

https://t.co/6WTmUjl1J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait. 

https://t.co/0DsIy6wtzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved John Hurt in Contact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sassafrantz Happy to see you back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmmireles93 I've never had a problem with people calling me cracker. I am one. I'd prefer saltine though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of stuff isn't art/cinema to me. But all art is subjective so...https://t.co/qDobgOabJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmnerdjamie I love it. The YouTube geek culture and culture in general has gotten out of hand. It needs to be ragged on a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmmireles93 How dare you care about things that are real life and actually matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to North Korea. https://t.co/jBGBQhWadh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS POSTER https://t.co/yThYvyq7E5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He absolutely should cancel and publicly tell Trump to go fuck himself. https://t.co/KCSpIdxF0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamDavis83 I haven't done it either. I'm a failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamDavis83 should be a national fucking holiday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM I can hear the message boards and fanboy blogs firing up "exclusive" posts about the Doom Patrol movie. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meaning, it's not ahead of it's time anymore. We've caught up. https://t.co/LgXApR6vm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if this is a conflict for you @BrianBooch but you should be making tv shows as well. https://t.co/GsD3dEuREs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when people were like: #Watchmen ... the book and movie were ahead of their times?

Well, not anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny story, you can't stop him. https://t.co/kRaNzqk17E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess they should have thought about that... https://t.co/5gdd91tMju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ticket already purchased. https://t.co/Nvqy8KSFiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelTweaton RIGHT?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is our society. Become a meme, achieve success. https://t.co/Qy99nDX5OD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah...I finally got tickets to see @billburr in AZ on March 8th. 

Dream come true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have a moment to speak about the gospel of Yanet Garcia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember when everyone said I sucked?"

-2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieDipiazza That sounds fucking amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no point in "killing" characters in CBMs and CB shows. 

I wish they'd all just stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't have a near meltdown. He stood is ground. Grow the fuck up. https://t.co/Z76xQZnu3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is forever, kids. https://t.co/qbqgsOzp74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a lot like Trump. Your own country hates your guts. https://t.co/2nvnEPmgRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way it should be. https://t.co/pUcgROJxSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say 27 definitely should have won oscars. 30 should have at least been nominated. https://t.co/0w7LZ1airj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markgatiss is hilariously brilliant in #Taboo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have any more intelligence officers to betray and disrespect? You're really good at it. https://t.co/IN4zJKl6W8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO YOUR FUCKING JOB YOU ASSHOLE. GET THE FUCK OFF TWITTER AND FIX OUR COUNTRY LIKE YOU PROMISED. OH WAIT...YOU CAN'… https://t.co/44V1rl14oO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why this isn't obvious to some people yet but Luke is not the last Jedi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump bans Pizza Rolls, I will join a militia to overthrow the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDMiller14 This show is begging me to stop watching it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember: Only assholes drink Mr. Pibb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Legion somehow already looks like it's gonna be the best comic book show of all-time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol oh Texas, you're cute. https://t.co/H96ttFXdbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 best things about the MCU. 

Cap
Guardians
Black Panther]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's on pace to blow the record for executive orders out of the water. https://t.co/FsLkpCMLLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@koenig_man @hkharpster Rey (or Finn) weren't alive when Yoda told him that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gorgeous. #HarleyQuinn https://t.co/o7QXOn0vi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ministry of information. https://t.co/huKb2FKT34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who voted Deadpool should delete their account. https://t.co/UiC7W6yA7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep has been nominated enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*a thousand year Reich https://t.co/xjBBsPGqQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelTweaton He was also in Bad Boys 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carter2480 Has there been any proof either way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hermann22 It nearly explains all of it. And that hug Leia gave her wasn't a normal hug. That was a mom hug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My official thoughts. #StarWarsTheLastJedi https://t.co/a8DGVW7S5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentBigfoot Maybe Han giving the Falcon to Unkar Plutt was payment for having him take care of Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentBigfoot There's a look of sadness/regret that Han gives Rey when she talks about "not knowing there was this much green in the galaxy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentBigfoot But is she Luke's? I still think she could be Han and Leia's. They moved her to keep her safe from Kylo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antovolk With a fuckin pencil...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheLastJedi is the most uninspiring film title in cinematic history. https://t.co/BEPyr5wPYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Atlanta for work. Never been. Should be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trailertrack @starwars I think the teaser will be before then. The first full trailer will be April.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/71lKCD0JiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw someone that said a movie title wasn't "inspiring." https://t.co/Phus9jiFph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd. Why would he get angry if he had the largest attendance for an inauguration in the history of the universe? https://t.co/Vzz3RYAXW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelTweaton Kelly and Mattis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why did you vote to confirm? https://t.co/ZAHXq7AX3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunflowerJD Love that movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gronk is in a luxury box instead of on the sidelines with his team. 

I HATE the Patriots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not "field gold"

It's "field goal"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the Secret Service for protecting that piece of human garbage and his family. He doesn't deserve you. https://t.co/QIdqhHU0in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't you ask your boy Putin? https://t.co/hp0kheUIBW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>