<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Maryam Mirzakhani, an Iranian mathematician, is the 1st woman ever to win the prestigious Fields Medal https://t.co/nhrgeYuLIg #womeninstem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MQPhysAstro @DavaSobel great! any link to that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm half way nice @DavaSobel book "The Glass Universe" that describes work by women at Harvard Obs in late 19th-early 20th C. #womeninstem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never said here that these 2 books were my gifts from The 3 Wise Kings: a textbook for lecturing at @MQPhysAstro… https://t.co/WzH2szOSNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so cool! Well done, colleagues at @Macquarie_Uni ! https://t.co/aeSXp8E9XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ey, look @pcoffeebreak, it's our friend Tabby in @TEDTalks !!! https://t.co/UOauXoL6IO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erfmufn Not a problem! I'm actually a bit jealous, I have always wanted to take deep, wide images of the sky showing faint nebulae!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another wonderful deep space image obtained by astrophotographer @erfmufn. Excellent work, Dylan! https://t.co/pgESDIasmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @JossBlandHawtho. I agree, since I saw photo by @DeepSkyColors, @apod 4 Jan https://t.co/f8PsrVAAyH, I thoug… https://t.co/yrtOoBeikP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please read this. Job insecurity is a problem for everyone, men &amp; women researchers, but I agree it can be particul… https://t.co/WeS6yq6XT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! A great deep shot of M 31 from @IAC_Astrofisica showing the clouds seen in recent image by @DeepSkyColors! Ima… https://t.co/sLNgOWYKkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few years ago I prepared this nice multiwavelength image of spiral galaxy M 101 https://t.co/GEt4n6qxZ0 En español https://t.co/g2rTYn28YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends in Brisbane, you're in luck! @astroduff will be in a free Stargazing event next 25 March for @WorldSciFest… https://t.co/CAfGg19jEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just spent ~4 hours carefully reading &amp; commenting a new paper draft for @CALIFAsurvey. Great piece of research quoting the Occam’s razor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just think about this... https://t.co/TbF4rsyqDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must read book by great #CarlSagan everybody need to read. I'm astonished how he predicted some of the important… https://t.co/yBem2qpuQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids are the future. They carry our hopes &amp; fears, with time, knowledge. They are little scientists by Nature, nurs… https://t.co/ApOoTaRHHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroHyde @AstroSocAus @vacant3rdman I was actually thinking on sending an email tomorrow proposing that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card game with science women &amp; their fields ready to print. Link in Spanish, Cards also available in English!… https://t.co/bgOgKMa5qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I couldn't help myself, here it goes my multiwavelength image of spiral galaxy M 101 https://t.co/GEt4n6qxZ0 #Astronomy #scicomm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope he can manage to travel to the US to enjoy the Space Camp cc @AstroKatie https://t.co/5JrxDn869X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! These are excellent news! Congrats @Cosmic_Horizons, very much deserved ! https://t.co/1xzeCXA6DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please support @sydneyobs to get the restoration of famous (&amp; almost unique) time ball https://t.co/cxk5hcQa24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearby spiral galaxies are soooo cool! Have you seen my multi wavelength image of this galaxy? https://t.co/9nScutlG1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful image of comet C/2015 V2 (Johnson) by famous astrophotographer @peachastro https://t.co/JwDMGXqUpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Australia, this is happening now. This Aus teenager just wanted to go to Space Camp in the US, but visa denie… https://t.co/u0LomqMKAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btucker22 @astrokiwi @AstroKatie @amytoast I'll ask at @AAOastro if we can contribute too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm an astrophysicist at @AAOastro &amp; @MQPhysAstro. Besides research I also do plenty of Science Communication in both English &amp; Spanish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7am in Sydney means I'm starting my "Australian time" in Twitter. As every day and except replies I'll only tweet in English to my ~8pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so proud of my fellow astronomers &amp; friends at the @AAOastro! Well said! Please remember Science relies on fact… https://t.co/NX4ppfJDbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems "Astronomía para Principiantes" at @SBSSpanish will be a bit later today, but definitely in next 15 min or… https://t.co/7WYC9cddiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next "Astronomía para Principiantes" with @viridianaazul &amp; me starting in ~25 min at @SBSSpanish 97.7FM also… https://t.co/hfPCwWY9ow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent move, @LEGO_Group, including girl &amp; boy in Lego Duplo train. My son learned counting with the old one (bo… https://t.co/aXnpfv2WrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune 97.7FM today at 1:30pm for new "Astronomía para Principiantes" at @SBSSpanish . @viridianaazul &amp; me talk about #VeraRubin #womeninstem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case you haven't seen this superb timelapse yet. Well done, Jason Wang, Christian Marois, @keckobservatory… https://t.co/res1p2FA4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have fun @GTCtelescope. I'll be at the @AAOastro AAT next March when the @BBCStargazing crew is visiting us here (I… https://t.co/YIbNZsQUnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still amazed by this wonderful movie, it is the very first time we see another planetary system in movement! Th… https://t.co/01Hw396Kom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Pea Galaxies are really, really, similar to nearby Blue Compact Dwarf Galaxies. Well done! I'll read this pap… https://t.co/hItKAPFRyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BankofWords thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to save gif but I can't do it with my iPhone, I would like to tweet it (with credits) using another account.Ideas?@astrokiwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm working on updating my science communication efforts + balance with research. Last night I updated my Twitter p… https://t.co/EdVXXo7fnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so happy a scientist, stem cell researcher Alan Mackay-Sim, has been named 2017 Australian of the Year! Well do… https://t.co/8ht8KrUojf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Included for my lectures! Observations by C. Marois &amp; team, orbit fits by Q. Konopacky, computer movie by Jaso… https://t.co/oKgMWyWQAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there, @MQPhysAstro @Macquarie_Uni !!! https://t.co/pDSixZSkBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will. Thanks for sharing, @upulie https://t.co/MtDsr5SiPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my support for all, scientists, rangers, volunteers and public, that are dealing with this crusade against Scie… https://t.co/DBgJsZCIzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing deep image of Andromeda galaxy and surroundings by @DeepSkyColors that keep astronomers very intrigued. Wel… https://t.co/x5nDIswgfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree. All people in our societies should understand this. How to do it? More Science Communication at all… https://t.co/SyZRkWqDQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward watching great @monsoon0 in action! https://t.co/ancHhW6XXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to watch #HiddenFigures when finally released in Australia cinemas next 16th Feb! https://t.co/RVQRvEAuut #WomenInSTEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure how may Oscars will #HiddenFigures get, but I know we have to move &amp; talk about this movie and the key… https://t.co/H7XJ6r7oR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Blue Compact Dwarf Galaxy NGC 4861 in Canes Venatici by @HUBBLE_space https://t.co/56WEVocVSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss participating in this workshop! I had so much fun when did it some years ago. If you can make it, don't hesi… https://t.co/67RL0ivshR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'll be at the @AAOastro Anglo-Australian Telescope for this! @ProfBrianCox https://t.co/7x9SQ8Yrd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cc @PenguinGalaxy #penguinawarenessday #galaxies #interactions #wow https://t.co/jBprOx8ztU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @NASA @CassiniSaturn spacecraft is amazing. I remember when launched, I was starting Physics Degree long ago. S… https://t.co/SZJIcWR6bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an good reading for my research: how can we measure the chemical composition of galaxies? Note: metallicity… https://t.co/l0dtmMjbXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice image of Mars! Well done, @SkyInspector. This little planet is not as easy to get as giants Jupiter &amp; Saturn https://t.co/yJYWxI5Vw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Absolutely amazing @swag_astro !!! https://t.co/KuMlBURB3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dwarf galaxies? Favourite galaxy group HCG31 as photo? Must read article! Note: my 1st science paper L-S, Esteban &amp;… https://t.co/68YOVLkTb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This new science podcast in Spanish is prepared by Yolanda, a 9 years old Spanish girl, to motivate other kids in S… https://t.co/TwWqnqysik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magneticlemur I'm also a bit surprised about that... was it directly under the sun @MQPhysAstro ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new @APOGEEsurvey spectrograph has just arrived to Las Campanas Observatory (Chile)! Yuju, well done, and all t… https://t.co/xXZHJAS1h0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Lately I prefer don't know too much about @AstroHuntsman: they are doing very COOL things in a desk near mine… https://t.co/yicdPw2q5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends in #Adelaide, I will not miss this. Breathtaking astronomy photos participating in @AAOastro David Malin's… https://t.co/WzDj9lkrqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there! Go, AAT &amp; @AAOastro , go!!! https://t.co/etnPRE90KG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain still is a world leader in organ donations (pity some of these Spanish Government press releases don't have a… https://t.co/xsgfrR2af8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful research about galaxies, star-formation, dark matter &amp; galaxy evolution by @ICRAR astronomers! https://t.co/OpI3YzJBv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38 C at @Macquarie_Uni @MQPhysAstro at the moment... good we have air conditioning... https://t.co/TQZLn8YVIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to start? Blue lights, white coats, fancy screens, no computers, working at the dome! &amp; (favourite) Milky Way… https://t.co/uCVgSeGU8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a VERY difficult choice: select the 2016 Astronomy Image of the Year for @Photo_Space… https://t.co/TlcUM88NvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you visiting Chile? Interested about science &amp; astronomy tours? Don't miss https://t.co/Zmv3XBP0yn by… https://t.co/9Xm4rVegNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful article about 1st science results using the #ASKAP for #WALLABY survey, led by L. Staveley-Smith @ICRAR &amp;… https://t.co/BEvtSAG9Py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuju! Well done @CSIRO_ATNF @HIgalaxies WALLABY team &amp; ASKAP! https://t.co/pSuSWLrQkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful all of them! Well done @AstroTanja ! https://t.co/fQa0qms960]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@upulie @Discovery hehehe, I actually like it, it's catchy, and it's also well explained at the very beginning of the article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would LOVE to attend this Conference but I can't... and return to Crete &amp; Greece, wonderful places. Enjoy it,… https://t.co/igzBW4xDJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who could get these data! Wait for a new, amazing deep image of M51 by @HUBBLE_space in the near future! https://t.co/cu2JGgRM0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely, the famous @sydneyobs time ball must continue falling at 1pm every day! I do support this initiative, d… https://t.co/3UPStpRHs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's also an increasing industry in Spain, that has the darkest skies in Europe (video in Spanish)… https://t.co/O2dbInr1Pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenLMasters Happy Birthday!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, read: "With this scarcity of leisure time comes the risk of losing sight of what makes us happy and fulfill… https://t.co/P8wi3cxOPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice article, very well written @callacofield @SPACEdotcom !! https://t.co/g1cMnpY1wP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @apod image of edge-on NGC 891, see the dust in filaments perpendicular to disc https://t.co/bTR5yJsJNm Credit:… https://t.co/vhT0FpiwVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A mountain in the Canaries" is @IAC_Astrofisica Roque Los Muchachos Observatory, site of 10m @GTCtelescope &amp; more… https://t.co/2mpejBbhTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And all, women &amp; men, have to fight together to get equal rights &amp; obligations in science &amp; every other social aspe… https://t.co/JJbc3r1Ztg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is precisely one of the short stories I told about #VeraRubin to @SBSSpanish just 1 hour ago! https://t.co/CJ1hajqgAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just been talking with @viridianaazul @SBSSpanish about #VeraRubin and #womeninstem for another "Astronomía para Principiantes" podcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcnees include it in the gif? Because I think we can't send gif+image at the same time via Twitter...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting @TEDx talk about the @GMTelescope https://t.co/H4GMfAaSsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And please use it! Very important to reference/cite/acknowledge the work scientists/researchers &amp; others do. I will… https://t.co/X4Z8LgiPod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always tried to follow this approach for my science papers (and sometimes even outreach articles) https://t.co/trQh7MlUIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebamf I follow a similar procedure described by @vrooje, usually read it as soon as I can, wait few days, and go back again. ~1 day total]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still remember following this alone in the office 10 PhD students shared at @IAC_Astrofisica. No social media the… https://t.co/pDlWoeN8Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just hope to be there in 2018! Have fun this year! https://t.co/w5a2vbfpnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erfmufn I LOVE Byron! Event tried to organise a conference in 2015. Also amateur/profesional astronomer! I hope to attend in a future event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with this gif we can prove there is an invisible, compact, massive object in the center of the Milky Way: a sup… https://t.co/zM37fDFGND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 2 days traveling from #Spain, the Three Wise Kings are finally in Sydney! Thanks #AmigosS for organising this… https://t.co/gF69Q3SgmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful #Sydney Harbour! I've not been in this point, North Head, in years. Nice walk from #Manly. Looking for lo… https://t.co/5XsGKYFFT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm been thinking for a while organising something like this in Sydney... I'll contact you, @astronomyontap ! https://t.co/Bfh9hLolmP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>