<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiona__Mills people get confused because they were a little to the right **of the Communists**, but still on the left spectrum. Socialists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiona__Mills cognitive dissidence in action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rusty_wow @ThinkFirst6 @worldnetdaily I'm sure plenty of stories like these. Love 2 see more empowered to come forward with stories of hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThinkFirst6 you never know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He was a child that I wanted to abort"
Dolores Aveiro, mother of Cristiano Ronaldo

Who knows what great things a life spared can achieve..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dancing with the barely recognizable people" 
Its a working title.
#DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hero is an overused word, not here. Not here. https://t.co/gL4vJjjWMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithM @Streamable Spicer was born to be parodied on snl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why a consensus in not a scientific outcome, it can be just a herd mentality. https://t.co/wUPMfUygZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of Irish people view the EU favourably, that view should not blind us from the very real chance of the EU, or E… https://t.co/c2gTz42kab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so much for diversity. https://t.co/hRK9pTtOyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeclanBurke2 zero moral hazard so all involved don't give a shit, and I include buyers who think they'll be bailed out too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanMcCourt @rte Is 'liberal guilt' the new 'Catholic guilt' I wonder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids programs can be quite cruel, just fat shaming for shits and giggles.
@GodfreyElfwick https://t.co/z3Qgly0D2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claffe_john Armstrong predicts next bubble to burst is government bonds, which pension schemes are mandated by law 2b heavily invested in..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have pension funds become Ponzi schemes?

CALPERS Trying to Cover-Up Leaks of their Mismanagement
https://t.co/Qyn1Mu34U2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithM incitement to violence if ever I saw it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A more informative and accurate headline:
"A man armed with a machete and a knife rushed towards soldiers shouting… https://t.co/vpvZ1kGTXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheball @NewstalkFM was Jim Telfer being mischievous saying Ireland has 3 quality provincial sides?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claffe_john this stuff is used like a liberal mating call, great fodder for virtue signalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I go on a peaceful protest I always make sure to wear my best dark cloths, and balaclava.
#UCBerkeley https://t.co/valNn5s5Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is hilarious, get your settlement cheques out quick @MailOnline @nypost https://t.co/hrRsOlUgZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Trumps hate.

That and rioting, setting fire to stuff. But mostly love. https://t.co/4NfuFoMVni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Irish media carefully avoiding coverage of the riots in #UCBerkeley overnight.
"Nothing to see here, m… https://t.co/nXkPJrXEv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The machines are now in charge.

Concrete Buffer Gone Rogue… Can Anyone Stop It? https://t.co/EJF6YhWwui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nailed it.
"Trump versus the media is like Iran versus Iraq: I want them both to lose" M. Graham on @NewstalkFM re #muslimban 
@IAMMGraham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke hence the rage, "were not Catholics!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if Ireland was put on the US banned list &amp; it was called a "Catholic ban". The liberal left would be apoplectic
#MuslimBan
#FakeFear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Murray_Kinsella what's the lineout node in the in-goal area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts are relevant only when they compliment the left wing media narrative. https://t.co/8sjubqSXF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor "did not break the law"according to medical experts.

Left wing agenda:
Abortion on demand (request, if that… https://t.co/2YbYYcyvpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 declared hottest year on record, 0.1°C above previous record in 1998.

So temperature pause continues, breaking the link with CO2 rise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discrimination!
"Ewan McGregor to be prosecuted for refusing to sell his wares on GMB because Piers Morgan is a pre… https://t.co/ujvr2KyN3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫♪♪♫"I'm a little despot, short and stout...." https://t.co/MfDDIJpCom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These cases are not outliers, and are why people march for life.
https://t.co/STCugZjjvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyJManning @gracey_knoll "I'm sorry ma'am, we believe you have a little Christian in utero, what do you want us to do...."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenGoosie @Kelli_Daley ..to rephrase Madeline Albright's line "there's a special place in hell for men who don't support a mother and baby"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenGoosie @Kelli_Daley I think you might find a Christian audience that agrees with you on that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No way to roast beans in heaven I'm afraid. https://t.co/XOrRQR1vC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nialljburke or her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any socialist worth his salt should be able to answer this. https://t.co/tQCwOVfecf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts are agreed upon, ah. https://t.co/SgzRiC6Xok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The banner could be mistaken for a "1984" slogan. Crazy. https://t.co/xCwX4WA2vQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke its a build up of debt that would normally have been sorted with a lira devaluation, they never modified the economy to suit Eur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just about sums up how crazy the left are in America. https://t.co/so3xVODT6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfRayKinsella i've no prob with cigarettes becoming history, I've a prob with it going underground &amp; requiring substantial Garda policing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithM link the amount of tax on cigarettes to the burden smoking has on health system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithM suicide is pretty harmful to health too. Has to be a better way to dissuade people from smoking than enshrining in law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to be blindsided by a Euro exodus, note how euro-positive we are in comparison to other member states. https://t.co/tAaaBGfjFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke ie, not to be converted to lousy lira!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke all debts called in before exit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Draghi is saying that Italy would have to pay €358.6 billion euro to leave — an exit tax."
https://t.co/vKxv3u8RpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was 0.01°C warmer than 2015, with accuracy of +-0.1°C
Why NYT Hid The Numbers For The 'Hottest Year On Record' https://t.co/1L4fMrlqkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavQuinn surely its a denial of service on discriminatory grounds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danmcgin @DavQuinn em, wrong guy your libeling there....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond I have a few old bed mattresses i need throwing out, I could pass them off as a car...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond from my experience rates are but another tax, never correlates with service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond ah, skin in the game, fair enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond but why are you the judge and jury on why someone uses *public* parking and busses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond sorry, not sure what you mean? I'm a big fan of both towns and a functioning bus network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doubleDfit @CllrKRedmond so permits are designed in part to stop ppl using busses? No wonder the rural public bus network is in a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanMcCourt they cant put a finger on what rights they are marching for, but march with/for those who **will** take rights from them. Mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanMcCourt yep, zero downside to Sharia Law, **especially** for women. https://t.co/k8CR5YBWuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TJMcGibney @JOE_co_uk @MKBurke1 I'm not so sure, check out the reverse one, its even weirder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bailing out banks is socialism, funding a war machine with tax money is socialism. When governments ultimately fail… https://t.co/Ri6DJmzhAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StapelChipsYT @GodfreyElfwick @Mr_McStevie worse, he chose to be a white male.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke and what a ridiculous thing to fight over, who fu**ing really cares!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidenburke what's this in relation to?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddyanglican @DavQuinn sadly I did read your tweets, and they offer no safeguards to the unborn. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddyanglican @DavQuinn so anytime, any reason, up to birth. Got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the Clinton Foundation is laying off 22 of their staff. Coincidentally, donations dried up after the election for some strange reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nialljburke "After all, the sun is the main source of heat for our planet" NASA confirmed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“[In] recent years, researchers have considered the possibility that the sun plays a role in global warming” 

NASA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immdaly @colettebrowne exactly, is this the level of curtain twitching scrutiny we are to expect from the IT over the next 4 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ian56789 sorry but you are discrediting you main point, that he is anti democracy (which I agree), by saying 14YO Soros was a Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@immdaly @colettebrowne what's with the creepy obsession with Trump's young kid? Chills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No left wing group meeting is complete without a good old fashioned bloody split. https://t.co/cSaf5j7YXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people suddenly give a shit who is playing at the US Presidential inauguration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianymoran @DavQuinn did the privileged men of PBP have any say in this submissive submission?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philosophyfan don't forget 'gun control', its like an irony festival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit!
Former Connacht captain 'kidnapped after antique shop robbery' https://t.co/4q8UIyOiew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony of death threats on a blind man coming from the same crowd who want more gun controls. How about some *se… https://t.co/69r4rewIwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendboyle are you high? "you examine evidence in its totality", yes, 10,000 years of data versus your "hottest year" in last few assertion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendboyle if you're calling NOAA data "spurious" then you are truly speaking out of both sides of your mouth. Keep the faith, bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendboyle "on record" only if you think the world is 100 years old. https://t.co/7lzGRwZLo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk  "hottest on record", records only being monitored accurately for past 100 years, does he think world is only 100 years old?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk completely agree, he used one year of *weather data* to make a statement on climate change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendboyle em, stating a temperature measurement for one year is not a climate pattern, its still a weather pattern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneyMack66 after which, Hillary coined the phrase "stop dicking around", true story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CO2 gods must be appeased, and normally I burn effigies but, you know, CO2. https://t.co/OcB97k0D30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video clip strikes an uncanny resemblance to the US presidential election.
Clinton: Shepherd
People: Sheep

https://t.co/0H6jSCu1VF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any chance that @Buseireann could pop into the 21st century and allow debit/credit card payments on buses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will they take back the Nobel Peace prize now? https://t.co/GjYHEQRxXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetalfirst @CalThomas @IAMMGraham @rte @todayfm @NewstalkFM very true, I just listen to podcasts so I hear them the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For balance, at least @NewstalkFM has @CalThomas, @todayfm has @IAMMGraham, @rte has??? crickets.... https://t.co/Q9KIDPtene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible for #RTEbias to at least **try** &amp; show both sides of US politics, Trump is going to be the US President for crying out loud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next CNN reporter **must** ask Trump about the unsubstantiated allegation: "when did you stop beating your wife?"
@fetalfirst @boucherhayes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is vile, shame on the UN for giving this ideology respectability on the UN Human Rights Council. No wonder pus… https://t.co/scgQOMb83w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being told you're abnormal, or have abnormalities. Deplorable label of t utterly defenceless, painting them… https://t.co/9AhaszBERx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanLawlor @ian_odoherty the "National Socialist Workers Party", aka the "Nazi" party, was 2 the right of the Communists, but still left.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>