<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[New Listing! Newlands, New Zealand

Super, spacious family home is an excellent location!... https://t.co/vHwwBURn17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Listing - Newlands, New Zealand

Wonderful - spacious family home in a fantastic location!... https://t.co/MxSFAuVbCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the investment spots?

https://t.co/VXD2rjbZ82 https://t.co/57zJbJWxpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of years old now but this is a GREAT intro to Ray White Leaders.

The technology and company focus on... https://t.co/8TrIcyxmVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are a buyer, disheartened by the strength of the Wellington, New Zealand market, be thankful we're not in... https://t.co/21SMUhwcz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Newlands, New Zealand

Great opportunity!

https://t.co/NEdieAYxMC https://t.co/9NHSZub9ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington Anniversary holiday does have history behind it. Ever wondered - wonder no more and have a great day... https://t.co/tqRdvO0PRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one amazing house!... https://t.co/2Wq1yj47wY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great start to 2017!  

Award received at out first meeting of the year https://t.co/i41OdtTFUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QUICK!  Do some of these today as TODAY seems to be summer (no telling what tomorrow or even this afternoon will... https://t.co/zrNYGDIGWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great guide to Wellington beaches...... https://t.co/YX7xfx7P1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[December stats are out.  

Wellington market has changed CONSIDERABLY in the last 12 months! https://t.co/uyRGGi197B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been in and out of that building many times over the years.  Wonder what will replace it?... https://t.co/BVorjY4PyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo of Pigeon Park (as it was then) in the 1950s. 

There is still a car rental firm in that spot and the... https://t.co/QHzn424Hbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First buyer viewing of 2017. 

We are here and available for appraisals - buyer viewings of ANY Leaders property... https://t.co/NKlJj26QMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all health and happiness. https://t.co/OMfkDwByxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big thank you from us for all of your wonderful support this year - 52 confirmed sales from Pukerua Bay to... https://t.co/Y2pS0WxDTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading away for the festive break?  Make sure 1) you know where your toby is &amp; 2) turn it off to avoid returning... https://t.co/ou47gvBprH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Denise &amp; Bruno from Churton Park - who won our November $200 Prezzy Card draw.  We hope this... https://t.co/UW0eulawG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD NEWLANDS - a lovely first home for a soon to be newly wed couple.  We need more listings, supply is not... https://t.co/0adhmBVr21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD PAPAKOWHAI - what a sale I could write a book about this one.

Despite all the market hype, not every sale... https://t.co/TeQzRgqcWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD TAWA - a perfect little investment for a soon to be very happy landlord -... https://t.co/DlxpHnYNkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Lyncia Podmore our Facebook Page Likers Draw Winner!!!!!! https://t.co/qFlIpKRPaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's great being part of BNI New Zealand and having the opportunity to refer my fellow members, all of whom I... https://t.co/VFHqQSrCHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/tHau8U6gSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD!  Aro Valley

14 COMPETING BUYERS.  HAPPY VENDORS AND BUYER.

We need more properties to sell.  Please get... https://t.co/aGjF18J0Uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always enjoy the Absolutely Positively Wellington Advent calendar.

This year they've stepped it up a notch with... https://t.co/GreQUdMF7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon it'll be picnic weather this weekend?  

Who knows!  Well - if it is Wellington has some great spots to... https://t.co/tmJl4DgbGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Tawa Flat, New Zealand (Tawa)

SUPERB FIRST HOME OR INVESTMENT... https://t.co/oX1GTQB7u0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Update from Philip &amp;amp; Aaron.  Implications of Recent Earthquakes https://t.co/ZODqeRWr1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING!  Newlands, New Zealand

SPACIOUS LOW MAINTENANCE LIVING

https://t.co/Ee5Gk614Su https://t.co/6kkHFA9kDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you reckon?  New suits for Aaron &amp; Philip?!

What's you're favourite one?... https://t.co/z8BunxuOIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a great weekend Wellington.  If you're spending it in our Coolest Little Capital City In World here is what... https://t.co/Whu6QuHd3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close of deadline today. 

100 plus buyer visits to the home. 
14 offers in hand. 

Market still hot for selling. https://t.co/ZRBlNKNJu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little wonder many of us are feeling a bit tired and on edge... https://t.co/6A5kdC1P7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know!  Thanks Straight Flush Plumbing Ltd... https://t.co/46Msxbyccj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of a long one but worth a read.  Thanks to Lissette of Foxplan Ltd for this information from ANZ

Loan... https://t.co/fq0MiIlrsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquakes TICK
Floods TICK
Gales TICK
Hail TICK 

ENOUGH ALREADY!

This photo was taken this afternoon by... https://t.co/BEmr8azkaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay up to date Wellington, New Zealand. Stay safe. 

https://t.co/y6MKeDPrq4 https://t.co/7cYlbiixmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scary few days for all in Wellington and beyond in these shaky isles.  A sharp reminder that Mother Nature is... https://t.co/7aUFAV0bIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think the market is slowing?  Nope. First open home today attracted 51 groups.

With most groups having 3 or 4... https://t.co/47qOFdciDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever buys 141 Aro St is going to be lucky. 

Popped in here for a bite before buyer appointment. So much... https://t.co/prE4EqxtE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Update from Philip &amp; Aaron.  Vendor Supplied LIM/Building Report? https://t.co/0qN5PZCbiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OCR cut!

Low interest rates fueling high demand but not matched with supply. 

Time to sell!  Call us today.... https://t.co/RZiv7GU6Bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's have our own poll.  Hit;

"Like" for Trump, 
"Love" for Hilary or 
"Angry" to spoil your vote! https://t.co/3sx4Ql2WOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Aro Valley

Superb home in ever popular Aro Valley 

https://t.co/mmvS0uqXYM https://t.co/DnzouA2QCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lacking some key background information, this article is interesting for a couple of reasons.  

First - it... https://t.co/2e0ugH4MbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure we've shared this before but it is funny for an afternoon distraction.

How NOT to negotiate!... https://t.co/wGDMyPH2Ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/cmoDPZMt7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a look inside the most expensive house in NZ!... https://t.co/si71OWLBRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon these would go down well in Wellington!  Imagine living off the grid.... https://t.co/476cFaMBHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DO NOT DISTURB sign is up for Aaron as he and Lissette celebrate their marriage with a well deserved... https://t.co/RJdKKoCChJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

Lovely owners were over the moon to attain more than $50,000 more than they were... https://t.co/RwopE3u7J7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always like a pat on the back for achieving great results. https://t.co/J0MsRt4Wjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting toward the end of a l-o-n-g day?  Need a smile?  Here's your amusement! https://t.co/ZSgLp2GtBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAMOUS (well sort of) - Wellington Property with Aaron Burke &amp; Philip Reeve as seen on Grand Designs New Zealand — feeling famous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think we'd cope with this house.  Feeling seasick looking at it! https://t.co/NUAvAF4u4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why why why would a salesperson choose this as the lead image for a property on TradeMe?!

We pay attention to... https://t.co/HsyqXeMV3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

New owners looking forward to getting their teeth into this project. https://t.co/ynCHnsmmxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

Big, small, rural, urban, new, well loved....we sell ALL residential property types... https://t.co/OEtnjGceh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/LhKUOwKC6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever we sell a home we send a survey to the seller and buyer.  This is the latest (abbreviated!) response;... https://t.co/WoiVBwv4m1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Update from Philip &amp; Aaron.  Reverse Mortgages Still an Option https://t.co/fhsmut56i6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are free....this yacht on the other hand is $174 MILLION of pure WOW WOW WOW!... https://t.co/gSiHKe8FrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What spectacular architecture!

Shilda winery in Kahketi, Georgia.  Photo: Michael Archviz Studio https://t.co/Ev8uUsvTWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington, New Zealand has overtaken Auckland, New Zealand as fasted house price growth area...... https://t.co/EjNeJklJL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING!  Newlands, New Zealand

Lovely Lockwood home

https://t.co/YbAvfzXzDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Newlands, New Zealand

Lovely Lockwood.

https://t.co/YbAvfzXzDE https://t.co/UV5zEqoeqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow these apartments really are tiny.... https://t.co/yr8pYwjh1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez we've come a long way in Wellington!

Who remembers the airport being like this?  Interior view of the... https://t.co/peEcGtTQHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will it REALLY happen this time?... https://t.co/X5mNRHSNEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will REALLY happen this time......?... https://t.co/CMhLSifzjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great urban design ideas here.

Love the reflective fence!... https://t.co/RkcVGxAUW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of hours behind these two awards!

Thanks again for your support with referrals to friends - colleagues and... https://t.co/wx0DJ1WmOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this story...

Foreign tourists met a kind woman while on a stopover in the Icelandic city of Búðardalur,... https://t.co/tGmNNzRT0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting wet out there Wellington, New Zealand

Time to build an ark...? https://t.co/ImSN1MIdjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conducted a "pre settlement inspection" last night (buyer checks over the home they have purchased before moving... https://t.co/4XMDkzg0mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really progressive development in Melbourne, Australia  

just wish this sort of innovation will become the norm... https://t.co/BeGpvDTAMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Tawa Flat, New Zealand

We need more to sell - all locations - all price brackets - buyers are falling over... https://t.co/AvMNrz5L8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received a "Neighbourhood Watch" email today and got us thinking how to minimise your chances of being a crime... https://t.co/jsbvenIP6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Update from Philip &amp; Aaron.  Gifting Your Home to Family https://t.co/bP1lH4p49R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too cold today - need some distraction.

No real estate - enjoy!

https://t.co/c9sv0w12Oy https://t.co/R1GgaZxLSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold cold day - need some distraction today - no real estate!  

Enjoy...

https://t.co/9RQpGxr4bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

We have buyers keen to buy but not enough property to show them.

Thinking of a... https://t.co/0uXK5vsH5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Newlands, New Zealand

Large family home that has seen better days.  Roll up your sleeves....... https://t.co/wiyEazVDH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW LISTING! Newlands, New Zealand

Large family home that has seen better days.  Roll up your sleeves....... https://t.co/RDOpBDfKqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the time to scroll through the photos of this gorgeous home in San Francisco, California... https://t.co/u43vXG7w2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you have had a good day and taken the time to appreciate or remember your father.

All the best from us Dads. https://t.co/VUqvonq1UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four... https://t.co/st4A1i2IWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three... https://t.co/3z7o5Vzo63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fathers Day!  That means DAD JOKES...  Here is one of several we will post today.

Start rolling your eyes now! https://t.co/bCYZ3LqO0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

We had our vendors in tears.....tears of joy!

They were BLOWN away with the result... https://t.co/ixl2eaxHFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOLD! Newlands, New Zealand

We had our vendors in tears.....tears of joy!

They were BLOWN away with the result... https://t.co/2RzlPYhyQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We work with many buyers.  Sometimes they end up buying from another company - such is life.  Regardless, when we... https://t.co/sZ8OOEVIJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a STUNNING property!  Well at $1.5 BILLION it should be.  

Mind you vendor seems negotiable with offers... https://t.co/ufWEPxNOj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've noticed a rash of scams popping up on our FaceBook feeds and emails recently.

Consumer has a good resource... https://t.co/DLiHcvw2fl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planing some renovations?  

Wall paper is HOT at the moment and some of these are AMAZING!... https://t.co/ZX4hWNB3Ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington is ready to host the All Blacks at Westpac Stadium this weekend.  Who remembers the days of Athletic... https://t.co/o29NNa5cp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having serious outdoor living envy looking at this Miramar, New Zealand house!  Checkout the video...... https://t.co/aca7P7mCcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if any of the hundreds of people we have sold homes to have followed any of these unusual rituals.....?... https://t.co/I099DBXpHg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>