<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobcat search mission! https://t.co/o3tEYa3a2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgetownMet Has that spot been empty since the partial collapse of the rear?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps @TheGeorgetownr should actually read the Executive Order to see who qualifies for deportation. Hint: It's way more than just felons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also bizarre that @TheGeorgetownr asserts DREAMers have no fear of deportation. Apparently the editors believe in the mythical "Trump pivot"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd editorial in @TheGeorgetownr on @MayorBowser plan for helping DC immigrants. Did editors actually read the Trum… https://t.co/72e1vscsUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Alliance of Thin-Skinned Men. https://t.co/0GWUfglsKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I noticed the "palpable air of uncertainty and chaos" when walking the dog last night. It was palpable. https://t.co/gWLP36Htsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA. White House. Same thing. https://t.co/2UIw4LLzMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenBudoff Fake Otto! This is the real Otto! https://t.co/onxpsKewvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Theon Greyjoy option. https://t.co/SY686CDzmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gorsuch nomination is absolutely _____. We strongly _____ this nomination &amp; urge the Senate to ____ the nomination. Please donate to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. An official twitter account for a Supreme Court nominee. That's a new one. https://t.co/5orn28G2Mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alpert Attracted by the leafy neighborhoods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Line bobcat. https://t.co/v2RAQEXgEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosenamy If I had staff that had done that, they'd get a lovely empty box as a parting gift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an astonishing statement. https://t.co/6JkfsxyCQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's gotta be some awkwardness between the committee staff and their bosses. https://t.co/v3ZhPlFiVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps the better question about Trump is not “What is he?” but “What will he do to us?” /How to Build an Autocracy https://t.co/wUA1VmicVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point by Frank Sesno: Whether a journalist is liberal or conservative, need more rabble rouser journalists questioning everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ari Fleischer: Media is missing the mentality of Trump b/c of his "blizzard of executive actions"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roberts: Trump doesn't need you guys!
White House Correspondence Association president: Yes he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point by Steve Roberts: Trump doesn't need mainstream media to get a message out; he's mastered alternative methods way more effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long-winded questions that meander, digress &amp; contain multiple parts are an awful way to try to communicate with this White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to GWU event on Trump &amp; the media and amazed by Jim Acosta's inability to be brief or concise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgetownMet then you'd need to kill off regs to adopt the regs that are killin them off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosenamy Study the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday: We consulted w/Hill &amp; agency staff to draft the order b/c we're inclusive.

Monday: We didn't consult with… https://t.co/1KwIXeQYgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality engagement between a writer and the audience. https://t.co/Ejz2wWo1Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substantial delays on the Red Line this morning. Per @wmata, it's only "residual". Great success story!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a good sign when a "massive success story" is touted by several high level officials anonymously. https://t.co/DeiJPNbYMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing to read this piece w/such broad generalizations about policing demonstrations. @Tanvim https://t.co/33H5c70H7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcivey @miller_stephen Or *are* there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maustermuhle Does the building speak?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindymoretti Yes! The tiny motors are amazing! And this is what @maustermuhle wants for DC with his velociraptor dome idea?! No thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arlusk @kristoncapps Is it ok to include plans for invading adjacent county &amp; global ban on peanut butter? Asking for friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristoncapps @arlusk What does self-caring entail? Serious question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGiambrone Although, to be fair, the first part of that sentence seems pretty broad &amp; clear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really; makes it a "case-by-case determination" w/no guidance on what factors that entails. Huge potential for… https://t.co/8p4tGcYXRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorter version: This is all the media's fault. https://t.co/rB51AtDGEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the heck?! https://t.co/3w6hQpatRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see the Inauguration bleachers getting used. https://t.co/hLYNuVJlK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HStGreatSt Well, he was also in the Navy. 30 years ago. So there's that level of expertise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Either you stand up for your principles &amp; decent behavior, or you go down, if not now, then years from now, as a coward or opportunist."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/mGo01fQ1pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can he be officially disowned by Queens? https://t.co/BdU61i6nLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something compels Otto to not go down these stairs. Probably the knowledge that he'd have to go back up them. https://t.co/KPqE826M0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srfrjulie @nikkimann17 Or they've all been taken and burned. As they should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srfrjulie @nikkimann17 The Nutella bacon donuts are a crime against humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wait, that's not irony. That's incredibly insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irony: There is far greater amount of review done to publish an agency notice in the DC Register than has been done issuing executive orders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bloomingdame Until it's in the Register, it's just scuttlebutt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it for this week's DC Register. If what you're reading in the news makes you angry, don't just tweet, go out &amp; do something about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BZA Order on 2 new one-family homes in alley at 1237 C St SE: https://t.co/ToPDNuyaBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DMPED 2/16 hearing on proposed surplus of Eastern Boys &amp; Girls Club bldg (261 17th St SE). Notice: https://t.co/ra8zAdJzms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorBowser has $150k in grants available for Immigrant Justice Legal Services. Info: https://t.co/SXwZPYuFNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dept of Environment has $950k available for Low-Income Solar Systems Installation &amp; Jobs Training Program: https://t.co/UFusZY1bNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dept of Environment has $60k available for Summer Youth Watershed Protection Education &amp; Job Training: https://t.co/uKnR1TGh0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor's Order 2017-20 appoints Brian Ferguson as Acting Director of the Office on Returning Citizens Affairs: https://t.co/57IrJbZha6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor's Order 2017-17 makes 2 appointments to the Historic Preservation Review Board: https://t.co/AYHlTVZ9l5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor's Order 2017-12 makes 6 appointments to the WASA/DC Water Board of Directors: https://t.co/6sl0B1hKQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DDOT issues final regs on beautification of tree spaces: https://t.co/59jneyvruj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor's Agent for Historic Landmarks 3/10 hearing on McMillan Park Reservoir (ANC 5E): https://t.co/VvTX0kBZFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OSSE 1/30 hearing on license application for Mid-Atlantic College: https://t.co/USDqpL9xqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ABRA license app for Yard House (812 7th St NW; ANC 2C); brew house; 338 seats; 40-seat sidewalk cafe; dancing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABRA 2/15 hearing on Pub Crawls &amp; Reimbursable MPD Details. Notice: https://t.co/hhh7Zic0OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ABRA license app for Pearl Street Warehouse (33 Pearl St SW; ANC 6D); tavern; 150 seats; live music; entertain endorse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ABRA license app for Le Pain Quotidien (1401 K St NW; ANC 2F); 149 seats; 66-seat sidewalk cafe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ABRA license app for Kristina's Cafe &amp; Pastries (4418 MacArthur Blvd; ANC 3D); bakery, sandwiches, small plates; 16-seat summer garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABRA substantial change app for Gin Rummy (3522 12t St NE; ANC 5B); requests later hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABRA substantial change app for Cloakroom (476 K St NW; ANC 6E); requests summer garden, but no number of seats given.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chair Mendo 1/31 hearing on reappointment of Kathy Patterson as DC Auditor. Notice: https://t.co/dYxxqkNGWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CM Allen 2/9 hearing on Sentencing in DC: Agency Roles &amp; Responsibilities. Notice: https://t.co/Y2sKgtdReX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Sunday. 1984 is at the top of the book charts. And it's a super abbreviated DC Register!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So by stopping old folks and children from countries that have never attacked the US, we're preventing another 9/11… https://t.co/2pBztluV66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With this standard for being on the National Security Council, I expect @timkrepp to also have a role. https://t.co/izgFIdGt6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thread on the organizing required for "spontaneous" reactions like what happened last night at airports. https://t.co/ufQ6dM0CjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true. https://t.co/AvOmw2rZNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My company didn't use robo-signing when foreclosing on people's homes &amp; in proud of that!"
&lt;record scratch&gt;
It did. https://t.co/ajpgKyDpxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scroll 3 mins into the video: https://t.co/mudTSB8jJT https://t.co/RVVoLCW7CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get the levity with which these stories are written in the Post. https://t.co/s9vb98DS1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamroberts_1 Ack! Didn't notice that. But still a heck of a burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not go gentle into that good night,
Old age should burn &amp; rave at close of day;
Rage, rage against the dying of the light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But as president, Trump's is a policy of cowardice. On every front, he wants to shrink the country into a shell." https://t.co/xfAOuRW1ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get the point of screaming at a guy who has no power over immigration enforcement. https://t.co/rOqY7rS1Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristoncapps I sympathize with the airport cops; neither they nor TSA have any control over any of this, yet are put in untenable position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20002ist @cuneytdil @dcpl @DCHistory I've filed a historic landmark application for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizqueenmama Morally, maybe. But for legal sanity purposes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizqueenmama I imagine there's going to be big push (&amp; plenty of scams) to get citizenship for qualified immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizqueenmama I'm suddenly glad my mom finally became a citizen a few years ago. She wouldn't be affected by current ban. But still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susiecambria For 911 calls, it should be immediate and seamless transfer to D.C. 911.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susiecambria That happens if you're calling from a cell &amp; closest cell tower is on other side of border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakesharrows My neighbor is one of the chefs there! Very tall. Needs more parking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifying. https://t.co/2FPnWwxErW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susiecambria Not tweeted yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@answercoalition that's great! Thanks for doing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord. This is insane https://t.co/RLXYe9Mgyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I take it that @answercoalition isn't planning on taking down any of their posters glued to utility boxes? https://t.co/WUsAKN6ntW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxthegirl Stay calm,  but be wary. The terrier motto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's this mean for all the foreign students and workers in the US? Are they all stuck in limbo? https://t.co/gCNY5sYRVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The misspellings in these angry tweets... not good. https://t.co/mFZ7HL1Pa3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>