<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, lizard people, a PSA. you're not gonna fool anyone with names like this https://t.co/KArzJHL197]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donniemnemonic that's a good #culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donniemnemonic bookhater#1730. i haven't played in a minute mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar oh, i spent six months with a physio on it, lol. just always looking to deepen my pool of knowledge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar game journos seem instinctively like a good source of tips because of the particular quirks of their work/lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar that's legit. i've had it for a while due to years of laziness, always on the look-out for hot new tips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar well it sounds like you have the perfect ~~pro gamer~~ body if you're only getting it a teensy bit. i'm bad at enforcing breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar i envy you so much right now. joint stiffness and hand cramps and stuff like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar as a ~~pro gamer~~ do you get gradual process injuries or the like? any tips 4 a fellow ~~pro gamer~~ on dealing w/that shit if so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you could tweet the plot of a michael crichton novel and a twitter centrist would do a 75-tweet chain calling it a Russian disinfo campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[memorise this for when you see fascists https://t.co/r85WwuRkiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Papapishu "this administration firmly believes in Pam head on Garfield body. The weak, lying media won't report this. Lorenzo Music voice"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotFaulty Ben Garrison has definitely been suppressing his lust for Streetcar-era Brando for decades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all new zealand loves kylie bax, a lovely supermodel that got famous! *two decades later* we regret to inform you t… https://t.co/hMmNCrbBbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English is a man so scared of losing power that he'll never publicly commit to a moral position, even when it's so obviously necessary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English then took his shoes off and attempted to walk on the eggshells covering the entire room. He tripped ov… https://t.co/LVwQLMuRf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[double the quota as fast as you damn well can. sink cash and resources into protecting the safety and wellbeing of refugees @pmbillenglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*putting my fingers to the man's wrist* *shaking my head* i'm sorry, this man has been brutally owned https://t.co/PptXAs7gKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for a very busy man who has no time to condemn openly racist US policy david seymour sure is spending a lot of time NOT DELETING HIS ACCOUNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick "it's not fascism read a book by the guy who fucking loves imperialism" is very very cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[does anyone have Moana Ete's email and can forward it on to me? Want to contact her about something for Pantograph Punch. DM me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's hard to choose my favourite hero child from the new monster factory but The Gender has definitely taken a comm… https://t.co/Us521Y3ESA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer your pasty ass got punched on tv and everyone saw you cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QBert. That wing dings talking dickhead. Absolute trash heap. I hate QBert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How bad is QBert tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce this is THE WORST PART of S class driving. I may be drunk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce as an avid SONIC ALL-STARS RACING TRANSFORMED player... no. NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing WRECK-IT RALPH gets right is that I respect Sonic. I respect him and I want him to tell me how to responsibly live my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Flinnja this is perfect. Thank you john lasseter for convincing me that tracer is bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Ralph have a different frame rate to everyone else in his game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, imagine playing a bonus level of a classic arcade game and now QBert's there. Fucking QBert. That's not cool. He's fucking QBert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the thing about WRECK-IT RALPH: if Vanellope Von Schweetz was in a real game, everyone would hate her for rubberbanding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emanuelle Riva gave one of the best performances I've seen in AMOUR and fuck i need to watch that heartbreaking film again. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know we're all tired of 'thread', but still. Fuck Duncan garner and anyone else sick of Māori reminding them abou… https://t.co/LX9ueOxOCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastercamels fuck this is so true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had never heard of this before I saw the trailer for it in front of the VHS for CONSENTING ADULTS just now, it looks lurid af, is it on dvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know about this movie, GUILTY AS SIN, starring Don Johnson as a charming murderer, directed by Sidney Lumet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico @ZeddRebel *vomits profusely* sorry, the bad thinkpiece got the better of me for a second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico @ZeddRebel the most interesting man in the world? Surely not. He merely has some strange but fascinating opinions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many of you see me tweet this arvo and get momentarily terrified you followed some rando old white dude with bad opinions. I know i did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought Mainlining today on the sole basis that its entire aesthetic is 'a child's drawing of windows xp']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[an entire country is under siege from authoritarianism + hate, stop yr pen before you write "a key supporter has some ideas i quite admire"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look, if your response to anyone in Trump's inner sanctum is "hmmm, fascinating, provocative, purists pipe down" stop and take a damn breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton ka kite, sure they're keen to hear why an avid supporter of a man who hates them is "one of the world's most interesting ppl"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hi_tide @jfacrawford new year new you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 6pm. Enjoy @jfacrawford, me and a very special guest talking Glengarry Glen Ross on this hot new SPACEY SPACE https://t.co/gxqn9qfd6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penthousecinema hey according to your website you're playing a 2013 German movie named GOLD. when yous getting the mcconaughey one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslevin thank you, got my fingers on the meme pulse with this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslevin @dillamonster @LiamMaguren i only found out about AGE OF SHADOWS because i live next to paramount]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslevin @dillamonster @LiamMaguren paramount haphazardly hosts these films now but they do a shitty job of marketing them tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw u see that the jet set radio future soundtrack is on spotify https://t.co/JdLjeQ86R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw someone suggests my appreciation of michael bublé is ironic or somehow meant to attack mr bublé https://t.co/D4gNn2IGsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've been informed that my previous personal brand was 'disrespectful' to my man mike bublé so, in collab with… https://t.co/8rVJQwmd0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me, an idiot: gerrymandering and voter ID laws are antidemocratic
you, smart: wow, "freedom and democracy are incom… https://t.co/nBjeo6biqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's so fucking telling that eric crampton thinks a man backing an abhorrently racist, sexist admin is "interesting" https://t.co/fEfmKpuhPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if a man who wrote a book on how multiculturalism is a disease was setting the citizenship test i would hope someon… https://t.co/EtRrwgvXJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donniemnemonic like many @kurteichenwald decisions, he'll tell you a bad, false thought process then accidentally reveal a worse, real one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cannot fault the ambition of any fringe artist who markets their show as a world premiere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fobwashed @austin_walker @patrickklepek @waypoint the twitch preview thumbnail's been ruined forever https://t.co/b54gWOQhP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm dreading this year's election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a *fucking* ghoul https://t.co/AFBzowtq3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistertodd (i knew that the Hunter tracks wouldn't even get a look-in at the Oscars so they were off the table)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistertodd oh sure. the difference is i'm right (i very nearly said Owen's Song, which goes *hard*)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistertodd i voted for I'm So Humble but Mona Lisa is absolutely the best Popstar cut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just bought a nintendo 64 with ocarina of time and goldeneye because i need to find my missing childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I've tweeted a lot about rising fascism but hey as long as ppl assume punching them is some kind of net nega… https://t.co/lDpRqH31sQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[his post "explaining" why he can call Winston an Uncle Tom is sanctimonious, poorly-written and so powerfully misses the dang point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronindrone he truly is a lukewarm flannel of a human being]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh is that what peter meant when he said "congratulations" https://t.co/KFi34a6kYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGirvan i'm sending a note to everyone who writes an article like that about Arrival to say "call me when GET OUT gets snubbed next year"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGirvan 8 sci-fi out of 72 Best Picture noms in the last decade (9 sci-fi if you count Midnight In Paris lol). That's 11% of noms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luceobrien wait, Vin Diesel wrote and directed The Return of Xander Cage? I didn't realise, he's so talented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@insequential @ringo_starrrr my qualified opinion is that it is his oldest son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso never #wholesometweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i think the thing i've always liked most about gareth morgan is how he's always been grateful for his friends and s… https://t.co/WpHXwHChPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this vanessa carlton/acdc mashup on the new neil cicierga album is a personal attack on me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josephmoore1 I'm sorry for disrespecting your labour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josephmoore1 i hope the New Zealand marketers put that on the DVD case and attribute it to 'Joseph Moore - Fail Army']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Oscar glory is creeping up on Justin Timbalake! Congratulations to the J-Man and his Oscar-nommed hit TROLLS! Can't stop feeling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I volunteer to stand outside peter thiel's wanaka estate and yell "more like peter FAIL" until he leaves the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZFringe twenty five lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BananaF4p @pkollar Phil, there's a really low-effort drawing here of a stick man pissing in a bush. there's an arrow and the name 'Phil']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm sorry for being a fringe theatremaker during a festival @google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol i just got my theatre company's email account suspended for sending too many press releases at once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkollar phil, i'm reading this first chapter and it's just the letter 'g' for twenty pages then "fuck" written in capital letters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donniemnemonic @BooDooPerson loljk as if the New Zealand Herald would cover anything about the confirmation hearings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donniemnemonic @BooDooPerson oh i'm already sending these tweets to the NZ Herald so they can say "even New Zealanders reacted to the vote"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooDooPerson @donniemnemonic lol it's all good, no disrespect meant to Rhode Island, which I'm sure is lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw yr name is a ready-made Presidential campaign slogan that you'll never get to use https://t.co/JeFXJhc3JE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[god, i'm really sick of these supposed 'liberals' who...wait... computer, enhance... whats going oN HERE https://t.co/tNi9gtlGjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistertodd @griffinmcelroy @JustinMcElroy also there's a STADIUM CREATOR? https://t.co/zXIu8IlV9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistertodd @griffinmcelroy @JustinMcElroy bumping this because look at this video, there are face "redness" sliders https://t.co/bkCcLhfkKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[confirmed: winston peters has fucked a sheep https://t.co/2rfAb6Ruyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nz herald media writer jon dinner has defo written an unpublished novel about a romance between a nubile co-ed and… https://t.co/lPCQe8C45O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For real tho, imagine writing with a sober face "It's not as though MLK was unblemished or that I agreed with everything he advocated"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hope i haven't driven David Farrar to support Trump against his will. we cannot afford to lose another self-appointed 'reasonable' sociopath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[be the change you wish to see in the world https://t.co/vwdQF34156]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless i can't claim it lol, that honour goes to @jodamico1 https://t.co/Mdg6kJN7A3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unfollow me @dpfdpf, you smarmy jackass with nothing better to do act like you're above everyone who cares. you absolute infant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sees an oil exploration called off* You Mother Fucker *sees anti-abortion protestors harass young women* thats the… https://t.co/EMuVY4TQBd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>