<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple maps had my bus route programmed into it. That's well impressive. Plus it knows where I work. That's a bit scary, I never told it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the back end of Edinburgh. Ain't no body got time for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's just hope I end up somewhere close to haymarket!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trams aren't working this morning. Having to make my first venture onto Edinburgh buses. Changed once already - let's go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded took Colm's advice and started Glitch, quite like it. And carried on with season 6 of GoT. #blood #boobs #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded I've recently watched The Crying Game, finished S4 of House of Cards, can't wait for season 5. Started the walking dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 lol I thought you'd come back with that. I saw them live when I was about 20 and could take it in the mosh pit-I got quite bruised!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish the Pats would come to UK again :( loved seeing them last time! https://t.co/HQs2Cq1QF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 Oh it can. Try Mayhem. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 oooo I like that band. You should go really heavy and listen to the Dillinger escape plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't remember the last time I got to leave work at 5 (on time) - ready and waiting for tram time. Let's go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 @Laura_69 you'll have to grow your hair long soon Colm! ðŸ¤˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 haha good man. Try 'good mourning america' on the same album. That's a great track.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 Love me some GnR! If only I was rich I could go see the original line-up now it's touring again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 lol - a new section... 'Colm's descent into Head-banging' - have to find some suitable heavy intro music! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 lol keep listening - you'll learn to love it. I'll make a headbanger out of you yet! Try LetLive you might like that, bit softer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back on the @Architectsuk train today. Still loving the album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow - she's a beast with the come backs! Love it https://t.co/aIdOAh1Ezk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kungfufuzz what you seeing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatsMcNeish fiery redhead.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 Depends if you like screamy heavy metal. If you do then get on it, if not, maybe start on something light and work up! ðŸ¤˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeryBritishLife Thank you! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally giving the new 'architects' album a go. Bang - it's awesome! Get on it people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only my daughter sits in McDonald's dancing in her high chair to Olly Murs. #specialgirl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out for a walk whilst the lady sleeps off a night shift. @Solm67 and @Onyersix keeping me company on @LastSaveLoaded - Thanks fellas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 amen to that! ðŸ”ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 too true. Not sure which is worse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 sad times. Clearly 2017 is gonna roll on 2016 style ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John hurt died? Oh no! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ava seems to be going off quicker than normal! Yay. PlayStation session I think tonight, long time since the last one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it. I'm done with client reporting at BlackRock. Sad times! On to Security Lending. Hi ho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 Thanks mate! Jumping into the deep end come Monday! ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day in my old job. Moving floor and teams tonight. SO much to do today before I finish though. Ouch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded this week, I've started Alan Wake, and back the future ep 1. Trying to clear a bit of my immense backlog (400 games to go!)ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Figured out my sky box pin, so can finally watch the Xmas Jonathan Creek special. Love this show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willing my daughter to sleep so I can cook dinner. #hungrymofo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Spanish offering a deal to Gib to stay in the EU if they come over to the Spanish. Gibs reply - not a chance son. Cheeky cheeky. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched a bit more #Frequency whilst I ate my lunch. Man I love that show. The story is so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 It was too early in the morning for cuddles. ThAt time of the morning is for hand-holding only! ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatsMcNeish you are looking for a husband in the wrong places. Try Harrods!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty tram. Some guy gets on with me and decides he wants to squash into a double seat with me. And then wonders why I give him a row. Dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 @NatsMcNeish Always. Trying to fit in with the scots here, maybe they won't realise I'm an English. ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatsMcNeish remember for next year ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @NatsMcNeish - Christ it tastes good. #merryxmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @NatsMcNeish - Christ it tastes good. #merryxmas https://t.co/EfBqVxmEIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicolalalalala lol I wouldnt have got away with that back in my day! Glad I'm not alone is suffering these things!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicolalalalala amen to that. That and the refusing to eat dinner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicolalalalala This. Everyday. ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a #metallica fan ðŸ¤˜#sandm https://t.co/rKlF9jZzuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started a new series. An old one from the sky box we had recorded. ' new blood'. It's ok, but a bit weird!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell I've forgotten my sky box PIN number. Can't watch Jonathan Creek :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 oh no that's awful, hate spoilers! I just read up on wiki, Turns out it wasn't a big hit in U.K. Can't imagine why.... lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 yep - but only by about 2 seconds lol. Nearly got me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 well that was different! I enjoyed it though, not my normal type of film for sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 Haha you'll outlive us all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 You might by be around - you'll be nearly 70! ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 thanks man, let's hope I can stay awake. Or it might have to be a two night job lol - I'm getting old too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 oh it says 1997 on the sky box, I was 6 then! I thought it looked 'old' for 1997!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 1997 - I was 11 ;) but I've honestly never heard of this film before at all! Recorded it off the sky box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 oooo now I'm intrigued!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching 'The Crying Game' - I know absolutely nothing about this film. Let's go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded I started the fresh prince of bel air on Netflix too. I think Colm should attempt the intro rap. In full. #doit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded I watched Sherlock - loved it. Hunger games 3 part 1, the purge anarchy. Also contributed House of cards season 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He-man is on @NetflixUK - yes! Loved this show as a kid. Now for them to add #MastersoftheUniverse and all would be complete!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #TheUndateables - love this show. It makes me happy to see it work out for them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zachinglis the opening of 2 is so fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally in love with LetLive. Such good songs. All thanks to @NotMetalPod and their top albums of 2016. Cheers guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started listening to LetLive today. I really like that band!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blasting out @blackpeaks again whilst I work. I've said it before but... what a bloody good album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the last episode of this series of Sherlock. Like a clever version of Saw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananyah ah man. Guess it's an excuse for a weekend away! Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananyah oh wow didn't realise this was coming to the UK. Hope it comes to Scotland at some point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Tony Blair... 11. Haha love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death in Paridise. Season 3 ep. 6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 lol think that's fair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 haha I've never seen that so can't comment. But yeah I was a bit bored!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiDaniell always classy! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched the hunger games 3 part 1. Didn't like it. The first two were much better. I fell asleep twice in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 best way to be! Old is boring! ðŸ˜‚ lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha putting snapchat filters on people on the tv is sooo fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moved onto #TheDailyShow - bloody love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been out for a Chinese. Now watching the end of GoT season 5... it's the 'shame' scene. #shame #dingding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow!!!! #winteriscoming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoT season 5 Ep 10 - finale. That flame priest is mental!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeryBritishLife @Airwavescast @sfdrummer @Tone7x20 yay - great news! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Airwavescast are you guys going to do a new episode in 2017? @VeryBritishLife @sfdrummer @Tone7x20  #fingerscrossed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic rap battles of history - Jack the Ripper vs. Hannibal Lector. Seen it loads and still love it. Lector wins by a mile I think! ðŸ”ªðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In love with that Alan Walker song - Alone. #deskraving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded fight fight fight! #round1dingding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded The last stand, the blindside and love actually (it was Xmas!) Oh and a bit more of season 4 of house of cards. All done! ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded Tour, I like that. Carried on with season 1 of shooter, designated survivor and Frequency. And a few films: police academy 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded started Preacher, but didn't like it. Started Arrow and really liked that, done 4 episodes so far. Also watched The Grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded finished season 4 of GoT and half of Season 5 - what a show! Carried on with season 4 of Person of Interest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded long list from me this week thanks to the holiday break. I finished off Homeland season 1, a few more House season 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made a roast gammon risotto last night. Just had the leftovers for lunch. It as awesome - I smashed it. #egobuilding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to an old @SwordAndScale episode on HH Holmes. Interesting theory so far on him being Jack the Ripper. Enjoying it so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game of thrones - S5 E8 (Hardhome) - what an ending. Creepy as hell. And that white walker is kick ass. Loved that episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastSaveLoaded game of thrones the tell tale series on steam. a few odd ones in the weekly steam sale, total about Â£30 for about 20games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up a bit early for work, so just finished off 'The Blind Side' what a great film!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solm67 @TrevDXB Ah nice, I'll that a go today too. Thanks guys! ðŸ˜]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>