<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How @boydie71 got away with this offering, I'll never know.
@PleaseDontHugMe #podcast https://t.co/lPQ4g02pOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh of the week.
No doubt about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18:21hrs.
That sigh was brief but there was real intent behind it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday night.
#podcast editing night.
With a BOUFFANT.
How did this become my life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loveclapham Neil grew up in #Clapham 1972-96.
This is his story. 
Please RT if you can. Thank you.… https://t.co/JV8GDW4Mvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The response to dire housing should not be studied callousness | Dawn Foster https://t.co/lA7iJtZRbt
#HousingCrisis 
@GuardianHousing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you everyone who RTd the last tweet.

Appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Neil's story. 

Please RT if you can. Thank you. 

https://t.co/f5aVcHSCLJ

#DRTisAvailable #podcast https://t.co/zhJkqEzI9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil has been diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis, (primary progressive ms) for which there is no treatment here in the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; In it, I ask my childhood friend Neil, 'Nelly, Remember this?' and recount our old south #Ldn exploits from back in the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans of my Daniel Ruiz Tizon is Available #podcast will be aware that this year, I have introduced a new feature, 'Nelly, Remember this?' &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICYMI
The rise of the ENSUITE BATHROOM.
Via @Storify. https://t.co/c57652knu1
#HousingCrisis https://t.co/yQYHS0FrWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The graffiti, I'd like to point out, was incorrect. My dad did 18 years at college before they turfed him as he'd done every course they had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end, the worst we were exposed to on that corner was some graffiti at my dad's expense, mocking him for spending 21 years at college.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent 24 years living on a house right on the corner of an #SW9 street and I always feared we were vulnerable to a mural.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It kills me when I walk past a house that's had a mural painted on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1996, I was walking home from a party in #Lambeth with some guys. We walked past a mural when 1 scoffed, "Yeah, that'll stop the violence."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They love a mural in #Lambeth but right from when I was knee high, I have always thought they were s***.
#SW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember at the end of Villa Road, opp St John the Evangelist, in the late 70s, some guy painted a giant mural. I HAVE NEVER LIKED MURALS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And seeing sheets of corrugated iron on houses in #Lambeth in the 70s was a common sight. There were squatters everywhere in the borough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a kid of course, I had no idea of what was going on in Villa Road. I just went through it whenever I went to Angell Town.
#Brixton #SW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was after #Lambeth &amp; the Villa Road squatters had compromised. The north side of the road would be saved, but the south had to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember Max Roach Park being built in the late 70s. #SW9
#VillaRoad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant programme on the Villa Road #SW9 squats of #Brixton that I remember well from my childhood. 
Lefties… https://t.co/LruzAi5MUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Londonist The rise of the ENSUITE BATHROOM. 
Via @Storify https://t.co/c57652knu1 #HousingCrisis 
#Ldn https://t.co/59zxUFV9YS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK home to 80% of top-earning European bankers https://t.co/aZ4uuwG5Za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 I've known you 34 years Mick. You've never shocked me like this. My next tweet will be a blank one to register my dismay
@O2music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 I'm going to have to stage an intervention. Surely @O2music thought you'd confused the Drake gig for Rod Stewart's Feb concert?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 And I was working so well today. I can't do a thing now. You at a Drake concert is worse than your body warmer period. 
@O2music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 Honestly, I'm taken aback you went to a Drake concert. It's up there with Harrison Ford getting his ear p… https://t.co/VIE29gFpEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 #Brexit, #Trump, shock after shock. But none bigger than you going to a Drake concert. I don't know the world any more.
@O2music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 You were obviously chaperoning youngsters to the concert. If I'm wrong, please don't tell me. 
 @O2music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boydie71 Did you genuinely tweet this?
@O2music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump doctor reveals secret to US president's hair https://t.co/jIzYBkiOv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of the ENSUITE BATHROOM. Via @Storify https://t.co/c576522MCt
#HousingCrisis 
@Shelter 
@GuardianHousing https://t.co/ATTPJggmPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StockwellNews #Stockwell writer with book out. 
'Me! Me! Me!' 
Find it here: https://t.co/CfB3DIioj5
#SW9 https://t.co/WTVCeza7Y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live at 10am.
#BibiDoesSoho https://t.co/IOlnTP7FiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Rail and the Brixton and Herne Hill arches: it's a shambles https://t.co/Gx6ezbLBC4 via @brixtonbuzz
#SW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you go out and pursue your dreams and ambitions when just the other side of that bathroom door is your bed?
#HousingCrisis
@Shelter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ensuite bathroom also has a potentially ruinous impact on relationships, new and old.
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, in a spare room, the ensuite bathroom comes into its own. But not as your ONLY bathroom.
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tomb offering no views to the cranes that have corralled your neighbourhood and carved up old homes into boxes. 
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ensuite bathroom is a tomb.
A windowless tomb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, the ensuite bathroom is a daily reminder of just how insignificant you are.
What you're up against.
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite 25+ years of the communal bathroom, I never felt ensuite was the answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should add, my dad himself always felt the communal bathroom was a good way to meet the neighbours. I myself didn’t quite see it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; you’d have thought I’d champion the ensuite bathroom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; needing to leave the bedsit to reach it, handing out maps to visitors requiring the loo so they didn't get lost &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As someone who grew up with the communal bathroom and endured it for two and a half decades+ &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you endure being line managed by someone younger than you who’s still living at home, when you’ve got an ensuite bathroom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you stand in your windowless bathroom, your bed on the other side of that door, can that ready you for the real world? 
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get out of bed and reach your bathroom in an instant, where is that sense of purpose?
Where is the momentum?
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to feel you’re getting something substantial for your rent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The momentum it gives you at the start of your day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I think you need that walk to the bathroom. 
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But is that a good thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you can be out of bed and in the ensuite bathroom within a tweet. #HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As our accommodation shrinks in this country, the ENSUITE BATHROOM is growing in popularity. 
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Docroddy That was an excellent team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BibiLynch With difficulty, I would imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Parkes rocking the Braveheart look. https://t.co/amme9NkIRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Little.
Villa. 

That is a fringe. https://t.co/dOv99ynO77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terry McDermott, vastly underrated and scorer of spectacular goals. His perm was probably better than this centre p… https://t.co/Jko06UDGAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 late night football hairstyles of yesteryear. 

Strachan - Aberdeen. https://t.co/3z8tok9T9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea's Antonio Conte in a previous life.
#cfc https://t.co/u2OhSXw4dQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow.
10am.
#bibidoessoho with @BibiLynch 
#radio https://t.co/72oHK9rN1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time I see people playing frisbee on the dog-wrecked Common, do I just not tweet about it?
#Clapham #SW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could be now this angry world no longer has a place for middle-aged tweeters drawing attention to the dog muck on #Clapham Common. 
#SW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mouth guard should've been in 14 minutes ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man City are the street addict that constantly roughs up Bubbles (West Ham) in series 4 of #TheWire.
#WHUFCvMCFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crimsonavenger Yes, I had to microwave my most recent saveloy. Split the sausage's distinctive-coloured skin right down the middle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crimsonavenger If we can find other saveloy lovers in major UK cities, it might help turn this little-regarded sausage's fortunes around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If ever there was a takeaway held back by its appearance, it was the saveloy. https://t.co/vXZpfdZUBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mullet common in that decade lent itself brilliantly to that often visualised moment of dashing to a stricken opponent's aide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my 1980s fantasies was being a footballer who saved an opponent from swallowing their tongue, a not uncommon occurrence in that era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do your Amazon shopping via https://t.co/Rcfj0NNny6 and a small % comes back to my site at no extra cost to you. https://t.co/ukmhiGIRqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libraries minister promises to act if councils cannot justify cuts https://t.co/kcOqtdBwoA
#SaveLibraries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss the considerable weight of 1970s bedding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Like finding venison in Londis." 

Daniel Ruiz Tizon is Available #podcast. 
#iTunes https://t.co/sCQq56GS55 
RSS… https://t.co/W2QMu6rPlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; It's like the 80s when no big live music event could take place without Paul McCartney closing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't seem to have #gentrification without a CostaStarNero taking up a spot on our bland, revamped high streets.
#Ldn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An early contender for my Top 5 most memorable moments of 2017. https://t.co/vCqgSWj6BY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too strong coffee threatening to pull a facial out of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICYMI 
Footballers used to have leg hair.
Yes they did. https://t.co/xUZYpbKc3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right to rent immigration checks put vulnerable people at risk. https://t.co/pmaEydARQr
@GuardianHousing
#HousingCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning's slumped posture is down to a combination of a lack of coffee and significant BOUFFANT pressure pushing down on the shoulders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The teeth don't know what to do with all the extra space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suddenly the teeth, like a tenant whose flat mate has moved out, find themselves with a lot more room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could be the jaw clench, if not stress-related, could be a consequence of the mouth guard coming out in the mornings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sigh and the jaw clench are like two people that shouldn't be together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I let the sigh pass if it's not accompanied by the jaw clench. If the clench is there, the sigh gets stopped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[08:32hrs.
Early morning sigh cut short. Pleased I had enough about me to abort it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your elderly mothers and fathers, says Tory minister https://t.co/1nozjikC6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK faces return to inequality of Thatcher years, says report https://t.co/DJDZofnYK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you got for me, February?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be off with you, January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's kids won't believe it, but here's proof that just 30 years ago our footballers had leg hair. https://t.co/Z3xvDI8rSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1930s Brentford players beat Arsenal's modern day stars to the post match selfie by 80 years. https://t.co/zXSYR9I6gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 1940s footballer is getting a knee massage from the trainer.
Yes, THE KNEE. https://t.co/lTd1TzIpRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarrenAJB The admiral kit was brilliant but the 80-81 @CPFC Adidas home strip is an incredible kit.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>