<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I want all the Kylie Jenner valentines makeup collection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I see tweets that aren't remotely connected to me I'm like shit that's about me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jane_c11 wit da frick. Lookin out for u no more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't even watch planet earth rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let him bop in peace https://t.co/5twHWqEcby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought there was lad culture in CCC but oh boy was I wrong. DCU is where it at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fell asleep on the couch in such a painful way. This is the end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frickin anxiety Makin me feel sick all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like my lil sis trying to scrape together €86 because she wants to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe ed Sheeran tickets are €86 what a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a good pup! https://t.co/FvJmHBgN5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to pay the troll toll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently constructing my underground bunker for when WW3 breaks out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs r so pure they even contribute to the disabled and needy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want 2 surround myself with doggos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw lordt I need another dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jane started a fire in the restaurant we were in today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None choco in house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found the purest meme https://t.co/8gCov1YQPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like what a genius concept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The picture of Dorian Gray should be compulsory reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I wanna get tickets to RockWerchter https://t.co/VwnLvuVnDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How these girls got da confidence to post bikini pics. Lik teach me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skrrrtt_Cobain of course, I can relate to this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to boys on the train talk about how annoying it is when girls use the machines in the gym. Like what do you expect us to do there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate the Kardashians but also want to be them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This book broke me. Do not need dis on a tv show gudbi https://t.co/ZLi8xk98Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took too many pain killers. Dis is weird :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skrrrtt_Cobain this is relatable. U changed nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching British vogue documentaries like why did I do law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LamiaT1098 take a shot to drown ur sadness because I think Jake Gyllenhaal is married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LamiaT1098 take a shot whenever you're sad you have never seen him in the flesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LamiaT1098 SHOCKED ND UPSET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryin https://t.co/xfNStayFmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Trainspotting character are you? I got Renton ! https://t.co/aIRfeFglIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jane_c11 the bone structure like how]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I acc took the most beautiful pic of Ciara last night. Can't wait 4 u all to see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drank too much redbull. No longer tired but unable to study]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrTrunney @Skrrrtt_Cobain the badge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Pepe actually a political thing now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently they have not handed in a draft for their ag science project. Disappointed in them :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody in LSC put my number down as their Mams and I keep getting texts every time they mitch :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who made bean a meme thing. I been saying that 4 yrs https://t.co/lXcHt9svC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me watching supervet: *CRYIN*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will my emergency tax return from war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't fkn listen to changes without thinking of FKn Shrek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm acc grieving Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAM BAM THANK YOU MAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition to actually name Ziggy Stardust as the messiah he was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will my obsession with Ziggy end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You vs the guys she tells you not to worry about https://t.co/3wHyV96Dtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have u ever tried to translate an 11 page official document from French to English. Lol don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciaarraa stop that is insnae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samuel L Jackson, what on earth https://t.co/IDFQw4i9qd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocked and upset that I wasn't born looking like Kendall Jenner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I use my little sisters boyfriends Netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julietwebster_ alrite, u can cut off my hand and I'll cut off yours and then we will offer them to Bowie to reincarnate him. Plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would actually amputate my left hand to see Bowie live during the Ziggy era]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MGMT need to tour r somethin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Mercury was no longer in retrograde??? Whathappenin???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't tell if I'm really hungry r feeling sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and lamia are gonna see Cillian Murphy in da flesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first valuable contribution to the course group chat ! ! ! https://t.co/H5IUlsGyGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was meant to get up early to study lol oh well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsniamhmolloy ultimate worst. Loofah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u catch da towel in da piercing. Ouch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had started a blog like 5 years ago I could be so rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During lc I used to study till 12 then wake up at 5 to study more. I legit can not even study for twenty mins now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwizKhalifaa I am both Lisa and Ralf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking through my notes and you can actually pinpoint the day I stopped trying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm disappointed in you all https://t.co/wSlrZInTmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not happy with this result https://t.co/wSlrZInTmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously thought Skins would be an accurate depiction of being a teenager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me watching oitnb lake episode: *CRYING*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciaarraa  woah you just old school memed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please pick 1 https://t.co/wSlrZInTmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankcollins97 only the vote will tell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyrockets can u do my exams for me thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A holiday nightmare: brown leather shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad I am not at I heart Bowie tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This better b tru https://t.co/CyWHSo0mm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I repost memes on Facebook a relative texts my mam asking if I'm okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY CANT I STUDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying https://t.co/AGbLgDNz0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: *intentionally self destructs*                                        Also me: lol we were not a race built to last!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHERE THE BELLYBUTTON. CRYIN https://t.co/lNM6lYn5HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT WAS LITERALLY THE FIRST THING I THOUGHT https://t.co/lNM6lYn5HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I am sad my doggo put her paw on me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that's getting me through January is Trainspotting 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For real @NetflixUK needs to be blocked around exam time. I am dOING nO sTUDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to post cool pics on insta and now I just post memes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have one lecture on a Wednesday and one on a Friday. why didNT they put them on sAME DAY????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FORGOT HOW GOOD RUBY ROSE IN OITNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oitnb just walked into my life and started killing all the characters that I was like emotionally invested in??? Why???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would anyone like to come to Bowie fest with me this weekend. Plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciaarraa true. Agreed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY https://t.co/c48OnE3anT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mine must be in post :) https://t.co/9yW092eTmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryin https://t.co/IEmqNtpIbR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>