<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared hard to argue. https://t.co/KvH71MbFyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonprophetess seems to be doing well 300000 last time I looked. Don't live in UK but I think a lot of Irish feel the same about your leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums had a fiver left stuck on this. https://t.co/VZR1rzlFJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums please hold on. I've had a mare this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker chelsea a good example of this. 2 or 3 young players with experienced players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared you don't need nothing except a sense of humour. Cmon over,weather is shite but and I have to tell you we still have flatley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 suck it up won't feel a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 could be worse https://t.co/941HIKVMHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanCollymore what's your thought on Clough returning to forest as manager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AccaTrackerTM no hope it's not  going to be one of those nights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AccaTrackerTM Senegal should be scoring there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums should of routed the little prick in the hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips thanks mate. Makes things easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips where do you follow the golf 3 ball games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips don't know what an accuulator is but I like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums 52 euro not bad for a fiver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums bottled it and cashed out. Not too shabby for a start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums what's left? No way of seeing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums cheers have a fiver on the swans if cross bar is hit and they will I get double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums was the cross bar hit in this game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieHolt22 and Roman constantly gets abuse about how he handles Chelsea. If there were more like him more clubs would thrive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums had to cash out. Was only worth a couple of quid more. Cheers lads https://t.co/ibexejP1Xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums I'm out. Well done again boys some run your on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared If Michael Flatley is performing any chance you can keep him over there. Sincerely Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews @SineadPrenders aren't we all. The 445 18 drove by with the driver waving his hands at us. Nothing arrived until 5 mins ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums well considering Madrid took as massive dump on my bet last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums please Barca don't fuck this up ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums can't believe after Southampton Madrid are fucking this up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums just Madrid and happy Wednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyleSports had great potential, sadly fell down the leagues. Hope he does well at Dundalk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 no only in Ireland can this be considered normal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums after the results this weekend I'm thinking i should cut my losses and run. https://t.co/GxA9RGE2Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richiem42 I sent that. No worries 2 yrsh left going nowhere although 80 million is a heap of cash  fecking chinese https://t.co/rhO7hu6eMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums an argument with a trainer and suddenly off to China. Anything for drama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 he's grand never going to tear it up. I did and did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 that's brilliant. Probably mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyleSports can u check if I'm due one if I dm my user name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyleSports hey folks is it free bet on all accas if one leg loses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips not exactly creative. https://t.co/7a4x3lU4gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 problem was I lost my bollox on every other race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @BBCTwo won at 8/1 https://t.co/EnSPbX9ktE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @BBCTwo I had a tenner on a horse called space oddity on new 
Years day. https://t.co/fxguSpNTim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @BBCTwo way huge bowie fan . Well me and  my brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 @BBCTwo I was there #Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips fecking swindon. One up at home and again to 10 men and they still managed to feck it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared this can't but cheer a person up. https://t.co/wC6NB6Zyh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morriskid they will wreck spencers head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums going for the bus now. https://t.co/XBTTpwViNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 no none. Camera shy the poor dog. Badly treated by someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 we brought a lurcher puppy yesterday to @DublinSPCA  if pearl needs a friend. Injured  but getting looked after now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadbrokesCare happy days thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ladbrokes if open an online account can I top up in store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootySuperTips sticking to the end it was a free bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums eh don't forget Portsmouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums oh Christ,putting in an early kick off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@truecrimegarage fuck off. I'm drunk and Irish and that is still quite disturbing. Happy Xmas keep up the cracking work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWEnclosure don't forget the we double that's going to make my Xmas. No pressure. https://t.co/gaGVFgyH2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums missed one. Papy djobgffrhgf or whatever 3 million sold 8 million. Someone should get a rise for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWEnclosure so as it's xmas any chance  we can have an ew double for boxing day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskPaddyPower what's the deal with the free bet on accas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums chelsea https://t.co/oevYz4yMEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reddaz928 @FootySuperTips depends if you need the cash mate. Nice Xmas pressie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums honest question. Is the French the biggest pile of shite going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums someone getting sacked in the morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshWaudby1321 @FootyAccums cash out nice earner that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums Portsmouth grrrrr https://t.co/B9itlCOQQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to @Ballack play next to kante. https://t.co/wfjUz5Byhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums yeah a score draw in that one. Not looking good atm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums ergh Reus sent off . Fuck off Dortmund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 ha a lot better now. Between manflu and a flair up in my feet it was horrible but it's all fucking off now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums so seemingly chelsea have sold Oscar for 52 million to the Chinese league. https://t.co/ksSBbcEM8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews where is the 5 past one advertised on your stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews all the 18's on strike? Absolutely disgusting service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 no sick as a plane to Lourdes. Feeling sorry for myself. https://t.co/A7hra1ckc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 or the northside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums this real Madrid match sums up todays football betting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_t4w4_m4ccers @mushypea007 I'm using this on Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums paddy power. Tbh next win I get I'm shifting to sky. PP is terrible for rabs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums I know that big acca is a long shot but it looks really good. Defo worth 2 euro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskPaddyPower sound thanks. Happy xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskPaddyPower say if I wanted an acca for 5 games all with over 14 corners in that game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower maybe I'm going blind from the drink last night but do you offer a corners only market?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums thought was a throw back to the last time diaby played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 doubt it although I have given him the look over the wall so he may start hurrying up a bit. https://t.co/D6jAPTtcGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 aye. Everytime I clear the payments when I go back its piled up again. At least the day will pass quicker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 he is ok bit of a mood yesterday but nothing too bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 great mags on a half day so I'm stuck with the....... https://t.co/ceSr6x5LBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 she has been alright. Up to our eyes so not much time for her shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 we could always stick mark in https://t.co/N48Y2JjgqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 nobody we decided to retire it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 haha bored already?. Nothing same old same old unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 remind you of anybody. https://t.co/AfSj4rwrD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail no worries just thought u should know thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail both your tag machines are broken at lansdown road station]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanCollymore my sons u11 team played out a 0-0 draw that was more entertaining than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 wouldn't have got through without your help. https://t.co/KazY0NVzXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas sitting at tallaght over 15 mins now and no sign of leaving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower Ibra and Jorgensen to score rojo karsdorp booked #whatoddspaddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootyAccums after Thursday. Woo hoo. https://t.co/PT2Fd0xc4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emilio_GW @Bullet_trauma that's brilliant customer service, take note nearly everyone else.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>