<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for the Democrat resistance! "Warren, Markey Vote to Confirm Three Trump Cabinet Picks" https://t.co/1ApsmPb5bF via @bostonmagazine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The age of unreason! "Judge in environmental activist's trial says climate change is matter of debate"… https://t.co/6w1ZzPbGjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeh what did the Enlightenment ever give us anyway! https://t.co/IRQ9i4ve7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More 'fossil fuels forever' madness from the bumpkins in the COALition! https://t.co/wcqTQYoOIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress can now start erasing some of Obama's environmental rules. Here's what they're targeting.… https://t.co/NZGkr8qYfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans move to sell off 3.3m acres of national land, sparking rallies https://t.co/lR2qdrAlY2 https://t.co/IMszF9IWmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because of "diversity" AOM can't take a stand on Trump's discriminatory ban - bizarre! https://t.co/18h1hRenMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Scientists Hit by Trump's Immigration Ban https://t.co/im1tISNmUO #science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trial Balloon for a Coup?” by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/jvpnBLJa0b https://t.co/wqEpOTjVzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A badge of honour! 'The man the mining industry loves to hate'  https://t.co/VLd7J7peZb via @newcastleherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It was like a nightmare': Iranian academic banned from returning to US after holiday https://t.co/mQPO1wMrXm via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss @MichaelEMann who will be visiting @usyd_va to talk about #climate change and Trump… https://t.co/LmVJ2QAHVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump and the Madhouse Effect https://t.co/L20r8MKJ43 https://t.co/tOxT0Qauvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the Rise of Trump, Is It Game Over for the Climate Fight? by @billmckibben https://t.co/fR4MicctMZ via… https://t.co/h745qeba6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s team fears climate change differences with Prince Charles could flare up in state visit https://t.co/OyNBIdU82B via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keystone pipeline will create just 35 permanent jobs. Don't believe the lies https://t.co/4X685qtBEh https://t.co/pGVvK521sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump to sack climate change scientists https://t.co/pZhJxUyqOF https://t.co/PePqzwru6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the World Passed a Carbon Threshold and Why It Matters https://t.co/uf7H2Z0IC0 via @YaleE360]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TransCanada Submits New Application To Build Keystone XL Pipeline via @NPR https://t.co/RznLIcf7xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will undermine government data. Here’s one scary place it could start: https://t.co/t8BflWpBAE via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports on climate change have disappeared from the State Department website https://t.co/gpMKnvktN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 All a bit Watchmen isn't it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaires' end-game! "Doomsday Prep for the Super-Rich" https://t.co/BWVhkx0Nca via @eosnos https://t.co/e2iKzVdYJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric cars will not stem global demand for oil, says BP https://t.co/DVrUXCNP2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe faces droughts, floods and storms as climate change accelerates https://t.co/X35W4YiA8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump bans agencies from 'providing updates on social media or to reporters' https://t.co/QfMe7lcHM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The staircase @sydney_business https://t.co/wux2tDPeHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the last Obama-era climate reports had a troubling update about the rising seas https://t.co/WWpE68fxJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Friedman’s oracular pretensions have never felt more ridiculous: https://t.co/S882tzKBJX via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musn't scare the punters! "Government 'tried to bury' its own frightening report on climate change"… https://t.co/VYzlnM9sI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAtwood @Guardian_Bkshop Now on my Kindle to read - thanks for the recommendation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't mention capitalism! "Things fall apart: why do the ecosystems we depend on collapse?" https://t.co/oMBkMU40tb via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance is futile (apparently)! "Utopian ideas on climate change will get us precisely nowhere"… https://t.co/pu6byHeEQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Climate Scientists’ Heartbreaking Pleas to President Trump https://t.co/uxPFXZ0R1B via @motherboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Whiny old fascists of America rejoice!” by @paulmasonnews https://t.co/mhVgKoW5c6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance Film Review: ‘An Inconvenient Sequel: Truth to Power’ https://t.co/frVtAqXnYw via @variety https://t.co/2geK64EHJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeySlezak Good article! BTW This piece on business people, emotions and climate may be of interest: https://t.co/uBwNsghGY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FunHoleNo_5 @guardian Yeh I know - written an entire book about this but journos still asking why no action https://t.co/n8jWt0zL13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Writing about climate change: my professional detachment has turned to panic" @MikeySlezak https://t.co/ogsrUXWcl5 https://t.co/zw1BHdCmU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultra, super, clean coal power? We've heard it before by @marcsrhudson https://t.co/a6ptOj8EzD via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change will affect all of us. So why the lack of urgency? | Polly Toynbee https://t.co/rzstaHJQAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Time to Stand Up for the Climate—and for Civilization by @billmckibben https://t.co/p4UHfYH9T3 via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘A cat in hell’s chance’ – why we’re losing the battle to keep global warming below 2C https://t.co/JbnQAptMHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's 'Dirty Secrets' Aired in Channel 4 Documentary on Climate Science Denier Network | @DeSmogUK https://t.co/hxHX8FOv7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global heat records broken for a third year in a row https://t.co/XNMCwSA4x9 #HottestYear # climatechange via @climatecouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘The last five years have not been great at Greenpeace’ https://t.co/GjwvsQZ0oF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump ‘worst possible scenario’ for climate" by @MichaelEMann (who is speaking in Sydney Feb 8 at USyd!)… https://t.co/SiKDLjGFhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge demand to hear @MichaelEMann at @Sydney_Ideas @ Feb 8 on #Trump and climate - don't miss it!… https://t.co/OXEDW1ob6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ivanka from Brighton sends climate change reply to Trump https://t.co/aFZBbrF1mB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to take on greed: why business schools must engage in intellectual activism https://t.co/88wjdxq3vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parts of United States are heating faster than globe as a whole | John Abraham https://t.co/cfgkNJvUEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia joining US in openly trashing global climate efforts https://t.co/qpAnHsR8GA via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Uber and Seamless ads reveal how Silicon Valley is screwing us” by @mattruby https://t.co/1eyVxGoyZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's eight richest people have same wealth as poorest 50% https://t.co/2WsW2JHvAJ https://t.co/SS715sR60w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise at South Head #Sydney this morning https://t.co/8iZ0tgZtJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irony alert! "WA miners to pay for China smog delays" https://t.co/aPrwTrtCwl via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the coral in Japan's largest coral reef are dead, and the rest are dying https://t.co/lYdLwsF2dR via… https://t.co/QYeKq7KC6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surreal! "Army of staff descends on Davos to serve WEF super-rich" https://t.co/5uv7fXB5p6 https://t.co/ShPpCeKf5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More on climate-denying billionaires funding Trump by @readfearn @DeSmogBlog https://t.co/XykFRxB5f5 https://t.co/USwtkYpciQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s Vast Source of Climate Pollution May Go Bust https://t.co/1gdlCwWfBO via @ClimateCentral https://t.co/4q5WmCcGC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoiding dangerous global warming no longer 'feasible', top economist warns https://t.co/fkP8O1T9BL https://t.co/qnohq5QG0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also good article on imagining climate futures re e.g. of Native American dreaming &amp; genocide:… https://t.co/CSyeNSl8Rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BAU and we're toast! "All the risks of climate change, in a single graph" by @drvox https://t.co/HLMivhZmPL via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Glorious Victory for Anti-intellectualism: “Drain the Swamp” Just Meant the Eggheads… https://t.co/JGrliT6NmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global warming is real. Here's the kind of question that climate scientists are actually trying to answer. https://t.co/P64OHkuQzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfAlisonK Oh yeh - it'll be filmed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few seats left - don't miss world-renowned climate scientist @MichaelEMann at @Sydney_Ideas… https://t.co/AAmzt3h4K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given it's @JamesDelingpole - 'deliberate misinformation' may be more accurate! https://t.co/tet5soz7hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science loses out to uninformed opinion on climate change – yet again https://t.co/K3GJNHOY5F via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['With Economics In Disarray, It's Time To Rethink Climate Change' by @kalahar1 https://t.co/S0QTBiTmNF via… https://t.co/B4wj15wTmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Brace for the oil, food and financial crash of 2018” by @NafeezAhmed https://t.co/4M0qa5Vlk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santos given go ahead for 6100 gas wells in Gladstone project https://t.co/d9t0j7eug4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change science removed from Government website within days of Donald Trump's victory https://t.co/UTceN9IeyJ https://t.co/P5asA9FNHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alphagranpa @guardian I find it hard to watch these docos now given the state of our ecocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC’s Planet Earth II did not help the natural world | Martin Hughes-Games https://t.co/CAtgXmTn9u? https://t.co/37Ein4QSN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian climate politics in 2017: a guide for the perplexed by @marcsrhudson https://t.co/1Afb61kros via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. isn't the only big country at risk of falling behind on climate change. Meet Brazil https://t.co/MfP1yQtGcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coral bleaching off north WA 'devastating' https://t.co/2r29mIhPIi https://t.co/c7QR7ffCno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the real eco-terrorists? Brilliant doco "If a Tree Falls": https://t.co/CmbjLgnoik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article by @drvox on conservative's climate denial  - the importance of social bonds https://t.co/HJ6dIQqVZw via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What role activism in an age of ecocide? My review of @tcboyle 's 'A Friend of the Earth' https://t.co/i9LqIc2lxP https://t.co/j5SXOJKGM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to see how Trump will destroy the environment, read this legislative roadmap https://t.co/2K9Son9YGY by… https://t.co/P47FZAZX7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished "A Friend of the Earth" by @tcboyle - loved it! A timely read in an age of ecocide https://t.co/UXlb5GzTVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adapting well to #climatechange - NOT! "Major flooding in UK now likely every year, warns lead climate adviser" https://t.co/ryvdfvHAMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunset on Sydney's northern beaches tonight https://t.co/GJjOsCan6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children of Men Might Be the Most Relevant Film of 2016 https://t.co/3fsqwB79VO via @vulture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss @MichaelEMann speaking at @Sydney_Ideas Feb 8! https://t.co/OGZNwsQOYn https://t.co/mjmBE7p9EU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will We Miss Our Last Chance to Save the World From Climate Change? https://t.co/223CI6Ovfr via @RollingStone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adani coalmine 'covertly funded' by World Bank, says report https://t.co/hVDlUxOzoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtesy of the LNP! "Australia's greenhouse gas emissions are rising, official figures show" https://t.co/1iv8XZbNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our politicians spruiking fossil fuels "Federal resources minister accuses ABC of 'fake news' over Adani coalmine" https://t.co/k4xjCfq0uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss CfP @EGOS2017 "Organizational Struggles Over the Natural Environment" https://t.co/YyKACSHBn9 https://t.co/k0wUNdbu91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Pole to warm to near melting point this week: 50 degrees above normal https://t.co/WcyydBvgE6 via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Hannah Arendt's classic work on totalitarianism illuminates today's America https://t.co/jmhp9oxorN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universities must confront a fossil fuels apparatus that seeks to rival legitimate science by @SenWhitehouse https://t.co/Zw3a83EyY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's plan to step away from coal casts doubt on Adani mine https://t.co/HKbLGfU2Ic via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Britain's coast is doomed https://t.co/0oO8XALNtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The web was never a liberalising force. The clearest message wins and the far right has it by @jason_a_w https://t.co/DoGfYCNmL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Denial Rides Trump's Coattails to a Roaring Comeback  https://t.co/Qjysb90tUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fossil fuel coup is complete! "ExxonMobil helped defeat Russia sanctions bill" https://t.co/LasfDvqAkc https://t.co/OchFyKOyri]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>