<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Yay, factory reset on modem and we have 4G back. But much lower received power and speeds (up &amp; down) than before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Nope, rebooted modem but still no service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Still experiencing a total service outage in Kaitoke - do you have an update ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ No, we've just lost service altogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wireless_Nation @vodafoneNZ we have been without broadband for two days. Patience starting to wear thin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ At the very least you'd think that by now you'd have a view on when it might, just possibly, get fixed ? 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Sorry, your web site claims the site has been under repair for the last 30 hours ? That's not really true is it ? 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Hi, still waiting for Kaitoke cell site to be fixed. It's getting frustrating - any news on the replacement part being fitted ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Thanks for the update - are we talking hours or days ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ any news on when the Kaitoke cell site will be fixed ? We rely on it for RBI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northumbriana @steelers Not a city, but Russell (briefly NZ's capital) named after Lord John Russell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northumbriana @steelers Wellington, Palmerston North.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M5.2 quake and reading Trump dossier. Neither are good for post lunch digestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teed up the year ahead by spending the morning having teeth descaled. Hopefully it will prove the most uncomfortable hour I spend in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sho' got them end of hols blues....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An inspiration to us all https://t.co/vx92rOZwa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recovering from two days gardening. More specifically two days of attacking gorse and brambles with a brush cutter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really can't beat a wet Sunday morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So farewell 2016. A tough year to mark. Personally a solid 7; globally a dismal 2/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uneasy feeling that 2016 is girding its loins in preparation for a truly cataclysmic finale. Zombie apocalypse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 continues on it's dreadful way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell George Michael. Requiescat in pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to be a Kiwi. #IsraeliSettlements https://t.co/GNEcGydkT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading home. One last flight and that's 2016 done. https://t.co/xsutMqpHgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the last time in 2016. A view from a hotel room window. https://t.co/AXgqVUleqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A throwback to a more civilised time: "Good morning John, good morning Sue, and a very good morning to each of you". #TftD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So farewell Rabbi Lionel Blue. A man who could be wise, kind and funny at ten to eight on Monday mornings deserves respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working from home not without its stresses. The hound snaffled @domesticexec's Xmas cookies. Ructions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here we go again... #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing John Key has stood down now to find time to concentrate on his batting technique. Much work to do by t… https://t.co/yjBWzEDzlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You go away for 3 weeks and come back to find the hound has taken over your favourite armchair. https://t.co/CyBTZKfCA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the land of the long white cloud. https://t.co/n9lVzTr10W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nagging sense I've forgotten something important. It'll come to me somewhere over the Pacific.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeward bound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another train journey - tanking through frozen, misty countryside at first light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Train cancelled. Euphemistically an "incident on the line".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tube. Rush hour. https://t.co/vOWdFESzbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from a hotel room window (an ongoing series). London - cold, crisp, early morning. https://t.co/yIgmXew5Hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OUI or NON. Politics in the 21st century. https://t.co/ZPy2oxBsdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitably miserable looking buggers - Heroes of the Reformation. https://t.co/SCxilNLKsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geneva cathedral, a tad Calvinist for my tastes, but some fine misericords. https://t.co/C4EMwPBIle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere over there is Mont Blanc. https://t.co/gCLUyBSLKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up before dawn, on my way to Geneva.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London - dark and Novemberish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New morning routine - wake up &amp; check Geonet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have been in transit for 34 hours, still an hour away from LHR. Time has become a very abstract concept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter at 35,000 feet. I'm embracing the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, spoke too soon. Waiting hours due to @SingaporeAir intransigence. And now the flight is delayed....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extended interregnum in Singapore over. Off again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SingaporeAir thanks for getting in touch. Have emailed details.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this'll be the last time I book to fly with @SingaporeAir 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faced with a 7 hour layover. There are empty seats on an earlier flight. But @SingaporeAir want another USD300. 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra, late Sunday night, raining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, here we go. Big plane, short runway #holdtight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back on the road: WLG&gt;CBR&gt;SIN&gt;LHR&gt;LCY&gt;GVA&gt;LHR&gt;SIN&gt;AKL&gt;WLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly the only people with a handle on what had just happened were the USGS in Colorado. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is sobering - timeline of the shambles that unfolded on Monday morning. Lessons not learnt from Chch. #eqnz https://t.co/MNOsXvpKCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recovering from major dental surgery: soft food only; dribbling; bad breath. I guess it's all a foretaste of what's to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation it's been a strange week - finding a good article in the @nzherald https://t.co/gC38r2lzxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester how many structural engineers are there in Welly ? Exactly how many checks were done in 24 hrs before you reopened the CBD ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welly EQ management plan: Mon - a quick check over; Tue - we're open for business; Thurs - oh, hang on... #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And another one....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be a sleepless night. After shocks rolling in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With inordinate excitement have set sky box to record the Mighty Sky Blues v's Scunny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still tanking down. So hunkered down on sofa watching Aussie batting being routed. #LifeIsGood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton tracking to get &gt; 63m votes. Only Obama has ever received more. But losing by 305-233 in EC. Rigged ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They’re still counting votes in the  US of A. Clinton projected to win popular vote by &gt; 2 million.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[165mm of rain this week, 100mm since Thursday. Soggy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All news is local. https://t.co/B0HxyQHE7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the police are hanging around waiting to meet a flight it's either a prisoner/suspect or the Prime Minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First off the incoming flight is our esteemed PM. Weird how he always gets the first row. What are the chances ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Delayed inbound aircraft' is the new 'points failure at Petone'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to work out if it's safe to go home yet. Fear @domesticexec has taken great umbridge with the US of A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though I can see the drawback of travelling in an airless vacuum tube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely this is the future for the Wairarapa Express:Forget high-speed rail, hyperloop will carry commuters at 760mph https://t.co/UjQN1tCl8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desperately looking for silver linings. I guess the street value of one of these has gone up by a few bucks ? https://t.co/gwpDXZeYtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat here watching Brexit 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still recovering from a tough weekend. The annual ceremony of The Clearing of the Barn. Skip full of junk; aching muscles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a pot of gold out there somewhere. https://t.co/gWnLUxu1VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a grim sense of self satisfaction I'm back to what I do best. Moaning about commuting. Auckland traffic &gt;&gt; KiwiRail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouseHstry I think you need to check the NZ flag - the stars are *red* with a white border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gives you lemons.... https://t.co/t0jWd4FRz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite Kyoto but not bad. #cherryblossom https://t.co/kPNPd1wo6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roobish ! Call that a forward defence ? https://t.co/bcpS05hvsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from the 'office' window. https://t.co/taJGAhqWgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These boats would be travelling a heck of a lot quicker in Welly . https://t.co/DJ6cnJyo2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from a Auckland hotel window. One of an ongoing series. https://t.co/INMDndGsDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City of Sails. https://t.co/3p8iQXvoub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK£ hitting new lows against the NZ$. How's that 'hard Brexit' working out ? https://t.co/wczOTlEj5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home again. https://t.co/iDWkbpFqtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to take off in a thunderstorm. This'll be fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In AKL. Arrived in pouring rain. Now stuck in traffic. Eagerly anticipating first conversation about house prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hutt valley is down there somewhere. https://t.co/Taiw8uIbWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the land of the Long White Cloud https://t.co/EqKxtHUYsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kapiti Island in the morning sunshine. https://t.co/o4iJoG2qun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body says 4am, clock says 9pm. Discombobulated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LAX. Usual scrum to clear security. Only 15 hours from home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, has it stopped raining in Welly ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You going dahn the end of the line or sumthin?"
"Well, yes, you could say"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London cabbie experience:
"Where yer goin' mate ?"
"Paddington please"
"Where you off to ? Goin' far ?"
"A long way"
Cont'd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>