<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of middle America is Trump supporters who don't read the news, think he had a great first week  https://t.co/FH0ObYYOGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Silicon Valley game is so Silicon Valley https://t.co/m91biq90gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Lies vs. Your Brain https://t.co/svjQKKEt9Z Science shows truth is hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like these kinds of big picture, step back analysis to get away from the day to day news noise  https://t.co/HxIbsyY7WU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a month with Google Home, still happy with "Hey Google tell me a joke"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPrimoNZ Now that we don't take the premium channels, no point paying Sky for re-broadcasting free to air stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow follower but feeling good about finally cancelling Sky TV sub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long, insightful read on the emerging new world (un)order driven by Russia https://t.co/3GVVTgMoPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be missed https://t.co/NECGdQq6by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plantoids: The First Blockchain-Based Artificial Life Forms https://t.co/PAFGn8VwWg Way for AI to be self-owning, evolving entity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said: the problem is us, not the Internet https://t.co/GY0RXZ5UZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Monday pre-lunch 5 min read on how stupid AI and chatbots still are https://t.co/ke656ytJrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reminder that better tech on its own doesn't instantly succeed https://t.co/i6IO5MQMVn Hard, real-world problems exist for a reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hear much about UK's PM so not sure if this is a case of sour grapes or damningly accurate https://t.co/dxHgWHrDeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've written about the 3 areas that companies can find opportunities to get started with IoT https://t.co/TpAtuw0s8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikapearson hard questions coming for society, paid for by individuals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Go (retail with 0 staff) will kill low end jobs like check out operators, packers. Gives coming jobs impact a stark, human-less face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like it each time I come across it: “If privacy is outlawed, only outlaws will have privacy.” — Philip Zimmermann, creator of PGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The microgrid in Brooklyn is moving again- solar + P2P trading + blockchain https://t.co/a70290DzRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of voice bots, AI so super interested to see where Alexa is going https://t.co/1fp75N5OV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty smart marketing from 2degrees https://t.co/vbfi8ZOELO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From today, the world moves to three centers of gravity." Best insights into Corda https://t.co/38rwSqHi9E from the best placed person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must-read for thinking about NZ's agri future https://t.co/5skwa6RuSL Classic disruption coming sooner than we think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a question about Cayenne or LoRa? Ask me online on Thu, 8 am NZ time https://t.co/JdHOtfLh60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz Hard to imagine in 2016 fundamental things like gravity can be explained in new ways. Science rocks...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New in the blog: IoT leaders digitally reimagine their business to deliver customer value https://t.co/WaWc77Hszh https://t.co/S3nN5okhWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent and badly needed- an open source framework to build secure blockchain-based applications. Zeppelin https://t.co/iqKoILLYhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep: "Policing algorithms is one of the great challenges that lie ahead for the tech industry"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy, cheap #IoT sensor data visualisation from @KotahiNet has been mostly missing. Fixing that https://t.co/4drAJNAZ0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: Mexico wants TPP without USA. Suspect NZ will jump on board and removing US-pushed distortions could turn out to be a good deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people need to read IGIS Cheryl Gwyn's concerns about new spying law https://t.co/ZCAZL9c5sU This isn't from the "loony left"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turned out to be really good- NZQA's CIO Lukasz Zawilski on their cloud computing journey https://t.co/2iHudSvfc1 Interesting insights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibrew Last time I saw that view the plane pulled up and landed at Blenheim as it was too windy to land. Today it looks perfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise the Kashmir story was so bad https://t.co/nqKhr0YkQz Sad this is happening in India]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My interview in the Listener- IoT has many benefits but privacy &amp; security need to be fixed https://t.co/bruPEAIHhY https://t.co/R8I1kxxzkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All go on the Diwali front https://t.co/95ZtBL4lc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMacEwan Exactly. Hope the irony doesn't go unnoticed even if it is clothed in centralised business vs bad others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMacEwan As a tech industry leader, whatever he says carries weight. Want to come back to this in time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bookmarking this https://t.co/hQphwtsI2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting at airport and being reminded every 5 minutes not to buy Samsung stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 AI better than human stories today in Stuff- predicting court judgements https://t.co/9q3UWUQQSc and Asian faces https://t.co/BUrWpQgaVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The conversation on immigration has to start from first principles." https://t.co/KbTkXbU5pU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshForde Here you go https://t.co/Pwb7Je6MCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes knowing the right questions to ask is the hardest thing https://t.co/As8wvoFyvF https://t.co/hkdBDXRWpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New word for today "brainjacking" https://t.co/lsEBsbR5aE Not what I thought- it's hijacking medical implants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post for people building or managing an IoT Product- a decision framework https://t.co/gFnYpqmuNT https://t.co/yIKGvUMlex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you look hard enough, spot our logo... https://t.co/KEXvKSPWRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist on journalism principles https://t.co/7kxufTHcCN Thoughtful. Principles good way to look at hard issues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of sales sophistication in NZ startups https://t.co/94ZJCejExw Given problem known for years, what are we going to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a couple of years, if the Q is who killed blockchain applications, the A will be patents https://t.co/zHdQni4Ngy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teh_aimee Yes but not sure the plane was convinced it was a good idea with all the alarms going off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe flying Sounds Air today wasn't the best choice. But we did land in Wlg so there's that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How mechanical engineering can't keep up with advances in electronics, making nuclear submarines redundant https://t.co/tFVxNzcReA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @dianecalvertnz for Onslow-Western Ward election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beta website from @KotahiNet  https://t.co/okQeHX0l4Z https://t.co/NFsBseGWdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So describes our times- arguing with a bot on Twitter https://t.co/GAT941Ipo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMacEwan And the Internet of Fridges spam, DDoS bots will be in abundance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA Nah, community comes together once a year to agree on what time it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there was an Internet Doomsday Clock, this just put it back 10 minutes https://t.co/PMnwa6H4Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good article on the energy, optimism and craziness of Ethereum. T-1 year  https://t.co/JTtoxWZTyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA No, but now I'm worried that it might have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Ecclestone Thanks, interesting. Can't happen fast enough for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard data of what we already know- no one reads terms of service online. 98% agreed to give their child as payment https://t.co/tQ79IRCkzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My debate takeaway: the choice Americans have is so stark how can anyone be 'undecided'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be a law against this https://t.co/04NIQI4Ewe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With governments, incompetency is usually more likely than grand conspiracy https://t.co/PDqOJTsW41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PR for our NZ efforts in @KotahiNet  from a global leader... priceless https://t.co/LxfsUQ9LIR https://t.co/nDO9qCsHF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen Good PR work... servers overloaded. Can't wait to find out my credit score, can't wait, can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish Amazon would make Echo global. Big market hole someone else will fill https://t.co/Ce3IGAaXHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Internet of Cows and tracking them https://t.co/f189G9CwyE Mesh + LoRaWAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This: "Like it or not, the New Zealand you think you know is not the whole truth." https://t.co/rANmC1ZCAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: Thinxtra "is now preparing for the second round of investment, with Series-B starting in October 2016" https://t.co/zp3Ou2K0ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandysimpson Congrats for the new CEO role]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KotahiNet extends LoRaWAN IoT network to Cook Islands https://t.co/OHSlIdUE8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to call my next visit to Raro a business expenditure https://t.co/N1ClZrDNQa https://t.co/WNYfeFwOWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwryan Ha. Now just need their AI to kick our response out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2016 and "A copy of the RFP response needs to also be sent on a memory stick by post/courier"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an IoT need that comes to mind in NZ- school lockdown in the US against attacks https://t.co/vl9VWtR0sP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's something quite direct about Americans (and their guns) https://t.co/g82ByqBIPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good read. Wardley Mapping sounds like a very useful tech tool https://t.co/fLwqqgo19a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read- Busting the billion-dollar myth: how to slash the cost of drug development https://t.co/EDeYfJNdrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was soooooo unexpected https://t.co/htzd1RDFqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grumble. Banks take blockchain, Ethereum, etc., "improve" it, patent https://t.co/OkAptTflnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: claiming ownership of photos you tweet https://t.co/vAjwapfbmS Attribution should now be easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still remember how Sabeer Bhatia selling Hotmail to Microsoft fuelled the dream of Indian entrepreneurs in 1998 https://t.co/waDDFDWYM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was in Hastings yesterday. Waiting staff offered tap water. Everyone had a good laugh at that. https://t.co/BijStAipLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National scale network rollouts need big $s or great partnerships. @KotahiNet  chose the latter https://t.co/vPSc0YgAzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting given Xiaomi's business strategy was considered legendary https://t.co/S1halMtDc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With reference to S2E1 of Mr Robot https://t.co/AxfPCq5MER https://t.co/LMRZ0UfuhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like most pro-privacy recommendations of Cullen &amp; Reddy left out of spy bill. Everything that helps FVEYs left in. Bad result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After your mobile phone, it'll be your car always spying on you https://t.co/x3uqriJGtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the Holy Grail of malware coding" https://t.co/BKt3ioHp3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the world record for simultaneously dancing robots? 1,007 https://t.co/KGcOXjPKn9 Set at a beer festival, obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupid: getting the OS to police (c) infringement https://t.co/ixnz3cxZVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people uneasy about self-driving cars adapt to autonomous surgical systems? Will we accept (lower) deaths from machines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is this what our Swiss buddies think NZ is- Switzerland with sheep? https://t.co/Mhg3qniMNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenging read: behavioural genetics https://t.co/CpP4O06i31 Genetics can influence (but not determine) so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT talk at #nzgather was based on sensor data as stream, APIs. More details at https://t.co/uugJsh8rKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdNZ Sure thing- I'm in mid-day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdNZ I'll be using lifelong learning as my blockchain example this afternoon. If you're there, keen to get your feedback after]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>