<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Transit Vancouver , please get your shit together ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong I'm gonna leave a jar in the lunchroom ... we can start a fundraising for marina to get Winston â¤ï¸ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong I found one while cleaning the floor and it was empty ... HAHAHAHHA god damn it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me it's not worth fightin for ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some old people are wayyyyy too talkative ... I thought I was annoying but nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forever grateful .... missing you, team metro ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hugging my teddy bear isn't the same as hugging @daofuu  ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deechieng remember when I asked y'all how to fix a washing machine .... by sending you a video of it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took a week off work to sleep and I'm still tired ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of blaming other people for your poor decisions in life, maybe you need to realize you're the problem, not people around you. ðŸ¤šðŸ¾ðŸ”ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it too early to want to punch someone in the face? Naw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" disappointment " should be some people's middle name....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate yellow. I also hate people that wear yellow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nails are so clean when I'm not working ......... ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wake up so early every morning just to send my friends memes ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to rekindle us , only to lose yourself .....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm in a good mood a 6 am on a Monday, you know I'll give a good week ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the whole entire sea bus is almost empty but this person just decided to sit right next to me .... ðŸ™„ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ˜­ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only I could turn off some emotions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sj1420 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™„ I hope you're not driving this week ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmaooo ME EVERY SINGLE DAY ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/ToALB6cLTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fall asleep at the wheel  we've got a million miles ahead of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew you were trouble when you walked in #shameonme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be nothin' without you ... #TheWeeknd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't control my face when people say something so god damn stupid..... #restingbitchface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate people that tell me to learn how to cook... ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong I'm actually watching it tomorrow, but not with you.. bye ðŸ‘‹ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klorenzanaa LOL I wish I could retweet this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Vans are Vans 'cause Tyler does not fuck with Giuseppe â˜ ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People that post photos of their feet makes me want to unfollow them on IG ... like why ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the hell spends hours trying to put a playlist for my overnight shift ... ugh where have you been all my life ? #suchabae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no place I'd rather be in this world ðŸŒŽ #VersaceOnTheFloor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gonna pretend I can still drink regular milk..... #lactose #byeicecream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a pho place is open until midnight ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday it will rain rain rain rainnnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goooood morning ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ https://t.co/gd0jAy0YSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring a seasonal bae. Please submit your CV with @sj1420]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless people that are willing to drive me all the way homeeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about to bounce back be-bounce bounce back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone thinks I'm shy.... #thatscute ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally loose my shit every time ' let me love you' comes on ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ‘‹ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klorenzanaa we miss YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorshipley20 HAHAHAHAHHAHA did they make you listen to their hold music ????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends are the https://t.co/XqePzaanEZ I literally love em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ines_Jovanovic literally same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally so jealous of my parents traveling around the world right now .... ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally woke up next to a box of chocolate ðŸ« #beautifulmorning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My place is literally trashed and it's 8 pm .... I love teenagers ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 hours of work makes me miss being a visual merchandiser ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you be there in the mornin', mornin', mornin' , mornin'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metrotown smells like fried rice every fucking day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong being on cash ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Itsjimmydee @klorenzanaa she said she wants more .... fries ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get so emotional when I hear " mark my words " by @justinbieber ðŸ˜­ so many FEELZZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must really love my friends that I agreed to go for yoga at 9 am on a Sunday ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regretting those days when I took living with my parents for granted... #missingmomscooking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High of loving my first tattoo ðŸ’•ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicananz when I was your manager all I got was customer complaints ... but I loved your savageness ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some dude just threw a piece of paper with his number it in at my head ..... that's super attractiveðŸ˜‘ #foreverunapproachable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We weren't necessarily put in the best position to make the best decisions. #purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People that annoy me on my day off are the worst.... ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong miss you too ðŸ’• better be thankful for me #Thanksgiving ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sj1420 I see that you kept all the jokes about yourself tho LOOL ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sj1420 where are your funny tweets ? I followed you for that reason ... ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless shaw open on the sea bus ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorshipley20 please tell me you've quit or else I'm sending you to rehab....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorshipley20 I wish I could  snap this moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is literally going on about ' five guys ' FOREVERRRRRRRRRR @taylorshipley20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to those  who are  snapping Flume live on their SC right now ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¾ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾ #thereinspirit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayraewong I sat on the steam bun.... I'm actually so upset ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day back to work and I got on the wrong train ..... ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klorenzanaa what do you mean? They always knew we were nuts ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way Robby looks at Jojo is everything. #BacheloretteFinale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My voice needs to come back ASAP... Slowly loosing my mind talking to myself inside my head ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear 90% of my date goes Towards Starbucks online orders.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if it's my phone that is slow or @TELUS 3G/LTE nðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorshipley20 damnnnnn Taylor. Back at it again with the Twitter account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally catching up on @Suits_USA #dayoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.... Also I've been home for 3 weeks and I still haven't unpacked âœŒðŸ¾ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klorenzanaa it's a shame I love food more than him #shhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smell of jet lag is calling my name ..... Fmlllll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've slept all day &amp; now it's time to sleep again... #whatamidoingwithmylife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hours left until my best friend arrives!!! #vacationmode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not even my birthday, also that's not my name so is this even for me? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/tb7Reuw6R8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving it here so much! Missed the warm weather! ðŸŒžðŸŒžðŸŒž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2Fab2bGhetto YAY I FOUND YOU LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a day off!!! ðŸ™ŒðŸ½ðŸ’†ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorEShipley we still follow each other on TwitterðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost forgot what's it's like to live in raincouver ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not having a voice SUCKS!!!! #sicklyfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know if I'm excited or sad to be back...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jet lag , you can stop now.... It's been almost a week ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh Nick #bachelorette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we take a moment to talk about Shawn's abs, please? ðŸ™ŠðŸ™ŠðŸ™ŠðŸ˜ #bachelorette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buttttttt I want breakfast in bed ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“â˜•ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually love this weather â˜ºï¸ #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food coma ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben H had me at sex Ed ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #bachelorette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the @BacheloretteABC makes me want to start dating again. Hahaha ha ha ha ahah lol #TeamKaitlyn #TheBachelorette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy freaaaaaakin Friday! It's my weekend offffff]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>