<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Open letter to the ISA Governing Council demanding stronger response to the Trump immigration policies. #ISA2017 https://t.co/ZXQt9ueUN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disruption. You live by the sword, you die by the sword... https://t.co/v5V6FfH1n7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, you can't say we weren't warned.... https://t.co/2yAMvjhxW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect if PM had come out early &amp; said "we don't agree with the policy" it prob would have sufficed. Now headlines are about being "meek"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBeresfordNZ @Corinhm yes &amp; the release from UK govt about dual nationals suggests rules changing/"being clarified" even as we speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't fathom why PM has not made any comment on Trump policies. He's going to have to say something. Turning an opportunity into a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful piece from leading American conservative defence intellectual @EliotACohen "It will not get better." https://t.co/JZwhJOdXUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 but after 1st crazy week of Trump admin, there's also larger question of what the "new normal" NZ-US relationship is going to look like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impt for @pmbillenglish to express NZ's strong commitment to non-discrimination, diversity etc, preferably to #DoubleTheQuota 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian Family Arrives in U.S. Just in Time, to Warmth and Relief, via @nytimes https://t.co/X1lMnIV8C8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure this is mentioned in Revelations. https://t.co/r1OYzwYuyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astonishing. https://t.co/VN6KOys0tJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gingrich confirming he's a woeful historian. What wld Maggie have thought abt cuddling up to Putin? Upping tariffs? https://t.co/uavBjCv8Wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd have thought Rolf Harris has enough problems... https://t.co/zJEudegzEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific piece, with a killer opening quotation from @leemakiyama https://t.co/WRmJHJppJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin sounds good. Travel well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @VicUniWgtn a big effort by small team, not just me, but many thanks. Really pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot on from @TheEconomist https://t.co/5zVSO6wIzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charles_finny @VicUniWgtn thanks Charles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm putting more and more of my Trump eggs in the Mattis basket. https://t.co/7qkIU5lHy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asssume Monica Crowley was handling this part of the transition planning.                                  -- h/t.… https://t.co/GVcpgI3SAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi Badge of Honour!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The bigness also hits because the - the size of it.The size."           And we thought '43 talked gibberish. https://t.co/GODKXaBi6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled that for 2nd year in a row Centre for Strategic Studies @VicUniWgtn ranked #2 think tank in SE Asia/Pacific https://t.co/kcJb3PcV8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaos. And this is their signature issue! Anyone who thinks the S.China Sea tough talk is nuanced new policy is nuts https://t.co/GU04HB7KV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s the single biggest simultaneous departure of institutional memory that anyone can remember &amp; that’s incredibl… https://t.co/uJr11dIWY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read. Think it's hard to follow Trump as an English speaker? Pity the translator. (What's Chinese for bigly?) https://t.co/RD2YQ0tsGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rarahsobson There is a place on the road into Matakana https://t.co/jpOY5MFkjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great opportunity to work with the team at the Oz High Commission. And happy Australia Day to them! https://t.co/S0RH5ZxaPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good read. Apart from issue of getting to the front of queue, US bilateral would surely have worse terms for NZ o… https://t.co/lMsDuKZuKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will be a president for everyone". Notable @realDonaldTrump had a teleprompter at DHS talk: try to get him back to more inclusive message]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leongrice Thanks. I'd be really interested to see them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec is pure word salad on voter fraud investigation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leongrice @RANDCorporation Thanks. I would have thought Northeast Asia would be a mile ahead in that respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon readout of US SecDef General Mattis' phone call with NZ counterpart Gerry Brownlee. https://t.co/FWcWBtMVxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leongrice @RANDCorporation "SEAsia most militarized region in world"???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin sorry comrade. Didn't see it or would've tipped my hat. Great minds! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On day US shuns TPP, PLA Col tells #FullertonForum China's vision is new regional security framework advanced in parallel to reg econ f'work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Col. Penkin asked by @ASPI_org Peter Jennings about DNC hack. Says "all accusations must have evidence.. [without that] it is fake news.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian speaker Col. Penkin warns abt risk of #cyber arms race &amp; imptce of strategic restraint at #FullertonForum A… https://t.co/sktK33yaek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As Maya Angelou said, when someone shows you who they are, believe them the first time." A very good read from… https://t.co/IhC5lTYe3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still suggests to me what @realRWTillerson said is not policy. @PressSec shld have expected question on this. Resul… https://t.co/eQxtFLGIZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysia Def Min @HishammuddinH2O keynote to #FullertonForum yesterday (my question to him about Rohingya at 50') https://t.co/v2kWrUaRJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Saying you’re ‘buying a house in New Zealand’ is kind of a wink, wink, say no more" Doomsday prep for US ultra-rich https://t.co/E2r6wK7MAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The text is hilarious. https://t.co/RB48POQFoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't discount that  @PressSec just doesn't know what he's talking about. Urgent need to clarify this. https://t.co/iPW6vKwsWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump determined to slash federal spending on web design &amp; logos by the looks of things https://t.co/eW6xEb4y3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorenzana warns outside states not to use ASEAN as a proxy, from last night's special address to #FullertonForum https://t.co/IvU8WHQX1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One of the most striking features of the early Trump administration has been its political uses of lying." Why lie? https://t.co/fdrGsWXAJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TPP RIP (with the US at least). https://t.co/fRuin51AeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorenzana recommends @IISS include theme related to ASEAN in the world as one of topics for Shangri La Dialogue 2017 to mark #ASEAN at 50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HishammuddinH2O says "need for issue driven subregional security initiatives. Stimes more productive to work via focused caucus of #ASEAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing cyber and new technology threats @HishammuddinH2O says fake news erodes public harmony &amp; damages confidence in institutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysia Defence Minister @HishammuddinH2O giving keynote at 2017 #FullertonForum. Taking aim at "pseudo-nationalis… https://t.co/EIFTK3uaDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin she will doubtless roll it in glitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama Presidential Library website now live https://t.co/19YfGzO9Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If partners refuse a reneg that gives US workers "a fair deal, then the President will give notice of the US’ intent to withdraw from NAFTA"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House website statement on America First Foreign Policy, w ref to withdrawing from #TPP &amp; renegotiating NAFTA. https://t.co/WchPdTfwdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From this day forward it's only going to be America first."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think there's any doubt @potus Trump wrote this speech himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haere ra e hoa @ambmarkgilbert Loved your pix from distant parts of New Zealand &amp; your mihi really raised the bar. Will take some beating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good review of Obama legacy tho' I'd be less harsh on his foreign pol. Less taking middle path &amp; more recognition o… https://t.co/4EkAi6ooSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oiwoods Already happening &amp; more than just defence ties. Notable @pmbillenglish stopped in SIN on return from Europe. Many common interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZDF to send Naval Task Group to take part in FPDA Ex-Bersama Shield &amp; Singapore International Naval Review in April https://t.co/GfTtiBOESO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ &amp; Singapore developing closer defence relations; including inauguration of annual ministerial meeting. https://t.co/GfTtiBOESO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@pmbillenglish says New Zealand will express "significant disappointment" to Japan about whaling in southern ocean. https://t.co/bI1RMkoZsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't seen any similar statements from @maggiebarrynz or anyone else in the NZ govt. Or did I miss something? https://t.co/KCFaKXrhcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some wise words from my @VicUniWgtn colleague @JasonA_Young in this piece on Trump, Beijing &amp; the One-China policy https://t.co/zwrHgeIkjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump calls NATO "obsolete" in interview with @BILD https://t.co/oHpB1GtG0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible all the attention on @realDonaldTrump 's small hands was a diversion away from his genuinely tiny ba… https://t.co/lUqopcTVrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrodsky FAKE NEWS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jljzen yes I already fessed up on Facebook. The ref to Nov5 gunpowder plot did have me wondering. FAKE NEWS! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well worth a read.  https://t.co/klcuLjlquk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reckless AND counter-productive strategy. https://t.co/B6ECGGEMfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sensible piece from @ashleytownshend https://t.co/d4db1FHdgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More details about collapse of big exporter of infant formula to China. https://t.co/KSltxIPSYV https://t.co/EdVtrMTlCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner tonight: spaghetti and tuatua, eaten less than 20m from the beach (and @SOHOWINECO 'Stella' Sauvignon Blanc). https://t.co/a6q0isU9Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what it's like to read that incoming admin wants to confront your biggest trade partner &amp; plans to build new… https://t.co/O1eSPv6X4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team "may not have fully thought through the risks of any new US military or trade pressure on China"  https://t.co/WB1SfF2Sy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the numbers: "Trump will be the most unpopular president on his Inauguration Day in the history of polling"  https://t.co/k8IEhWHtNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful collation of Mattis' answers to Senate questions... https://t.co/MLsBbwiioA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin that is correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin I agree, they're not quite the same, but Trump still humiliated him. Looks like he's dining on a large plate of dead rat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The exact ignominious moments they struck their respective deals with the orange devil..."  https://t.co/F1c7VQmiuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FFF182 ha! let's hope it was a "misspoke". The alternative is much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear news abt Graham Taylor. Huge manager for Villa &amp; I also saw his Watford team play the All Whites at Athletic Park in 1982.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given T-Rex hadn't even raised Russia with Trump, hardly surprising they didn't debate details of South China Sea https://t.co/hUSbggxGS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hectic game of Friday night touch rugby on the beach at Whangapoua. https://t.co/x3frMag5LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The claim they "changed course" to embrace RCEP is nonsense. https://t.co/vUa4wOhurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrAndrewButcher glad to hear it (but sorry you're stuck inside). Happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson’s warning that US wld block China’s SCS access "shocked and bewildered lawmakers &amp; diplomats across Asia" https://t.co/DxHbiDO0gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If true, US has decided to risk war w China over "access" to islands &amp; talked of prev war w NK-all b4 Inauguration https://t.co/XajWMABwtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day was going so well... https://t.co/wUmjezYfaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ @pmbillenglish meeting with @NATO SecGen Stoltenberg. Transcript omits PM's remarks (why?) but can watch in video https://t.co/5oLoFixNmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the dirty work Rudy did for Trump and he gets a job that sounds like a glorified events manager. https://t.co/zwY8bkvue4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good read on Caroline Kennedy's term as the first woman to serve as US Ambassador to Japan. https://t.co/jXTnHs6JQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonus points to Moby &amp; Charlotte Church &gt;&gt; Who Is Performing at Trump’s Inauguration? A Shortlist - New York Times https://t.co/DGn0fFMueA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least an honest Trump nominee... https://t.co/8OxEBm9dXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US intell officials "expressed despair at the election of Trump during recent meeting w. their Israeli counterparts" https://t.co/bDxMBAezki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mproctornz "We're going to have to send China a clear signal...your access to those [artificial] islands also is not going to be allowed."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>