<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraMPSI Walk if you gotta walk buddy. You come first. Fuck everybody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RummHammm Mine was always "just drawing".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kirrrsty This is gonna make the valentine thing kinda weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Levi_McK Ah not too bad. You'd probably get it on PS3 or PS4 digital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty Yeah I hate Randy Orton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebeccahLouise Michelle 2020 with Springsteen as VP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon now. C'mon. https://t.co/2Ayf3KnN2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the poster was brilliant. https://t.co/0zHlqUaehA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soz kids but there'll never be a better Royal Rumble than in 2000 when Kane murdered everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want a pot of tea, a fire and some Simpsons Hit and Run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RummHammm I seeee. Great idea if it's done right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RummHammm How does mental health soc work? There wasn't one when I was doing my undergrad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichStanton Such a tragically underrated game. I'll never stop being annoyed that they won't run further with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(And that's okay)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(And I probably never will)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I didn't watch the Stranger Things speech)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen *Starts questioning how many times I've been rejected for being a non-smoker*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back as a full animator (as opposed to FX) for a little bit. Remarkable how quickly I get rusty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably not though. Their competitive advantage definitely is in the arcade. Foolish to try compete on a less advantageous market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I've barely seen it but it's CLEARLY framed around Kojima's vision for Silent Hills. I wonder if Konami have any regrets on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested to see how Konami are interpreting the numbers that Capcom are getting with Resi 7.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is very much Monday. No mistaking it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmzFool Innnteresting. I'll have to take a look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmzFool The Final Girls eh? Is it a horror?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmzFool I haven't even seen the trailer yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmzFool It was so well shot I was astounded. He's so impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw John Wick today. Such an enjoyable flick. Pure popcorn. That Keanu lad looks younger at 53 than I do at twenty seven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molly_finn_ I'll open up a whole new world of stews to you. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elparkojr Hahah I'll do a regular one the next time I have a day off. This is "Notion Stew".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If badly produced cooking stories are your jam. https://t.co/tYNhzlrZIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharkie__xo The worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyandcolour Why the scarf hate though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt. You were awesome. https://t.co/oQws3it8yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evadiminutive I'd go short, judging on these photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyandcolour That hurts, *squints* "Amy".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyandcolour I feel like I don't even know you any more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyandcolour You're gonna need to unfollow me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fokellh I'm nothing if not selfless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's fine like, I don't need to eat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalnutSoap God's work is what you're doing Paul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick, someone encourage me to spend a hundred and fifty euro on another coat in January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just made a breakthrough about my own mental health and it's not even ten o'clock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bed_Forever_ I can't see through metal, Kent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that much of a Resi fan but I'm absolutely raging I can't play the new one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmzFool Here's a polar bear cub. https://t.co/GNWICUTRrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only six months to E3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a black leather jacket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winchestwhore How do you wanna die? Can we do it in Swords? Can we have a party. You came into my life in a party, it's only fitting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winchestwhore Deal. But you have to watch me eat it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to save this as some sort of shortcut. https://t.co/HaJKUImuUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffwagenheim Oh 100% genuine, and very admirable. Just works well with her new post-loss image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not be commanded,
I will not be controlled, https://t.co/TnkZBQzCMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmmm. Might take an hour on Sunday off and bake something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-defeat face-turn by Rousey perhaps? Good to see. https://t.co/nL4EQ8BQf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmmm, wonder if this is connected with Sony's Spider-Man project? https://t.co/lGZbGA8dzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verdygood Totally agree. Gorgeous city, filled with absolute bellends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My *perfect* Sennheiser HD25s were stolen last summer and I'm still bitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions I'm hoping to spontaneously combust some time around late February.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions On the plus side you don't need to worry about things like rent in six months. We'll all be dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen That's totally vegan too. Get on that cashew butter. It'll rock your socks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions Yep. Just like all the nationalist groups in the UK. Racism is being validated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen Aye it's literally 100% cashew nuts. I made this with it. https://t.co/pFGPeA4aqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen Well this is like peanut butter but much creamier. You can make fudge with it and everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen Can get it in Supervalu. Will change your life. Goes great with ice cream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions Yep. Crazy that people will stand in front of a live broadcast and be like "yep, Nazi".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darthellen Give cashew butter a go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions Yeah I wouldn't be able at all. It's also gonna be a lightning rod for dickheads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adamissions Only worked out what it is today. Looks exhausting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And let's be clear. A dude saying "H*tler did nothing wrong" is a Nazi. There is no ambiguity there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasontammemagi I think current political climates (both US/UK) are doing a lot to enable this and disregard history. Very worrying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasontammemagi My thoughts exactly. Like, there's no more hiding. It's like the Twitter eggs have hatched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Assaulting a man with divergent political opinions"

Assaulting a Nazi, you mean? 

https://t.co/bUp8hlmmVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017, lads. What are ye at? https://t.co/otGibmEKll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd murder any one of you for Bunsen right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done. Done. On the the next one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man will be in history books. https://t.co/OYqG70beFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molly_finn_ *Crosses fingers*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilverStGroud Happy Birthday Stacy. Hope it's really fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see they're letting interns make posters now. https://t.co/dg9ZO8pkJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty Yeah. Let's just say I'm readying the nukes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty You hold the boom no? Who cares anyway you're bad at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty @verdygood Yeah climb off Ric Flair's dick and say that again you child-faced glorified mic-stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verdygood @WMWhitty I'm sorry you got dragged into this. Kid can't fight his own battles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty Go climb a wall you petrol station culchie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty @verdygood Calling in reinforcements are we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty I'd eat you alive, jobber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WMWhitty Me and you kid. Me and you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetbroaders That looks great man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanCoughlan Aye get them healthy fats in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanCoughlan Well up until now I've been eating the same volume of food but junk so maybe my body has caught up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanCoughlan Possibly! I think it might just be a complete lack of energy use. Like I'm at a desk ALL day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanCoughlan Mainly chicken breast, small amount of potato, few veg. So I'd say 50% protein 30% carb 20% fat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I only ate about five hundred calories today and I'm not hungry. That's a bit odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karolinecelly I know I really would have thought you'd get in there faster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not nearly enough trolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two more minutes and then we're deleting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess that would come down to your definition of art. But I'd be inclined to agree. https://t.co/8Igfu9uOD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why use an anonymous service to reach out to friends? — You can get honesty out of people if they're anonym... https://t.co/rvmfNeRM0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you lick McGregor's post fight armpits for mo... — How much? https://t.co/MZFEQBNcAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the weight of the beard count as exercise? — If it does then I've budgeted my calories all wrong... https://t.co/4ueKIcPOAv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>