<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger ereaders are also permitted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona in Liverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton v SC trilogy by summer hopefully ðŸ‘ŠðŸ‘Š great fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson I think Matip has joined him too ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson you need to attend klopps positivity classes though it'll be tough for him to put a positive spin on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson I had to go to the only country in the world that doesn't like football to give my children a chance ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeefandLobster @OliverDunne looks savage, can't believe it's calorie free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona you mean dog food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson don't u hate being right all the time ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona EOL 9 out of 10 min]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ole_LFC ending our unbeaten home record with a bang ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona @OliverDunne does it come with its own brown paper bag, peasant drink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona if both show up they'll hit that. My fear though is someone (falcons) wet their pants on the big stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona probably secured the nomination ðŸ’¦ðŸ’¦ðŸ’¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona @endabolger we're given free copies of Annie. One of the perks ðŸ˜‰ ok the only perk..... ok it's not a perk ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ at least I'm not bald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair no reason why it can't finish high unless the day gets to one of the teams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair packers cowboys was the only close one. Hopefully the final isn't one way traffic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair like a house of cards now ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair game set and match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair yeah home decisions are great, it's like watching Utd ðŸ˜bell is a huge huge loss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair u could throw in overall at this stage. Very little being given away for free here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger only soundtrack album I ever bought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chippie1974 they've been on such a good run I thought this'd be a close one. Dallas game taking its toll.patriots could do the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The packers couldn't catch a cold, game over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yay_yee @Sidhu6_ have to agree with you josh, Rory would take it to the mat with Daley. MVP would be a great stand up clash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona they're looking pretty pretty good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona who you fancy for the final next week ðŸˆðŸˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBNLukeThomas @HiImHenry WWE watch out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson @DarwinsPitbuII @idriselba @SkyIreland rumour has ticketmaster are involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAmicks he wasn't going to go asleep the way it was on him, just a broken neck or jaw instead ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RJcliffordMMA a neck crank by a gorilla can do the trick though especially while he was still fresh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson should do, in about 4 yrs or when the world ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona some fine jumping from a standing start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona Jesus will save the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger email will not exist in 2021]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger you'll need to fake your birthcert ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII @Will_E_Wilson in saying that we won't win shit but it's nice to keep an interest come may unlike Arsenal come march ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII @Will_E_Wilson no other club have suffered the amount of injuries,can he can't he play BS pool have &amp; we're still in the mix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII @Will_E_Wilson good to blood the youngsters to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson onwards and upwards will ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimKennedyMMA very well said, best of luck in all your future endeavours. You gave us plenty of good fights ðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII who knows, they must've something. Mass genocide perhaps ......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII at his club. Seems like Cameroon are being right cunts, if he doesn't want to play, move on and pick someone who does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII you're right, too much â˜€ï¸ðŸ˜Ž. But when we did actually want 'Stephen' at intl level and he refused why didn't we screw him up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the difference between Matip for Cameroon and Ireland for Ireland? There was never a mention of Ireland being banned from club footie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeyGartlan he'll have to if he wants to win a game ðŸ˜‚ he needs to go after Andy Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair they must have read your tweet ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianStann looks like an up surge in tv sales in Dallas tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennyflorian some strength and technique is those arms ðŸ’ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodgers is a beast ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona some catch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona packers goin to win it here with a no pressure kick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona yeah real snooze fest ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona and back ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona long way to go yet but a nice brace there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game on #CowboysPackers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona good fresh airing there by butsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yay_yee @SBNLukeThomas cowboys packers is getting interesting though ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona Packers need a snow storm to hit in the next min ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interception ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a game winner there #CowboysPackers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona @ilcapitano7 they needed that, keeps this game interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona @ilcapitano7 poor child, never had a chance born into that household]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys there for the taking. Packers looking good ðŸˆðŸˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireofthekop and when he plays centrally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf are pool playing at, pub league football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair don't see it changing today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No way back for the Texans now. A good honest beating dished out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani @SBNLukeThomas do you reckon there's any chance Dana announced floyd mcg to bump Hunt down the headlines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona child services are en route]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeyGartlan @ConorEmerson @FMcDyes @DarwinsPitbuII SPLITS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona but back then you'd to kill for a souvenir, to get a piece of Dave gahans wife beater when he threw it into d crowd ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona @TicketmasterIre what a bargain, a souvenir to remember a wonderful event by. They should roll that out across other gigs ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson Utd game is huge, if we play like that they'll demolish us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson we've a decent first team but a shallow squad. Matip is a big loss as well as mane and we don't have the quality to step in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FMcDyes @ConorEmerson @DarwinsPitbuII 99 of them goals were against the bottom 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson it's a marathon not a sprint ðŸ˜¬ can't play much worse than that again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson @joeyGartlan just as long as it's not too near the post then it's ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeyGartlan it's great, we might even get to the knockout stages now if we really practice our peno's. New rule to 'No blemmers allowed ']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona goes without saying at this stage. Not even the Chinese could afford Hendo â¤ï¸ï¸â¤ï¸ï¸â¤ï¸ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ole_LFC some money grab by FIFA, I thought the euros had been watered down too much, this is taking it to the next level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAFighting @arielhelwani CF in for one ugly beating ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ole_LFC and still not qualifying ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona aspas should be in the running for the award next year ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danow247 an ugly beating, GB getting stronger and stronger with each game.looking good,i didn't think I'd see that after the start they had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danow247 they need to TD soon or this game is over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBNLukeThomas unlike the fighters after nearly 20 yrs commentating on the sport he never improved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danow247 not looking good for them alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair coming on strong now. They love the cold ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona sure it will, chin up. Sorry I meant finsup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squawka not bad for a fatty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins = bigger chokers than Arsenal or Spurs. #embarassing #publeague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coloconnor @DarwinsPitbuII I thought it was decent. Defo innocent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona early doors but wuuuhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ole_LFC better to get the shit ones out of the system in the fa cup than the league. Reminded me of the Burnley game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarwinsPitbuII he speaks damn fine Italian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_MacIomhair @BG_Iona do u reckon the steelers will do it? Maybe if tannehill was playingðŸ˜‚ajayi or bell will decide this. Close game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BG_Iona Texans, shitehawks, ðŸ¬ðŸ¬ and the giants this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeyGartlan @DarwinsPitbuII won't somebody please think of the children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_E_Wilson well when they manage reading &amp;hull and the likes it makes it that bit tougher.once giggs gets the chelski job it'll changeðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>