<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews back and forth trying to drag this time together out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews If only she could bring herself to tell him how she felt. That he made her feel alive and loved. Slowly she rocked her hips —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews down on him. "Hold me here...like this."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews A shudder escaped her lips and she moved to sit within his lap. Both legs wrapped around his waist as she sank herself back—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews At this point she was pure putty in his hands. "Sit...sit up babe. Please."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews beautiful once more and then kissed him with a deep passion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Again she rose up to greet his body with her own, a gasp falling from her lips. She held the back of his neck, called him—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews time they connected it brought them closer together, on a deeper note as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews A gasping moan fell from her lips. Her hips began to slowly rise and fall in time with his thrusts. She swore each and every—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews That kiss made her moan into it. Her body surged up against his, hands moving to grip his bum as their speed increased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews slightly. The look of pleasure was evident on her face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews With a smile Matilda reached up and stroked her finger down his nose.She even licked her lower lip and bit down on it —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews brush hair from his eyes and gently kissed at his neck and lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews The slow steady thrusts were exactly what she wanted from him. There was no need to rush things. She even reached up to —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Mhm..." She just whimpered out against his lips and relaxed as best she could. Still her hands roamed his back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews This time the slow thrust of his hips and the new sensation caused her to grip his hair in a fist and moan out "Nngh Nathan."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews a pause before she reached between them to align him:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Needless to say it turned her on even more when he swore. Maybe because he didn't seem the type who normally did. There was—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews His groan made a shiver run up her spine. She stopped at the curve of his neck to suckle on slightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews his hips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Her nose drug across his sharp jawline as gentle kisses pressed to his neck. Meanwhile her knees came up to press against —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Shh." She just leans up to peck his lips and scoots over just a tad for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Curious, she couldn't help but glance down at the sight with a slight bite to her lip. "Bloody hell Nate, you're gorgeous."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Her breathing became laboured, chest heaving slightly as her body curved up towards every kiss placed upon it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Right now all she was trying to do was to clear her mind and focus completely on him. His sweet kisses caused low soft moans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Already she laid there with her eyes half open merely enjoying his soft lips on her skin. Lazy shapes were etched between—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews She laid back with ease and placed her hands on his shoulders in the process to bring him closer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews little second of this experience,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Fingers tangled themselves in his mess of hair and yet their pace was slow and passion fuelled. She wished to savour every—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews this small act of fondness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews All of it was felt. That storm that she always felt she carried inside was calm for a change which only drove her to deepen—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews drove her lips to part this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews She couldn't help but melt in his hands. With him it was like she mattered, as if she was worth something again. That's what—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Even though she was technically naked, she still ended up blushing and looking away as if she was shy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Honesty was in her face. Honesty and hope and a sense of adoration for him. "Yeah? I don't want to make you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews the end of her sentence. It had honestly been since she was with Liam since that happened. Everything else was just fucking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews She utterly avoided eye contact even though she faced him. "Could we...could we make love?" Her brows pulled together near —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Can...can I ask you something?" She nibbled on her lower lip and messed with her own hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Another kiss went to his lips and her fingers stroked a bit of his hair behind his ear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews That reassurance made her feel at ease now, like a weight had been lifted off her shoulders. "Thank you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerInASuit The warmth felt nice but she still didn't leave Carson's side. Rather her thumb stroked his as they moved through the store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Her forehead nudged against his and her nose nuzzled his with a soft smile. "I promise to try my best."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda pulled back once again to look at him. "I really like you Nate...very very much."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda had been far too trusting in the past to jump straight into this all now, but she wanted him close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews It seemed to be a silent agreement between the two, that they both were lost in complete adoration for the other. But —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews There was no way she was ever going to tire of this with him. It just seemed far too meant to be as she settled between—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews There went that flutter inside her chest again. She ended up cupping his cheek, thumb brushing over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones "Zed is my mini me. It's utterly scary at times. If it wasn't for the age difference..." Tilly laughs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Mhm. Your lips definitely are yes." With a flash of a grin she rested her lips on the curve of his shoulder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda gave a soft laugh before composing herself once more. "I want you terribly Nathan."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Her lips worked back up his neck and to his ear. Teeth clamped on his earlobe to tug gently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews An index finger pressed to his lips and she kissed down from his neck to his shoulder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Rather have you drive me mad..." She mumbles again and nuzzles her nose against his neck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews With a gasping moan she pulled back just enough to whisper and look him in the eyes. "You drive me crazy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews This time she was the one that pushed him back, laying atop him as they kissed again. The taste on his lips made her moan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews through her hair. All of a sudden Matilda was sitting up and moving over to kiss him, to taste herself on his lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda's skin prickled entirely, body writhing in pleasure as her hands stroked from her hips up to her breasts then —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews from the walls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews That was all she needed. Hands clawed at the bedsheets as her body quivered and various curses and shouts of his name echoed—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews knew that at any moment now he'd undo her completely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "N-Nate~." Tilly moaned out again, her hand falling from his hair and back onto the bed. Even if she wanted this to last she—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Though there was still a slight struggle of her hips as she gave a tug to his hair. Nate was definitely good at this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Shit..." She breathed out with a lift of her back from the bed. Even her fingers ended up in his hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Right now she was completely at his mercy, hands above her head as gentle praises slipped from her lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Once his lips met their mark there was a sharp breathy intake and her body fell back once more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews She propped herself up on an elbow to look down at him. "You're so fucking hot."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Though her mouth was hanging open like she was going to say something, but the kiss to her thigh just caused another moan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews By this point her eyes are locked on his and she's nibbling her lower lip. "If you stop there I'm going to cry."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Both brows lifted in surprise at this. But rather than say anything about it she merely moaned 'Nathan' out in a whisper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones whinging when you read to him, so he's definitely mine and wasn't switched at the hospital."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones "Zed is in that stage of thinking everything is hers and tried to colour the walls of her room in. Daniel will only stop —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda lifted her right hand up in order to push her fingers into his hair. She wanted him now more than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews That moan made her shiver and groan. But she still lifted her hips up once more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Her leg went around him and down across his bum, ankle tucked under his leg. Unable to help it her hips rolled upwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Heart beating faster, her hands rested on his waist, lips and tongue working with his.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews All Matilda could do was smile. Smile and lean back in for a desperate kiss while she placed his hand upon her breast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Swear I could kiss you for the rest of my life and be completely happy with that choice."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews knew that he was a little broken too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews When Matilda did pull away it was with a kind smile on her lips. To her he was radiant and utterly beautiful even if she —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones "Oh we will!" She just laughs and walks to the living room petting Iago's ears in the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews settled on his thigh as she pressed into the kiss more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda could stay like this forever. Just the two of them in a world of silence and books, sharing sweet kisses. Her hand —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones "Ah there you are. My one true love." The tabby is picked up and cradled to Tilly's chest. "Yes tea and stories!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones me two kids that are a handful each."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones She chortles slightly. "Really? I must hear these stories. I question Tom's sanity everyday. I mean he married me and gave—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuizzicalJones "Oh shush it you." Tilly pecks her sisters cheek and steps inside to find Iago. "What kind of strange things?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerInASuit close to his side for warmth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerInASuit Tilly laces their fingers together as they cross. Luckily Top Shop wasn't that far from the tube station. Still she kept —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Fuck, you're so..." There isn't even a word for her to say. Rather a light kiss went to his lips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews ran down his chest. "Amazing..." She whispered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews "Mhm..." Matilda's chest rose and fell heavily as she caught her breath. Even her nose nuzzled against his whilst fingers —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews to her chest as she poured herself into him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews down that could possibly provide her happy ending. That thought just fuelled her side of the kiss more, holding him close —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews If this day never ended she'd be perfectly happy. Here she was, some lost wanderer that somehow found the right path to go —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews was real and not a dream. If she didn't know better she'd say she was falling hard for him right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews moment they shared going between them. Both hands fell to his chest. He felt so warm to her, so alive and here with her. It —]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews Matilda moved slightly. Just a simple shift in position to where she was sitting up yet leaning in towards him to keep this—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews of his neck to hold him close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews cold damp flame would flicker. This was different and scary but so promising and beautiful. 

Her fingers moved to the back—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorMathews A kiss was all she needed as a reply. She kissed him with a new fire that had started back up inside of her. No longer that —]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>