<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck is synergy anyways? But twitter get your shit together. Or not. That way i don't end up broke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin dougal did a dance so I guess so? I was reading and having tea so I was elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay twitter adds are weird... I am getting fertility adds (stop.it.) and synergy ones.
What. The. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching two guys play fifa as I sip tea. I feel like I am observing some weird ritual. Hell one asked me to applaud a goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a reboot button? Restore factory settings? https://t.co/qSfKBYd6GE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They fit him better than me.
#housemateshenanigans https://t.co/uMBhU1Tfiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you. This is wonderful. Beautifully written. #repealthe8th https://t.co/aQCDfoDdT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone asked me about an unplanned pregancy and I joked about travelling. That is all it should be. A joke. #repealthe8th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drg1985 nice! One of my housemates was very confused on opening the cupboard. (He's new)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fucking love this book. (Yes I hated Romeo and Juliet. Still do.) https://t.co/DDh0KzrVAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn nessa carey. It is SO interesting! Highly recommend. And i am only on chapter three!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn oh thanks! I am currently taking a break from that for The epigenetics revolution. So fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn I am proud of that. You can get your very own UNT mug from firebox. Hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*childish giggle* https://t.co/uCwIMSnQfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irishsmurf i may need to borrow that small book of yours... https://t.co/FqkQPcxbOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 28th will be a good birthday. Will be enjoying the heck out of #HamiltonLDN booyah! https://t.co/EekrZPj08f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irishsmurf i bought two for my birthday... i am weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irishsmurf yeah well i have cursed child this year so i am not as bothered. Enjoy though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irishsmurf i could have gotten some for 200 pounds but eeeeeh no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth. Being uninformed must be so relaxing. I am just a cauldron of fear and rage right now. https://t.co/ydMvv1y5rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awesome. I love it so much. https://t.co/ovvB7d4JcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a leader. Not my bloody taoiseach. https://t.co/XEzRlUTM51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithigorman maybe a bunch of women standing at the gates asking where their rights are? He would run like the wind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday I will have these WITH me when I buy books. Someday. https://t.co/YBRFy4gB8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin anyone irish who bitches about immigrants can fuck right off as far as I'm concerned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin my favourite ed byrne joke "we have been populating the globe since we figured out how to get into a boat"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophswhynot heck I was looking up masters in it. And I ain't ready for that. But argh. https://t.co/MoLXlKBnkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To distract myself from the shitshow outside I have immersed myself in science. Reading science listening to it... I love it so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin accurate. But I do want to take that violin and start swinging...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin first we must out Kenny. Cause he is a wimp focused only on not rocking the boat. THERE'S A MASSIVE LEAK YOU PRICK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why i was avoiding twitter today. The world has actually made TINDER seem like a better option. https://t.co/MKYVuGUKzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointed but not surprised. Damn you Kenny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless he plans to punch him in the face... it really isn't. Have a backbone and LEAD for once. It's your JOB after… https://t.co/OdwIvXfPSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this guy. *sniffles* https://t.co/iDrL6KaJuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophswhynot with a careful eye on the leaders of this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yeah when I saw "stick it to the Man." I mean it. I will be sticking to the Man. And anyone who stands by him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophswhynot and it isn't hyperbole. It is legitimate concern for the state of our world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I live in a time where everyone I am friends with is just turning to one another and saying "revolution?" "Yeah"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was the mini boss. 2017 is the.big battle.

2018 you had better not be the sneaky "actual" final boss.
I am wa… https://t.co/ti55y0zU3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorsqueaks make it a double.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day another shittier injustice. Why do I never have emergency alcohol??? A rookie mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin still horrible though https://t.co/YlS06XD1wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin I just looked at the signs disgusted. This time so bloody stillbirths so they are getting better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-choice by the gpo. Why do I ONLY have my badges on!?? Ah well best I avoid them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin "stupid and dangerous feminist propaganda" someone pass me a bucket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 50% of adult male sheep are straight. Podcasts may ruin me for normal conversation. "HERE ARE MY FAV FACTS FROM THIS WEEK. OOOOOO"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorsqueaks firebox. Got mine on sale but you should so buy it... here https://t.co/iiAqsUUr6d it is AMAZING. Will be christening soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitestNoise i just need a science one to complete the set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitestNoise I feel the really capture a lot of my personality. The nerdy dork side and the SMASH THE PATRIARCHY side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear some people get cRaZy on Friday nights. I just flipped my mattress.

This. Is. Living. #flop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also just saw Drumpfs tweets about vaccinations.
SO MUCH NO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda Kenny was just a recommended account for me to follow.

No.
No.
NO NO NO NO NO. https://t.co/fSxOv2MFIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vadar's March is just BLARING in my head constantly. Argh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why must we gender glasses?? I think i could pull off these quite nicely! Stop gendering this shit. https://t.co/TA5yidOcCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human penis is in fact extremely dull" damn this is sooo good! https://t.co/mdOx7zm3xH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I still need more mugs. But these are awesome. https://t.co/sI6l30dT7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am right there with you. Also blame online dating. Tinder is destroying us. And we know it. https://t.co/IBirVLFoGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorobotic aka I DO NOT UNDERSTAND THIS DATING THING. Some lads have issues with my loud liberal dorkiness. Looooosers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorobotic someone gave me the eye yesterday on the bus. I tripped out in surprise. Online dating makes things tricky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorobotic oh god I feel so old now... and I am going to use this phrase UNIRONICALLY. Kids these days...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent a good five minutes ranting about "motherfucking folates" my job is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today when I seem to be at my clumsiest is not the day for tomato soup... when I am wearing my sole white shirt. Oh no. #ohnooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitestNoise is this a joke? Please say yes otherwise my head may explode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalwayForLife @CoraSherlock "empower" women by restricting their options?? How does that make any sense??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorobotic so good!! His articles are brilliant. I wish I could write like that!... I hear practice helps...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ideal date. Ha https://t.co/JZ628vcvp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorobotic there really isn't. But I have to finish Ben Goldacre's "I think you'll find it's more complicated than that." So much science...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is ridiculous how excited I am to read a book about epigenetics. #nerdporn #talksciencetome https://t.co/UjcO6G2hrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMurphy12150 we have had this chat Emma. The Nazis banned abortion. Please stop using inflammatory information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised that me sitting here with three books, the dorkiest bag ever and having plans for this evening is all 16 year old me wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god facebook is at this story business too. No. Damn social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True. And yet... *swipe* *swipe* https://t.co/i8ut4bbiFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drg1985 just adding insult to injury really. #honestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one should have this much influence on healthcare mandates. Ffs. https://t.co/fDOPbL5TiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant. Well worth a read. Speaking as a "snowflake" and all. https://t.co/9Ya1NcLqzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uuuuh YES. Finally some good news! https://t.co/l9reqFiYvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am getting fertility treatment adds??? Twitter STOP THAT RIGHT NOW. I am happy with an empty uterus. Very much so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophswhynot he is dancing now. I really do not get this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My housemate is yelling at fifa 2017... I really don't get soccer or games about it. So much confusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldenactuality this is my pick. You got #badscience!?? I will CRUSH YOU! Ha. https://t.co/YxxoGl1Q72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot describe the ridiculousness of this packaging. LOOK AT HOW INSANE THIS IS!??? https://t.co/Bqq4UwXOyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh it has been soooo long since i've been paid!! $$$ https://t.co/kUKhkulqcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though the packing was overkill. https://t.co/fhu45Bj3Sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo cute! Well worth the wait! Thanks @firebox! https://t.co/t6SZHBQBqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone truly loved me they would buy me all of them. https://t.co/aPjb5StQSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithigorman I'm sorry but what? Are they trying to give people an existential crisis?? I don't think that can help...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alas it's true. I bet he would tweet to complain stuff was too easy to break https://t.co/sTAf0TNSQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin oh totally kylo ren but he would DEMAND the theme song. But I am sure even they would be like woooooa… https://t.co/pmZXFmJm0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else hear darth vadars theme when they hear something new Drumpf has done? Cause I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FemInDublin has gotten to me. Coming up with #repealthe8th skit dialogue in the shower... oh well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irishsmurf thank you! I was just hitting subscribe! Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone got any recommendations for science podcasts? Kinda feeling the need. So much need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I only just noticed this... yes I am giggling. https://t.co/HWuAOqfbfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SexSiopa @sorobotic even as a child I remember being very bored by Cu chulainn. And now feel weird after being called Saidbh for 8 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @SexSiopa and @sorobotic talking about badass irish ladies I feel cheated by my irish education. Not for the first time mind you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_swervin putting it mildly. I do love how his own son subtweeted him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan can we do ANYTHING right Piers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the reactions to #Strike4Repeal are just silly. Sorry for the inconvenience guys but lack of healthcare is a bit of a bother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebeccahLouise yeah. What did we do to deserve tinder. https://t.co/qLyTQMsKeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnHyphen @DirtyButClean it's a collection of his articles. So good. Covers a wide range of topics.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>