<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillMakesStuff TEASE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nutmeg Spinning Guild is working hard! https://t.co/utVYuDDTwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 4 of #yarnlovechallenge is speed. I could easily knit a hat in an evening except I'm finding… https://t.co/BrxNZCOdQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe finishing happens only when I really want it more than the joy of a new cast on :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe I wish I cared about finishing some of these things. I knit for joy and sometimes all the joy is in starting ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a hilarious amount of wips. I cast on what I want, when I want and I finish it only if I… https://t.co/362TovyfiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woodlandsprite me too. But not just for the eggs :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe @Kikiluscious ha. of course :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @purlewe Thank you! I think I need a sweater but handspun or Painted yarn? decisions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe I think it will be up for a while :) 4 years ish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YarnGeek @earthchicknits @addknitter @sparklypia wasn't one of the reasons women are ill suited for politics is that they're too moody?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe interesting. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is our new color for a cause. If it looks familiar it's because it's a re-release. This… https://t.co/zW8JDUkONO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe do you have a recipe or some such? I"ll give it a shot when I have time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PurlingDervish hair is like a hat you don't take off. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthchicknits @sparklypia If Bannon is really leading things then he's already expressed his endgame "dismantling the US govt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addknitter @earthchicknits @sparklypia yup. That's exactly what it feels like. Helpless and am I next on the beat down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This swatch and yarn were part of an article I wrote last year (not released yet). All the other… https://t.co/0ePU1E0SC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over loaded with duck eggs if anyone needs some. https://t.co/JijcZy8S9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe I haven't. We're overrun with eggs again too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever have a day where you're doing it all and you start a project then forget it to go do something else .... like filling your dye sinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthchicknits @sparklypia I think the thing is that his advisors support this behavior. They don't want to stop him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lil Boog came home from dance class and was horrified to find out I'd been left home alone for… https://t.co/40xrmsg3mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/e8AEVN96Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw @knittedwit playing and I want to play too. We'll see how good I am at following the… https://t.co/WctaZ2eDAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo  @SenatorCollins!  Thank you for hearing your constituents! https://t.co/eCu4Va1gBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes to take naps in the snow? #farmlife #sheep #cvmromeldale https://t.co/EVjtSkEQvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonyaphilip @Flickr and that dress is perfection!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justmaryse damn. I'm sorry Maryse. I know the stressed about work feeling. It's never good. Xox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @elingeling I had oatmeal but topped it with Cheezits and choc frosting. Yeah, I don't even know what direction I'm going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elingeling @Kikiluscious I love you guys too. Man, we all really need to be better to ourselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elingeling me too. I am thankful for my second job where I have no computer and phones are off limits. self care in overworking. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally casting off this shawl. I decided to make it double sized. Hopefully pattern will be… https://t.co/r7LggN1K6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maine has yet to have sanctuary cities. Any mentioned, there's great opposition. Where are Maine's good caring Christians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Hallowell!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️ stand up for humanity. https://t.co/E3H5X7OgZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrieoke mine aren't even hiding behind religion any more. They're wearing their bias like a crown. #ugly sorry for us all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ @jeremyscahill @theintercept I believe this is only the beginning. Who are they coming for next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farwellclay except there are other lawyers on the other side. True good vs evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Misty. She's a beautiful goat even she looks kinda goofy here. https://t.co/dkob1nYRcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purlewe They're so grown!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a dream.... that I can close out the tabs for messaging my rep and senators. Someday, I want to not be messaging them daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious I get responses from every one but sensor Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @thriftyknitter same here. Tried leaving it blank. I end up choosing ms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @thriftyknitter mine too. I just assume it's a formality thing. Elderly write in, they like that formality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is smart. Those going to protests, have you set up a plan? Not all protests will end with us going home right… https://t.co/QljlW9rw5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a small sampling of the fibers I'm bringing to Saturday's class on singles yarns at Nutmeg… https://t.co/kK6EFp8BVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously?
These are American values? https://t.co/zQ22qopp4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenmexted @KweenBoda Tell me something I don't know. The worrisome thing is that now the world is being dragged into the shit too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ we need someone to do something. Some one with some pull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ it's the strongest they have opposed anything yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ yeah, he's been late to the game with a lot of things. Almost a no count in many. My rep is Poliquin. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @rachellake it was here. I'll DM you the statements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ I'm betting my name is on a list. Shit is only gonna get worse unless some govt stand with us. Disappointed in our reps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afm_ because they blindly believe the rhetoric they've been told. That refugees make their lives worse. :( We're all targets now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @rachellake did you read what she wrote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @rachellake I'm being argued with by someone that thinks it's ok. Omg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda this isn't the point. I hope you have good evening. I'm not continuing with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda are you native? If not you're immigrant stock and this could have been your family. Selfish. Mean. Un American. Un Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda we've also banned citizens. People that have lives and families here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda know your facts. Not alternative facts and lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda if anyone unilaterally banned based on religion, I would be against that action. It's horrific and wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda I'm not anti Trump. I'm pro American and this goes against American constitution and values. It's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KweenBoda you mean the no fly list? I disagree with unilaterally banning someone because of religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @rachellake you and me both. Holy Hell. How can anyone think this is ok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. This has put a target on our backs https://t.co/yKBsoyoC0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweeting a lot because I'm so horrified at what our country is doing that I'm almost speechless. #RESIST #muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @rachellake.  :( this can't last forever. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @helloyarn @kimu @rachellake For the first time since discovering it, I'm glad my account is over drawn. Take that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twlldun @LiarMPs   The Vatican wall was built around 850 to protect from actual phys attacks. #history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious ha. exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthchicknits It might take a while... and it will have to be more than one really. Politicians (either side) rarely make a solo stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthchicknits I haven't seen reports of any currently in office. Someone has to have though, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone (Gypsy) fancies herself a special snowflake goat. She's not wrong https://t.co/NOesCxAMmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the grandma I hope to be (or grand-aunt) or whatever. Cool old lady making rainbow sweaters for kids. https://t.co/Nf4Muig02e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloyarn @lorengoren but only some of it. Ya know. The parts that white rich guys don't use. Or better yet,  just make it accessible to 1%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This yarn is beautiful https://t.co/2rKFNXh4Ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloyarn I think that first tweet had a silent "for white people only" in there. Hard to see in a tweet but I bet that's it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiberistaFiles LilBoog and I are going to read that as part of homeschool. I ordered a hard copy in case it dies on the Kindle. KWIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I placed my first seed order for the year. Ready to garden! Almost. I'm not rushing away winter. It gets warm too early for me already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seems copies of 1984 mass paperbacks are selling out. heh. I wonder how other dystopian novels are doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter skies are fantastic. 180 degrees. Winter storm look to the left, sunny and spring like to… https://t.co/sJik14eOyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["you have the boldness of a much younger woman"... rewatching 30Rock for a little levity in my day as I do paperwork.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone forgets to close the back gate, everyone runs for the orchard. #farmlife #sheep #goats https://t.co/RPlQxG2gDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious @JewdyGold ditto. Truth is, I was probably going to anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duck taking walks with a crow? I'm writing a story in my mind... Romeo and Juliet.... https://t.co/F902TleemB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloyarn @daisykpgardner read the tweets, may not be exactly true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kikiluscious I found that reassuring too. "Omg it's that pain in the ass from Lisbon again"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinaJL_GB I'm glad you liked it. It's so pretty all finished up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_m @Kikiluscious @woodlandsprite I use a habit tracker too. But I take so many diff  vitamins + herbal I need the container]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would absolutely vote for a scientist. Can we have a new political party too? The science party or something clev… https://t.co/MaKY0p6UCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woodlandsprite I've had one good at least ten years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@savoryknitting I think we all are. But. We are stronger together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart aches for Syrians. I don't want more kids but I'd take in a Syrian in a heartbeat. So many orphans. So much hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twistcollective healthy home made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twistcollective I didn't have one either. Succumbed to raw cookie dough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@splityarn @McYarnpants brilliant. I've just being saving everything as a Google email draft. Duh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a pretty sunset https://t.co/ddaw69TJBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinaJL_GB It's gorgeous!!! - SW Targhee "Caribou"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthchicknits I thought there was something unlawful about blocking funding to sanctuary cities. #ffs #nogooddeedunpunished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psyckology awww. Thank you . You are very sweet. And you should know, every person counts. No such thing as just one ;)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>