<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmacfie piwik does both of those things â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubiousStephen I often wonder if those who actually change the world are the ones that don't get to enjoy their own life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HandleTheJandle haha yeah, nobody in particular as I'd just unfollow them. Just a general thing across those I follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argh. The end of America sure is ruining Twitter for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsSpastk there is no rationalising The Bachelor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea @DubiousStephen I first saw his series where he mentions it here https://t.co/5bmgPAL76U Worth watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could go wrong?
 https://t.co/aPbhqprYGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of having a house like a sauna ðŸ”¥ https://t.co/jLFtNaiae2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haquaman @MrsSpastk thanks :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton @MrsSpastk @spastk lol, thanks mate, you too! ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„ And don't worry I get notifications either way ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justicefries @theRoostStand awesome! Love it when things live up to / exceed expectations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 weeks into my job as a "Cloud Farmer" at @8iReality and I couldn't be happier. Great bunch of people and some amazing tech!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽµ one more week until boxing day ðŸŽµðŸŽ‰ #xmasbegone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haquaman well done bro! Well deserved I'm sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verifying myself: I am sry_not4sale on Keybase.io. xa1gySsM1EsCq7fNz2oEA97sGPvq4DL-M2HC / https://t.co/T3fYecamTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HandleTheJandle lol that explains the first sausage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronTheMad or giant hand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day at @8iReality done and dusted ðŸ¤˜ What an amazing place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @SlingshotNZ ah looks like my tweet fixed it #yourewelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rimuhosting and back, good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch, major packet loss to @rimuhosting Auckland data center. Not a fun way to spend a Friday evening â˜¹ï¸ #poorsysadmins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normnz @CatalystNZ thank you Don]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton damn it. Ulumni is in my dictionary for some reason lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton am I using that word wrong? Lol #neverwenttouni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatalystNZ they tried their best, but the cake was too great a distraction ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton thanks mate! I now join the select group that are @CatalystNZ ulumni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton @CatalystNZ already happened! Hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the awesome send off @CatalystNZ - I will see y'all around https://t.co/eARrOY9fMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day at @CatalystNZ tomorrow - lots of good friends I will miss very much ðŸ˜­ but excited for the future ðŸ¤˜ #mixedemotions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea yeah neighbour has had power out all day. I think it's just one pole giving issues so had to turn all houses on it off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Issue with power on our street, so the power has to go off for 2 hours. Moments after it gets turned off I get an icinga2 notification ðŸ¤˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CM14.1 nightlies out for a few new devices (including my Moto X 2014). So smooth, recommend! https://t.co/8uPuJmFYQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman you'll always be samurai-hair-dude to me (you have many other amazing qualities too, that was just the first I noticed)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to have worked on this with a mighty fine team at @CatalystNZ https://t.co/3LSJ35h4YS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HandleTheJandle @YuliyaBozhko @8iReality thanks mate, can't wait to get started!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuliyaBozhko indeed! 8.5 years ðŸ˜² most of my working life! Off to @8iReality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two weeks left at @CatalystNZ today. ðŸ˜¢ but also ðŸ˜± and a bit of ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ @Danjite @TeslaMotors for comparison, hard to get a Mercedes for under $100k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danjite @TeslaMotors @JennyKayNZ already announced pricing. ~$100k to well over $200k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton this has been discussed mwuahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton my dad used to have an exhibit, model trains are awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton might have to check out this train expo tomorrow tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton used to play hockey there, great facility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmacfie sounds like he could be a bit more subtle about his plans to murder someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heytrav and why always the late evening? ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, no more right-before-kids-go-to-bed quakes kthanks #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The epic #brazilgp was an excellent distraction from last night's #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman caffeine pills in your first aid kit, never regret it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theunfocused sure it wasn't a rat's arse? Would you rather your cat didn't give a rat's arse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buildmaster thanks! Although if it's anything like last VR rollercoaster I tried I'll have to be strapped in and bolted to the floor...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@satrun77 @8iReality @CatalystNZ thanks, I'm really excited about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am excited to announce I'll be starting at @8iReality in December, after 8 fun filled years at @CatalystNZ. Exciting times ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is done. I am now @sry_not4sale and no longer @spastk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnat @ramez ðŸ˜± he's coming to NZ!?! Nexus is my favourite book series (alongside Expanse)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering switching my Twitter handle to @sry_not4sale - to match all my other online accounts. @spastk can be a bit polarizing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The darkest timeline... #ElectionNight https://t.co/uyxKTn8iGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea I'm sure they'll nail it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@old_sound stop and read the books, or you'll get to the end of the TV show and regret how long to wait for season 2. Books are amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a week! Time for a lie 
-down me thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8iReality I noticed https://t.co/I5yZOvpvYU was available so registered it. DM me if you'd like and we can organise ownership transfer :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an amazing chance encounter this afternoon with some Orca. Man do I love living in Wellington! https://t.co/PchbBGnMC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, random caller from Ontario, I am not interested in your unsolicited investment advice. Sheesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kathrynpipesup you'll do amazing, you're awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Productive weekend! We built an outdoor set, and replaced the screen on mates phone. Phone even mostly still works ðŸ˜€ https://t.co/FyDKmw0RRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["potential" arghghg https://t.co/UL3dAjSGSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amcafee @majicDave thought this was Ambience for a second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be more like my generation! Just write a disapproving tweet about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If disapproving shakes of the head actually made a difference to the world maybe baby-boomers would have left us something worth inheriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libbyobrien https://t.co/ibFkXeeru7 might help. Too easy to use lots of data nowadays. Android has a nice report of usage - might be useful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theunfocused @andychilton yeah. I didn't recognise the UI and thought it might have been the Cyanogemod version in Marshmallow :-S my bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton Nougat will fix these issues once and for all :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsSpastk well the end result is the goal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea @MrsSpastk thanks for coming along #awesomeneighbour :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton I'm glad to be over it. Ended up just being a battle against the sunk cost fallacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuliyaBozhko well played, well played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton moving on from the project after 12 long years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychilton haha yeah - selling up so not as fun as it looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My weekend... surrounded by car parts https://t.co/SZD2WyYhwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was an emotional rollercoaster. First NZ gets a 7.1 eq, then the @spacex Falcon9 exploded, and tonight I finally saw Suicide Squad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindKits daughter would love this. Hope this counts as a mention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac you're lying. It's not the first time, is it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theunfocused I liked the ambiguous one better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spastk nope. they just rate limited @catalyst for making too many requests haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG stack overflow is down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwryan heh. David Mitchell is just fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonwryan great video. Thanks for the link. Have you seen this? https://t.co/Nc07gRBeoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac at the very least backup the output of "tree /path/to/music"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman The Expanse or Mr robot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelmcnie was awesome to catch up man. Must do it more online!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the lifts at work smells like cats...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac as I understand it, they do have a service - https://t.co/9H46sMXiWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsSpastk aww I miss working with you too! But then that's why we have our own projects ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cupcakes of Independence +1

Made by the one and only @MrsSpastk https://t.co/pUXMPivsYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman @slingshot moved me with only 11 days notice which I thought was pretty good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelmcnie check no bulbs are blown, they'll fail you if your car is unfit for the test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsSpastk nothing like a clean slate (until you see how much work it is to refill it) ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is an empty code review backlog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libbyobrien YouTube YouTube YouTube. Nothing like seeing someone actually doing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui awesome, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui nice. That games looks fun, hopefully works under wine]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>