<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodeJonny @prodAdvice @ianshepherd Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themify No worries. Got it sorted. Had to remake the modules but it seems to be ok now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reddit is the original vision for the #internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themify are there any known issues with your contact forms at this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Most Important Infographic In Mastering And Loudness Normalisation Right Now | Christopher Carvalho https://t.co/ggDjRR45fD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a a pair of Genelec 8030 Red Studio Monitors (Limited Edition) w/ @genelecusa @ProduceLikeAPro &amp; @warrenhuart.  https://t.co/xMiYnoaSXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIFE GOAL: Appear on the #AskGaryVee SHOOOOOOWWWWWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ListenTo "My first wave lol " ⚓ https://t.co/xLFNVDoT2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coaching Success - Labi Ramaj | Christopher Carvalho https://t.co/ZR6wshVkGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMA about #MusicProduction over at #musicly https://t.co/1zM58Hks33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headroom for Mastering | Christopher Carvalho https://t.co/ZEs4ttoaLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Way To Level-Up Your Mixing Game | Christopher Carvalho https://t.co/vN4HZmMI8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garyvee lol you said "the breast"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/RJ6iO7NMWr Le monde est barge - I have a dream * August 28 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/7VTBzVVkiL DeJay ft King Aggi - St Paul's Jammin | @dejaye @kingaggi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Product_London @PLDN_Mastering Thanks :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeironYoung1 anytime, friend 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeironYoung1 That's fair enough. Send something over and il give you some direction for sure 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyosOfficial Great! If you could do with another set of ears, feel free to send the audio over. Link in bio 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paigenblue Hey Paige! It know how you feel! If you want some free impartial feedback, I'm happy to. Link in bio :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteefvdMeer9 Hey Stephanie. If you ever need some impartial feedback on your mix, I offer free mix feedback. Link in bio :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConHatesMondays I know! The point isn't the change it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulOfCreation @deejaysham Hi Paul, feel free to send the audio to me for free advice. Link in bio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeironYoung1 it certainly is! If you need an objective set of ears, I offer free mix feedback. Link in bio 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PLDN_Mastering @Product_London Hey guys, just letting you know that is starts from £25 unless I missed something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLARecordist @YouTube THANKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/doUG0XZ5Pv Mastering Considerations in Logic Pro X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raddeaux Thanks for liking my tweet/song before!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, on Spotify

https://t.co/iBtGQ1zXFY

#ambient #music #newmusic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/Wr9L5gKf57 Automation Modes In Logic Pro X Including Trim And Relative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! @TrainYourEarsEN https://t.co/QFBYxqxCE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/t92Kc2Y5cX How To Edit Mulitple MIDI Regions In One Piano Roll Logic Pro X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it! #unlockyoursound https://t.co/qIdd3pCuBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLARecordist Happy New Year, Will! Looking forward to another 365 analogue vlogs, which are vlogs, and logs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiddjdm oh ok. You can change the duration of an audio region by alt-click-dragging the bottom right corner of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamFlower93 I know the feeling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Feria305 Love it. Let me know if you have any Logic Pro questions 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiddjdm is there any particular struggle that I can help you with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewhewitt what seems to be the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sirrmarky let me know if you have any Logic questions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Available on all platforms January 7th

https://t.co/5XS2tRflIp

#ambient #music https://t.co/o2db638tT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divagare Thanks for the retweet, Pablo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piXXelOfficial Glad to hear it! I produce ambient: https://t.co/boPCCVDIiF what about you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeBrownartist EP would be good to raise awareness before you go full album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeBrownartist first release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badlydrawnbilly however, if you did choose to upgrade, it's likely you'll gain some benefit over time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badlydrawnbilly I think if it's fulfilling your current needs, the carry on. But if and when you do find a limitation, then you can progres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piXXelOfficial Feel free to AMA about Logic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badlydrawnbilly depends on your needs? Does GarageBand work for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tie_bond8 Well done! Let me know if you have any questions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwankyRicky happy to help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pitchmomo Just got it? Let me know if you have any questions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP George Michael

We will always miss you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespacecaptin You're welcome :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Music Production https://t.co/VmV5e0O8dJ 

#LogicProX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently offering mastering services @ £15 per song from stereo mixdown. 

Pay via Paypal when you are happy. Simples.

Merry Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Kind Of Blue (Legacy Edition) by Miles Davis ♫ https://t.co/NH37IDANoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOUND

#NowPlaying Speak To Me (Live At The Empire Pool, Wembley, London 1974) [2011 - Remaster] by Pink Floyd ♫ https://t.co/q2BHmbQaCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Some Polyphony by Petter ♫ https://t.co/qGMoo0RbKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinBam2Sykes Great to 'meet' you today, Kevin. Hope that was useful 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logic Pro Tuition | Christopher Carvalho 

https://t.co/ShllKJtnzZ

#LogicPro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need to get it out of the #daw to have a good listen to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people you look up to didn't get to where they are by clinging onto someone else's narrative

#unlockyoursound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeArePixl3 Thanks! Means a lot coming from you! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Swedger_ happy to give you a price of £15 per stereo track 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New site: https://t.co/euqODvNYOG 

#LogicPro #AudioEngineering https://t.co/jV1IRdhaD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free mix review: chris@unlockyoursound.com 

#MusicProduction https://t.co/Z2FMENfhb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megashaun Is the self-doubt because of mastering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danielescobedo_ Hi Dino. I'm an audio engineer. How can I help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Swedger_ how much can you afford?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenkiller808 Hi Helen, Happy to help with regard to mastering 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@e________k is it your own song? It's so difficult to treat ones music objectively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElliottJJames Have you tried Retro Synth yet? It's awesome 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MasterP_da_dj fair enough. As long as you are making music, that's what's important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MasterP_da_dj something I can help with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world does not belong to the pessimist" 

~Warren Buffett

https://t.co/U94OJgvEsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealkenchase Fair enough! Feel free to reach out going forward :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KizzErnie Great! Let me know if you need any help going forward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TAGMusic98 glad to hear it! Feel free to ask me anything going forward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_North how come?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealkenchase flat? Can you share a screenshot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcashhole can I help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MasterP_da_dj what's up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KizzErnie is this still happening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lebasfondmusic how's it going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMaddenMusic If you previously purchased 9 for App Store you can download it for 'Purchases'. Why not go X?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElliottJJames @thereadyset where exactly are you struggling? Logic is well set up for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsMaxsta Using the 'gain' control in flex pitch can help whilst retaining an organic sound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespacecaptin You'll find 808 drums backs in the preset library for EXS24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattSwaringim @AppleSupport this is very strange. Have you tried reinstalling the app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colincanread where do you store your projects?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TAGMusic98 how can I help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9C0RE5 happy to help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeprendsracine @WeAreFocusrite have you tried turning core audio off and on again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josietaylorr haha that's totally normal. Anything I can help you with at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakej654 what plug-ins are you using?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsTazzyM nice work! Let me know if you any Logic Qs :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJOneted what happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinBam2Sykes no worries! Monday is fine. Have a nice weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room test

#NowPlaying Un-Break My Heart by Toni Braxton ♫ https://t.co/jlTcLj57sh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>