<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRobertOConnor definitely I am horrified sometimes for what passes as "journalism"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRobertOConnor I think with health especially it is vital to present the FACTS with expert opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Device allows 'locked-in' patients to communicate https://t.co/8KwDQ3sHci via @rte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gerry_Rye thank you so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene possibly linked to depression identified  https://t.co/5EPksiMnoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AverilLarke @chronicmom1 @BadMammyBlog thank you Averil for sharing &amp; Lisa @badmammyBlog for writing this piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to listen to patients with chronic pain,chronic illness, and not just dismiss what they are saying-Great pi… https://t.co/mYNB7CJKZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebielinski @twisteddoodles isn't it just lovely @twisteddoodles is so hugely talented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crabbers thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fdcsticks awww thank you 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PriscillaLynch @deirdre_dm he certainly was a character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motionsetc thank you Frances I appreciate that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tori_RH thank you 😊 what a lovely tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallHeenan thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnaPBarry I know! I was a snivelling mess when the dart arrived]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRobertOConnor thank you Robert we need more balanced reporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolquovadis @Claredaisy it's costs nothing to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeonieCorcoran aw you would... thank you x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to think meds cheated the mental healing process,Now I know (when used responsibly) how they give back lives… https://t.co/CV82MwNr9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkconlon I hear you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryMc_31 aw thanks Mary but anyone would have done the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nettykent thank you that's just lovely 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks fascinating https://t.co/d3wsQWoq53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay day! and I'm going to totally lose the run of myself by buying posh crisps with my SHOP BOUGHT  wrap #notions #januarypayday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She got no help or care. It didn’t exist then -Ann Lovett letters: heartbreaking but important read 
https://t.co/59z5jXbvub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geabstaire what a lovely thing to say thank you 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tori_RH awww that is so lovely thank you. That hug has set me up for the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanMoloney1 aw thanks Siobhan but you would have done the exact same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh that is sooo much better thank you https://t.co/Hz6XhZquts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@linglang thank you Elaine it's a completely new concept to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaoiseBee thank you but anyone would have done the same 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marybuckley549 thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Judearoo aw sure you would have done the exact same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was gone just as I reached up for my hug. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/by6kfSGi5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't sure whether to tweet about it in case I was accused of what @Donal_OKeeffe told me about"virtue signaling " but it was a #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisteddoodles thank you...sure you would have done the same. 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psychpopgirl yes I am sure it will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AineDvs21 aw thanks but anyone would have done the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spiller2 awww not sure about that you would have done the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Claredaisy yes she's fine now he dad arrived &amp; gave her a huge hug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireoconnell ah sure anyone would do the same. 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irish_IreneB she was but once her dad arrived she was fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inkwellHQ yes her Dad arrived &amp; all was well. Poor little thing #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As they went off together hand in hand I almost asked him for a dad hug too. In bits here #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as I was considering what to do her dad arrived, thanked me &amp; gave her a huge hug. I was the one crying then #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The poor thing was v upset I didn't want to crowd her but part of me wanted to accompany her to school to make sure she was ok #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I bought her a ticket &amp; gave her my phone to call her dad. #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met a young school girl crying outside the dart station. She forgot her ticket &amp; her phone &amp; had no money #darttales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly! https://t.co/0O2v22hV5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSeapig 😂😂😂 Scoop Shannon that's what they call me. Thanks Ray 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a real dilemma for GPs https://t.co/IuKQ7bo4hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorTMcGrane does this happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My worries exactly Ciara https://t.co/W0HGRSS7je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNiNuall completely agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true https://t.co/kFRpeF3UUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadorourke thank you Sinead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely need more counsellors https://t.co/TVaVPg6Mye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sorry to read this https://t.co/t95Eg5DlfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programme well intended &amp; raised good points but lacked balance sure what do I know I'm only a lowly medical journalist #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoBW yes it lacked balance unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annf32 @Murpht01 @SvtigerStephane details of public/Medical card prescriptions available from PCRS (anonymised data)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoBW my thoughts exactly Jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hands up everyone who orders drugs online with their pizzas WTF #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susancloonan so sorry to hear this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymcevoy that's great to hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mgtmurphy123 @drnickgp @DrEvaOrsmond @ClaireByrneLive he did a great job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please do not stop taking any prescribed medications before discussing it first with your GP/psychiatrist #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymcevoy sorry to hear that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should be encouraging multi approach to mental illness including med(if needed)psychological support &amp;healthy lifestyle #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadorourke yes I was v disappointed by lack of balance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not comfortable with this finger pointing &amp; blaming people who take medication #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very worrying dismissive attitude to fact that sometimes the drugs do work #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy for Dr Eva that Walking the dogs helps her but that doesn't do it for people in extreme distress #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunnyScattered so happy to hear you are doing so well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindfulness is hugely beneficial for a number of conditions &amp; pain management programmes work very well for some #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certainly important that codeine containing medication guidelines are adhered to however patients are also responsible #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addiction is such a crippling disability #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisapower nope I'm here too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is that poor man still alive with a functioning liver/kidneys #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree and this is the same with all medications https://t.co/LJM0hi3rVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzanne_Brett best attitude to have but yes we all need to take responsibility for our own health too #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshgroveAnn it sure was 😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordmuca and mine for the last 12.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a worry but hopefully there will be balance in second half https://t.co/VgqlKTvQJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackBlacknab I totally agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshgroveAnn aw how lovely...you had such a long journey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbairrins yes but it is so much expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As someone who lives with depression &amp; anxiety &amp; was admitted to psychiatric hospital the chemical solution saved my life #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying undertones of all medication is bad waiting for some balance #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's @drnickgp speaking perfect sense &amp; outlining real difficulties of being a GP &amp; need for support #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benzodiazepines work well for an acute episode of anxiety but should not be used long term #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benzodiazepine addiction a big issue inappropriate prescribing definitely going on @ColinPBradley does great work in area. #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly https://t.co/ovKm8f7YZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are GPs supposed to do faced with a patient in severe distress and waiting lists are months long #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are huge waiting lists for talk therapies and that is for those WITH  a medical card #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree that we over use antibiotics #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course all patients should have a medicines review at regular basis #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it a surprise that people over 65 are taking multiple medications? We are all living longer as a result #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw I never got to ask him that 😂 https://t.co/KkGjhivDor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a thought but it is thanks to Prof Harrison's pioneering work on IVF in Ireland that I had the chance of becoming a mother RIP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>