<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackmcintyre67 if Van Dijk still played in this league he wouldn't be as half as good as he is now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenpark12 aye it works both ways I suppose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenpark12 some of their fans wish they were you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewescfc happy birthday mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeparkx you were in Glasgow and still made use of your time to go and watch hearts? aye that was bad crack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine travelling through to Glasgow to watch your rivals no even play your own team https://t.co/0STt6usz95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairio96 happy birthday mate, hope it's a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorhmfcclark @lewiscampbell21 @callumbuchan95 end of the day we need players and he's bringing them in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lincoln City on ye go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewiscampbell21 @conorhmfcclark Cathro is already preparing for his interview after the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorhmfcclark @lewiscampbell21 well it makes it less disappointing soppy bollocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewiscampbell21 @conorhmfcclark just being realistic mate so I'm no overly disappointed tomorrow, honestly despise them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewiscampbell21 @conorhmfcclark nothing will happen apart from a comfortable Celtic win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewiscampbell21 @conorhmfcclark going to get pumped anyway may as well make money on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauldickkson that'll come in comfortably, celta Vigo were a great price eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauldickkson already put my bet on mate. No great returns back but I could really do with it https://t.co/j10s7harmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorhmfcclark Scott Sinclair any time and Celtic to win, 3/1, lump the bastard. There's the taig in me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_R_1967 shout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacgregorrx ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I'll hold you to that mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacgregorrx ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ only saying it's tough to call because hibs haven't played a side above their level this season mate, aye spot on saan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacgregorrx definitely mate, think it's a very tough one to call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdyhearts1874 @MattMacgregorrx @Dale_Lovell_97 correct, you'll hear me say that the morn after my Â£40 coupon comes in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMacgregorrx @Dale_Lovell_97 doesn't matter how you win in cups mate as long as the job gets done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southampton playing a weakened side as if they're going to win anything else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Lovell_97 jinx myself too much as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11/10 and I didn't put it on ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorhmfcclark @Janjo1874 he canny play unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 teams, one has won, one is winning, two are drawing and the rest are losing ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half my coupon losing already haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wolves ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that Evans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsnaataalie_ player btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_R_1967 genuinely don't think they'll get top four]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool are a fraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bootboy100 most definitely ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a feeling I'll win a coupon today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenpark12 good to hear, he's a forward eh? We lack depth in that area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top ten at ten will never be the same again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_JMAR they don't stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man United fans away from home are superb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9Webby @smAFC18 @hertz77 @Gungadin1875 the Edinburgh derby is a more relevant game than any game on your fixture list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairmurrayy @ScottishFA fingers crossed Blair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairmurrayy @ScottishFA would be ideal mate but I've already taken the Monday off as I know it'll be a Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairRae234 @Sinclair1875 we're horrible in cups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairRae234 @Sinclair1875 still canny believe you said that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sinclair1875 we didn't beat you last year and I think you're harder to beat this year, not as good going forward though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sinclair1875 put it this way, I really didn't want you in that draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smAFC18 @hertz77 @Gungadin1875 why say our derby is irrelevant when we're both bigger than you and you don't even have a derby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hertz77 @Gungadin1875 @smAFC18 to be fair Rangers hate them as well Ty. However it's clear Aberdeen are irrelevant when it comes to Celtic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sinclair1875 because it's perfectly set up for you's to lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announce Hearts penalty against hibs @ScottishFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game over, bring them on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallqmccabe04 I owe you a fiver because my team has too much of a winning mentality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funniest thing about this is hibs fans laughing at a team drawing with us who they've played in the same league as for 3 seasons now..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did we no die when we had the chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEwen97 @RFBorthwick I dinny leave my house to watch them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_johnboy1 imagine we still went out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two games to beat Raith in 90 minutes and we failed to do so, hope Celtic go easy on us this Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relief isn't the word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieranTant how you getting in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending a birthday message using flipgram is a blockable offence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiddlerLloyd shocking price tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aleshiaingram lol you're muted for a reason you goth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Finbar__ that first picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if we get there ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be expecting something very similar in the derby if we're ahead with a few minutes left @1Jackhamilton https://t.co/ECKyPViPbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieranTant @_johnboy1 bang on keeko expected better from him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Medio96 happy birthday mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woody1875hibs nah I do, just won't be surprised if we lose mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woody1875hibs no sure they'll show Raith and Hibs on tele mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woody1875hibs you no banned for celebrating or something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awmaaaate happy birthday mate hope it's a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reaganmcguire3 you and many others my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niall McCabe has given in, very sad day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakemccreadie @JamessDavidson far from it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@67ONeill no sure I think Raith will give them a decent game especially with home advantage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@67ONeill that's no a very accurate tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish we got Stirling Albion or Clyde at home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to be hilarious when Raith put us out on penaltys this Wednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanBrett62 dirty bastard ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now last time I checked it was Rangers you beat in the final? https://t.co/0HsP4dT4m1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 nah still wouldn't be true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 aye you've missed out a few]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 well we beat Arbroath in the league cup at tynie last season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 I'd accept that if St Johnstone was a Scottish cup game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 well it isn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gungadin1875 that's no true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjjjj_rfc well played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjjjj_rfc but aye collectively I absolutely despise them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjjjj_rfc could've sworn a few years ago you acted like one of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnysoldier_ wouldny turn a ticket down if one was offered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnysoldier_ who goes to a rod stewart concert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will Celtic fans call it a day with acting like they're at a take that concert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnysoldier_ @Selliott01 Hahahaha nah but in all seriousness we need to give the guy a chance. I'm giving him until September/October]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnysoldier_ @Selliott01 no it's no, give him time fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we play like that next weekend it'll be a fucking cricket score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liam_H_11 correct, we'll win the replay but that's class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely we're going to sign another striker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebrando1 you surely seen the sarcasm there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebrando1 https://t.co/eS9FHrgYwY best fans in Scotland hhgh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>