<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely loving that #Inside is getting some love at the #SelectAwards2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright @IGN_AU let's do this... https://t.co/afddkHbYJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a sudden urge to watch that episode of #TheSimpsons where they visit Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaosKittyEm @LuckyBonez Oh don't you worry, awkwardness will be in abundance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaosKittyEm So I can expect to see you and @LuckyBonez all suited up at RTX then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh sh*t yes, absolutely cannot wait to get my hands on #HorizonZeroDawn
And now that I've said that, I can only be disappointed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure whether this is a good thing or not. I mean, there's only so much raging I can do in a game of #Overwatch https://t.co/xpeytxqjqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t, absolutely cannot wait for the next #BanjoKazooie game to be released! https://t.co/nDCmfBYEEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of an era that's for sure. #GoodGame https://t.co/xJvy5431my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh damn, now this is completely unexpected https://t.co/PmEswBq8Hs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, I would've played the sh*t out of this had it been completed as #Fallout 3 and not as Icewind Dale https://t.co/Uq43lIVCOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could it actually be...?
Could #Skate4 indeed be a reality? https://t.co/YLuogzn3v2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the outcome I wanted, but credit to #Federer for winning the #AusOpen.
Great stuff after being out for half a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fedal2017 #AusOpen final, here we go....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 week in and we have a #MuslimBan. 
Oh boy, can't wait for what #Trump has in store for week 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRileyLittle is there a unicorn pink option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as I'm coming down from that #NadalvsDimitrov high, I found out that #Manor is gone from #F1 
Back to 20 cars on the grid...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t, awesome stuff from #Nadal &amp; #Dimitrov.
But the bigger news is that we now have that #Fedal #AusOpen final we've been waiting for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, some great hitting early on at the #AusOpen from #Nadal and #Dimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooooo much good stuff to get in the new #Overwatch #YearOfTheRooster event https://t.co/6HrdPAP5xA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff from #Nadal. One step closer to that #Fedal #AusOpen final...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaosKittyEm I yelled at my phone when I found out #YourName wasn't nominated. #TheRedTurtle getting a nom slightly made up for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of stupid #OscarNoms, can the Academy get over its wanky love of #MerylStreep? She's great and all, but #AmyAdams deserved the nom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm happy that #TheRedTurtle got an #OscarNom but nothing for #YourName? Of all the stupid things the #Oscars have done, this is the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, #TheLastJedi isn't a bad title per se, but it kind of pales in comparison to the fake ones like "The Order of the Dark Side"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Inside was one of my favourite games of 2016 so I really can't wait to see how this turns out https://t.co/W4bO156L9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only taken 2 years, but it's great to see #Nadal back in the #AusOpen quarters. Now to look forward to his match against #Raonic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're only in January, but the bar for op-eds is already ridiculously high https://t.co/j4i3cBpOLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff from #Federer but sad that #Nishikori was hampered. At the way this #AusOpen is going, a #Fedal could very well happen again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, top 2 seeds out in the 1st week of the #AusOpen 
I mean, we joke about it, sure. But for it to actually happen? Absolutely mindboggling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes, #AndyMurray in some serious trouble at the #AusOpen 
Could the elder #Zverev do what his little bro just missed out on doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome stuff from #Nadal and #Zverev at the #AusOpen, glad to see the champ move on but expecting to see some great things from the kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus, #Federer is looking absolutely ominous. The Fed v #Nishikori match is going to be an absolute cracker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to revisit the world of #FFXV me thinks...
#FFXVCarnival https://t.co/qOrGcMDG5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having watched both #Logan trailers quite a few times now, I'm definitely getting some sort of Joel &amp; Ellie vibe with #Wolverine &amp; the girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with #SystemShock3 in development, we can have both! https://t.co/AlGaaRwhls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full credit to Istomin, he held his nerve when it really mattered. Now he needs to back this up and win the #AustralianOpen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, #Djokovic out in R2 of the #AustralianOpen 
I'm now wondering if I look out my window I'll see cats flying or something else crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t, 1 point away...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen #Djokovic play better at the #AustralianOpen but credit where it's due, Istomin is winning this rather than Djokovic losing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Djokovic down a break in the 5th set in R2 at the #AustralianOpen 
Oh yep, this report is just in, it is indeed now snowing in hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a hunch he saw those #Overwatch Jeff meme videos... https://t.co/8Xx65iUBSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I wrote a little something on the #StudioGhibli museum today. Now I want to revisit that magical place again...
https://t.co/i9IYWCEomK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#keinishikori taken to 5, #Kerber taken to 3, #Wawrinka in the 5th &amp; #Federer back after months out. God I love the #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet, now I can show off all my mad #Overwatch highlights where I stupidly kill myself &amp; somehow manage to take 4… https://t.co/mSJuK0fF84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Props to @PlayOverwatch &amp; @Blizzard_Ent for this. Now if only they can ban that 1 toxic player on my team who plays… https://t.co/T65ObnbQqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need this. I really don't need this.

....I need this. https://t.co/Hlfj7t5h7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shout out to my man @DrJ_SBSPopAsia who is leaving us at #SBSPopAsia for better pastures elsewhere. 
Will miss having you around buddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's #BreathOfTheWild, #SuperMarioOdyssey or #XenobladeChronicles2 (or all 3).
Whatever it is, looks like I'll be getting a #Switch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #NintendoSwitch presentation was meh, but I still want one. God damn it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Deadpool's PGA nom means it has a chance of an Oscar nom. God I hope it gets it because I want to see @VancityReynolds turn up as Deadpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t, does this mean what I think it means for season 3 of #BetterCallSaul!?!?
https://t.co/GtGLP1O1sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good news for all those #Sombra &amp; #Roadhog players out there. For us Ana players, a little bit less so. https://t.co/UsRyCWtxX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #Scalebound debacle sucks for all - fans lose out, developers lose 3+ years of work &amp; their health, &amp; Microsof… https://t.co/Mu31aW7WKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lost a bunch of #Overwatch matches, but then I saw @VancityReynolds &amp; #AndrewGarfield kiss, &amp; everything was suddenly right in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slightly disappointed, but I'm all for it if it means they will finish the next #ElderScrolls/#Fallout game faster. https://t.co/k3OuvJDpZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to #LaLaLand to save the #GoldenGlobes, from the opening monologue to winning everything.
That &amp; Meryl Streep being awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRileyLittle @cm_GG Don't be like that, Mr Little. Someone has to take 1 for the team, &amp; who better to drink all the diet coke than you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cm_GG awww shucks, nicest thing anyone has said to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRileyLittle @cm_GG I may not agree with Mr Little's Diet Coke drinking tendencies, but you MUST watch #CowboyBebop, Mr Gravelle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewatching #Watchmen for the 1st time since I saw it in the cinema 7.5 years ago. Let's see how well it has held up over time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cm_GG What can I say, FF15 brings out the best &amp; worst in me. I still get twitches every time I think about that Pitioss Dungeon *shudders*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely a case of what might have been if #FFXV was given another 10 years of development time. https://t.co/NKrG6mO51S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see @rhipratchett go, but excited for what she works on next https://t.co/sGlrtajS8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRileyLittle It sucks. (I lie, Oasis is pretty cool).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. The #Overwatch Winter Event is over and all I'm missing from my collection is the #Nutcracker Zenyatta skin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hours later, I finally beat that fu*king Adamantoise in #FFXV.
Not sure if it was time well spent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 hour into the #FFXV Adamantoise fight. No end in sight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't deny that the guy had a big year. https://t.co/7UVRE8AP0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, I bit the curb (so to speak) and watched American History X. Gripping &amp; intense stuff from Ed Norton. Enough to overshadow any flaws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp that was 12 mins of nonstop #nye2016 fireworks. 
Honestly, they aren't that different to any other fireworks display I've seen....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 mins to spare, but @andy_trieu &amp; I managed to get a decent view of the fireworks #SydNYE https://t.co/zqhP1nzGYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaand with just hours left before the new year, 2016 claims another victim in Ronda Rousey. Kudos, 2016, kudos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd watch this. https://t.co/NIsGP4rUNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess that means it is time for a #Dishonored replay. https://t.co/LgLwGP1RSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus fu*king Christ, 2016 is not finishing quietly is it.... https://t.co/LIZDdeNrBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally saw #HellOrHighWater &amp; #KuboAndTheTwoStrings 
There have been some sh*t films &amp; some fantastic films in 2016 - these are the latter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never thought I would be saying this so soon and it breaks my heart saying it, but may the force be with you, Carrie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good fu*king grief, 2016,  haven't you taken enough from us already?
#RIPCarrie #CarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, so people didn't like the #AssassinsCreed movie? What a surprise. In other news, water is wet. https://t.co/vIrYZytlJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this #FFXV Christmas story is just too heartwarming for words. https://t.co/8qJLBb6PXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaand now we're reminded that 2016 STILL ain't over yet... #GeorgeMichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to all and if everything goes well, I'll have more to announce soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have something exciting in the works. Can't reveal much atm but here's a little #Overwatch teaser of what's coming,… https://t.co/zK595e9v9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HurdyIV Well since you asked 
https://t.co/Pva6f0mmnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished #Inside again. Still absolutely beautiful. Love how there's not a word &amp; yet it still has a better story than #Uncharted4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big news about Tracer - she doesn't need to wear her chronal accelerator 24/7!
Oh, and she also has a girlfriend. https://t.co/rjvtfZ9pra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't we just accept that #Overwatch comic for what it is - a moving short story ft. Tracer as a selfless badass &amp; a lonely Winston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely surprised at the amount of attention over Tracer's sexuality and whatnot in the new #Overwatch comic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goddamn it #Overwatch, why must you bring tears to my eyes with your latest Tracer comic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, why not? https://t.co/ZX7oGtkr1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, so the #AssassinsCreed movie is sh*t? 
In other news, the sky is blue &amp; #DonaldTrump has the intelligence of a 5 yr old handicapped kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've yet to finish all the side stuff in #FF15 and they're already giving us more stuff. What a great problem to ha… https://t.co/E8j8Q0dI5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st 2/3 of #RogueOne was quite the slog, but boy did they almost redeem it with that 3rd act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright #RogueOne let's see if you are a POS, a masterpiece, or something in between.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #FF15 piece by my buddy @cm_GG and quite possibly one of the few things I wholeheartedly agree with him on. https://t.co/SLycb9VZSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to a fan to make an AR Pokemon game that's better than #PokemonGO https://t.co/qojUFXuatn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably won't happen soon, but it would be nice. https://t.co/Flg7tkqmlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not jumping on the bandwagon or anything, but the #BIGBANGMADEFullAlbum is pretty fXXking amazing... https://t.co/bf7fm8d545]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched #YourName again. Just as beautiful as the first time, but with twice the amount of tears shed.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>