<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinhollinrake car parks more important than 3515 children in poverty in Thirsk - it was shameful today @CPAGUK #Endchildpoverty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burystedlabour In Dec 2015 4079 children in Poverty in BSE @JOChurchill4 but your MP talked in HOC about car parks… https://t.co/3dM6bS4nCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torbaylabour @TorbayLibDems Your local Tory MP prefers car parks to dealing with Child Poverty. https://t.co/Dt8fw9Kf3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_j_foster  over 5k of children in Torbay live in Poverty &amp; you talk about car parks - shameful.
https://t.co/XM2oE5ciEK @Torbay_Hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_j_foster You might like to explain why you think car parks more important than #childpoverty - shameful in H… https://t.co/ePMwHaPdm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CPAGUK Bury St Edmunds MP @Jochurchill4 thinks car parks are more important than child welfare - today in HOC talk… https://t.co/sJXhVrsEXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKuncut Conservative MPs Kevin Foster &amp; @Jochurchill4 talk about car parks at the expense of children in poverty -… https://t.co/G4fH6EMaUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware the ideas of autocorrect https://t.co/y88uR3Hb9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear USA
Fascism - it creeps up on you. 
Love 
The world https://t.co/fa7oCSn2kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English Democrat Goldspink - Cambridge is already on the map and doesn't need a visit from fascistic US president… https://t.co/LEm9HUYZV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't he ussually like to wear a fake police uniform - oh at least he has got his phoney badge https://t.co/wP4YVtSJLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a thing after getting a Masters degree I still couldn't do that thing expected of kids of 5 to say what my… https://t.co/A82rqVFHxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am sure the low graders will love this just as much as all the rest of the fascist guff he spouts https://t.co/h2Rd6u7IhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kind of DIY - just need sellotape &amp; you have my whole kit https://t.co/cGTAagVRcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomLondon6 GB prides itself on fairness - but probably one of the most corrupt governing classes in the world with revolving doors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielZeichner This is an unwanted &amp; unwelcome vote for most in @UKLabour don't let it become factional &amp; weaken opposition to Tories again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drbenwhite @theresa_may And remind me why NHS is facing crisis - being starved of £20bn funds by Government choice. This is deflection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are not - you have DOUBLED the figure. By the way UK residents cost spain £30m - Spanish residents in UK cost… https://t.co/8pzcStNhqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drbenwhite Govt estimate is max £300m &amp; this can include expats returning for health reasons. https://t.co/tGE1a2wLce PFI costs £2bn/yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For what its worth FBI recorded 17320 arrests for rape in 2015 all Americans https://t.co/z6xe2QmoQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickjcapone @OwenJones84 And the Cray's are your other role model for your kids ...really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/N5EzEOM6xl redneck v. Trump on Muslim ban. Not quite what you expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An impossible choice https://t.co/gdXyLRMmiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stellacreasy We might not always agree on our Labour politics but continue to admire your responses to this sort of abuse - best wishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourEoin Absolutely right - please keep taking this on. https://t.co/8PLDiTCDPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyJHardy I wont heckle. I have seen you deal with them. And you are right but if it gets the numbers on the ri… https://t.co/ezDE113hV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john3ners Update.. Kudos to Foyle where now 1107 people have signed the petition! https://t.co/3iz82CakT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TippersSimon Please share with me how many deaths from terrorism have been caused in the US by anyone from these n… https://t.co/ZypVmQZzHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TippersSimon @POTUS  it is not partof a war on radical islam it is an indiscriminate attack on people based on country of origin &amp; religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dave4labour Good to see comrades united against Trump https://t.co/J7GqW18FGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TippersSimon u obviously have no idea how irrelevant this @POTUS order is to combating terrorism but attack on lib… https://t.co/ULHlMLMO4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heidiallen75 Good to see your constituency signing up in such numbers v Trump visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StandUpToTrump Best banner - France called we want our statue back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ed_Miliband we must speak for the thousands of the people outside of this house ...voices of... no millions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minutes before Alan Duncan in HOC sits down at 8.45 the petition v Trump hits 1.5m #StandUpToTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielZeichner Nearly 6% of your constituents have signed petition against @realDonaldTrump visit powerful mandate… https://t.co/rOoOI76R5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You dont have to lie just offer alternative facts https://t.co/Rn1OmHSGUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 4k Cambridge signatures v. Trump visit. Join the protest at Great St Mary's https://t.co/qiuxmPeeJU @DanielZeichner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomLondon6 Economical with the truth - this isn't poor rules enforcement it is clear corruption. How corrupt are w… https://t.co/JMGOnjuixR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The no. of people saying no to Trump visit exceed Jedi's in the UK in 2001 - even in Cambridge. @PhilRodgers… https://t.co/iitPSCQc6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 2% of Cambridge people oppose Trump visit - so far over 3% in Brighton. Come on Cambs do better.… https://t.co/Q2L6Kb3se7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May wants an exception for British citizens - so muslim ban ok if you are a british muslim. May its just not OK. . https://t.co/i4WMbI6Raa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heidiallen75 Why is your government doing this - it is shameful, cruel and abuse of human rights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dwppressoffice @Conservatives Why are you doing this? https://t.co/FH9vE5fo2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check this out to know that there is not even any logic in Trumps banning order. https://t.co/qwldOugvom https://t.co/jUbeerNOUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st map lighter yellow least signups for https://t.co/8i0a8EUutS 2nd darker purple most UKIP votes in GE - see a pa… https://t.co/hK0Tt9426D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conservatives @UKIP This is a lesson repeated thru history of refugees stimulating industry &amp; growth - and you cho… https://t.co/UFf6V9ueLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheresaTheAppeaser Succintly put unfortunately Queen has record of dining with opponents of fundamental human righ… https://t.co/4n8wyQCp8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be no state visit full stop for this evil man https://t.co/0pTaaARQIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly - dont care about Queens embarassment - do care about stopping misogynist racist corporate fascist being le… https://t.co/yh1yvOnD5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ix7xuv2BM1 @heidiallen75 Your Govt, your leader has endorsed this racist &amp; legitimised his actions by silence. Speak out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK to withdraw from Euratom https://t.co/NoT9hnxbpp Just so foolish - @Conservatives just not competent &amp; failing us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Jb47yVXEq0 @DanielZeichner @UKLabour  How stupid is this for our economic future? The @Conservatives failing us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he turns up make this the largest demonstration against racism, fascism capitalist abuse &amp; misogyny ever. https://t.co/ZNwAeLnmhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What big hands you have........... https://t.co/3b51LIc5LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didnt think that easing workload, respecting professionals or paying a decent wage might help retention… https://t.co/8Symn59l9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/L9hpf8N4QX UKIP happy to use torture however inneffective &amp; inhumane https://t.co/VG0Pa5zlmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour need a strong alternative to beat 'deeply disappointing tory candidate to speak for all including the city https://t.co/RbLX519QbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35 yrs ago Beaconsfield by-election 1982 Labour's vote halved from 20.2% in 1979 to 10.4%. The candidate Tony Blair lost his deposit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politicshome &amp; how much has the region seen in cuts in expenditure &amp; investment over the last 6 years - Pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VIQYydHhMI Do the people of Stoke need someone prepared to defraud them of their taxes. https://t.co/Niwn851wZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be fun when the press ask him questions on metonymes &amp; anthromorphism. https://t.co/iZnJxbsEvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This can't be true if the President said he saw millions at his inauguration. https://t.co/jRGOg1fytw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And we caught them in a lie, a big lie and they (the media) are going to pay a big price." On the numbers attendin… https://t.co/5wsnrJHH1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will not dent the long term cuts in education spend since 2010 before £3bn planned cuts already spend less of… https://t.co/XOkHbMQV8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is chilling and frightening that he has people working for him prepared to lie so blatantly for him &amp; that this… https://t.co/tGWOS1SZxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My President is -sorry- has the biggest dick ever" Anyone who says otherwise is a liar. https://t.co/cPZeuPG3Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VIQYydHhMI This document describes Farrage as functionally illiterate &amp; outlines allegations of EU fra… https://t.co/EWFHxGDCds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourEoin Agree. Challenging the charlatans who have stolen our assets will require a revolution in thought and action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VIQYydHhMI The full document - UKIp fraudsters people of copeland &amp; Stoke should see this. https://t.co/JPaohyZxhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are seeing a fascist state in the making - this is the propoganda arm. What you saw is not what you saw - https://t.co/jdf8OBU2j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zelo_street Farrage functionally illiterate - according to Eu Olaf document https://t.co/VIQYydHhMI https://t.co/ZkLNpXMrsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VIQYydHhMI More evidence of sponging off taxpayers by UKIP/ Farrage https://t.co/ZkLNpXMrsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomentumCambs @UKLabour #hopenothate https://t.co/ON3NHxturB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely right. The grammar of those throwing abuse on twitter is appalling. https://t.co/5WSbtYfaZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haddenham Village as busy as Oxford Street .. who would have guessed! https://t.co/8WRaMzFQC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks - I was a bit confused by Daniel tweet today! https://t.co/yr3Ow0xfIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophie4labour Is Emily Thornberry meeting today. In Camaraderie it said it was at the CLP meeting on Friday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hopenothate #bridgesnotwalls @trbl_up_tmillrd Mill Road Cambridge on the way to "little Russia" https://t.co/ibcdlf6c9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harrylaststand You might also wish to know that the EU commission are investigating him for fraud… https://t.co/iZtmWGjTEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielZeichner Where and when Camaraderie said Friday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourCopeland Nuttal apparently faces allegations of fraud involving misuse of EU funds  https://t.co/Fte9byJDHe… https://t.co/CKcQn2T09j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The video &amp; the comments attached may show where the states are going - a divided society. The police embracing their new role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't Labour be standing up and argueing for their values not adopting Tory_UKIP to get elected. Legacy of Blai… https://t.co/t7dusjJ5L0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DpEgL74vjJ Removed from Nuttals website don't let people of Stoke forget he wants to stop them having an NHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigel_farage Trump describes “two simple rules”: “buy American and hire American.” So where is the trading partner… https://t.co/nM4rfWChCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbyn50plus Not much room for that "special realtionship" if it ever existedd https://t.co/q6sFh2pHPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour @Conservatives this is who we are doingBrexit trade deal with.Trump describes “two simple rules:buy American and hire American.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel4Copeland Well said but saddened you didn't make it. https://t.co/6CrsxvWzw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyburnhammp In a Tory world I guess it makes sense. #NHSCrisis https://t.co/q0vPuhg3Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EurpoeanYorks seeing your address reminded me of Harry Ramsdens in a nice way -"Biggest chip shop in a whole of Yo… https://t.co/kseXyI9ny3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Fte9byJDHe Tell me about this UKIP thing @TeddyUKIPClark @LabourCopeland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nd0QfTAwAW Opposition to PFI and privatisation at the heart of @jeremycorbyn @UKLabour @LabourCopeland… https://t.co/64tyiZJ8oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/90NTIhjgyC NHS Privatisation a Tory thing ...really?! @LabourCopeland @TeddyUKIPClark https://t.co/ZJ4NFptbSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardly worth going through the evidence again, Corbyn campaigned harder than any other remain politician. lie serve… https://t.co/8DtnlB7s9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YVoHcSFqfk @UKLabour @LabourCopeland this is what a Tory-UKIP Brexit has delivered - we can do better. @JC4PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourCopeland This thread was about the damage done by Tory cuts to NHS. UKIP want to give the NHS to profiteers - https://t.co/reBhHFQGbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conservatives What happened - what May says is not what was promised to those who voted out of the EU. Tory-UKIP c… https://t.co/mSbhqtaOAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour @jeremycorbyn Over 65% of Labour voters voted to remain in the EU please build the arguments against the… https://t.co/5o8gyIFAi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel4Copeland @LabourCopeland This is what UKIP offers on the NHS - say it loud. https://t.co/fXVeYOQ9TP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>