<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he actually say this? He's about as dim as a 6 volt bulb. https://t.co/5Rq35TEbcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As David Cameron found out, posing with farm animals is just inviting trouble. https://t.co/N2bnaiZE6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drumm returned to his mansion in Malahide. https://t.co/f7cLWxItYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All together now, Awwwwwwww. https://t.co/51BCEF9qHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Including himself? https://t.co/CpEs6Jhxyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoconnorbl who was the DA that let him off on the Trump university fraud again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@panmidwest @jasonomahony "Ate too many bananas, you know how it is, luv"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is America the first country to willingly vote for a tinpot dictator to replace democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsoamesmp @TimHenwood1 Actually, they are. Only problem is, they're reading from the Nazi history books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady I'm not appalled. He TOLD them this was what he was going to do. They still voted for him. You get the dictators you deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taxbod @openDemocracy that's ok. We'll remember that when we have to vote in a referendum on allowing the U.K. to leave the EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans: voted for the bag of snakes. Afterwards: but I didn't think the bag of snakes would bite us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House right now. https://t.co/6vpUz2CGdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Irish are next. https://t.co/E3BsNpsWPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They might want to revise that figure after trump's presidency. https://t.co/wekt2TeOtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autocar they've left it in the microwave too long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arthurhbaker @IrvineWelsh @CoryBooker you elected an actual fascist and are surprised when he starts acting all nazi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, he does like to sexually assault unwilling people. https://t.co/u7ZwXRKOHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 "You're my wife now, Dave"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twitter by letting overt nazis spread hate and threatening to kill people ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SovietSergey hopefully it kills quickly but excrutiatingly painfully. @EllenMorris1222]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that is the problem when you allow a foreign power to establish beachheads on your territory. https://t.co/AKTUPP8cZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SovietSergey could they get the message out, loud and clear, that tweeting is not voting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autocar cheap cologne and barolo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox actually, the whole of Europe has to vote on whether to let the UK leave or not, Funniest bit is, UK people won't get a say,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[paywalled. It'd be nice if you said that first. https://t.co/DtZgW0mpqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*worried laugh* https://t.co/nSKRULT4aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe target trump buildings and/or govt buildings instead? https://t.co/rOGgLedud6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MediocreDave ok, just Trump then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banning Americans from our countries might be a start. https://t.co/WvCR2DYEhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon your PM supports trump. Clean up your own front yard first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmch99 tutting at him and saying "ah now, you've gone too far this time!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, people are starting to cotton on to this. It's slightly too late though. https://t.co/4cYlWV5BJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Ireland we ban l-drivers from motorways, then expect them to be magically capable of driving on one when they pa… https://t.co/2H6uKoNfij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund because Brexit is thinly-veiled racism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colettebrowne or a bank account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colettebrowne we elected Bertie three times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill the smell for a start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLM_cork @despod a few well-placed signs and voila!! Imagine them saying "we went to the trump place in Clare, it was a dump!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drg1985 why is rum there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Donnie has been lied to about the location of female genitalia. https://t.co/MtQPd4QhFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland you forgot the "I'd rather pull out my own toenails with a pliers" option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww yeah, short selling, amiright? https://t.co/SJzBCY68o5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since we have the Obama Plaza, I think Clare Co. Council should rename their facility in Inagh to "The Trump Dump"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You on your knees, that must be a sight." https://t.co/KTSKMp1Jwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh please let this be true. https://t.co/j8h5PaFjO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is all Reich https://t.co/MWLVQeHJ7v one for @karlbrophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SovietSergey Vlad will call him a cuck and then all hell will break loose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May snubbing the Irish govt doesn't seem so bright now, does it? So Brexiteers, tell us why we should allow… https://t.co/KityfzMbRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have they told Trumplethinskin yet? https://t.co/JozETcr8zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satirists give up, you can't be funnier than this president. https://t.co/mRUcngiBa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[current mood. https://t.co/X0gfmQjwbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JolyonMaugham @jessicaelgot looks like the deckchairs have had a further re-arranging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, the irony. this would be funny. @JolyonMaugham https://t.co/ZNNevL4MpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerrytodayrk @AnMailleach @jerosullivanRK there is a non-politician running it. Tony O'Brien. The guy responsible for nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American voters be all like... https://t.co/t5EaQ5p8GD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[or give him an alt-high-five. https://t.co/LNE4AlqKHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wait, he's got four years to be worse. https://t.co/haqq1yN9qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @TelegraphRugby @GavinMairs the funniest word in that headline is "elite"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything to be said for another mass? https://t.co/ahePhLQI3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please god, grow a brain for alt-right Clyde. https://t.co/3XRSR3ekcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[something, something, metaphor for the US right now. https://t.co/hyhW7eJpnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenkinsella up to the big smoke for the day? Have you the hang sandiches?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnMailleach Will somebody buy him some lego, FFS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits They could always write about an "alleged murderer of dozens".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JolyonMaugham I'd be wary of using that description to refer to the Irish Nazi Times. I'm afraid its gone all Daily Heil recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_Asquith @IrishTimesBiz "resistance is futile, you will be assimilated "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally is actually a 400lb hairy, disturbed dude. https://t.co/qkC8YN3Zn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman wigs on the green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozlandia @LACELimerick @UL @thechieftains @IWorldAcademy Are you aware of @Mexrrissey ? Mexican Morrissey tribute band. They're brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda The same ones that invite actual nazis into the room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taxbod its going to be judge Judy, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoconnorbl LOL, Brits in being arrogant cocks shocker!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PistonHeads Easy. RS6. The beast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but nobody wants them? https://t.co/Pii4orlSJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiffofCordite I'm polishing the boots in anticipation of a late callup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimForde Turn it into a starbucks and be done with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's on, like fat Pat's thong". That Malcolm Tucker has such a way with words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlBrophy @AnMailleach reading the Daily Heil gives you brain cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AodhBC removal on Friday followed by barbecue on Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor @kurteichenwald he knew exactly what he was doing. He's establishing dominance by wiping his cock on their curtains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHellzapop it's just hilarious watching all the trump supporters slowly realise that he is going to eat them all alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AodhBC it was very disconcerting at first when the male family members go for the cheek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AodhBC are you stil on two bisous? You know you're family when it gets to four or more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The SC judges tomorrow morning getting ready to read the #Article50  judgement https://t.co/6hB8kBtqmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomaninHavana @taxbod at which point, all hell will break loose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samsanders @cspan in a week or so its going to be something like this? https://t.co/kPw2ouTfzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected murderer of many still lurking in background. https://t.co/ValVEDFknn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LDNCalling @taxbod Lads, I think i know how that Trident accidental launch happened. https://t.co/rohJjvXull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidschneider and your specialist subject is "Alternative truths from the Trump Administration and actual facts". "i don't accept that"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josefoshea "Are you going to try to enter the UK through our non-existent border?" "No." "That's grand so, off you go!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JolyonMaugham @TheLawyerTasha I would have expected a little more of a pose since you are now considered "Hot". Or at least a hairdresser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpdiggins this will reduce unemployment, raise median income, reduce burden on state. they are using health insurance as a weapon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpdiggins Because if so, there is a genocide happening, not of race, but of social class. They are eliminating the poor. 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repealing healthcare in US will kill 43,000 people P.A. Am i right in thinking that stastically, those on welfare will be hit hardest? 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know when Trump said "Drain the swamp"? Well, I think this is what he actually meant. https://t.co/KXYu9RRQLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimForde Fuck that, we need blackout drunk fridays once a month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he serves no time for a fraudulent loan. Well done, the establishment. looking out for each other. https://t.co/9iuSAP0Tlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoreenBowden @ccferrie Irish = undoc, everyone else = illegal. Do they really think that will help them? they shd plan for deportation now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[three are some shower of useless wasters. https://t.co/aXetQ3gDH0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>