<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what makes America great right here, teachers (read: human beings) like this: https://t.co/1pT1cMlKHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/cLoimIcYUm #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/cLoimIcYUm #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/cLoimIcYUm #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raychel____ @kalpenn I really hope the new administration doesn't change the vm because kal is amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I called my senators and the WH to express my disdain for confirming Sessions. Am I wrong or is it @kalpenn 's voice still on the comms vm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 end of this convo. I calmly &amp; logically debated and answered all your questions for you to deflect and provide 0 discourse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 hes endangering lives, creating a nation of fear, destroying foreign pol &amp; appointing the most underqualified cabinet ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 1. Judging by your Twitter he's not even your president. 2. That's honestly what you came back with? That's such a cop out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 uh he's draining federal funds and putting people in charge that have no idea what they're doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 baits Isis &amp; encourages further attacks. Intelligent appointments and funds for intelligence combatting domestic terrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 to start do not remove joint chiefs and intelligence from SC. Do not propagate narrative that all Muslims are bad b/c that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29  most US terrorist attacks past 30 yrs have been from US citizens. All 15 9/11 terrorists wouldn't be included in this ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes same guy who said he was a Leninist and wanted to "destroy the state" right? https://t.co/HejuasNe01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commanderpark29 1. And neither are you 2. This is unconstitutional. US has an extreme vetting process already https://t.co/FHqODPYFiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint I just called. The woman on the phone said to contact them on the website since they don't take messages on that line....???..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats @SenateDems  American living abroad and trying to call my senators but their mailbox is always full. What should I do to help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson ...which shows that he 1. Does not respect our constitution 2. Is willing to turn his own prejudices  into legislation /4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson ... equal treatment of all citizens regardless of religion, sexuality, race, etc. He advised Pres Trump on #Muslimban /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson ...I urge you to demand your colleagues for further vetting of Sessions via a second hearing. Sessions does not stand for /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorIsakson hi, I am a constituent living abroad. I just called your office regarding my concern over the nomination of Sen Sessions /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue ...which shows that he 1. Does not respect our constitution 2. Is willing to turn his own prejudices  into legislation /4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue ...for equal treatment of all citizens regardless of religion, sexuality, race, etc. He advised Pres Trump on #Muslimban /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue ...I urge you to demand your colleagues for further vetting of Sessions via a second hearing. Sessions does not stand for /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue hi, I am a constituent living abroad. I just left a voicemail regarding my concern over the nomination of Sen Sessions /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker From NJ living abroad 🇦🇺 When my non-US friends ask me if theres any leader fighting for justice&amp;equality I proudly point to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the America I love: https://t.co/lnVpYtn1u5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say it louder for the 'all lives matter Christians' in the back https://t.co/4NhziNOYSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/fA1OsURMV8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/fA1OsURMV8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/fA1OsURMV8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheResistance starting line-up: @TeenVogue, @ACLU, park rangers, @ShaunKing, Shia LaBeouf and captain @BernieSanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicolecammarota I love you too. It's so hard to watch this from over here and feel helpless but glad there are ppl like you in the us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cried tears watching this. This is the America I want to be associated with. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/1kMQruBo7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't get enough of this https://t.co/7dFBsvlx70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Hoboken today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/7bJHmgdO6B #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Hoboken today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/7bJHmgdO6B #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Hoboken today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/7bJHmgdO6B #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STOP my sides hurt https://t.co/mHSysiwAKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Irvington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/AnoZTscAUp #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Irvington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/AnoZTscAUp #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Irvington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/AnoZTscAUp #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit I even know about this issue and could answer this question .. and I only have a bachelors degree. #wtf… https://t.co/1kHWjv0Bnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Bridgeton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/r41me6fcbX #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Bridgeton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/r41me6fcbX #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Bridgeton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/r41me6fcbX #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/o3co7ImOj1 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/o3co7ImOj1 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/o3co7ImOj1 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, 2 people were injured by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/d8HL3PVGKt #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, 2 people were injured by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/d8HL3PVGKt #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, 2 people were injured by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/d8HL3PVGKt #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/Hr02ESX1aA #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/Hr02ESX1aA #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/Hr02ESX1aA #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/aQ9gSfDnre #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/aQ9gSfDnre #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/aQ9gSfDnre #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All in favor of ignoring the 22nd amendment in favor of Obama say aye #PresidentObama #obamafarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[president of my HEART #obamafarewelladdress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/8QvflT1SIT #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/8QvflT1SIT #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/8QvflT1SIT #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Paterson today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BcjpztEdfX #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Paterson today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BcjpztmBRn #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Paterson today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BcjpztEdfX #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/t9eRuOPzhP #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/t9eRuOPzhP #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/t9eRuOPzhP #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BebchJAvdi #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BebchJAvdi #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BebchJAvdi #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BHtc7Rdnf2 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BHtc7Rdnf2 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Camden today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/BHtc7Rdnf2 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Burlington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/y6xzJimIim #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Burlington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/y6xzJimIim #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Burlington today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/y6xzJimIim #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and everyone from New Jersey said amen. https://t.co/91rSsR8Nc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/PkGh9fIx7e #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/PkGh9fIx7e #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Jersey City today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/PkGh9fIx7e #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Willingboro today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/TaJovA3SM8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Willingboro today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/TaJovA3SM8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Willingboro today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/TaJovA3SM8 #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/A7IQPzJheG #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/A7IQPzJheG #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one injured by guns in Trenton today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/A7IQPzJheG #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/ddvg0VOF1H #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/ddvg0VOF1H #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Plainfield today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/ddvg0VOF1H #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegrandtour you're coming to Sydney!? My partner is CRAZY (fan girl screaming level) about you guys and I would love to buy him tickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepTomMacArthur, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/UEyQ1nJlTh #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/UEyQ1nJlTh #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker, another one killed by guns in Newark today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/UEyQ1nJlTh #shootatweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen casting department: *puts diamond earring on 'kevin's' left ear* "fucking perfect. well done us."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[german shepherds are my reason for living https://t.co/JEptDFLu30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking off my new years resolutions this month instead of next month because 2016 is the devils year and I will have no more of it. #bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thread https://t.co/nXc6yonDn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez, another one killed by guns in Monroe Township today. What will you do about it? https://t.co/GpzlAU5Z88 #shootatweet]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>