<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kominsens @nzherald That was my point - win some lose some - some people will like his handling,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstevnz @nzherald @nzhpolitics Labour will be hoping he brings people with him - fingers in many pies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstevnz @nzherald @nzhpolitics Had some strong views on seabed and foreshore,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win some lose some? Political Roundup: Bill English loses the Trump immigration debate https://t.co/7AJ5HDEuyC via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bryce_edwards @MarkHubbard33 Who is Waatea backing this election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big call. Willie Jackson dumps Maori Party for Labour https://t.co/hcuOX0RBQX via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onThePaepae how long ago was that - show finished years ago didn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Delwynd1 @SkyNews God ;-) - sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onThePaepae @DailyCaller Fox is morphing stranger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onThePaepae @DailyCaller I'd never seen him B4 - the aw shucks approach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good @skyNews is boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onThePaepae @DailyCaller He is a very good propagandist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onThePaepae @DailyCaller its very odd - headline sells as querulous - but turns into justification. PS have u seen Tucker Carlson on Fox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives Defend Stephen Miller: A ‘Brilliant And Courageous’ Man https://t.co/xwO9tF0rKn via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My giddy aunt. 'It's disgusting' - Kiwis give their take on Trump's travel ban https://t.co/u08oJ0sttW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's travel ban bears the hallmarks of historic 'shock events'; don't let it fool you https://t.co/4UCd5r8vca via @dallasnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @Carolyn_nth same outcome shurely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick And ironic by the sound of it ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brett O'Riley resigns as ATEED boss https://t.co/KzOH8zwjmY via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFieldNZ That's the trouble with rogue states ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDHB head steps down as State Services escalates probe https://t.co/8iKTOGAYPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHe64908658 @redsteeze As opposed to those who have been involved in deaths and have Trump investments - happily,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont agree with substantive blog, but HRC role in promoting spokespeople to Checkpoint is odd.  https://t.co/GDEzQa5dSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This promo would not have been cheap. Highlights: Liverpool stem losing streak in Chelsea draw https://t.co/XSTUXJEh2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FBI’s Secret Rules — an investigative series by @theintercept https://t.co/eYKdx7l8qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubFeatures @realDonaldTrump @reporter__ryan @NewshubNZ True - shambolic, mean spirited - pointless but not a muslim ban at this stage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLerner @althecat @Medium Is Trump really out to destroy the Trans Community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf @althecat Yes - much worse to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@althecat @dpfdpf Not sure - you are correct though - The Right is falling in behind Trump, Remember the dire warni… https://t.co/4Fx8mus3v2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bannon Files: Divorce Records Reveal Marital Discord and Questionable Parenting https://t.co/1YKMOe3she via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time goes strong. 'There’s true risk that the world dissolves into a dystopian nightmare' https://t.co/DZA4NTSM3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtreacher @Pno_nwa @whaeapower I'm surprised - MRF is normally rational. Its not at all racist to question the level of immigration,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pno_nwa @robtreacher @whaeapower Racist? - My giddy aunt! You can question  or oppose immigration without being a racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think Trump will do a "toot toot" as they pass the Ecuadorian Embassy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spikedonline any port in a storm ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@althecat @dpfdpf Farrar has warned about Trump ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervRobertson @emmawehipeihana An odd couple - any which way :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klendool @billbennettnz @CheckpointRNZ @CnrJoe I guess not -it would be surprising if a Checkpoint survey had foun… https://t.co/yGv2K7NTf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klendool @billbennettnz @CheckpointRNZ @CnrJoe Yeah - spot surveys are nonsense - whether they are on talkback rad… https://t.co/NDV4Tkj0K8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz @klendool @CheckpointRNZ @CnrJoe My reckon too - I just hear that RNZ was keen to have John J Campbe… https://t.co/4FXJEAbs9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Situational Assessment 2017: Trump Edition” by @jgreenhall https://t.co/lNdDyBQ6Z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dean_Nimbly Cold shower for you Mr Nimbly ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy My Giddy aunt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz @CheckpointRNZ @CnrJoe Exactly right. I wonder if the @CheckpointRNZ aud has got more liberal with JC there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phillipglasgow Are you suggesting there are no working class people driving Prius? That excludes most Uber drivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz I'm cooking tea ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz @CheckpointRNZ @CnrJoe Plus its a Leftish audience - these spot polls are always nonsense - but especially so with RNZ demo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHe64908658 @redsteeze Maybe - It loses credibility excluding Saudis and UAE main sponsors of terrorism. Incom… https://t.co/1c21LY3Qty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze @ChrisHe64908658 You still need to be competent with the implementation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOOD STORY.Ministry staffer alleged to have helped foreign firm prepare licence application https://t.co/PhNtmU146G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rumpole3 Gorgeous things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newshub says Kylie Bax is a player too ;-)  How Trump’s immigration directive exposed GOP rifts https://t.co/wPrBGNNFUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posts faeces - who does that remind you of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JTheory_ @idealogmag crazy to launch campaign while he did not have own person aa AG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Let's face it - the people who object to Peters and his views on immigration qare never going to take his views seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Does everybody have to make a statement on Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems optimistic merger is going ahead, Sky TV to pay early dividend ahead of Vodafone merger https://t.co/TvF9IhC6cD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holding company chiefs speak out against Trump immigration ban https://t.co/4mmljscyif via @prweek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ResearchRanter I have one of those too - has come to disbelieve anything that was pre Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newshub has Govt turning to advice from Kylie Bax from her ties to Donald Trump. When was last time they met? Does he know he knows her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake JeremyScahill twitter account being used by pro-Trump campaigners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Okay - ta - there will always be a base I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like we should be hearing more about how working class Trump voters are thinking - to see if support is slipping or rising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goshahoods @jeremyscahill It sounds like the account has been hacked- no doubt pro trump people will retweet extensively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremyscahill I can only hope that you have been hacked ... it sounds that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremyscahill Do we have to avoid embarrassing facts now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aus_business @MSMWatchdog2013 @australian They'll be cheap to hire ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop - seems like it is questionable. Thanks Jessica. https://t.co/TENcLimlJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @snopes Wow.Anywhere else? Seems remiss of msm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know if this is true - can't see why msm would hide it. https://t.co/tVaeUinFkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LBJ1941 @josiepagani Rabid racist of course,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCE_PC @GraemeEdgeler That's true - she may well poetry as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @Pno_nwa I;m being a bit silly ;-) - It must have a compliant soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange choice fromLabour for promoting shadow Cabinet ... https://t.co/Bt0me5VPHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JodiIhaka @nzherald @nzhpolitics Did she fall over? Why not get @AndrewLittle MP in that pose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wikileaks can't move on ... https://t.co/V0PE04jaJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tereoputake @lornaajohnson @paulbrislen Prefer him to Key]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @Pno_nwa I'm too conservative ...;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__BLiP Good point - item seems to take claim at face value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunmen attack mosque in Canada during evening prayers https://t.co/ByrMfjchLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @Pno_nwa The notion of a cat on a leash is somewhat wrong - like a labrador up a tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen Snatching defeat from the jaws of victory ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THR @WilliamHMacy He 'd be good as Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that true? Or opinion? Internet users increasingly 'desensitised' to ads on mobile sites, apps, Snakk Media says https://t.co/U5m4D5GNe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conradhackett Why are Americans so impressed about people having a college degree - its an outlook that snubs  working class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markjschilling @Slate No views - Trump has a million opinions doesn't he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS As the Wellingtonista says - there are fascists in our midst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markjschilling @Slate Because - some claim the Trump Project is anti- jew - just saying it seems unlikely given approach to Israel,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanmearns @NZHumanRights Does that mean you cant slag off at Aussies - seems like big ask for Chappel Hadlee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS I was being polite - silly of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Okay - not sure what he can say beyond America is wrong on this.admit more Muslims i guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @LewSOS sorry - Newshub sd English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Hasn't  English said he is agin Trump immigration policy and would not do it here? - Newshub reported]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate Do we really think that Trump is anti-jew considering role of son in law etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @Pno_nwa Cat on a leash ...pfoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog comment: "Wellington’s supposed to be a liberal bubble, but fascists are everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nitrone @spikedonline @SpikeD Its mind boggling there are many factors ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nitrone @spikedonline @SpikeD Very true - openly complicit with a corrupt system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzzashow Especially - Ban White Old Men !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nitrone @spikedonline @SpikeD Agree 100 per cent - Dems seem to be lost tho - Warren and Bernie seem to be best hope - both quite old.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>