<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this guy more than he can imagine. On one hand, it's hard to believe he's turning four… https://t.co/WYc1dOk4VQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media offers a toxic combination of escapism, envy and pride. https://t.co/ycFdfBTRSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our social media habits are a window into our souls: https://t.co/q2nR90VZsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people in the prime of their lives wasting 7 hours per week on social media? https://t.co/WXK6F2cW6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fire of pride can't burn very long without the fuel of comparison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of this guy. Loved hearing him talk about his vision for Grace Hill with an incredible… https://t.co/ukM5vZvaeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't follow God for outcomes or for the benefits package; we follow him because we love him." - @bcloritts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a lighter note, I also preached about repentance yesterday. You can listen here: https://t.co/RtgYNIKZUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we won't allow Jesus to change our minds, can we really call Him Lord?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Christians, we are all aliens and strangers.  That should shape our refugee response.  https://t.co/Y2V0RWMKRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When our city, country or world is talking about something, the church should too. Refugees are a gospel issue: https://t.co/LqIaggsYrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long before refugees ever became a political issue, they were a gospel issue. New Blog: https://t.co/SyI0kYcaGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightYearsIP speak up passionately, respectfully and gently.  That's my goal - see previous tweets for my thoughts on refugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never changed anyone's mind by belittling them.  You can be persuasive or insulting but not both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As an American, I have many thoughts about how our country has gone from, "Give me your tired,… https://t.co/lK1zq47QLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus calls us to a life of self denial for the good of others and He has the most all encompassing definition of others ever articulated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is completely incoherent, never mind wrong, to say you are Pro Life and against refugees and immigrants. https://t.co/ShPHwel20n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be pro life in a way that melts stone hearts and revives crushed spirits.https://t.co/VeovFubCdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be selectively pro-life. It's an all or nothing deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our world desperately needs the church to advance a culture of life for the unborn, for women, for refugees, and for the disabled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real leaders are easy to spot. They're more afraid of losing their integrity than losing their job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for our College Community Group tonight at GW.  Hit up @jamesmarshallg for more info!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the way Restoration City is responding to Boundless so far: https://t.co/QNO6Q6ljWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your attitude at work opening or closing doors for the gospel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you put your hope in people, you'll crush them under the weight of your expectation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to get the hang of this smiling thing! https://t.co/aKS0B9rY0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power in you is greater than the challenge in front of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self centered never leads to significant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how often getting more information cools our outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We most need to read our Bibles when we least feel like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's when we come to the end of ourselves that we hear God most clearly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Aidan: leaning forward, full of joy and life.  Hard to believe this little one turns 2… https://t.co/mDFIRjDqnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our participation in the temporary is shaped by our anticipation of the eternal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The certainty of our citizenship in heaven carries us through all the uncertainties of our earthly citizenship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gossiping about other churches will only weaken, not strengthen, yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If you are not firm in faith, you will not be firm at all.” (Is.7:9)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venting frustration in prayer is always going to accomplish more than venting on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray First, Act Second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self righteousness blinds us to the depths of God's love for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: "Do you know Daddy has been alive for 39 years?"

Jack: "Wow, are you almost dead?!?"

I now know where a mid-life crisis comes from!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pride focuses on what everyone else did wrong. Humility tempers that with the reminder of our own shortcomings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If grace hasn't captured our hearts, it won't shape our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We won't be able to extend grace until we first learn how to receive grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course people don't deserve it. That's why it's called grace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdeckard what's the other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the start of Boundless this past Sunday?  Talk is posted online for you at https://t.co/y6fAHuc3CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sobering and absolutely true! https://t.co/HhiHQlnodx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’ve settled for a version of Christianity that works without the power of God, you’ve settled for something that isn’t Christianity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brrr.....it's cold out there! https://t.co/QquxNPf0Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're bored as a Christian, it's because you're disobedient as a Christian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Church is the only society that exists for the benfit of those who are not its members.” – William Temple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhilaration: working really hard for something you really believe in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone wins when leaders get better. - Bill Hybels https://t.co/dio5nwOcKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_mcgee I'm from Syracuse!  And it's really not that bad here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bundle up, kids, it's cold out there - just don't miss the start of Boundless this morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to start our new series, "Boundless: The People, Power, And Mission Of God" tomorrow… https://t.co/ll395VSB0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup, I'm in love with her! https://t.co/mxtTEiVxk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News out of Fort Lauderdale is heart breaking.  Be near, Lord Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The church is most beautiful when she's most sacrificial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our ability to rest is directly linked to our belief in God's sovereignty. He's in control, so I don't have to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst thing to waste is time - no way to get it back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is always telling me to "send good thoughts" to people.  It's hard to imagine a more meaningless phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting what I pray will be the most culture shaping series yet at Restoration City this… https://t.co/mnnmVm6Erm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carry the wonder of Christmas back to work with you today. https://t.co/exTbjxHAxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The grace that forgives compels action. https://t.co/OHBkBRCT4d https://t.co/OmzA2fKaod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are loved by the God of limitless faithfulness; He’s never going to change His mind about you.… https://t.co/PdiCE7lQBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back over 2016 and realizing how frequently "hardest" and "best" travel together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting gospel amnesia today at Wellspring: https://t.co/RX525rXcWb https://t.co/BtmRmvPdYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What shaped our 2016 wasn’t God’s willingness to offer grace, but rather our
responses to that grace. Read more:… https://t.co/co9S92Ia34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wellspring: A New Year's Guide" starts tomorrow.  Download your copy and follow along: https://t.co/d5dQA5zdfL https://t.co/LA80364Mc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you missed this from @timkellernyc last week, it's well worth the read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God isn't just an end of life insurance policy.  He's the fountain of all our life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s impossible to get into the presence of God and leave disappointed. https://t.co/HQOmaVP3gH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't have to spend our lives looking for hope.  At Christmas, hope came to find us. https://t.co/jw0TRA1Qsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For to us a child is born, to us a son is given" (Is. 9:6) https://t.co/OZ9KQoeRTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Eve with Restoration City. 4pm. The Synetic Theater. 

Love to have you join us if… https://t.co/lor9qDu0Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbross319 would be a total game changer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I say we give a Nobel prize to the person who invents an auto-reply for text messages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus wasn't born to admire our perfection.  He was born to offer us His.  https://t.co/rsyEqXqZlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the longing for perfect prevent you from enjoying good. New blog: https://t.co/75B8BqadPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas From The McGowans. New on the blog: https://t.co/h01l3H3mBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, @zulily is so cheap because it takes a few weeks to deliver! #thingsIwishIknewearlier #Christmascrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many attacks on God's character are misdirected frustration over our own apathy and disobedience. https://t.co/K8YxInvbLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling to find hope these days? Then yesterday's message at Restoration City is for you. "Glory In The Gloom" - https://t.co/nrphkKGktf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for tomorrow at Restoration City!  Diving headlong into all things Christmas! https://t.co/2gqMt0QW1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God is strong enough to overcome his enemies by becoming vulnerable, transparent, and humble." - John Oswalt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key and often overlooked distinction! https://t.co/g8pAVN9AMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of what we call drama, the Bible calls sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's going to disciple my kids. I'd like it to be me! https://t.co/xbPlqcrFJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus didn’t come to perfect your image but to transform your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel isn’t a convenient accessory to our ambition. It’s a total remapping of it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time with Jesus fuels passion for Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reston/Herndon friends, here's a great opportunity to connect with a new @SummitNetwork church plant launching in 2… https://t.co/3YPRLpQB0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision comes from abiding.  So many of our vision problems are abiding problems in disguise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People flourish under the care of a leader and wither under the demands of a dictator. Look around you - more flourishing or withering?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insecure leaders use power to hurt and control. Secure leaders to bless and release!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas should be wonderful, not stressful. New on the blog: https://t.co/lZI8btKiIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmarkcomer grateful for friends like you that point the way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So often, we keep people at a distance because we know that if we let them near, we would be forced to abandon our pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hope of Christmas is a perfect Savior, not a perfect holiday.  New on the blog: https://t.co/AoDNx901Nk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>