<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What would Trump the candidate have said about that, I wonder? (2/2)
https://t.co/YaewcVnXn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's strategy for managing his first foreign policy test--renewed violence in Ukraine fueled by Russia--is just to ignore it. (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing Trump will pick based on who has more followers. Currently @JusticeHardiman. https://t.co/sBYlId9GRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawDavF @BrunoTertrais I'm not saying we won't get our hair a bit mussed. But 20, 30 million casualties. Tops. Depended on the breaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawDavF @BrunoTertrais Who in our field doesn't love it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Purity of essence, eh? https://t.co/WwCrLQKrqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A headline-worthy insight indeed! If only someone had thought term this term up before now!
https://t.co/07qILOWYjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This account is almost certainly a fake. I am deleting my retweet. Please delete yours too. 
https://t.co/toImF4D1r8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted "Follow Your Conscience" Cruz, ladies and gentlemen. 
https://t.co/2GUGsW2bVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMizaur Yes, I think you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ROK officials are relieved that DPRK will apparently launch a Musadan, you know it's not going well.
https://t.co/HlPax7zivL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those who foolishly sought power by riding the back of the tiger ended up inside."
--John F Kennedy, Inaugural Address, 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDexterClaw Well, at least I acknowledge when I change my mind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On reflection, waiver-less sanctions would be mistake (though still support new Congressional sanctions on Russia).
https://t.co/Br5iOMzs8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope it's true that court orders have been obeyed--it's the main reason I went to Dulles today. But judicial verification needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First protest of my life. Because, seriously, if you don't stand for the rule of law, what will you stand for?… https://t.co/fM57GMW8Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As CBP at Dulles reportedly refuses to abide by court order over attorney access, let me re-up this. https://t.co/JsKVO6RTkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens next--Does Trump respect the courts? If not, does the GOP support him?--provides a profound test of democracy's resilience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a reason this news is coming out on a Saturday night when media attention is focused elsewhere. https://t.co/A1M25IWP9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mean heroic choices like fleeing to China and Russia, rather than being held to account for your actions? https://t.co/kwUw4Hs2xZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have started to understand the concept of the "banality of evil" recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd also note that Mattis does not control the CIA, which, Trump says, includes officials supportive of torture. https://t.co/sdiS0gaLGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fairness, Trump has now said he will defer to Mattis on torture. https://t.co/bhLlEb6F0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mattis will save us" is the plaintive cry of nat sec community. Given torture &amp; poss lifting of Russia sanctions, how influential is he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was actually thinking of Nitze's "Assuring Strategic Stability in an Era of Détente." Nitze was on Team B, right? https://t.co/FnM3kJcN3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fully aware! I also know that any idea inevitably gets watered down, so better to start with it in purest form.
https://t.co/TQVcOVyRt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress must act. Pass sanctions on Russia with no waiver authority. Override veto. https://t.co/4SsgBD6Q8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a malignancy who poses a profound threat the sovereignty and political independence of the US and our allies. (5/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, support for arms control should not be confused with naivety about Russia or, more specifically, Putin. (4/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record, arms controllers (like me) argue for US-Russia cooperation on strategic weapons because it makes us (and them) safer. (3/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia must pay a price for its interference in our election. Lifting sanctions would severely undermine deterring future attacks. (2/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirms rumors relayed by @FabricePothier yesterday. A profoundly concerning and dangerous idea. (1/n)  https://t.co/4SsgBD6Q8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating how nuclear hawks can bash Obama admin officials for being insensitive to assurance, but not mention POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only a matter of time until someone invokes again the importance of throw-weight ratios after the first round of a nuclear exchange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assuring allies is like the national debt--it only matters when a Dem is in the WH. @ArmsControlWonk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another thing that amazes me about many nat sec professionals: lack of willingness to discuss implications of Trump for assure/deter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how many nat sec professionals still give Trump benefit of doubt onNATO. "Maybe a ploy, to get allies to pay more on defense..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how serious nat sec professionals treat off-hand Trump comments as serious policy proposals and make up details as if he said them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelb8309 @NuclearAnthro Ah! 140 characters can promote misunderstandings... Glad that's cleared up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelb8309 @NuclearAnthro So the question is now not whether I have evidence. It's whether you are interested in the evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelb8309 @NuclearAnthro Now, according to CNN, IC officials have convinced him torture does work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelb8309 @NuclearAnthro Then he spoke to Mattis in November and suddenly changed his mind. https://t.co/akCge71Vdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelb8309 @NuclearAnthro OK. Here's the evidence. Trump was (mostly) pro torture in the campaign. https://t.co/32mUu1jm1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalling. Also apparently illustrates how Trump's views are set by whoever he talked to last. Get used to it.
https://t.co/Rwfvq100bF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many tweets these days end with the word "sad." Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pledged to accept the validity of the election if he won. Couldn't even keep that promise. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To my friends who argue that US advances are making counterforce easier, note this is a two-way street:
https://t.co/RsNUZlHw8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder that negotiating a treaty and then failing to ratify does not lead to the status quo ante.
https://t.co/S9SuTR2t0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love it--but you might want a hyphen (or two?) in there. @MaryNorrisTNY https://t.co/Dtdg4tMVfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP_Hunter Not necessarily. George's tweet was that new missiles are being manufactured, not that new missiles are used for tests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP_Hunter I was wrong.
https://t.co/1CDdsGJfSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeWHerbert @ArmsControlWonk @shashj Are new airframes manufactured?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP_Hunter @ArmsControlWonk @shashj I believe missiles are periodically refurbished, not replaced by new ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sputnik mentions Yu-74 hypersonic glider in addition to Yu-71. Is this new? @russianforces @TheDexterClaw https://t.co/6US1UhtsCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP_Hunter @ArmsControlWonk @shashj I don't think new missiles have been manufactured for years, but am not 100% sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk @shashj 5 early fails + 2 recent =&gt; 7/168 = 4%. Agree?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk @shashj I was just trying to calculate the overall failure rate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK and US Trident missiles taken from common pool (I believe). So should consider total failure (c. 4%), not UK failure rate (20%).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Patriots played the Yankees at, say, bridge, who would you root for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Metro nightmare today. 1 to 1.5 MILLION riders on platform at Court House. Easily. @unsuckdcmetro https://t.co/f297rfugF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was wrong. Easier just to make up new facts. Apparently.
https://t.co/hHJ1XP8Ph3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to dismiss crowd sizes in 3, 2, 1...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmsControlWonk You mean has a bigger effect on the outcome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ThanksObama. You are missed already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worldwane He just admitted to Congress that before recent briefings he didn't know what DoE did. Watch him. https://t.co/hhl3AJkxvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worldwane Are you denying that as a presidential candidate Gov Perry called for elimination of DoE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran for president twice &amp; advocated scrapping @ENERGY without knowing its role. Worst part: Not even surprised.
https://t.co/TGe9B0NS74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@konrad_muzyka That was sarcasm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Friendly_Gadget I doubt that a nice modern nuke like you has a Po-210 initiator...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day of discounted registration for the 2017 Carnegie International Nuclear Policy Conference. https://t.co/on3UULNnSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intellectually equivalent to Nixon claiming that Woodward and Bernstein undermined the Presidency.
https://t.co/AMEWQ9bus6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coffman_Law @ArmsControlWonk Fundamental goal is to enhance national and global security. Nuclear risks are important but not only danger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coffman_Law @ArmsControlWonk I'm late to the party on this. Will add one thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also reductions agreement should be mutually beneficial and stand on its own merit. No linkage to sanctions relief. https://t.co/lZkpPL4JoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week it's reductions; last week it's an arms race. Don't treat these utterances as serious policy statements. https://t.co/oqHMQCMIrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The interview is terrifying. Don't normalize it by praising one off-hand comment about nuclear arms reductions. https://t.co/eUxv9HoRId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@capitalweather Help! I need to get to Middleburg VA from DC tomorrow. What's best bet for timing? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A republic, if you can keep it."
--Benjamin Franklin (maybe)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Trump indicated in September he would replace the generals, who knew he meant the DC national guard?
https://t.co/boe8LrmFwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoigu remarks reported (in brief and confused form) here: 
https://t.co/aoTTzY1Aiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia DefMin Shoigu's remarks that conventional weapons could replace nukes are part of a trend. My analysis:
https://t.co/sqgfNbYmoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, and by the way, discounted registration for the conference ends on Tuesday!
https://t.co/on3UULNnSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't vote, we might end up with Panely McPanel-Face. @Joshua_Pollack https://t.co/e8waNbLhWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day to vote for topic of final panel at 2017 Carnegie International Nuclear Policy Conference... Please RT!
https://t.co/e8waNbLhWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those were the key takeaways for me. You can watch the whole speech here. (15/15)
https://t.co/cDYdvn95cU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden's closing message, slightly paraphrased. (14/n)
https://t.co/F8Xza6ayIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden on key challenges for next admin: North Korea and strategic stability with Russia. (13/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note that new admin *not* legally required to conduct nuclear posture review, as Obama admin was. (12/n)
https://t.co/uXGhBns0dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden called on new administration to conduct nuclear posture review and assess whether further reductions possible. (11/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden also announced that POTUS had withdrawn c. 500 new warheads from deployed stockpiled, which went down to 4,018. (10/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not exactly controversial in academic circles but significant for VPOTUS to say so publicly. (9/n)
https://t.co/ejBpqTX0Ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...he recognized that US conventional superiority was a driver of Russian posture change. (8/n)
https://t.co/xT6XxlApBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden criticized Russia for increasing role of nuclear weapons in its defense doctrine, BUT... (7/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden highlighted progress in providing POTUS with "flexibility" to reduce need for "launch under attack." ( 6/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden stated that progress in nonnuclear forces since Nuclear Posture Review enabled such a change. (5/n)
https://t.co/QPaHdzIzFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest news: Biden said he and Obama "strongly believe" that US "should" adopt sole purpose because... (4/n) 
https://t.co/WklEnRcJN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First, Biden's passion for and commitment to reducing nuclear risks is remarkable. His leaving elected office is a sad moment. (3/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The speech may have been drowned out by other news stories--but it was significant nonetheless. (2/n)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Redux--my take on the @vp's speech on nukes at @CarnegieEndow yesterday. (1/n) https://t.co/kVDdwZJbKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLEASE RT! Day 2 of vote on the topic for the last panel at the 2017 Carnegie Int'l Nuclear Policy Conference. 
https://t.co/e8waNbLhWk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>