<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In honor of the massacre at #BowlingGreen we should all do this tonight... #hardball https://t.co/dgLfh8N5l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day, the truth, it died...and they were singin', Bye Bye this American lies, on the telly I heard Kelly, but th… https://t.co/T7ohyE1SGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You said it not us. Look forward to you, Bannon, KellyAnne and the gang to hit the road, jack!  Buh-bye!! #BadDude  #ADIOS @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS - Seattle judge issues temporary stay to travel ban effective nationwide immediately #NoBan #NoWall https://t.co/dk6ORVCGAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbwhelan @joanne_stocker @Makofury Watched it live on TV account is 100% accurate + POTUS gave Wagner signing pen, she nearly peed herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, keep in mind that Trump still is executive producer of The Apprentice so he's willing to say anything to boost ratings @HardballChris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris that comment tonight letting KellyAnne off the hook was pathetic &amp; pandering. Don't insult our intelligence man. Dude. @HardballChris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU Chris that comment tonight letting KellyAnne off the hook was pathetic &amp; pandering.  Don't insult our intelligence man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You coin the shorthand term Alt-Facts then host the Queen of Alt-Facts without challenging her - what does #hardball mean?!? @HardballChris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything KellyAnne said was a lie including Obama issuing 6-month ban on Iraqi refugees after phantom #BowlingGreen attack @HardballChris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Srsly Chris, you knew you had to say something about #BowlingGreen &amp; that's all you could muster? Not very #hardball if you ask me. WTF man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How soft have you gone? Really, KellyAnne meant to say 'Plot to massacre'? Come on.  And lied about Obama ban, too @HardballChris #hardball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crack in the ban could help...spread the word.... https://t.co/mMIdoZIV92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencebetty Mark Kleinschmidt says: 'Here's a tip: beer was invented to be consumed when there wasn't any potable water around.'  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencebetty @inversedotcom How much does it cost to buy a Cabinet nomination? One meel-ion dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencegurlz0 @sciencebetty ...or in drag, fur coats,&amp; gold chains depending on the night, if you're Milo. They don't even like each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencebetty @SenThomTillis I said 'Do you have more of a concern&amp; obligation to the children of this country or to one rich billionaire?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he talks about UC Berkeley not allowing free speech??  The hypocrisy is incredulous and frightening. #RESIST https://t.co/f8Qasv9Znk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Threats to a free press my friends.  We must be vigilant.  The dangers of a fascist authoritarian state are here an… https://t.co/anCt5coNlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU get smart.  A right-wing white male Trump supporter killed 6 innocent Muslims, wounded five more, not 1 word fr… https://t.co/evbeDqvKSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote NO on Betsy Devos please!  She's NOT the right person for the job.Tar Heel native, former UNC-Chapel Hill student here. @SenThomTillis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has been formally PUT ON NOTICE for telling daily lies &amp; being a very mean person.  Should have stuck to tele… https://t.co/UnrLF95DFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something true out of Trump's mouth...he's not very ''kind'' at all! 
 Are you trying to START a war you fucking id… https://t.co/NgMer9xAOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the fuck do you think is paying us to protest?Somehow I missed getting my protest check in the mail.We protest for free @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandyLJensen How about saying Her Ass as an honorific instead.  A fitting title, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tmJe096f78 @maddow @chrislhayes This is the level of ridiculous that we've reached. Those dangerous Norwegian Prime Ministers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former PM Kvell Bondevik, on behalf of the American people, our apologies for your detainment at Dulles. Ridiculous. So sorry. @BondevikKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To former PM Kvell Bondevik, on behalf of the American people, our apologies for your detainment at Dulles. Ridiculous.So sorry.@oslocenter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandyLJensen A sudden not-totally-tragic outbreak of Legionnaire's Disease at Mar-A-Lago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me in helping the many victims of the horrible Bowling Green Massacre highlighted by KellyAnne Conway. https://t.co/iI982jSlKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HardballChris was so SOFTBALL on KellyAnne  https://t.co/aCBrCjhZDj kept giving her credit for her gr8 responses. Bowling Green?  #Hardball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VassMoe @HardballChris That 'interview' was disgusting. You had time to review it too! What a waste of Town Hall time with that skank liar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU Why were you so easy on Conway??  Giving her repeated credit for her 'great responses', i.e. Telling lies with a smile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU It's not like you were interviewing her live.  You had time to review that interview and STILL didn't correct the LIES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU https://t.co/jKzyg6VnqU   The @washingtonpost knows what truth and lies are - how about you apologize for showing them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU If you don't come out tonight &amp; call out KellyAnne on her Alt-Facts, cough, LIES, ie Bowling Green Massacre, just quit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU Why the hell would you schedule a 1 hr town hall and spend 10 minutes of it showing KellyAnne spewing her garbage? Ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU How dare you waste 10 minutes of Town Hall time with your #softball game with KellyAnne? That was disgusting.  All Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @AmericanU Srsly Chris?  That was playing hardball with KellyAnne?  Her responses are bulletproof? Bowling Green my ass.  Come on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin and his cronies will literally KILL you if you oppose them.  Trump wants to be his best friend.  Draw your ow… https://t.co/tibHBLMafA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES.  Do not be afraid to stand up and speak the truth, and call a spade a spade.  #RESIST https://t.co/DKOjW8Vsfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand @joan_moon @womensmarch Protesting at Supreme Court, Faxing Senators about Cabinet votes, Sharing truth on FB and Twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some journalists in the past have been able to accurately predict the future...
@realDonaldTrump @RoguePOTUSStaff… https://t.co/Gsi1NF4Ah3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religion, race or national origin discrimination is illegal and disparaging someone because of that is Un-American!… https://t.co/lmw4ule6Cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, WTH...Trump can't even get along politely with one of our strongest and safest allies.  Arguing with Austra… https://t.co/iT2rf7R7fC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of insanity resulting from Trump's reckless, stupid travel ban.  There's no extreme vetting going… https://t.co/MxqUWuvmMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frederick Douglass 1818-1895. Social reformer, abolitionist, dazzling orator, writer, and statesman.  Did amazing t… https://t.co/AWHXxbCGPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be wrong to vote on Trump's Supreme Court nominee, since there is less than a year remaining in his presidency.  #ImpeachmentSoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what it feels like when you're NOT smarter than a 5th grader.  I wrote better reports, amazing ones, when I… https://t.co/Zwvhsj68en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton This is what it feels like when you're NOT smarter than a 5th grader.  I wrote better reports, amazing ones, when I was 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbassadorRice This is what it feels like when you're NOT smarter than a 5th grader.  I wrote better reports, amazing ones, when I was 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something to think about... @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/w25B6X4J39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts Ha! The GOP = Grand Obstructionist Precedents.  Obstructing over governing is their MO, Hypocrite is their middle name. SMH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traceyBVoice @AnaPetrovna @Luxomancy @ScaryMummy09 Chapati is an Indian flatbread, so it means - Bread on top of your head, you bum! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees ALREADY more heavily vetted than anyone on Trump's Cabinet! Random Syrian or Steve Bannon - who would you trust?  @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dems are delaying your picks bc every single one of them sucks complete ass and isn't suited to be a dog catcher! Getoverit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's really in charge at the White House right now?  Does it even matter? Worst of two evils? #RESIST… https://t.co/pknZlRxHOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 killed &amp; 8 injured in a horrible attack in Quebec &amp; Richard Spencer asks 'Why are there mosques in QC, one of NA'… https://t.co/LXVK2QTWQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer What's more beautiful, Quebec City or a Nazi with a black eye?  Alt Right once again showing its true xenophobia and hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be clear that we must be vigilant and smart about our actions.   Do let them win by trickery and inciting chaos.… https://t.co/80rF1gW5f9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Québec mosque shooting: five killed in gun attack https://t.co/UUpdDKxpdv  FYI Muslims have as much to fear as any of us... @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These words are not just poetic musings, they have real meaning. Will we remember what the meaning of LIBERTY reall… https://t.co/xNwS3ERjHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump False false false, LIES LIES LIES.  You know it, you cannot fool us.  You will pay for your lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How does it feel to lose?  Get used to it motherfucker.  So much for you.  So much WINNING for all… https://t.co/VMdzUpTlSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I hope Trump enjoys losing. He’s going to lose so much we’re going to get sick and tired of his losing,” ACLU - @realDonaldTrump #BigLoser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I hope Trump enjoys losing. He’s going to lose so much we’re going to get sick and tired of his losing,”  https://t.co/iZfge37DRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My birth father&amp; his family were Italian.  100 yrs ago I would be subjected to the same hate &amp; suspicion the govt i… https://t.co/zfGTH1krNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is the evil incarnate mastermind behind all of the shit we are seeing right now - He is enemy number one - Nazi scum  #RESIST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must be OUTRAGED, and we must NOT 'Keep Calm and Carry On' - this is war.   The fight has just begun, but WE ARE THE RESISTANCE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...present danger so they can justify even more horrific power grabs and removal of our rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want to trip us up, make us so angry and upset that we can't see straight, hope that they can use certain situations to claim clear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's White House is generating chaos to confuse us all - straight from the Fascist Handbook - there is no other rational way to view it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...have no doubts about it. We are ALL in grave danger of losing the country we so dearly love and cherish....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and the SS in Nazi Germany - THEN YOU NEED TO START DOING THAT RIGHT NOW. This is not a drill - the danger is right in front of our faces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me say this very plainly &amp; clearly - If you ever considered the hypothetical question of what would do to resist Hitler, Goebbels, and..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- we must CREATE the resistance among us. The battle has begun, but remain hopeful - we WILL prevail.  Take heart, brave souls.  #RESIST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dear friends - I am fearful, I am filled with outrage, I am ready to join the RESISTANCE. We cannot wait for others to take action for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon is the real danger on the inside, have no question about that.  #resist https://t.co/2WUF6Uu49K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More news from the inside... https://t.co/CAhQIC8SBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean...I just...what the...I can't even. This madness has got to stop. We have to make it all stop. Fight with ev… https://t.co/4I0pvBecFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody Expects The Spanish Inquisition or a Muslim Ban in America in 2017 - spanish inquisition | Meme Generator https://t.co/pBwnxIDMpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is turmoil, unbelievable, disgusting.  We must resist stronger immediately. https://t.co/N1LhTVWnbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Jobs, the son of a Muslim Syrian immigrant.   I'm just sayin'...
@RoguePOTUSStaff @AltUSFWS @Alt_NASA… https://t.co/26jrCiYtcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Jobs, the son of a Muslim Syrian immigrant.   I'm just sayin'...  @realDonaldTrump @nytimes @washingtonpost https://t.co/0sgGsIDFRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/zq23mmqZ7i   Here's some really GOOD NEWS about you Mr. President!  You're welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes To quote your many mindless minions 'JUST GET OVER IT!  Such a big crybaby...wanhh!!!  Poor little President. SAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes @washingtonpost Gas?  As in gaslighting?  Or are you lighting your own farts this morning in the White House?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Spencer, known-Nazi (though he denies it), retweeting Trump. https://t.co/02VkQU83aG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder of some Trump words.  So Presidential.  Retweeted by Richard Spencer last week. @washingtonpost… https://t.co/j60khyjaVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep it up brave insiders...you're our only hope #ResistTrump https://t.co/N9kiLgVas1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RESISTANCE is HERE.   Take heart.  #ResistTrump https://t.co/x0snCxy4J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance - we have them on the inside... https://t.co/jdxps3RfkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many attacks on our health and well-being - Scott Pruitt as nominee to head EPA is one of the worst.  #resist @ActualEPAFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what Trump?  There's one fact out there that I know is true - You're a #1 Asshole!!  @realDonaldTrump @POTUS #assholepresident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder to keep in mind what we are all fighting for, which include the great beauty in our world.  Take time to n… https://t.co/fhIu9FokvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatlParkService You have nothing to regret!!!   Some people can't handle the truth, that's not your fault.  We love our National Parks. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS @realDonaldTrump Who would make a better leader, Trump or this thoughtful owl living in Prague?  You deci… https://t.co/yGbtq9I8Zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpy, we know your game, we see through you better than a Mexican border without a wall. So Sad!  https://t.co/lpuIO9FjUC @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer Star Wars and Star Trek both had holograms.  Steve Bannon says he's Darth Vader.  Anyone see a conne… https://t.co/PNmT8fiI2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump you did NOT have the biggest crowd at inauguration - NO ONE was there. What you saw were all holograms.  #FakeCrowd  @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>