<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina Maybe I'm showing my privilege - but I felt like anyone could wear anything at the marches. Which was kinda the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina Photos I've seen have shown marches to be hugely open, kind &amp; totally inclusive. Huge solidarity against all discrimination?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipsTane All the people still doing their NY's resolutions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ I guess, a very high price to pay and certainly not tearing any part of our movement I know apart. Bigger fish n all that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ not really. We've kind of got our hands full with, like, all the hatred. Low blow much on such a shitty day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news - Jacinda is fantastic! https://t.co/QuKHRzfT9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have just realised I am quite sensitive to noise. Mother of two kids under four. Too fucking late, as my mother would say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie ok, it is hard in that format to make every point be exact &amp; precise. I get that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie but not clarifying that the common language included elected reps? C'mon now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie it just feels like you'd like the meme / semi-truth to continue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie sure, but also up to you about whether you want to perpetuate the meme that the process is about "HO".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie (apologies in advance for being so shit on twitter!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie language, don't you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie elected by members who know this is one of the most NB roles they play. Quite important to be clear in our]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie interchangeably but most often in a derogatory sense cf to 'faceless' HO. Whereas NZC reps on panels are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie @BeeFaerie i think it's quite NB to distinguish bt the roles of HO and NZ Council. Phil's right they're often used]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haydenwilsonnz but also, so flipping funny!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorsays_ hope you got your walk this arvo! Peach of a day in the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100 you don't have to defend anything to me, lovely mum! You're wonderful and this is your way! Those kids faces in am!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorsays_ on the bright side, southerly has chased the horrid weather away and we in for some fine welly days. But yeah the bumps r yuck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCLASSYKiddo *blush*! Means a lot from you! gonna #changethegovt next year so all got to be sparkly! See you next year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCLASSYKiddo merry Xmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCLASSYKiddo have fun though! Love Samoa! You need a good break before next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyjack888 how awesome, shows how important your work is to ppl! Compassion goes a long way x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three fantastic candidates selected for @nzlabour this week https://t.co/wMtEHXDg48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll miss @annetterongotai being the MP for our fab electorate, but admire her reason v much. Thanks for all your work Annette, v grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed @DavidShearerMP's valedictory tonight, esp the reminder that MPs are humans too! Go well Dave. No doubt you'll do us proud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming @ginnyandersen @priyanca02 thank you for your help for our campaigns! You're the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwoodnz lots of us still hold hope for light rail up through Newtown to the airport. Would be amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyjack888 totally understand! See you next time (hopefully before!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyjack888 Missed you today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so great. Would be really great if we could stop the parent-judging! https://t.co/i2ojoYBnlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ my boy's kindy teachers are the ppl I trust most. We can also work together after coming up with strategies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipsTane easy as! See you Saturday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipsTane great to spend time with you today tane! Onward to victory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @Independent that hotline gonna run so hot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andr3wCampbell any time! Just let me know x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andr3wCampbell do you need a place to stay? Couch here brother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianRobins also met your sister in my campaign travels! Great convo had over a drink in Dunedin. We should get old gang together soon too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianRobins lol, I was of course referring to that other important election!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm feeling a little more resilient after this awful week, and here's a perfect antidote to the attempt to silence… https://t.co/mWnlV6LE04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbdj @nzlabour thanks Deb. A huge privilege]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drsapna aw hope you guys have a great weekend - I've been away so much lately, just need to be home with family for a bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @metiria oh my! That's my home. So beautiful. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellingtonians: please buy books from John at our own kids bookshop in kilbirnie! Don't want to lose that great wee… https://t.co/s8ZcluuxxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay @nzpolice @gredge @NZTAAkl or even some of those council dudes that walk around the city on bikes? Cheaper; we have them already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay @nzpolice @gredge @NZTAAkl now that's a blimmin good idea!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMaKiwi all 4 folks are boomers &amp; all but 1 fit cliche. Husband's Ma is brill, but other 3 like theory of being grandps more than reality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMaKiwi the life of gen x'er with baby boomer parents. Sigh. Hear ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddAtticus my fave is the electorate vote grant. But that's just me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progressive Welly voters: Polls are tight, please vote for @justin_lester &amp; get all your whanau too.  
https://t.co/q4vFbDDDqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to start reading RD to my children. He made me so happy as a kid. Happy birthday! https://t.co/QcNWPLwJOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know who I'm voting for, but then I expect my mayor to give a little more than one word answers. #lesterformayor https://t.co/IQTx0Avlsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @duncangreive @FlickElectricCo @TheSpinoffTV mean it! A laugh goes a long way some days as you well know! &amp; someone getting it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duncangreive @FlickElectricCo @DearMama_ @TheSpinoffTV Emily is a fantastic voice for parents. We love her. Saved parent meltdowns heaps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Borchard, because he listened to us &amp; let us be ourselves #BestTeacherEver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Coats quoting our own Norman Kirk #futureofworkNZ https://t.co/M14aWU10HO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHuggard @SharanBurrow this is the crucial question across our movement and in our progressive parties!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @CCDHB, our boy had an op at your hospital yesterday &amp; your staff were incredible to him &amp; us, every single one! Thank you. V grateful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week I was inspired by @FleurFitzsimons - lawyer for worker &amp; human rights, activist, mum #WomanCrushWednesdays https://t.co/rlRvjYyKEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir did it used to be the messengers' maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico if you have a track record of these things, please can you go to bed now?! No offence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming when do you get bread and when do you get a roll? Regional?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey solidarity sister, such BS people do that. Take care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellClarkNZ same and mainly it's coz I don't have cash and sometimes they do it anyway in welly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyrwalker I can imagine. I often wonder how this could affect the psyche of MPs. Horrible situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyrwalker I can't stop thinking about her kids. In and out of tears this morning. Husbands words about enveloping them in love, so sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyjack888 lovely ladies! Congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owrwegiei @IBCycleWay the level of debate in IB on this issue has been anything but healthy. All I saw was insults &amp; name-calling. V sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owrwegiei @IBCycleWay Not so much pro cyclist, just pro sharing and healthy debate rather than the disgusting rhetoric we've seen from anti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay the thing is: all users can see, slow down or stop for each other! The road is now friendlier for all users. We need to share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery some ppl@also take a position &amp; feel they can't change their minds cause they've backed themselves into a corner. A shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymccourt That's right - people also have a right to know what they're voting for. Mature MMP thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History shows Labour's vote goes up when its clear about partnership #changethegovernment https://t.co/Q9nZ4AXpR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruthdysonmp YES PLEASE! #changethegovernment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's time for change" @AndrewLittleMP. Yay!! #labourgreens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it was a dad who took eyes off his kid at the zoo for a moment, he wouldn't have faced half the hate that mum has. Sick of anti-mum shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My feels exactly  https://t.co/C6Vy2PLK5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellClarkNZ welcome to welly! What is the new job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[200 ppl came to @justin_lester's fundraiser last night, only half of them the 'usual suspects'. Reason 501 to support: brings ppl together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to look at IB cycle way survey results https://t.co/FcIcaBW057]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A place that's very part of me  https://t.co/TQaG4u9lry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men boycotting all male panels isn't the full solution, but a great thing men can do. @GenderAvenger. https://t.co/vUaVltrajq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz @Omearanz @janepatterson @MutchJessica @LeeTaylorNZ fantastic job! Well done to you all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ omfg. Give us all a fucking break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for all your work Campbo! You truly are one of nz's best. Sure you'll be snapped up! x https://t.co/U5GS5mia9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddAtticus oh dear! Thank goodness you didn't go about like that all day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @kiri_te_karnage obv not Peppa pig but lots of the other shows on kid zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @kiri_te_karnage um, doesn't stuff that gets NzOA funding need to be on publicly available tv? What about kids w no 'net?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ Eventually got through last night after two attempts and asking for a ring back. Not particularly satisfying. Busy isn't an excuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg @SparkNZ. An hour to talk to someone on the phone and 30 minutes to use your chat service!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gross people. Seriously?  https://t.co/ZdpGFYX9z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay @pablogl yeah Pablo, I can. Where is it? I can't tell from the vid sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHuggard @docperrin you're too kind. All the doc's work. I bought the roti!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin which protest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming wow, she's brave. If Angus &amp; Lewis did that to me, I'd be 'nup']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry can't make your launch tonight @rtoomath! Have a great time. Loved the N&amp;S article! Dr K will get me a copy tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHuggard @JheneAiko yum! Except the lion brown!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>