<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts Apparently so. A sodomite. Didn't you get ordained online somewhere? Should add that to the name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts this has made me actually chortle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is possibly the greatest thing that will ever happen to me in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am bouncing around my room with PURE JOY @cgpgrey liked my limerick! (I'm number 6!) @HelloInternetFM @BradyHaran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I never expected myself to be reading about in Japanese: particle physics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts HOW do you just have a pair of tegan and sara tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weeks of the year that I dislike: Freshers week, Refreshers week, RAG week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so angry about so many things, and completely powerless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has been my thought as well. https://t.co/t8ZLK4vNi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I walk past the Enterprise trains to Belfast I feel like... why can't iarnród éireann be like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry Yes!! I apologised to the people at the clinic numerous times today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry well it is definitely a thing now! We should get matching bracelets. "Good luck finding my veins lol"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My veins remain difficult to find. I am the blood donor clinic's nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicehchuckles I’M AN ABSOLUTE PLANK I’m so sorry happy birthday I hope you had a delicious takeaway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicehchuckles I HAD THE GODDAMN REMINDER ON MY CALENDAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annie_mc_mahon I was reading something about this and how hard it is for English-Japanese translators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both times I've been to the National Gallery there has been a Turner exhibition and both times it's been an extremely pleasant surprise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't want to make anybody feel guilty but it can be a little lonely when the majority of your closest friends are in relationships?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing excited children at the Dead Zoo is giving me a new lease of life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day so far: I moved a bumblebee off the footpath and saw some yellow crocuses from the bus window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m angry about a lot of things today so I’m going to eat some cereal and visit some museums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still shocked about the JLPT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Case in point: While writing that last tweet, I spent more than a minute thinking about past tense forms of “nosedive”. Nosedived?Nosedove?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that my communication skills have nosedived as a direct result of being a language student]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts I had to use seven staples on mine, it was very elaborate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts You did not get this from me https://t.co/h6vY3tKhSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts BY THE WAY the japanese audiobook is brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts It looks SO professional goddamn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts GOd how did you do this mine was rubbish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That said, it was one of the most convincing Irish accents I have heard in a film so. Good woman. Fair play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something about her accent nagged me the whole time I watched this the first time and now I know why! She is not actually Irish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yer wan in Sing Street is channeling Evanna Lynch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase in number of random accounts following me. Nothing to see here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@banabeibii a) we should definitely do that and b) I’m afraid probably none of the next five or so days are very good but after that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someday I will be relaxed on the day before a deadline, but it is not this day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin Dang yeah I am constantly in awe of them!?? I can’t even fathom having kids ever. How do they do it? Magic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Magikarp song fills me with unbridled joy. It is the Best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately there is not an English version of my FAVOURITE SONG EVER https://t.co/7A8zgAOFyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin Yes I do get that it would be probably very painful… and some kids get their teeth super early too…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m having a fun time comparing how the Pokemon Company went about doing the Slowpoke song in English. For RESEARCH 
https://t.co/5PcNnL9a1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin Yoo there are probably all sorts of reasons, if you want to learn why. https://t.co/rjvPxaDnuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*slamming fists on the table* More cafes in Santry! More cafes in Santry! More cafes in Santry! More cafes in the DCU area! Please!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of those songs that makes me nearly start suddenly singing in public every time I hear it https://t.co/rneb8CYWSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kind of want @99piorg to make a video about the standardisation of Japanese toilet function symbols. https://t.co/JnSyG4UhgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@banabeibii DISCUSS IT WITH ME I AM FROM THE LAND OF SING STREET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful beyond words to have had Pete Seeger’s voice drifting through my house when I was growing up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing transports me into the past like listening to Gordon Bok, Ann Muir and Ed Trickett singing together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry That was a very good matcha latte… The food it came with was also A++ https://t.co/KhkOdUmEwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry Hooray for terrible composition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry How I felt about every coffee shop in Kyoto. https://t.co/hZFg3LLkKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry So I’m looking at my local cinema and actually there are not that many options but I do want to see Moana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts Teach me your ways I am struggling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to concentrate and be motivated? Asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to look up a Japanese word and then got distracted and that was nearly two hours ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are honestly about four different movies I want to go see in cinemas right now, this is unprecedented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coollike YES all of my possible thoughts and feelings about this idea are VERY GOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hankgreen Usually a change of taste, or not wanting to follow a creator who says/does things that are… not good, to put it in vague terms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin To their (sort of?) credit the cast were not wearing blackface. Which. I mean. Still many many many issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin I got to watch a stage of white people saying things like “if we get any more white people in here it’s gonna be a suburb”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenuinePanic here, have a pun comic. https://t.co/AvWPAyWBzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cellery_ can I retweet this? I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(though of course the point is not to be proud, the point is to be good)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about good people in Ballaghaderreen makes me regain a bit of pride for Roscommon. https://t.co/TIITQiDE6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_kurdtin oh lord no was it hairspray? my local musical society did that one last year. in rural ireland. why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexcanroar I was watching an interview with Emily Blunt today and she reminds me of a cross between you and maybe Kate Winslet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really bad at coal fires.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skunk Bear is such a good channel. https://t.co/nuxHG73QWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts Was it on Parnell st. because it always seems to do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's taken two and a half hours to get to Mullingar... @IrishRail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail the announcement system on the Dublin-Sligo train could use a check-up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have now been on a train for an hour and a half and we haven't even made it to Maynooth yet :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail sorry I know you must be totally inundated, but any estimates on when the 17:05 Sligo-bound train will be in Boyle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something like six hours have passed since I got back? How did I manage to lose those hours? What have I been doing???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know that feeling when you come home early to eat and intend to go back to study and then suddenly it’s after midnight? Yeah, that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s a phrase I just heard that I don’t understand: “Overwhelming minority”
…
This is an oxymoron, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beirchearts I’m both NALOPKT and C-P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even just the visual of someone yelling dramatically at the sea and walking deeper into the waves with irritation is really great. A++]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I just want to eat delicious food without having to work!! I just want to sleep in my cosy bed without doing anything!! Aghhhhh!!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically: The guy is yelling “Everything is such a pain! I hate having to go to work in the morning! I’m not bothered!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly this is probably the best song I’ve ever heard. The lyrics speak to my soul. https://t.co/WeOgN8K2bN (It’s in Japanese)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love every set of ボンレス犬 stickers but honestly the second one just speaks to my soul https://t.co/OdD1MTEpRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay probably none of you care but I knew who the voice actor for Blue Diamond was within seconds of her speaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably nothing serious, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up at 5am with pretty severe abdominal pain and then by 6am I could’t even stand up straight or walk, but feel better now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annie_mc_mahon They are doing that here too. I’m not sure how it makes me feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedaBuhHuh Okay haha. :) Did you change your twitter username? It made my chuckle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedaBuhHuh (was it you????)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedaBuhHuh oh yeah I think probably everyone knew, I never shut up about it haha. (Is the note weird?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The narrator of the Japanese audiobook for Harry Potter and the Philosopher’s Stone is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay but Waterford Whispers News tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice irony in seeing that a localisation company’s website hasn’t been fully localised yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may someday get the DSC RX100 III, but I will actually save for it and wait until it is cheaper probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry Oh of course. I mean. I’m in the library, “studying” and thus also on twitter and watching YouTube videos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally unrelated but: It’s very hard to watch the O’Donovan brothers without grinning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and she said “Oh I’m actually just after finding a camera!” and then someone came over to hand in her phone. Happy endings all around!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently the girl who handed it in had asked about a lost phone and someone said “oh that’s awful another girl’s after losing her camera”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m so happy to have my camera back. Had a great exchange about it at the issue desk of the library.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear whoever handed in my camera, 
Thank you!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad I got to see Kubo and the Two Strings in a cinema because dang was it pretty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allezberry And at least 900 of them are kind of terrible!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>