<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBennetCO you missed a wee typo: "qualified" not "qualifed"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerraMasterEU hi there, I have 2 D4-310's. there is diff. behaviour with the HDD lights (always on vs. off). how can i make them the same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerraMasterEU hey, the D4-310 isn't on https://t.co/LMg3Bgr0Ms (or amazon.de, or amazon.es). What's the story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBennetCO (constituent here) Do you consider embassy security sacrosanct, given Benghazi and the attacks in Turkey? Do you oppose SB11?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryGardner (constituent here) Do you consider embassy security sacrosanct, given Benghazi and the attacks in Turkey? Do you oppose SB11?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerraMasterEU hi there, does the d4-310 support UASP (USB Attached SCSI)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereistanya can ye have a look and confirm https://t.co/DT3p4yPL3f ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another trip, another round of fun with the cats and @Petcube. Love this thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cat (n): a four-legged furry creature that knocks your stuff onto the floor just to see what happens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlEdman @charlescwcooke @justinamash but that was before my political awakening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlEdman @charlescwcooke @justinamash probably lamenting that there wasn't a vigorous discussion and recorded vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnemyofKhanate @alllibertynews @charlescwcooke @justinamash not bringing issues to the floor or vote is not "no"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke @justinamash this argument falls flat when Congress fails to fulfill its responsibility to debate and vote on the Prez agnda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on the road, jet-lagged, and playing with my cats with my @Petcube. I wasn't sure about it at first, but now I love it. Audio, ftw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flameeyes SFO this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flameeyes safe flight. it's to the wilds of MTV for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flameeyes are you in LHR T5?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find myself surrounded by my people. And by "my people," I mean frequent flyers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkozloff ah yes, that's what I like about it too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkozloff what do you like about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrowadat Bellroy wallets are good, so I've heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrowadat can you not, you know, direct the market as you see fit? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenCoryGardner that's a nice idea but Congressional GOP have been more about talking points than action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k9 yep, turns out globalisation is a thing. challenge != win, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k9 troubling to be sure, but govt action can be less noble. cuts both ways. I think the ISDS process needs results before judgment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k9 I imagine it's to level the field against capricious actions from a national govt out of spirit with the trade agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajkilbane all the best, you'll be missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redbreast Lustau: syrupy creamy sweet and popcorn. Not overpowering. Very good. #celticwhiskey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redbreast 12, a near perfect whiskey. #celticwhiskey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 yo: vanilla lychee and green tea. NAS: indistinct barley sugar and astringent #celticwhiskey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First week back at work: brought in the Palace Bar 12 year old (port cask) for Gentlefolk. Bottle proved to be extremely popular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warriorbob9 try a puff of air in the Glencairn to dissipate the vapo/u?/r. should help with nosing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warriorbob9 I'm still trying to decide. It has some upsides (especially for higher-proof) but I think I'd still default to Glencairn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 days with a Norlan whisky glass: seems to strongly subdue alcohol vapour vs. Glencairn. Wide lip takes a bit of getting used to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 years in port, Palace Bar Literary edition is class. #iwsibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Independent bottler evening with the IWS, excited! #iwsibs #iws #whiskey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMalina @HrishiHirway @WestWingWeekly that'd be Toby's line: "credulous simplicity" (from Pirates) in scene with Sam and Josh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMalina @HrishiHirway @WestWingWeekly I pre-watched ep. 20 for next week's cast and noted I think the first G&amp;S drop-in in the series...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @DublinAirport was a medical divert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail hi there! do you have any contact info for the public API from yourselves? I've got a quick question/request.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gondoliers! Sad to miss this (will be at a G&amp;S festival in England)! https://t.co/mliT18TRrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizthegrey welcome back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbarista It might just be to @3fe.ie btw -- I got a bounce for hello@3fe.ie. https://t.co/4lnsZde4M2 might be ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbarista hey Colin, the 3fe email address on the website is bouncing. :-) I want to buy stuff and can't get a question through! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmetMurphy_ that Brora is unreal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msleedy I see a little silhouetto of a bap...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aircoach is the "Bewleys Hotel" stop in Merrion Road actually the Clayton Hotel stop now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cirillosdublin do you do takeaway? (looking to take home a few pizzas tonight)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PassportIRL hi there, the turnaround times on the Passport Tracker and https://t.co/tuNd5hqzu8 are now different. FYI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natural20 a wheel of taoisigh, each in office a proportional number of days to the number of deputies in their party. #obvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Postvox hi there, is it possible to track whether or not a postal order was cashed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_phred if you have multiple nodes in each DC, you might be better off creating a DC-DC VPN for all services to use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Meteor_Mobile Can you change my broadband plan to the 4G SIMO 15G @ €14.99? Trying to minimise the faff for what seems like an easy change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Meteor_Mobile I was given a number for "retention" so I can change plan. I've called twice -- "office is closed." Should I just cancel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMulliganGrocer Oh, I see from a prior tweet you're off on a jaunt! Delay understood!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMulliganGrocer hey there, still taking bookings via email? (been waiting a response for a day or so now :-))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can attest. Endured this film on a recent TATL. https://t.co/Noe5arDtQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warriorbob9 aww, thanks! miss y'all as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing Colorado more when I see photos like this :) https://t.co/eloVddQKi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real-time bag tracking from @AmericanAir is so cool! I now know that my bag made my short (27 min) connection in Phoenix. Kudos folks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sierrakim giant hagelslag, what is this magic? (I did find a source!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sierrakim think a castle in Cork and an unspeakable love for hagelslag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falun because it's close enough to be confused with OO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An advert in an Android notification @hotelsdotcom? Bad call. Uninstalled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DesKitty settings icon (mid-upper right) -&gt; Send Feedback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hankgreen minor nit, can you say "all sides" instead of "both sides" (re: last vlogbrothers vid). "both" implies a black and white choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJaredPolis @RepThomasMassie with an absinthe chaser?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UPCIreland Hi there, how can I report potential signal leakage coming from the physical plant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky are like the overly attached girlfriend. Cancel and they try 17 ways to keep you. Then when they fail, they send a "we're sad" letter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flameeyes I managed, after much pushing to get the savings and current accounts closed. The credit card is proving vexing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KBC now claims the card is actually really honestly truly closed this time. We'll see. #notconvinced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have to hear "Thank you for calling KBC" again after ringing 6(!) times to close my account, I might lose it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgpgrey I thought you should know: 2xHello Internet, 2xCortex was about right for yesterday's long haul flight. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_phred thanks for the link. btw, +1 to the notion of a check character and separating id from human identifier. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_phred in this case, any randomised string will do (collisions can be verified by index, distribution handled by a prefix)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_phred if you really want human factors, you go alphanumeric (e.g; tinyurl, bitly, imgur) where you can create shorter strings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_phred that sounds like a terrible idea. uuid's are just for this and come from the standard book of magic that everyone understands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crashcoursestan @TheCrashCourse I am very much enjoying the IP series. Well presented to make the material accessible and fun. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskKBCIreland I sent in a letter asking to close my accounts about 2 weeks ago. How is that going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskKBCIreland Hi KBC, I have moved my banking to another bank. How do I close my accounts and credit card with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isomer probably a lot like a waste of £600 (unless its legitimately rare and not a marketing gimmick)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexChasko Thanks for the tour today! Looking forward to your opening and the future :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgpgrey are the duplicates intentional? (cat input | sort | uniq)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAirways 36 mins for baggage on 709 arriving SFO. One belt, big crowds. Poor show; need to do better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help that's what I was looking for. thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help At my current bank, I am limited to transferring €15k per day to a beneficiary. I'm curious if you've such a limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help Hi there. I am shopping for a new bank in ROI. Are there daily transfer limits on your current accounts? (what are they?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMikeCoffman Pres. Obama, Congressman. That you don't use his title (though you do for yourself) suggests you are not being honest here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krellis Get what you pay for, I suppose. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krellis Hertz Gold. Its made of awesome and sorts exactly this problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBennetCO think of this and arguments for less regulation. Regulations aren't inherently bad, but process-intensive compliance is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@British_Airways hey there; I did a UuA to CW; the tax/fee diff has been taken from my CC but not the Avios. Just wanted to follow-up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raruler that's me -- nice find. ifconfig xn0 -txcsum ? If so, that's interesting (though I've since switched to an older hypervisor)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Airbnb why not just answer the question? if you link a google account, Airbnb want more access to my account than seems reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Airbnb why do you want to manage my contacts and see my docs if I link my Google account? (access revoked btw)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@British_Airways A bit of a typo in my MMB today. I don't think Sacramento is really that scary ;-) http://t.co/0pD62nIrTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EttoMerrionRow you absolutely killed it tonight folks: the veal carpaccio, risotto, and chocolate pot were superb. clean plates all around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskKBCIreland can you help make my credit card payments to you not result in a follow-up telephone call from KBC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewtrumbo @_jared i feel like that's a reasonable reaction. the police reaction is not confidence-inspiring.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>