<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet Which McLuhab book(s)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#facebook https://t.co/xURs5Zcxlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And now, the end is near", is it? https://t.co/awTGLOgmjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually no. We cringe when our leaders act as you are. @pmbillenglish https://t.co/nzalJSscfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julespenner Because today wasn't depressing enough.  That man....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Mother Nature,

We get it.  We are upset about Trump as well.  Please stop throwing tantrums.

Yours truly,
  New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton Yes. We hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton Hormone treatment only. So fatigue but nothing else, luckily. When it stops working, on to the next thing (chemo).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton I do that all the time (the BP thing) around that place now after a lifetime of 100/55. So irritating. Good luck w infusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@not_friends Opening is on Prime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta How long have you been a diplomat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacyStClair Big theme but hard to watch knowing what actually goes on and how indigenous people are treated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to see an Olympics Opening ceremony written from the POV of the indigenous peoples for a change. #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think Trump supporters realise that when the Hunger Games start, he will be in the Capitol, but they will still be in District 12.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stealth nerd justice. https://t.co/b85uiHyjqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone took grumpy pills today.  https://t.co/KDHkX7CjVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clementine_ford If Andrew is this sad, then I am glad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From up here the ferry is SO NOISY. https://t.co/uoiXdDRkB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's RNZ interview on extending Iraq deployment shows the critical thinking skills you want in government. https://t.co/6mE4y5zekS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton I was all confused until I realised that they changed the century 16 years ago.  I don't know any of this century's music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta Love this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @labocalocanz The doughnuts were good.  Your problem may have been looking for actual food at Armageddon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clementine_ford "20 minutes of action".  The mind boggles.  (I'll bet the dad will never stop regretting that Freudian phrase.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickhide @Richard_Schiff @WestWingWeekly Totally agree.  And had me in tears in places. Loving the podcast (and just rewatched series too.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joined the 21st century w my first ever binge watch: The West Wing, which I finally finished, 10 years late. Bring back Bartlett! (Please!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robin1226 You show remarkable naïveté as to how parenting works in the real world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBJanney The rest of the world would be grateful too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not channel outrage over #harambe into boycott of palm oil items that destroy gorilla habitat: ~1/2 of packaged products in food shops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robin1226 That's right. It is a rare event. Most parents have scary near misses once in a while but get lucky.  Also some kids are FAST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robin1226 Or we could, as a society, accept that accidents happen and not seek a scapegoat for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robin1226 Accountable, how?  Killing the child seems a bit harsh. Kids sometimes escape; that's the nature of parenting. For everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sad about the Cincinnati gorilla, but honestly, would people really prefer the child had died?  Priorities people. #harambe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandonEvrs The apes are NOT drugged, so the choice was the ape's life or the child's.  Hard to see any other call being made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandonEvrs The public demands that we have open environments and not be behind walls or cages.  This is the result.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta Endnote?  Such a time saver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msjuju8 Me too, start to finish.  May take some time yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msjuju8 Just this second finished S6E14. Almost there. So refreshing to see principled politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard @HuttCityCouncil @huttnews @HuttHub That was my fear. Ended up in SV as I'd hoped, but with no signage it was quite unnerving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard @HuttCityCouncil @huttnews @HuttHub And trails either have no labels at top or incorrect ones (eg "no exit" on polytech path)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard @HuttCityCouncil @huttnews @HuttHub I'm getting an idea after a year+ of trying many out, but many dead ends, and few maps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard I took my border collie from Wainui Rd up ECNZ track yesterday to Stokes Valley, but it's always a guess where tracks go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard Gorgeous day for it.  My dog prefers tracks where she can be off leash though. Would love comprehensive list of local tracks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evilrooster I had that dress only pale blue and cap sleeves.  It was great.  I was also 15kg slimmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs Just threw out dozens of them.  What in the world were we thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarecurranmp To objectify and demean women, and perpetuate the idea that we only have value if we are selected by a man.  Duh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that no NZ media can/will report concerns with proposed NZME/Fairfax merger is a perfect example of the problem with the merger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey Responding to criticism by attacking someone else (whom I hadn't mentioned) is hardly appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey I was speaking about your personal approach to ceremonies, Julie, not talking about someone else.  The policy is petty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey I'm Lower Hutt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey It's about priorities.  Others make it work.  As I said, it meant a lot to me to have them there; glad no petty politics for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey What a petty policy.  I was delighted to have list MPs at my ceremony and am glad small-minded politicians didn't ban them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80k people out of their homes, 1,600 buildings destroyed and the WSJ is worried about tar sands production. https://t.co/pPgftVJweu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelGlucinaNZ   Good to know that someone found him good to work with.  I'm not sure his vision (flaming ruins) was very helpful though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyrwalker Same here.  When I switched apps I deleted the whole backlog and felt free.  Still subscribed to far too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyrwalker It's insidious.  I remember having 5Gb of podcasts waiting, and stressing out that I was falling farther behind every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly thought "miscegenation" was a word for the history books and that we'd moved on. This is so awful.  https://t.co/SCRHLxaoFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton I don't know but it makes me heartsick.  We're getting worse so very quickly after a promising few decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evilrooster Teens are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBeeton maybe they're just easing into it, starting w closer kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaJobszPR Good luck w recovery. (And don't get complacent --I did as you did, but was still one of the 1%. Still very glad of surgery!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy to see this. :-) https://t.co/ol3w7P3RbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ES_chickadee The cross on St Gerard's monastery can be lit up. Would that be it?  It would be halfway down Mt Vic though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So after over 100 years of women in aviation, QANTAS introduced female pilot uniforms ... yesterday.  Mustn't rush things, you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Kimbabwe_ @Megapope Royals thought that removing label was all that was needed to make it okay. "But art!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Kimbabwe_ @Megapope As long as royals have huge painting of "Negro Page Boy" in view while receiving Obamas, can't see dolls vanishing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ Thanks very much for following up and making it right.  I'm very happy. (At least till next bill arrives.)  Good work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voldemortsbicep It's possible that the people in relationships find that state more rewarding, if they're acting superior about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ "Retention" has been in touch. (Again.  And made incorrect adjustments. Again. I should be glad they're trying, right?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelittlepakeha  Reading it gives me hives.  OCD parenting 101. Next will be complaints that no one ever takes the kids overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Warehouse is having a "Seven Day Weekend Sale." seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIXTH wrong @vodafoneNZ bill in a row.Tonight was 6th support call in under two months.Appalling.(Now waiting on retention to fix. Again.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs Podcasts are the answer. You can watch them while listening to interesting adults.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta We have underfloor, but only double g when replacing windows.  And far too many windows!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress Much easier to discredit witnesses than defend abuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta Our house is always cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_berry01 @clementine_ford No actually.  Men still make more.  https://t.co/aWgCSdJbvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta @CheckpointRNZ Perfect for today.  I'm freezing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bootstheory Didn't you know?  They're trying to "help" keep them from rotting on the streets. The streets they walk on anyhow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NintendoAmerica What's up with letting #gamergate trolls dictate your personnel policies? https://t.co/alWkbyJCY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joywritessongs I assume she was attacked.  Few people are prepared for what follows her kind of publicity. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazingly well deserved.  Such an exceptional performance https://t.co/TlgoO5UICD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now we enter the First Week of Easter, also known as "No choir practices for any church choir week".  Phew. #fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost Not impressed with this action of your couriers (nor your response).  https://t.co/iKtp2vXGuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 That pretty much sums up his appeal levels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta @MsBeeton what a pain for you!  Hope it's fixed in time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheckpointRNZ ...also great roads, lots to see and do for all.  Comparing Parliament House to the Beehive does make one want to cry, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheckpointRNZ Canberra people there were thrilled at direct flights here too.  Can't forget that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheckpointRNZ Just back from a perfect week there.  Great bushwalking, lovely cafés, great sun, kangaroos... Returning w the family, asap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jobourne Gaudy Night is a movie? Must. Find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[69 is the new 27.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethHoyt Seriously? People need to find hobbies to fill their time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Key, lying, can taunt others w the bogey of rapists, but sexually abused women MPs get thrown outof Parliament for speaking. #rapeculture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just so you know.  #fb  https://t.co/DyfiCvIpCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME Amazing how when you look for qualified women, suddenly you realize that they were there all along.  Well done, @JustinTrudeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jobourne @VictoriaDahl @courtneymilan There's a genetic component to face identification. (I.e., I blame my parents for my ineptitude.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta I was glad I made A go when X won a prize.  (In sport!)  (We set him up for "most improved" by having such a low baseline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing says "Time to temper that frying pan!" like an overdue report and a blank screen in front of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A Canadian is a Canadian is a Canadian."  Well spoken.  Now to undo the damage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf I am so jealous.  Totally unavailable in Wellington. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UNGA2015 @UN must tell @MashiRafael - respect #indigenousrights &amp; end criminalization of nonviolent protest in Ecuador! @MainaKiai_UNSR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>