<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you had lots of cash but your opposition had access to lots of volunteers, Sept 23 is a strategic election date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: every NZ First caucus since the 1996 election has contained at least one MP who is a migrant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrmurphypoetry @nzherald @NZStuffPolitics Actually just hung up after you called me a Nazi and a f-ing maggot. Didn't raise my voice once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainLG Done. I'll drop a line with your office and get the ball rolling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainLG Saw yr immigration press release, and agree we must tighten protections for immigrants. Happy to talk through report w/ you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHunter5 "Let's pull some bitchin' capital charge action those health board ho's and get stunting on that scratch". Well, ahem, rather!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHunter5 "Yo dog, that capital asset pricing model is da bomb."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainLG @_hehir_ Still would prefer 1,000 Thiels to one Bill Liu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @IainLG Stand corrected: "Note that different rules apply depending on the type of overseas person. "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @IainLG Nope! "You are an overseas person if you are neither a New Zealand citizen, nor ordinarily resident in New Zealand"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainLG @_hehir_ The difference is literally a passport. Plus Thiel is the unique kind of talent NZ needs. But, you know, politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @IainLG Now, wasn't it the Labour Party that granted him permanent residence in 2006?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a more retarded OS than Apple? The answer is "no". I spit in Steve's grave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr Labour says credit agency report proves Nat govt not fit to hold office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an absolute twat https://t.co/yO1fRKSCgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz not trying to be obtuse either but in buying a house aren't you effectively renting from yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz but presumably each dollar has already been taxed twice, PAYE and GST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz Why include cars in yr equity tax? Equity falls over time.  Genuine question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msbananapeel @Hamley_Maqnirez exactly. But downside of dino extinction: where will I get all my clickbait?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msbananapeel @Hamley_Maqnirez buying media dinosaurs in the age of digital comets. Hmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasHaig @garethmorgannz It ain't free. Invoice is in the mail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasHaig @garethmorgannz Referring political optics. Home ownership rate is in 60s. How is this policy a vote winner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasHaig appreciate you putting words in my mouth w/@garethmorgannz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz You're in politics now. Good luck getting the middle to vote for a tax on their aspiration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So in a country that prides itself on home ownership @garethmorgannz , in seeking the popular vote, wants to tax home ownership. Okay then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop This sounds like something Asenati would say, only without the words "semi", "reminder", "esque", "parody", "regular" &amp; "account"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenesaJeram @DrAndrewButcher @RachelWebb37 Only a stereotype coz it is so prevalent. https://t.co/2a7sjj7xyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franks_lawyer From @EconBizFin "Under [Key] the country has been a haven of prosperity and stability" Tad Hyperbolic but comparatively true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuuuuuuuuu ⚡️ “Italian PM to resign over Referendum loss”

https://t.co/5YbfM5qL4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Depression is merely anger without enthusiasm"  - Steven Wright. #notdepressed #fortherecord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody migrants stealing Kiwi's jobs. What? Labour force participation rate at record high of 70.1%? Oh. Oh dear. https://t.co/EvLdDac7FE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson I've read Kahneman (thinking fast and slow), Sunstein and Thaler (Nudge), so know the background material well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson It is on the reading list as of now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson Very nervous over where a nudge turns into a shove w/ bad outcomes e.g. Kiwi saver default fund is conservative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson On pref we keep finding "irrational" defined as choices ppl make that veer from what said expert would have chosen. eg sugar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson Definition is useful for policy setting. Can govt know yr preferences better? More choice tends to mk ppl better off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloise_gibson curious to see how it stacks it up. Coz economists define rational as ppl behaving consistent with personal preferences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith Ah, bliss of taxication. The feeling you get from a tax rebate. Lasts only until you realise it was your money to begin with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phil_goff's targeted rates on hotels to pay for Ateed not insane. Beneficiary pays rule. Q is why has this taken so long?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @MaxRashbrooke here are some interesting fact on Uber, care of economist Julian Morris https://t.co/lGKLGHTBxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on @FrankMcRae, stop holding back. Tell us you really feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae short memory. You forgot dubbyah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_marks To quote Francis Urquhart: "You may well think that, but I couldn't possibly comment" https://t.co/u8aHhqoC86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaceyKirkNZ @cjsbishop @NZNationalParty Damn you Stacey, you beat me to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert "Live the brand" as former boss used to tell me (he dressed almost exclusively from the marketing gifts cupboard).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar daddy? Pfft. I aspire to be a sugar baron. https://t.co/xrDP4LdxU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How NZ politicians see Uber: Predatory cowboy gypsies lurking at a taxi rank near you. #21stcentury #robotsRcoming #abouttimetoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenThomasNZ I know, right? I should be a perfect 5.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir @mwyp That's gypsy talk right there, you know the people who refuse to obey Parliament...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford Are those all the remaining union members in NZ? Wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwyp If you though "gypsy" was gold I urge you to read the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What... the .... fark? https://t.co/7sosewxtha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaserlin the temerity to be in the path of your golf ball! Well deserved I say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParrotDog Love your work. Can't wait for you to be dishing it out at a location near my home. Drunk walking is still allowed, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @MaxRashbrooke @TimHunter5 that crawl space in San Fran rents for US$500/m shows extractive potential on land almost limitless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @MaxRashbrooke But where do you live then? Still have to buy accommodation at current market rates, as noted by @TimHunter5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battling to see the diff between radical preacher's antisemitic rant and Brian Tamaki blame gays for quake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking @avancenz And here I thought that imodium was supposed to prevent the runs...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking @avancenz tre rock n' roll. Keiff would be proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton I prefer when the classics go all death metal like: https://t.co/YygVJoO8Sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loathe as I am to admit that anyone could match the original, Richard Cheese might just have done exactly that: https://t.co/VW7kwwSZQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae Call him out on it. You may offend, but he can hardly call for censure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae There might be more to it than that, as Brendan O'Neil explains. https://t.co/9btEio5Skc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico @sashaborissenko Got their hands on the last pro-free trade country in North America and they're not letting go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerdennis @paulbrislen @WIRED Hey white people, here's another thing to feel guilty over (still not forgiven for hair metal)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir I feel your pain. I ride a moped to work. Shudder to think what would happen if a quake struck while I was on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir You do know that there is a +90% chance of a 6/7 magnitude quake in the next month, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching tonight at Macs in Wellington. Come find out how we can make local govt suck less: https://t.co/uIoN0pizmx https://t.co/Nyazp6a0w9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHunter5 if StuffMe tanks where do I get clickbait from? Just today I read a bride wrote a nasty note to caterer #4thestate #vital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_marks your comments cut him to the bone. He must salve the wound by buying another luxury automobile and some jewels for the wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BGCraven It is like The Apprentice all over again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bishop Brian Tamaki, such a nice chap.  https://t.co/rUtUy8qhwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you thought yr vote in the local govt elections counted for zip you'd be right! Find out how to fix it on 21 Nov https://t.co/uIoN0pizmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rafmanji @nzinitiative Fret not Raf, one is on its way to you too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimRose69872629 @EricCrampton @alan_john_moran @SincDavidson A very pertinent question. There is a case to be made that Musk is rentseeker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest @nzinitiative report will be hitting the desks of MPS, mayors and chairpeople soon with a plan to fix lo… https://t.co/ssWR2IIdrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbseymour @jo_moir I'd hoped you'd be serving something stronger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Cresswell Total face palm moment. It so bloody dire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz daaaamn, that is truly vile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @SEaqub. Loved the vid, but wondered if someone slipped something in my coffee at first. Also, haast and moa disagree on sustainability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_marks I like GLOW: Gay, Lesbian or Whatever..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did gay turn so queer? https://t.co/v84MxG1P9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae Not asking for different rulers. Asking for more accurate rulers &amp; sanctions for those who lie to get projects across the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae Amid all the "rail is the future" love in the paper and among pollies of late, I thought it prudent to point this out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae Now you're picking and choosing. Flyvbjerg's large data set is quite an edifice of evidence that shows rail tend to be worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae @nzinitiative Study shows road benefits under-est, not over! Costs too, but less thn rail. Pls read report (link in story) #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amused to find someone set up a site diametrically opposed to @garethmorgannz's https://t.co/NpbY52hYsd. It's called https://t.co/hb23Roi2pk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJessBerentson There are only 10 kinds of logical argument]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJessBerentson Seriously though, I'm beginning to think it is a gender neutral form of abuse. 'splainin' is a problem in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJessBerentson Mansplaining is when men explain things to women under the flawed assumption that women need it explained to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenesaJeram @RachelWebb37 just so smart and insightful https://t.co/48JPPTa9OR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geoffsimmonz while I have you on the line, great news about TOP. The election just got waaaay more interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geoffsimmonz the sleep of the righteous and proud then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr those monitors aren't going to prop themselves up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimRose69872629 Weirdly just put that on the reading list today (from @Firing_Line_ column)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man high on LSD and cough meds rescues dog from imaginary fire. Cops confirm he is not a "cat burglar". Kid you not. https://t.co/BEPkypFHOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton A case of epigentic clustering if ever I saw one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_marks Weirdly I have been looking for an alternative therapy for my restless legs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CG tells LG to get their freedom camper regs right: A case of "You take the costs we take the benefits?" @lgnz https://t.co/WiGPTORN1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauloCanning @nacin @JohnRentoul @Jake_Wilde @JPSargeant78 @nomoremister Point made, but didn't govt send vets to war in the first place?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>