<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lately I've been going into the shower with my socks on by accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was walking around the house in shorts and my poor dad had no idea I had any leg tattoos almost had a heart attack when he saw my thigh LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally started riverdale and cole sprouse is a total babe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmcfatterr it was a glorious moment. I'm so glad I was able to witness it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gonna pretend like mike didn't puke on my leg and wear these pants tmrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm baby sister material]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the type of girl that will try to look cute infront of a guy and end up knocking over a drink and spilling it on him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things can only start getting better now right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My laugh ruins all of my Snapchats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to 6 random men in my room ... who are you why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a real hard time holding everything together wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losing my president, job, cat, and bf all in the same month #2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy to see everyone protesting trump in van]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly nammer I don't want your caramel apple vape smoke in my face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day I check my gut to make sure my unhealthy lifestyle hasn't caught up to me yet ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My eyelashes are great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it when I need ppl more they swerve me even harder wth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I have to start looking good again ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human lives don't matter nearly as much as puppies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't watch any movies with animals because I cry too hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am i so needy and annoying today holy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexsquelch h8rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real friends buy matching pants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love how you don't give a shit about how you look" actually took 2 hours to get ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably having the worst day of my life and it's only 50 minutes into it ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/o to the guys cheering me on while I puked out of Emma's passenger door that is the kind of support group I need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My doctor gave me meds and told me to rest but my meds don't let me sleep so how??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@w0ng3mily omg just saw your bio and I'm so jealous I didn't think of that ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me n my cat just played tag for 20 minutes life is perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yelled "I LOVE PRISON DICK" so loud not realizing my client was just around the corner ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to marry Alyssa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any friends of mine have strong muscles and a truck? ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing I won't be able to take my cat with me is making me wanna jump off a bridge ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought we were over this tissue box brow trend damn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can never finish the last bite of food or the last sip of my drink??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiecasee thanks it was the only good pic I had of myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jk only pussies throw up their antibiotics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No sorry I can't work I'm sick" gets wasted off 2 beers and throws up all my antiobiotics anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would get the flu the only year I actually got my flu shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever get to the point where u just keep skipping songs until you've skipped all of them but one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheetos can cure a sinus infection right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiecasee I'm glad my pain brings you joy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up every hour to take cough medicine is annoying this whole turning up thing isn't funny anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gonna throw this out there lmao https://t.co/geRIvmnxV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectly content with spending New Years with my cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreckynMarie ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I'm so happy you noticed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time for some big ass changes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took night time cold meds instead of the non drowsy ones ya TURN UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreckynMarie life is sad ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up even more sick than I was on Christmas happy new year ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thought that keeps me up this late at night is why the heck are poeple okay with abusing animals???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Paul Wall 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know Christmas was a success when your dinner is just all the chocolate you've been gifted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my bf because even tho I killed our Christmas tree he still decorated it with lights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every year Alyssa and I get each other the same thing but it's the best thing ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vubahuynh YEAH of course I'll come wit you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vubahuynh can u get me a ticket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayleyMelo they did this to me too today ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I not get sick before Christmas k thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crystalizedbby I wish my bf would ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started calling my bf "dude" all the time does this mean we're bros now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordering BP from van sucks because I know it won't be Shaun delivering it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he hypes you up for chicken wings then doesn't get the chicken wings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gives you lemons, delete your WhatsApp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[December brings out the crazy in everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What choice do we have but to just power through the roughest and craziest times? Life keeps movin yenno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dirty dishes make me depressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@w0ng3mily omg I know, so unexpected and beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just so you know post malones album is really good?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the world did end in 2012 and we're all in hell rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All foods make me feel sick but I also love all foods ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ life is unfair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama means family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low key wanna get fake tittays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poulinian it's a hard life for us folk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_shauun @cgravenor @stevestatia @villageofmarch @mmcfatterr there are so many people here wow plz take off your shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigRedLang I want to be them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@villageofmarch @_shauun @mmcfatterr hello welcome to my party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crystalizedbby omg it's a date]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohh hey yeah it snowed 2cm so I couldn't come to work even tho it's only 6 blocks from my house :)))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crystalizedbby our bf's should just date each. All he talks about/watches when he's drunk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiecasee my life has meaning now. You jealous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_shauun @mmcfatterr Ok waste yo money then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_shauun @mmcfatterr new phone who dis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just gotta wake up one shoe at a time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enchant light maze is a rip off don't waste yo money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I'm really upset my kitty comes to snuggle me. I know it's just because he wants my beer but I'll take it #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscar has found his home and I'm low key sad because I wanted to keep him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayleyMelo love overbearing parents and old men #jealousofyourlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving down commercial and the whole northbound lane is just broke down busses!! Gl if you trynna save urself by taking transit today lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: starting to love this cat. He has a spiky Harley Davidson collar and likes to snuggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A random cat literally came into my house, shat and pissed on my couch then started drinking water from my tub. Help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be okay with being chunky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our money has meat in it what now vegans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Used the last of my Burberry primer so my face would look bomb for this party and didn't even go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it already pretty much December? I feel like summer just ended last week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also dropped salad on the ground and he ate it. What cat likes salad? Wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does my cat keep biting my lamp ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiecasee those bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waking up to yelling everyday can really fuck u up ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched deadpool...is that really the shit they closed the viaduct for?!?!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>