<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharing my own tiny wetland on #WorldWetlandsDay2017 @RamsarConv https://t.co/H0oeszPWl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking read "Utopia? Kathleen Ngale is 85 years old and living in conditions I can only describe as hell" https://t.co/iJZNNoWtLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think reporting on Trump is hard? Try being a journalist in Donetsk https://t.co/hJ8aM8iLng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["America: behold, your Snowflake-in-Chief" spot-on article and great snowman https://t.co/QFYBVp1COW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Music Donald Trump Can’t Hear https://t.co/AUSO8UhDET via @adamgopnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Shield shrimp lay eggs that can deal with all the kinds of extreme temperatures that inland Australia gets. https://t.co/j4g601gCFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sussan Ley may lose her job over expenses. She should lose it over health policy https://t.co/9OlzQMcJ0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous owners seek world heritage status for ancient freshwater fishing structures oldest in the world https://t.co/fXJUEBLBDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanking you for sharing Eyre Creek in flood, every Australian should be looking at this with awe. https://t.co/GpsfGQbLpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrEmmaLJohnston WOW that is some tail! One proud skink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaires get more leeway than vulnerable citizens. It’s obscene https://t.co/vd72yaSiQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So beautiful, thank you @DrEmmaLJohnston__ The forest below. #algae #habitat #intertidal https://t.co/nKKPEIiqJS”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another, more beautiful America is rising. Trump will be resisted https://t.co/0d8kwtKnKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Christmas read_This Christmas, think about Syria. But don’t forget to laugh. Don’t forget to live.  https://t.co/v7Ecfdbxra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great story of 2 people finding a way to be together “@nytimeswell: The Night Girl Finds a Day Boy https://t.co/367c53rJfM”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glen Le Livre sharing Earth's advice for mankind and it's spot on.  https://t.co/0vdXhxTeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book-choice app Alexi aims to free readers from 'algorithm rabbit hole' https://t.co/JUsU60HNlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second sunrise over Newcastle Harbour this morning. @1233newcastle https://t.co/vfAdbkPmJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little guy escorting big guy out of Newcastle Harbour @1233newcastle https://t.co/iKrc3q0NIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid downturn in milk prices, dairy-farming families making essential product in 
a labour of sheer love. https://t.co/PYaOdZV37n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hate crimes surge in Donald Trump's America"_ No surprise, that's what he used to fuel campaign https://t.co/4RuaKucpA5  |@paulmcgeough”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hopeful message from young Jessica Cornwell_Millennials have been rocked by this election. But our day will come https://t.co/TPml5tvcsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBakerSF @TristanEdis Yikes!!! That was quick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites No fair, you get to have all the fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton spotted hiking on day after conceding US election https://t.co/RnHLkKr3zR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorker If HRC succeeds as she deserves to, would love to see NYM investigate why it's taken so long for US to have 1st woman president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIllary Clinton is America’s best hope | The Economist https://t.co/QhDbrGxGR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wendy_Bacon NO, don't agree. Why get rewarded for something that is part of job, especially when Urban Hrowth efforts were so shallow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame on @cpyne for sinking so low to attack Gillian Triggs on behalf of a desperate LNP_despicable. https://t.co/h4TSolaYPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame on Christopher Pyne for sinking so low to attack Gillian Triggs on behalf of a desperate LNP  https://t.co/uM7fVmD2mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorker Perhaps describing them as "debates" should be reviewed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Abbott use of gun debate cynical? READ Samara McPhedran for actual facts on gun control and gun in question. https://t.co/kVeRwlrt6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claims over lever-action shotgun are pure fiction. Thanks Samara McPhedran for actual facts, polies shameless. https://t.co/kVeRwlrt6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprojecttv @jonathanvswan Disappointed, should have provided more info on size and scope of poll, implication was  "41% of Americans"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WikiHillary for President, great vision, liveHillary could offer same message to public, but media might mangle. https://t.co/O6DKDO2oBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Why does this crap get press, it does not deserve any oxygen, deserves only to be ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus No thanks, think I'll pass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro I am with you Jane, so admire @HillaryClinton not sure what more she would have to do to be recognised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems like a good time to ask: is privatisation of electricity networks ever a good idea? https://t.co/JZ4Cn0MJg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites beautiful, reminds me of slime molds colour-wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro Winds giving a hard time to my Poppies and sweet peas too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KKeneally @frankjotzo @TurnbullMalcolm @smh Malcolm Turnbull is a sad shadow of his former self. He has no excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wetlands doing their thing.  https://t.co/WnZdTTpWYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to imagine any football supporter with a heart and red blood in veins that is not behind the Bulldogs. https://t.co/KKpuWRu7n1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why you should be supporting the Western Bulldogs today https://t.co/KKpuWRu7n1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World-first genome study reveals rich history of Aboriginal Australians. Hope it attracts the attention it deserves https://t.co/Q20X9HmfAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should be proud of this discovery_Indigenous Australians most ancient civilisation on Earth, DNA study confirms https://t.co/fP2wxudsI9”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia does not have a welfare problem, it has a poverty problem Poverty is not a sickness, nor a crime.  https://t.co/5YFV1e84Ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great promotion for @olympicpark_syd, congratulations to Swapan and team @Mozziebites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who do you want running Oval Office? A highly qualified candidate with great record  or a dolt with a bad toupee? https://t.co/chzPJ0ed6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManuSaunders Thank you, I even love the words "mini mossy meadows"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites the Hawks Geelong match would have been a choice, tough game, unbelievable ending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites anything else but revisiting draft, not on a Friday night, bad vibe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewbogut well you are one up so far. WB won very well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Life is not over’: Syrian boys photographed jumping into waterhole in war-torn Aleppo - - https://t.co/KMHWh8E2PP https://t.co/4mOeIw7a4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this rainy day an optimistic or maybe desperate frog has blessed one of my marginal water pots with eggs! https://t.co/H0oeszPWl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China’s proud 300-year history of female-led mosques is an inspiration to the west https://t.co/DJ33FNXsn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens @lenoretaylor Does anyone believe this self-serving garbage from Abbott deserves oxygen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughriminton Just saying though, this explanation soothing for the messy-cum creative ones but offers no solace to partners and housemates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughriminton Thank you, will show this to my husband!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research: Abbott and Turnbull the worst economic managers since Menzies https://t.co/sh5DBtDGZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewbogut we loved watching, cried at end. If it was about heart you would had your gold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenMcDonell and without some of those dodgy ref calls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUSOlympicTeam @RBroekhoff45 Boomers playing with great heart, so proud of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasketballAus Take to them boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGaze10 We will be watching and cheering on our Boomers from Newcastle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smh I am horrified to see John Coates doing this when our athletes are still competing. Showing no respect, shameful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasketballAus We will be up watching cheering you on. Lets hope the Serbs sock it to the Yanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't  John Coates wait until the Olympics was over before trashing on our medal results? Shameful! #7Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb Will you be sharing the recipe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull’s Maladies - https://t.co/U3A8IM3TtZ @beneltham on Turnbull government fumbling or missing in action, certainly not leading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boomers we love you #AUS #GoBoomers #OneTeam @BasketballAus @Olympics https://t.co/ZqRAc2Dp4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BiodiversityGuy Winton trees are both beautiful and spooky, like ghosts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCthedrum @avrilhenry These hoons made fools of themselves, showed their ignorance, that should be broadcast far and wide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFP Tokyo and Seoul, Capitol cities for two beautiful countries, any improvement in relationship is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewbogut Watching every match, we are Aussie wannabes born in USA, love your passing game, behind Boomers 100%, it's time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twitchathon Ha betcha he forgets he fell asleep and still loves it. Its about the Dad time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarepolks89 @TheMatildas We love you girls, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_hannam Why ever are they being so looked after? Looks like favouritism to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCthedrum Is anyone weakening and feeling sorry for MT yet? I say don't be sucked in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Boomers are playing wonderful basketball, ALL should be watching, ALL should be proud Go #Boomers #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WorldRugby7s @7olympics These girls are so amazing, wonderful role models]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanMcNair @adamlmorton Just tried to fill in using First and Second householder, system not happy, rejected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprojecttv EggandBacon Is common Aus wildflower, brown and yellow flowers, likely Bay named after plant species and not food preferences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ed_hawkins @BiodiversityGuy Yes, but it was good material and good timing, I was impressed that they featured Climate Change so strongly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4corners  last night was the Tony Abbott try to take down Malcolm Show, how did that come About? Found it very strange. @murpharoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing and beautiful  chronophotographs capture the patterns of birds in flight https://t.co/R3YhxjwhNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayneReport @PaulBongiorno Why give these extremists oxygen so soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers for Hillary: event attendance 'through the roof' after Trump remarks https://t.co/aemQDzOQ8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on Brazil, making Climate Change a themes of olympics opening ceremony @PeterMacreadie @MaxFinlayson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil using the opening of Olympics to make powerful statement on climate change, using some of most recent graphics_ good on them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT_Trump, who criticized slain Muslim soldier's parents, got 5 deferments from Vietnam, including 1 for bone spurs https://t.co/IWNI5acLIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites YES, Daiso in Glendale, hooray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mozziebites Not sure but going on search today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Xeni, Same for me_ Hillary Clinton's speech was a powerful, primal first – and it blew me away | Xeni Jardin https://t.co/wUJyISdiMG”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Amy DAVIDSON, watched Hillary speech and am mystified at lack of cover_expat in Australia @tnyCloseRead https://t.co/18uRwBYm9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro @ABCaustralia Listened to entire acceptance speech live today. #Inspiring Hillary was ready to lead in 2008, even more ready now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking About Hillary — A Plea for Reason — The Policy a MUST READ especially if you are not a fan. https://t.co/wSAbapexJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ideas from 35 years ago! Newcastle 1981 Harbour Foreshore Comp winning scheme @emfarrelly @mikebairdMP https://t.co/LG2kEnIT5f”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hon N.Wran opened electrified rail services to Newcastle 1984 but failed to integrate 1981 harbour-front plan https://t.co/V9lj4JUNwn”]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>