<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@chakraqueen One nil, Lewis with the only goal and I cop the lot!  First, last and anytime scorer!  Am signing off now.  Enjoy the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm ever so sorry to bore ya
With my tale of an anytime scorer
I've unloaded a chunk
And bet it on Dunk
And I'll probably end up much poorer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ou_tis @MontyCFT People in Horsham used to call us penguins when we went into town on Saturdays.  No idea why https://t.co/m4gI0Kqw9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MontyCFT But ... are collies smarter than penguins?

#Subtweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't believe in the same sky fairy as us we are formally putting you on notice"  Sean Spicer https://t.co/ubTOMsT8y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MontyCFT Well I'm inclined to believe you seeing as Collies are the most intelligent breed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really don't get this Hockney thing.  Did he think the S*n demographic were now going to rush out and stock up on prints of The Splash?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baddiel Some of those early albums are gorgeous.  He was great live too.  My pals band supported him on tour in '86.  What a character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I doubt there's ever been a better protest song than this one from Cheech &amp; Chong's Nice Dreams movie

 https://t.co/6Up8SSqWLB via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just opened the fridge and put the piri-piri chicken on notice,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's another White House presser about to start and I'm gonna try and post this old picture of Sean Spicer every… https://t.co/6rKERowNwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJhamilton you're welcome. I hope you get some interest. Let me know if you don't and I'll try and give it another nudge,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanineCluster @wscountytimes I should be.  I'm pretty ashamed of that one to be honest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No charges have yet been made. https://t.co/s81YwFDEiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's plenty of non-food items that you can donate to your local foodbank. https://t.co/WCWhwhSNVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pass it on please.  Reviews, blogposts and features will really help here.

#JournoRequest
#PRRequest 
#Bloggers https://t.co/8UnKYGf2xO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_kierangoodwin In light of current events I'd add history to your list of "must haves"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HbfBritain Does shoving it up Kirkland Tellwright's backside count as useful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MontyCFT lol.  Monty's on Twitter. What a time to be alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little heard in public, Bannon is quiet power in Oval Office   https://t.co/Sg1ebaGazK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just checking ... is it just Iran and Mexico that Trump's threatened today or have I missed any other countries while I was away?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willsmithwriter Imagine fucking a pig's head and it not featuring in your "top ten worst things I've done in my life" list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since 2010 rough sleeper numbers have been spiralling. Why? https://t.co/7AABO9ibTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voltagesparks I'm not sure everone's joined the dots yet to work out what's going on.  So obvious. #$$$$$$$$$$$$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry he won't forget you.  There's 150 billion barrels of oil in Iran that he and his mates have got their e… https://t.co/hhZCyGovgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPJHodges I think he may have threatened Iran with war shortly after you tweeted this. No biggie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobHarris What odds will you give me on the groundsmen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Tosh - Equal Rights &amp; DownPressor Man (Live) https://t.co/fY0EVIalgy via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone tells you that the Premier League is the hardest in the world I'd recommend pointing out that Crouchy scored 100 goals in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizKershawDJ Depends if in this context "DJ" stands for diabolical joker.  Plenty of them have stood for parliament, and got elected!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the hemp bible, a truly fascinating read, originally penned in '73. Have a look at the chapter headings and… https://t.co/U2YEAtcjcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geordiecat2012 I'm a bit fuzzy headed and things are taking time to process so you're probably right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holloway in dressing room:  "Keep it tight for the 1st 20 mins lads, quieten down the crowd, take the sting out of the game" 
GOAL! 41 secs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stegsythedog @Edwina_Currie Goes without saying Nigel.  Imagine waking up next to John Major though!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just heard Devo's "Whip It" being used in a Premier Inn TV ad. No idea what story this is meant to convey.

https://t.co/BsrxJYgzy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've let yourself down badly there @Edwina_Currie, go and have another lie down for a few years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.... and just three days later he announces his choice of opponent.  Iran. 

#TinyHands #Iran https://t.co/A8LyNFTGN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, who had Iran in the sweepstake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDekka @Stegsythedog So near and yet so far ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stegsythedog I backed Dhoni to be top Indian bat. Morgan to be top England bat.  And England to win at the break @ 2/1 (They went odds on)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've done my absolute conkers on the cricket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDekka @RowleyfileRRR Actually "often" may have been overplaying it a tad but I've suffered mass exodus a few times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RowleyfileRRR Hehe, I often lose more than that in an hour.  You'll manage without 'em somehow Simon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye then.  I guess we'll all just have to somehow manage without you. https://t.co/0D12RgDNqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's actually called a petition. I've just checked and so far 1,792,857 people in the UK have signed it. https://t.co/CYa4TX5jNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lou Reed ~ The Day John Kennedy Died https://t.co/jW4CCUgmyd via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TweetSomethingPositive https://t.co/tOxZzzhagY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should randomly spin the dartboard between each leg so the 20 isn't always at the top. https://t.co/DbEGrEIGsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanineCluster @TheNewsThumpAPL lol.  It's the will of the people innit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough one this ... https://t.co/CEpUjJ0aww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental health needs a #fairshare of funding. Sign our petition and help us reach 100k signatures by 22nd June https://t.co/cut6xRNChd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheech and Chong - "Born In East L.A." https://t.co/NQTleajL5A via @YouTube

#FuckingWall @TommyChong @CheechMarin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed up with petitions?  2 Years ago this one got 100k signatures &amp; people are alive today that wouldn't be otherwis… https://t.co/FiFEEpvrcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Annabel_Giles In that context it is good language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and Peter Hitchens.

#JustSaying https://t.co/ywIlVIugAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mutablejoe Beautifully crafted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Debate the possibility that the "Will of the People" has changed since Brexit https://t.co/rFjP2wyygJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we have a winner ... https://t.co/pg5j5ox1uA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all being told to study by a man who's never read a book in his life and gets his insight on world news from… https://t.co/pO4hZT9QmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophiasundh @artistsmakers and the next Trump EO will likely be an attack on the LGBT community. Well done Brighton for such a big turnout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow.  It'll be the disabled next. https://t.co/Z06KopKndc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowded House - Don't Dream It's Over https://t.co/oAzT9lc6uH via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream Academy - "Life In A Northern Town" (Official Music Video) https://t.co/SGddujEXfi via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voltagesparks @YouTube I don't listen to the radio so rarely hear stupid pop songs anymore!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_razor101 @arobertwebb @andwarn Yup, no idea why I asked tbh.  A schoolboy error on my part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Avett Brothers - Down With The Shine (Live on Letterman) https://t.co/AsF2cCbrRS via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Isbell - How To Forget https://t.co/k5n1vSe8TN via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_razor101 Ewwww, glad to see I'm not missing anything meaningful, sensible or profound. @arobertwebb @andwarn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voltagesparks @YouTube I can't listen to that song too often 'cos the bassline gets stuck in my head as an earworm loop for days after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/s1CIjxvIRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Doobie Brothers - "The Captain and Me" (Full Album) https://t.co/iRBBnCx2nr via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey you government
Never try to separate the people
Hey you politician
Never try to separate the people"
#MuslimBan
https://t.co/ha0Bqf8cyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky Dube-Feel Irie https://t.co/8mgGVxkFvT via @YouTube

#TweetSomethingPositive #Reggae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stegsythedog Me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natural Ites And The Realistics - Picture On The Wall - THE TUBE https://t.co/kiG375P2Jq via @YouTube #reggae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Who - Don't Let Go The Coat https://t.co/lwTMLqpzeW via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kinks - Come Dancing https://t.co/S79qQydHF0 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-NEW- Something In The Air Thunderclap Newman HD {Stereo} https://t.co/0MyBf8A2NV via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Housemartins - Happy Hour - live https://t.co/kp3Q5Bcu0p via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freshies - I'm In Love With The Girl On The Manchester Virgin Megastore ... https://t.co/lsbToCjc6Y via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Waifs - Falling https://t.co/bzQAD07sPP via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your Mother" by Keston Cobblers' Club https://t.co/DU91RNnjKQ via @YouTube

@CosyFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andwarn @arobertwebb So I've not missed anything then? Hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whiskeytown- "Pneumonia" (Napster Pre-Release Version)  HQ https://t.co/L3pcg3VA8R via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arobertwebb @andwarn What's that idiot said now?  I'm blocked so can't see his nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The last time I worked with Paddy was 1983; I nearly throttled him."  Martin Stephenson on Prefab Sprout's Paddy Mcaloon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Stephenson: The escape artist https://t.co/qImkTy2wfl

@MGStephenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlantaPress @rawedgespassion @katellstephan @CultureHUB1 @Bandcamp I've literally just tweeted out a few more  @MGStephenson songs.  Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Road - PLAY LOUD!

@MGStephenson &amp; The Daintees

 https://t.co/2zzfhuxILB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home - @MGStephenson &amp; The Daintees (From the album Western Eagle)

 https://t.co/tosd0hKKzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Summer - @MGStephenson &amp; The Daintees (From the excellent Western Eagle album) 

https://t.co/afMIQ1KZrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Biffo183 @YouTube I was at that gig!  JCC is amazing live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardosman Kanye West IS a pointless celebrity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redtache We live in truly scary times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small chance?

Unknowingly? https://t.co/OLmrf7IpLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie This guy spoke more sense than that idiot Spicer https://t.co/5c5TxH2HFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I predict @seanspicer will be fired by Trump sometime in the next month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of these journalists at this presser should just ask @seanspicer "Sean, how do you sleep at night?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Ministry of Misinformation spokesman Sean Spicer is live on CNN again. https://t.co/TovM5mOnqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TweetSomethingPositive https://t.co/rP5crv00Pj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>