<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcolville Power Word: Chill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acosmos @MOOMANiBE I dunno...My expectations are pretty damn high...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zerohedge @penultsquire so we can add "delusional" to his psych. profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alex_macdonald @SteveSaretsky it's almost like the government had incentive to intervene ... oh wait. *sad trombone*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraveArcanine @Harmonix *when they can't figure out that it's the politics that's hurting your business*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GammaCounter @martin_fff Not alright, alright, alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @FIVRE604 Wow - that service list is basically the how-to-avoid-the-foreign-tax checklist. "Please send kids".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson @jpegan "I've found *my* moving buddy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpegan @1baronjennyson *cackles maniacally*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson Moooooi? *innocent batting of lashes*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom @martin_fff I'd rather keep bad people out of government. Who's with me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rev_chas @AbbyHoward Both, and canonically as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MOOMANiBE That's a serious influx of capital. Ka-ching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BitUniverse I hope it's good. I really do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BitUniverse Thanks! I worked on all the ship cinematics you see in that trailer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencasselman @berkun @kathryncasteel @pewresearch How ironic that many "New Worlders" fled England to avoid religious persecution...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dgalinko @pierre It's regrettable that people actually died because of a knee-jerk, hastily issued and implemented policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BitUniverse @TessFowler and I've been blocked. That escalated quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteSchaad Agreed. That's how I felt at my "temp layoff" - they spoke to me like they would never see me again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of this. https://t.co/K5w4qrZ1eR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simonunger That would be lovely, of course. Best breakfast burrito I have had is at Railtown Cafe (so far).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathicks @Independent Worth every penny. He would have wanted it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BitUniverse @TessFowler At least one person read it with the intent which it was offered. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessFowler Tensions are obv. high and maybe you misread/miscontrued it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessFowler Wait. I wrote that Liberals (meaning government) have taken that approach for decades. I didn't say they should now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crunchywizard @SlyFlourish Might only work outside of pre-written...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessFowler It wasn't an attack. I'm on your side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessFowler This is the Liberal stance, that for years, does them no service against Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elcio_T_Lopes Do they only work within roll20? Is it possible to use them in something like Fantasy Grounds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashemedai Seen it before and we suffered 4 years under a moronic President. Thankfully, Obama happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simonunger It's signalling the Tim Horton push into Mexico (was announced) and extending a hand to our Southern brothers in solidarity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjacobsson @Beschizza I think it's still being covered in Canada - which makes sense. Didn't fuel current US gov't sentiment so "non-news"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS - just call them dark brown. https://t.co/NLhaHChwze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading about "Morrowind" for ESO reminds me that introducing new content rarely fixes/changes fundamentally the problem of MMOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashemedai They won't. Which is what makes them perfect opponent for the Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @GreatDismal it was either that or marginalizing people --- oh wait...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Inkybat so this rash of labelling liberals as "mentally ill" is recent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riggingdojo Wrote a script. Forgot about the spreadsheet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius for anyone looking to gobble up fallen stocks... I wonder who has the money for that.
https://t.co/mWPc38ibEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson Wow. Sounds like the seedier conversations that are being had in Vancouver. Ripe for this sort of thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpegan Need to really soak/boil it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson Think of it as Canada's Texas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson Yes but more importantly, particularly with Alberta, oil money (and other mined resources)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riggingdojo Is there a quick way in Maya to nuke the transform limits on all joint nodes in a skeleton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kylegriffin1 But thing is, they know this, yet are not scrambling to stop it. Awareness is not action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roll20app Dumb question - I buy maps / etc. on the roll20 site. Is it possible to use them outside the app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@somethingbetter @Khaaasteh THEY'RE GOOD BIRBS, KATIE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson Aim for the throat or ears OR if you are intent on the face, aim for the divot under the nose or lower lip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcolville @matthewmercer I only remember that game as the one everyone wanted to have Glitterboy armor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcolville Usually the first game? Single paragraph as intro than *bam* into the story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love how I am reading Trump apologists saying it wasn't a ban when Trump actually used the word "ban". #notallbans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump replaced the acting director of U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement on Monday night
https://t.co/OCjVpaHVHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprising ABSOLUTELY NOBODY. https://t.co/9AIYwKFdg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FIVRE604 Would love #5 to be applied generally. Flipping prevention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteSchaad Actually heard about this from a Global reporter... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_mcelroy No. Learned a lot of interesting parallels between his/your business and the game industry/vfx studio life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_mcelroy My brother-in-law is/was the voice of the Whitecaps. Mentioned that this was def. a possibility today. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinchans Player name checks out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaikit_tim basically back where we started from before the tax was implemented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saladinahmed @nytimes I hope he gets a rose this season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are going to defeat ISIS by marginalizing people" said no intelligent foreign policy person ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judicial Branch of the US government has been removed from the White House's official website. #ruhroh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This protest sponsored by Tim Hortons. https://t.co/OlTemCfywc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattcolville Just finished a re-watch of "Brotherhood of the Wolf". Forgotten just how D&amp;D that movie is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@rockpapershot Better late than never but players have prob. already moved on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPerkinsDnD Wait a minute ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Angela Merkel is the leader of the free world ... what a time to be alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson So he can say she craved the D unironically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asphaltOnline piffington!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1baronjennyson I almost wish now there was a pre and post weigh-in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think "Brotherhood of the Wolf" is the closest we ever came to an actual Witcher movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlderLaneeggs @steeletalks980 @DonutShorts No. Just paid for, which we already knew. First time I am considering voting NDP out of spite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @DuranCKNW980 They already do. Expecting a 30% surge and then collapse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc The amount of proxy buying is going to be incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuranCKNW980 @penultsquire Gotta keep that bubble going at all costs. Going to be amazing to see how many min. wage earners buy real estate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JessicaValenti @usweekly @moorehn They are one meeting away from a network deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanKerrigan @Inkybat Oh man, I have to find a way to add one to my campaign! Regeneration, resistant to bladed weapons, no vuln. to fire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@padamlucka @mikemearls it's only week 2. Give him time to go "full Mussolini" ... or stop him before he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathicks Could be he's afraid because of a medical condition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["IKEA's Flat-Pack Refugee Shelter Just Won a Design Award" https://t.co/O94b41hgbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelseyanzai @cathicks You are just catching on now to the grand US pseudo-Christian hypocrisy ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty much perfect.
https://t.co/zipfh73Wpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yantor3d Gosh, I would love that, too. Colorado is gorgeous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlyFlourish Is it a good campaign setting? I know abs. nothing about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jk_rowling I didn't hear him use the words "lovely" or "successful" once. The cheek!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RyanLizza @GreatDismal It's his great advice that I wish he would do to his own administration. Trump - Folding "with dignity" 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jonrog1 @nypost Proving that US customs agents are dangerous in that they feel beholden to nobody; let alone the law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MoneySenseMag Isn't this the exact reason that Starbucks is currently facing problems? That caused their stock to slip several points?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OliDuggan I hope he does. I will be spending exactly 0 dollars in the US as long as that order stands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I, too, welcome our US West Coast brethren to the fold. https://t.co/JxrSBS2zk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simonunger Wow. This would simplify my life so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dirtytea Well played, history. GG2EZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlyFlourish @FaustoReluctant The old Bard's Tale games had similar system to what you describe. Lines of ranks: Melee, Ranged, Spellcaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlyFlourish @FaustoReluctant It was more in response to someone using gridless but still wants to push minis around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlyFlourish @FaustoReluctant have a piece of string with 1' marks. now you have measured movement without a grid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JimAxelrod I predict a circuit of TV interviews in the next couple of weeks for that man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we still asking the "is it ok" question? https://t.co/9uTKyHFyXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FabbriLRSD @LinoD @Inkybat @JustinTrudeau I am already a Canadian citizen, born and raised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McJesse if "open minded" = "liberal" then yes, I think they do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinoD @Inkybat @JustinTrudeau Does this extend to Americans right now? Because, damn son.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>