<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the cokiest White House since Charlie Sheen's set visit to The West Wing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToTheDeathcomic, use your sway and help me attain the original. Geoff can use me in any way he chooses. Free intern, love slave, anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Geoff Senior Megatron/Springer picture might be the purest Transformers thrill I've felt in 25 years. Perfection. And yay @jcburcham!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to live in THIS universe. Graham's done an amazing job imagining what Transformers UK would have looked like… https://t.co/cTUHeV3mRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danmcdaid With a face like Dave Gorman's tattoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenKPirrie Maybe the same page! I dunno. Something from Sins... But nothing's leaping out. The splash from #5? Or Verity in the snow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickRoche 'Favourite' is not the same as 'best', but y'know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another page for use in this week's @Pulsec lectures: My favourite page I've ever drawn, from MONSTER MOTORS.… https://t.co/qjlA0LjJzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoubsGsy @xenonsisyphus He's in the current NOVA series, I believe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoubsGsy @xenonsisyphus I couldn't bear for you guys to think I was some Johnny-Come-Lately to Deff's 'Edd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoubsGsy @xenonsisyphus Check out Marvel's Revolutionary War/DH 1-shot from 3 years back, I drew the two of 'em. Sorry if you already have!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xenonsisyphus We're partying like it's 1991. Top, top stuff. Chuffed you gave 'er a spin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say WHAAAAT? This is ACE, Matt! https://t.co/va6LP6GXww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynpie You're a better man than I...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boxofficeartist You're insane. I can't speak to you, in case I catch your craziness. If I could catch your talent, fair enough, but... MAN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynpie Either delete your account or that tweet.Choice is yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two of my insanely talented pals are teaming up on what looks like one of the most definitive slices of Star Wars a… https://t.co/EJdjN30XfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_milton75 @Pulsec @AndyLanning @Alancowsill Can definitely do *A* version of it at a Con or something. It's more general comics than TF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_milton75 @Pulsec @AndyLanning @Alancowsill No, it's for a proper accredited course, so folk would have paid to partake. Sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cracksh0t Just live-roleplay it with the rest of us, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynpie No,Simon Bisley is the REAL and famous artist Simon Pegg's character is named after. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway, ask nicely and nice people will be nice to you is the lesson? Rummaging through old artwork ahead of this week's lectures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;@StephenWacker told me he wasn't convinced (He was right) and could I "Get my inner Bisley on?" (His words.) I got… https://t.co/SBSz2SxjYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[File-trawling. I was assigned a different REVOLUTIONARY WAR title originally, but wanted to draw Death's Head. Sent… https://t.co/CJ2p2z8B5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buboniccc I'm not sure if I ever thanked you properly for your TFCON sketch, did I? Thanks so much! You're, like, well-nifty, innit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't remember if this made the Trade or not, but here's page one of the #SinsOfTheWreckers pitch. https://t.co/Va7zJb18u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...This is what I found; thumbnails based on @Alancowsill and @AndyLanning's loose plot for REVOLUTIONARY WAR: DEAT… https://t.co/MQIFpeb5xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of my lecture for @Pulsec, I'm scavenging old emails from @AndyLanning and @Alancowsill for Death's Head making-of gossip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go see it and treat yourself to a cheeky print! (Mine's the 'Underground' one!) https://t.co/oqyhGI4hy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briantruitt Oscar talk, comics talk. Fuckit, I miss Ghostbusters 2016 talk. ANYTHING other than the news, Brian, please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danmcdaid Between Trump and Kopkins, this format has done more for fascism than a 1930s beerhall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC 1 still showing The US Apprentice. That's weird, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JekyllDraws The first one is happening, and the second one will be once I find time for a cut. Ditto backatcha, sistah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YukonShaun It is against the mane and not the man that I shall measure myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 You're optimistic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccreaman Powerful, almost Michelangelo-esque! And fair fucks for turning out something that finished in company. Couldnae do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt had fucking great hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LowmanX @glovestudios I hear ya. And that question is literally the only one I'm capable of forming coherently. Uncharted territory, etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljholden Saving up for two more to assemble the full swastika.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatbuggygirl You probably saw this at the time. Teaser page from the backmatter. https://t.co/F8S5p0WYpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatbuggygirl Ha! No, just might not be what some people are after. It was one-man (ish) show this time. IF there's a HC, I promise fiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatbuggygirl There's no 'in-universe' stuff or fiction in Sins' backmatter. It's just tons of sketches and detailed chat about process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strike315 Love hearing that about the extras. Thanks so much for saying so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YousephTanha @CaseyWColler I remember getting told off by... Corin, maybe?... for doing it. 

SO much handsome in that grab, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LowmanX Yeah, I'm on the same page. Looking at the countries either side of me and thinking "Maybe Euros are more useful than these pages".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatbuggygirl I would say yes... but there's 15 pages of process stuff, with LOADS of text annotations about the design and story elements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 @glovestudios Guido probably flogged his within seconds too. But it's a record you stand to hold, I think. Maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 @glovestudios Said 'still' twice. Like a prick, A PRICK.

Said that twice now too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads up though, the impending Apocalypse is making me consider cashing in all my original artwork to build a bunker, so watch this space...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-@jroberts332 You're STILL the only person to own MY original lineart from the book still! Waki's and @glovestudios' inks are out there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraLePew Only because YOU said so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dreams are very niche, but drawing Slash and Mondo Gecko for TMNT was another one come true. Here are the nekkid… https://t.co/aW3mdrFC8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! Check out this Mighty Mutanimal-icious cover for @IDWPublishing's TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES #69! Lines by m… https://t.co/3nF0PVrpFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Drivaaar A deserved stroke of luck for one of life's tolerable guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JZBelexes Achievement Unlocked. :) 

(Thanks for reading it. Sincerely.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know we could all do with a feelgood story, but despite that, please buy the collected Sins Of The Wreckers to fe… https://t.co/dPbHMN2YVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@79hfg3n3948rhf0 Thanks! It's  long time ago, so has plenty of problems to my eyes. But hope you enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll snap out of it in a second, don't worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having one of those days where I fantasise about doing a Dinobots series or one-shot or SOMETHING with @SimonFurman3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new favourite ship, sitting on my old favourite ship, looking at their favourite ships. https://t.co/XSRdRQa3ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The colour art (immeasurably improved by @jcburcham) is Out There now, so here's the lines for LOST LIGHT #5's cove… https://t.co/ILLh9E5nRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like Corbyn could be the Walter Peck in this analogy, but it might just be the beard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The inevitability of May meeting Trump is the Keymaster/Gatekeeper conundrum of our times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_comics Jeepers. That's the angle right there. Could you imagine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_comics Giant-Sized Locke &amp; Key meets Monster Motors Holiday Special. We can tell Joe and Brian about this later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_comics Monster Motors come to Lovecraft?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 I very much enjoyed that. he's over-reaching like fuck on about four fronts, but good stuff from one of my top 3 Queen members.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 I was just starting secondary school, so about to be exposed to Big Boy music. (Metal/Grunge.) No Iron Maiden by this point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332  I would have been 11/12 when this was out. What it would have done to me then. It's doing things now, but... The CG alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 The... Darkn--? No. It CAN'T be. I'd LOVE this shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickRoche @jroberts332 @nellbailey He's my favourite out of The Breakfast Club. Bender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 I need to become familiar with the latter three. If they're anything near the caliber of the first two, then what am I missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 I absolutely and genuinely know you're not! The first tweet made it seem that Borderline had passed you by, or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 I wasn't sure if you were wildly dismissive of her in general, or was into her W. Orbit phase. Hmm. You're a curio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 No! Well, yes, because of your 'Borderline' utterances... but I want to know the measure of the man here. We used to be friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 Gimme your Madommeter; which of her songs would you consider good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroberts332 Wow! Well, I retract the original 'idiot', and replace it with a differently-intended 'idiot'. It's proper good that one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dox this idiot. https://t.co/x2FpiBZSnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saved Earth 3 times already, but kudos to LaBeouf for his commitment.

Would totally watch the Art Protest version… https://t.co/pzzwy8PC17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CampbellLetters Hey man, you probably DID know this, but the link to your website leads to an online shoe store? Maybe that's the dayjob?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StockmanNate Set before he made sergeant, correct?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_comics Hey, Gabriel, I'm trying hard to hate you, but then you pull something like this. Why can't I quit you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:O https://t.co/J1l59ayotN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little doodle of Venom, from my favourite comic series of all time, Marvel's "The Nineties". https://t.co/fZT8zaNQ5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLawrence_Art I've heard it. And, no, you don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLawrence_Art No, I remember your penchant for competitive bellowing. Just didn't peg you for Oirish traddery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLawrence_Art This one came from nowhere, Jack, I'll have to admit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLawrence_Art Like every Irish singer, I feign Mid-Atlantic Yearn. Sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLawrence_Art With an accent too. Obnoxio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cracksh0t I like it when you talk about The Darkness, Jordan. I feel less alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOME COVER, BOI https://t.co/j1kU31oNWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And breathe. My fave Irish band, Wexford's @frankenbolts have some dream pop for you.
'To Make The Sunlight Thin'. https://t.co/Skl7HyviKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may THINK you're still 15, but it's not until you chuckr a checked shirt over a Smashing Pumpkins t-shirt that you realise you aren't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to... everyone for this wonderful union! My pal Andrew Griffith teaming up with Cullen Bunn and Jimmy John… https://t.co/i4O7GxSdgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all a bit tiring, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherAntos Smug Points off the charts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briantruitt Listening to 'Drive It Like You Stole It' is its own reward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Furman wants to win, he goes big.

Well, I say "big"... https://t.co/wtHGoqrasP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is what Batman looks like. https://t.co/rpn6Qq3QMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaseyWColler I think you've got a good Superman in ya.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>