<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gala best selling apple variety in the USA followed by Honeycrisp https://t.co/3vsAbuLDu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysterious and deadly brain illness in India caused by lychees https://t.co/3O1YAcI1qO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oppy introduces new grape varieties https://t.co/WoTdQXlkLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We want to transition the tropical roots category from ethnic to mainstream' https://t.co/pIDAPTIHRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Brazil’s cocoa market crashed–and how genetics is reviving it https://t.co/bDAasZnY9c via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel ramps up Europe-bound avocado exports https://t.co/KCNewcS1jh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NAFTA rejig may bring opportunities, says Canadian produce rep https://t.co/kaf4RtkPci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agriculture_16   How would I post my tweets on your website??  Pardon my ignorance please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bayer launches Minigustos snack vegetables https://t.co/6HYiYkbNy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avocados rank third in the consumer shopping list 2016 https://t.co/BW5QSFSEw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important tips when quick freezing bananas https://t.co/aEVCB6Riat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oppy introduces new grape varieties https://t.co/kkVlMDfChT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will Trump’s ‘2-for-1’ executive order limiting regulations mean for GMO labeling law? https://t.co/2Q6ZzqaXXh via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monoculture in cover crops is often better than polycultures https://t.co/r6UDRxNBjf via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programming Antiviral Defenses in Plants through Genome Editing https://t.co/RuTkAr7uLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers Use CRISPR/Cas9 for Precise Excision of Transgenes from Rice Genome https://t.co/Odw7mC7Cbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Florida Research Team Discovers Genetic Key to Restoring Tomato Flavor https://t.co/hjXZbRMW5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Collaboration to Discover Sources of Genetic Resistance to Corn Diseases https://t.co/b7uowJsWMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reducing ethylene levels allows higher storage temperatures for vegetables https://t.co/tD6OVDbxqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penn State publishes plasticulture strawberry variety trial report https://t.co/cThpeL0aDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cristal, Chile's first kiwi variety https://t.co/D4oxCXHqtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists find way to breed healthier spinach https://t.co/NmdCCWy9o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important tips when quick freezing bananas https://t.co/wtR01movnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oppy introduces new grape varieties https://t.co/zqLtTG08M7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish lemon program enables year-round supply for US customers https://t.co/DntTsf8rN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epigenetics Around the Web: Can changes acquired during an organism’s life be passed on? https://t.co/39KVRc9g5c via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: How breadfruit became a staple food in the Caribbean – Pt. 1 https://t.co/tha1ER2mVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chile’s curious double standard: Produce GMO seeds for export but not for local planting https://t.co/7I6FwCDH9X via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next ‘big thing’ in agriculture? Genetically modified microbes https://t.co/SXV46l2Yu8 via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was a bad year for crop biotechnology and science https://t.co/HvzGHduY23 via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA asks for comments on plant gene editing guidelines for food use https://t.co/r1xvOdPN5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia intercepts, destroys 60MT of Polish apples https://t.co/vn5WAVT39n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-day breakfast: McDonald’s gets its wake-up call /via @globeandmail https://t.co/cCFqmdYtpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the mild weather in Ontario impacting winter wheat | https://t.co/w5jMokJrTK https://t.co/04g8H7vXxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economic Situation And Outlook For Prairie Agriculture With Dr. J.P. Gervais -CTV Farmgate | https://t.co/w5jMokJrTK https://t.co/3Rp0GfkmJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pouch bags drive organic apple growth https://t.co/g2vbFE0Tm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jalisco avacados stuck at the border - exporters seeking new markets https://t.co/h9ZfFBI6Rv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump stalls Argentine lemon imports for 60 days https://t.co/OKYmTtyOxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US vegetables flown in to Europe during unprecedented shortage https://t.co/RIrA64uery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breeding slower growing chickens: Is that a good idea? https://t.co/74gsQc99XT via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian govt invests in greenhouse tech for organic microgreens https://t.co/xelbZzIQa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should regulators, biotech critics stop searching for ‘breeding surprises’ from GMOs? https://t.co/BCGu71kiPE via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How conflicts of interest, NGO activism undermine European bee health oversight https://t.co/ryVve5XHeY via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will release of GMO American chestnut trees have ‘unforeseen’ consequences for environment? https://t.co/cw2FMrUIlV via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil and Peru compete with China on ginger quality, not on price https://t.co/233coswF41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organic bananas and specialty varieties showing strong growth https://t.co/Va2vO5mfAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stockton CEO to give keynote on marriage of Agrochemicals and Biologicals https://t.co/rNeoqz2b9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How conflicts of interest, NGO activism undermine European bee health oversight https://t.co/uG0EBX2EWt via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labels without packaging increasingly hit the market https://t.co/jr4mkDyReo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingerlime, the new gourmet citrus https://t.co/w7N4Sab4Al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingerlime, the new gourmet citrus https://t.co/AxIauUnZs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump stalls Argentine lemon imports for 60 days https://t.co/SrgqHgC8A4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TPP exit leads to uncertain times for US produce industry https://t.co/DrGLnhatYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing GMO concerns: Big Ag won’t let farmers save seeds https://t.co/f1Ap95CfxZ via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing GMO concerns: Are agricultural chemicals hazardous, overused? https://t.co/GLjLEpmIrq via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chile to ramp up production of South African Stargrape 2 variety https://t.co/1VMn6Ls41k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy’s Kiku gears up to roll out new apple varieties https://t.co/QnMuPztVEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. puts Argentine lemon import access on hold https://t.co/lw1NL1CikW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing GMO concerns: Are foods “made in labs” the same as those “made by nature” https://t.co/Vv5yHgb3hw via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Environmental Working Group’s “Dirty Dozen” discourage  eating fresh produce? https://t.co/sfHOlYnPAO via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seed industry, farmers ‘pleased’ with proposed USDA genetic engineering rules https://t.co/NDcRhAGqMX via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These types of fruit contain the least amount of sugar https://t.co/mdMpfzlS8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These types of fruit contain the least amount of sugar https://t.co/z6zWxC7h7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OVERVIEW GLOBAL COURGETTE MARKET https://t.co/9cV5GlRG1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Management Practices for bee health in horticulture https://t.co/JjbDypk6TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinks brands compete on sweetness https://t.co/lrMR65dp8o via @FoodManufacture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada to grow more Ontario apple trees to boost industry https://t.co/YAbXgBSmXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answering the 3 Most Common Internet Objections to GMOs https://t.co/Yov4QZaq8b via @eatcookwrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing GMO concerns: Are foods “made in labs” the same as those “made by nature” https://t.co/GC4Nrt0Lsq via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thorny policy issues follow advances in genetic modification technology | Crop Protection News https://t.co/tjYZ4dou8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two patent lawyers weigh in on the advantages of genetic modification technology https://t.co/xR5VOBidHp via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth busting: Is agricultural pesticide use in the US, and its impact, going down or up? https://t.co/hWxR7oQgLL via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salad was the largest organic market for 2016 https://t.co/Paa9NOlnfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Influx of grapes as Peru season ends and Chile begins https://t.co/nIJsrT4BPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hazera shows off pink tomato in China https://t.co/jsqEkb8VRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aphria expands Leamington facility to 1,000,000 sq. ft. https://t.co/WXfHRFehOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Table grape varietal reconversion underway at Capespan Namibia https://t.co/UphmaJSZ9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth busting: Is agricultural pesticide use in the US, and its impact, going down or up? https://t.co/pksXv9xjgX via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth busting: Is agricultural pesticide use in the US, and its impact, going down or up? https://t.co/rdJ00KL8qD via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 ‘post-truth’ anti-GMO headlines: Biologist critiques outrageous 2016 claims https://t.co/4fM3ZaFwoL via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating hot peppers decreases mortality https://t.co/PXbhT1EHw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating hot peppers decreases mortality https://t.co/Weoxw06beU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Produce industry launches draft Ethical Charter on farm labor practices https://t.co/z6oykZM0dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More pesticides than iron in Indian spinach https://t.co/gvhnQsJabX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human health implications of organic food and organic agriculture https://t.co/vvMkOfDT4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario's greenhouse industry challenged by cap and trade https://t.co/Dk5FoMu49N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic politicians’ mostly anti-GMO views lead list of liberal anti-science positions https://t.co/nnfzmbUizG via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth busting: Is agricultural pesticide use in the US, and its impact, going down or up? https://t.co/cKHuAMMIen via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 ‘post-truth’ anti-GMO headlines: Biologist critiques outrageous claims from 2016 https://t.co/e5I49yoNsi via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media saves on SWD insecticides in Kentucky https://t.co/x8hP5V9mzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saffron, an interesting high tunnel crop https://t.co/6k60KuL16P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor savings with new strawberry container https://t.co/aksRxwCCwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blueberry variety for U.K. growers in sight https://t.co/YMRq4iIcCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Nuclear Science to Boost Plant Biodiversity | International Atomic Energy Agency https://t.co/bF2MySOR5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Nuclear Science to Boost Plant Biodiversity | International Atomic Energy Agency https://t.co/HCs45Rwap7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian vegetables trending in the US https://t.co/CFTOzJFQxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian vegetables trending in the US https://t.co/8AyaqbIUWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International kiwi agreement increases production in Southern Hemisphere https://t.co/tUaeEdTli1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International kiwi agreement increases production in Southern Hemisphere https://t.co/o7fDTUHS6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House releases coordinated summary for all US biotechnology regulation https://t.co/m94xfmHQJh via @GeneticLiteracy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>