<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Garage Project to open new brew site in the Hawke's Bay  https://t.co/pzq5V8oZJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farming option for classroom approved https://t.co/FIYJ7bTqXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Primary school encourages students to wear slippers in class to improve grades https://t.co/f65aqVUjWE via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools 'more reliant' on donations https://t.co/FulqCRCgg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literacy priority for urban Maori fund: https://t.co/h1rIUAWlPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher shortages inevitable with rising house prices https://t.co/idqQoh3su1 via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positively educational | Otago Daily Times Online News https://t.co/MBuFoGSfEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Stores Are Still The Best Way To Make Consumers Love A Brand via @forbes https://t.co/zO2ZVORuB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collaborating beyond our comfort zones https://t.co/JFpTbYVVbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Is Helping Us See Environmental Problems in a Whole New Light https://t.co/9z69A8Kj5Q via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evolution of the City by BestReviews https://t.co/0QNuMIolWY via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Amazing Video Shows Just How Much Software Has Eaten the World https://t.co/oj38gReoQN via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National portrait: Gareth Morgan, reluctant politician https://t.co/lMUCYL6FBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria University to open state-of-the-art film facility in Miramar   https://t.co/erQqzBvqyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real cost of schools competing for students https://t.co/FJnryg8048]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dennis Ngawhare: When adults pursue learning, it demonstrates the value of education to children https://t.co/iAxkgGruD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand children could start school at age four under cohort entry proposal https://t.co/zg55IZ7pzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to school road safety advice for parents https://t.co/cBgjS3uFOS via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: What's it really doing to our kids? https://t.co/fnrpLvJ09b via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home schooling has doubled in cost, some South Canterbury home educators say https://t.co/Pf4t7CeoJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School year begins for over 765,000 Kiwi kids https://t.co/XjKaiQlHQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s still time to make globalization work for all. Let’s start by fixing wage inequality https://t.co/mAuB8sCxUw via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Davos download: global economic warming https://t.co/qjQcAxQ1hM via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher shortage 'at crisis point' days before school starts https://t.co/EsDqgxoihz via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dodgy teachers: 50 censured or struck off in 2016 https://t.co/aiWNdsOC7v via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principals say holiday move a good idea - in theory https://t.co/Fo25nmoNco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$270k to inspire young women into tech sector careers https://t.co/WmcvZnKTpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University centre to open in the heart of creative industry https://t.co/nrE0U59uNv via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A billionaires' dream: The most expensive home ever listed in US goes on sale for $250million https://t.co/kqhkzh49rh via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional Federer urges Nadal to stick with him https://t.co/enBN2viHy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fast-track Kiwi https://t.co/wqPj98Inun via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is globalization anyway?  https://t.co/FWm6ioH6Cw via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 predictions for the future of retail – from the CEO of Walmart https://t.co/pZpuKyx8tJ via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China will impact the world economy in 2017 https://t.co/yznnK1W3e8 via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global implosion of trust https://t.co/ZBoNuqCYNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-driving trucks to haul cargo between shipping terminals in Singapore https://t.co/100JTMTWkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Future Robots be able to give Birth to Their Own Children? | DaVinci Institute – Futurist Speaker https://t.co/bFIUKjdZ84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robots will destroy our jobs and we’re not even ready for it https://t.co/9kDuyx9T3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maori resourcing a priority for new NZEI head: https://t.co/b2pPtCqvQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunne Launches Campaign to Change Summer Holidays https://t.co/EaxKWU0ww0 via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of funding makes home schooling 'unrealistic' for some families, home educators say https://t.co/AUwvJmhAaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand children could start school at age four under cohort entry proposal https://t.co/zg55IZ7pzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher pleads for second chance after NCEA fraud https://t.co/JsGSdt9Ai6 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal stress: Overworked principals are burned-out and 'just surviving' https://t.co/qdK75Mae7t via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mounting cost of getting kids back to school https://t.co/o1lB2bGjvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for a teacher training shake up ? https://t.co/2AzVtTDBCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers blame government for added stress https://t.co/9cggGDXPxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists raise $13k for women to study https://t.co/nzz04ezH0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the World Is Better Than Ever—and Will Get Better Still https://t.co/mB18Tyn2EB via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shift summer holidays? Kiwis say yes https://t.co/QEHbouoV6x via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's CEO earns 130 times the average salary. We need to talk about this https://t.co/abKJrghpG4 via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest stories from Davos 2017. https://t.co/sxWw4zXhWG via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sergey Brin: I didn’t see AI coming  https://t.co/fvh6YUkVzZ via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make the world a better place, we should focus on these 3 things, says Jack Ma https://t.co/fAlBe3pkY2 via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canvas is now fully integrated with Google Apps for Education https://t.co/RXyk3ZbBcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating a culture of student sharing, improving classroom results https://t.co/LRHvRajgAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stripe expands NZ preview, now available to all Kiwi businesses https://t.co/fI9iD7V2O2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the inventor of the electronic spreadsheet https://t.co/P37v51MuUK via @TEDTalks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cellular Reprogramming Rejuvenates Old Mice and Boosts Lifespans 30% https://t.co/kMTWJsg2FS via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aging and Death Are the Evolutionary Price of Complexity https://t.co/uzaHgwO5uj via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stem Cells Are Poised to Change Health and Medicine Forever https://t.co/TrV1IkHprX via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of fifth birthday school starts could hit preschools in pocket https://t.co/MsM6U1fGAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student loans are getting bigger and harder to pay off, new figures show https://t.co/m3LijIO1iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otahuhu College writes its own NCEA history https://t.co/lueQtX8sXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angela Roberts looks back on ups, downs and almosts of four years at helm of PPTA https://t.co/8lX8Ubx7k6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Canterbury reveals new campus design https://t.co/KED4fzdBMn via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maria Johnson: Early education needs funding boost from Government https://t.co/B9ETpkEDmM via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Duff: Education best way to get young Maori away from gangs https://t.co/QdV6t9nJTa via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The challenges of NCEA https://t.co/5gjvDwNzPP via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minimum wage to rise | The National Business Review https://t.co/CZzT7u9B3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1000masterpiece a good quick read. Identify the customers top tasks, use metrics to prove what does or doesn't work, continuously improve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School costs: $40,000 for 'free' state education https://t.co/n8i5meEjR1 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College students are not progressing in English and maths, DfE data reveals https://t.co/9ocng1uOx3 via @tes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost of putting a child through school to year 13 has risen to more than $38,000 https://t.co/bXLOga8GLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National denies kids their free school education https://t.co/t6MHBWx2xj via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECE technology expertise shared with support of NZTC https://t.co/BpDxTY6NNr via @scoopnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manukura students excel with 100% pass rate in NCEA https://t.co/RkcrYp58vg via @maoritv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maori resourcing a priority for new NZEI head: https://t.co/HoWsVA7AtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished "Transform: A Rebel's Guide for Digital Transformation" by Gerry McGo... https://t.co/0Z9IQOHn3v https://t.co/CFLiu9anaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is our response to the Green Party’s critique of our environmental policy.  via garethmorgannz - https://t.co/NCLu4NBGol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sergey Brin: I didn’t see AI coming  https://t.co/fvh6YUkVzZ via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the Green Party miss the memo that we can improve the environment without stuffing the economy?  https://t.co/DD1DdZ9uf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Us Two: The Black Seeds frontman Barnaby Weir and sound engineer Lee Prebble https://t.co/RDn3ZRIKK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Cider Vinegar - The Wonder 'Drug' of Yesterday and Today https://t.co/rlCFVWBtkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fourth Industrial Revolution: what it means and how to respond https://t.co/3Bw7ciG9kO via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big increase in new dwelling consents issued in Auckland in November https://t.co/DgscnZ2NAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xero chair resigns after Trump appointment https://t.co/ieoY7SY1h5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the precariat, the new global class fuelling the rise of populism https://t.co/lQnzOtoN6d via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China will impact the world economy in 2017 https://t.co/yznnK1W3e8 via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Ready to Love Math With This Sweet VR Calculator https://t.co/qXj3ZA5Q2i via @singularityhub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toontastic 3D: a playful storytelling app for kids https://t.co/xIKt7J4Otc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools desperately recruiting overseas to find qualified teachers https://t.co/FbxC5hYpCo via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Te Kura offers online help to students needing more NCEA credits https://t.co/qv2DpJ9DmP #Educators NZ #NZQA #NCEA #Te Kura]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shakira: What motherhood taught me about a child’s developing brain https://t.co/qSWLbIekqD via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the one thing you would change about the global economy? 10 Davos experts respond https://t.co/mfTRksvRla via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the most inclusive advanced economies in the world https://t.co/Rl67nyeiZB via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft HoloLens Review: Winning The Reality Wars via @forbes https://t.co/BwQ0VpOacF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Schwaber Accepting Boston Business Journal Lifetime Achievement Award for Innovation https://t.co/PI2IH9tHh0 via @scrumdotorg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2uaMR4mn56 | The home of Scrum &gt; About &gt; In The News &gt; Ken Schwaber Receives Lifetime Achievement Award https://t.co/j636DkzQgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwi named in Trump's team https://t.co/7Ybsqi8OkR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>