<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Hopefully her day gets better from here 💜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wholesomeIE Yep. It's a day for steamy busses and wet socks alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betrayal/standing up for what's right... https://t.co/I3piKv77wL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Poor thing. What a rotten start to the day, and on the rain too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wholesomeIE Aw man!! I knew I was forgetting something!! #squelchyfeet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue Spreading the love, what else can we do these days!! 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaneSinead fair play, you're some woman! Great achievement! https://t.co/JCEptzl4J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing @realDonaldTrump There's an Irish one growing too, asking our head of parliament not to travel on tra… https://t.co/w7EHbj3cAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True strength lies in standing up for what is right. Even if there's a chance you'll stand alone. https://t.co/XpTCqCBp6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no matter where they come from, no matter what their background, religion or anything else. https://t.co/Q59V4HRIMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DFB. Saving the world, one goldfish at a time...heros!! https://t.co/5BsafgKaWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see at least one TD responding in this manner. https://t.co/a35rssIwEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how a leader should lead in the free world. https://t.co/jdtDm0NfJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dereklaffan I understand people live in a world of fear &amp; uncertainty but it's the responsibility of those that le… https://t.co/NaIVC6xYQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dereklaffan Yeah.The very word 'extreme' doesn't sit well with me.'comprehensive'; 'fair'; even 'extensive' vettin… https://t.co/NBd9qkJocA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfJimLucey @walkinmyshoes None of which ultimately helps ot changes anything for the person in need right now. W… https://t.co/78hFHiNNK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dereklaffan Really good idea - flipping this on its head shows the ridiculous nature of these policies. Great thinking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@limitless_nrg thought you'd like this https://t.co/2hTQZGTVL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScienceMarchDC Because without it this would be much worse  
https://t.co/ZUmtBIP3HX - increase in predicted Irish… https://t.co/k4hYBVAbhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are passionate about actual rather than alternative facts, and want to support others who do, pls follow @ScienceMarchIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiona_od @tommjburke Big congratulations Dr!! Fab news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebyrnesNUIG Indeed, hopefully it passes quickly!  All is good, hope it's likewise with you x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebyrnesNUIG some.good news that might interest you! X https://t.co/TxmZzUZa07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brain hurts and it's only week one... https://t.co/TmQIr8pJVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you're not ok &amp; you've asked for help. Now what? Some practical thoughts for the next… https://t.co/yNoxkrR4aq https://t.co/ylJUnTUGSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon I guess I should pick up chocolate biscuits for with the tea too...just in case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If everyone resolved tonight to do as much good in the world as they possibly can, and then did it, the next 4 years won't be so bad maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauras_Views It was, they're both so lovely. And the Aras is gorgeous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauras_Views Bunch of us got invited up because of volunteering with Childline. He wanted to thank us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauras_Views Of course I had to wear high heel boots that day. Rookie mistake! https://t.co/apkk0zFp8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauras_Views I had tea with Michael D and Sabina in the Aras... Does that count?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And dignity. Just in the forthcoming events cause us to forget... https://t.co/v7pZQT3ps6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon I could bring extra Barry's??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aunua_ie Thanks!  some parts of it can be tough to remember sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first book thoughts post - https://t.co/GglsSoiiXQ https://t.co/vb92UNoQWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always good info to share/save.you never k ow when you/ someone you know might need it https://t.co/UpzLg8AJRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's a hashtag worth getting behind! https://t.co/LhG5a2dClp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, why wouldn't you donate? Not like you'll need them wherever you're off to next! &amp; isn't saving lives the most… https://t.co/NR2nuUfh8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course these children will need extra help and support, and this should be well in place before the children arr… https://t.co/YNvg5XFKlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyShortall The poor man. And what an awful night to have had to sleep out! This is heartbreaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This caption has a completely different meaning in Ireland!! 🙊 https://t.co/jI1XujYIYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon To make sure people read the whole thing??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@speccymcspec Hahaha, clearly I need to top up the auld caffeine levels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommjburke There's a lot to be said for people-less research also though,  all the same!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: I actually love doing research with young people. Their thinking is fascinating! #WiseBeyondTheirYears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommjburke Ahhahahahaha!! Gotta love a bit of autocorrect!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually love doing research without people. Their thinking is fascinating! #WiseBeyondTheirYears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A noble aim indeed! https://t.co/pbO6brjtoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["... dealt with by the court." - the problem &amp; question is who's remit it is &amp; why aren't they doing it? #HomeSweetHome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Gilligan makes a fair point that "it is not the matter of suitability of accommodation was not to be ..." #HomeSweetHome (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure they'll be getting a lot of non-rent related question given the developments of the last 24 hours! https://t.co/HjVKJWo3iO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dereklaffan Fair play! I'm sure it will. Great study!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon DCC, don't undo all the progress already! https://t.co/XslLb3bJxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GHMCalvert Fair point!  I like the cognitive reappraisal you're doing there! I 'looked' at 1 today. Just looked, nothing more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guys from the @BloodBikesEast are absolute legends, and really lovely guys too! https://t.co/029SrJ7znM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However bad my day/week was, it could be worse I guess... https://t.co/PtJr3BAX1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GHMCalvert Could be worse. Be glad your ingenious thoughts can process it all!! Can you guess I'm procrastinating??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyShortall I think your story would be a refreshing one to read because you didn't use any gimmicks. Fair play!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny_McShane Enjoy your diary shopping!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenny_McShane Paperchase!! I practically keep them in business!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon Best of luck with it, I look forward to seeing the final piece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon God love you having to try and make something out of that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon That's an awful lot of redaction!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejoicing at getting my reading mojo back! - Twenty-Six Pages In, or How I got My Mojo Back https://t.co/bYxF913WGQ https://t.co/vBnRyhbhCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickoshea I like to follow this one and peroidically pretend it's not a parody, just for the sake of my sanity https://t.co/MVQyZeAaD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe Brilliantly written piece Rosemary. I actually feel educated by yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StyleGuideBlog Absolutely. Not for any reason, but especially not for body shape/size reasons!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StyleGuideBlog No worries. You speak truth! The amount of beautiful bodies that suffer unnecessary self-hatred because 'ideals'. SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dunno that this was the best response to the issue. CF my RT re the AP opinion on these types of articles. https://t.co/EPRf7q1Inc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread! Your body, your business. https://t.co/4OEleWhQIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be funny if it wasn't so frightening!  Have to keep checking which is the parody &amp; which is the real one. https://t.co/7VtTK44GYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stonetravel4 @ItsCherrySue Thanks Corrina, that she is!! https://t.co/Kw0W7JzWvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue Naw, sure it's all only truth like!! 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ItsCherrySue, hope you don't mind but I did a lil piece on you... https://t.co/PkJvJB4uz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Person of Note: Sue Jordan https://t.co/o0OhLxOFr9 https://t.co/0WXs8bspwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey guys, we did it. We got through today!! That wasn't SO bad, now, was it?? #BringIt2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strumpetcity @Independent_ie I'm not disagreeing w/u?There are many issues&amp;each needs to be dealt w/ using appropriate long term solutions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strumpetcity @Independent_ie it may be but blaming only one reason is risking an oversimplification I feel. This is a complex issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strumpetcity @Independent_ie I'd say there are probably various reasons, but that could be one possibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/r7i843vXOM Surely empty beds are indicative of other issues than just 'availability' which need to be addressed urgently also?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyAnnFoley absolutely 😀 hope it's going well for you, we must meet up soon! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring it all on!! https://t.co/nCltMCeVfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GHMCalvert @HannaIsotalus oh I'm sure my "ingenious brain" will be able for the job at hand...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobKavanagh I won't have a word said against him. That voice!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue finally got around to writing a 6th post. More to come next year!Thanks for ur support, hope the new… https://t.co/TW8LUDh3yQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten things I wish I knew Ten Years Ago https://t.co/zt6yrmrO6t https://t.co/gh9zo3UNja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell ya what, the great big green room in the sky is proper kicking it after this year. Heaving with legends now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainiaLong Agus tú agus do teaghlach freisin Grainia. Bain taitneamh mór as a lá!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They did the maths folks. It's fact. https://t.co/zNf94TuNdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipoconnor it's beyond time for it. Hope to help in any way possible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipoconnor so well put. Hopefully this is only the beginning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiMind_Irl this sounds exciting, I can't wait!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure you'd want them to be 'able to become not homeless?' https://t.co/Al61pY9nFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanicaRibeiro exactly. These people have enough uncertainties in their lives without not knowing if they'll be safe night to night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is AMAZING. can anyone help?? https://t.co/R8SpdqyuCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That last part is important. That's what needs to change here. https://t.co/xBMXF3F76t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue @stonetravel4 ah no, you don't have that kind of cruelty in ya Sue! I've experienced that rage. Bury the potato in a drawer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue always good to have a potato on hand. You never know when a potato-related emergency might strike!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegalEagleStar you're right that the bigger problem is a govt issue but it was on the judge today to put such a stipulation in place also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghdoyle @HSHIreland great, cheers!  would love to help if possible.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>