<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair Trying to talk to your service centre about a flight on my credit card I never took. Told wait was 21min &amp; after 15 I am cut off!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSSURVIVALB2B thanks mate looks interesting. Unfortunately I'm carrying an injury now and not sure when I will be 100% fit again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched #spies because I enjoyed #SASWhoDaresWins. But it's total shit by comparison and am off to find something else to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia ooh it's available through naked wines!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#isitok for someone to be hiding under your desk while you are sitting there???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#dickFarage without a doubt. Has managed to transcend both sides of the Atlantic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dskipwithNZH I have some background info about a story you have in the herald. Can you DM me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamhillscomedy love your perfume ad for Brexit- so fucking perfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamhillscomedy just watching last night's show- can't blame Castro for missile crisis - not his bombs &amp; not his finger on button!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with the Wallabies on this one... https://t.co/bEIn6JuxEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonfox1976...Bro looks like you...   Big Aroha. theSlacks https://t.co/uzurcuif61 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia Let hope they make a better job than they did the June one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday night, glass of wine, rugga on TV- awesome. . . https://t.co/fOMTMizXS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[York to London £5 each way. . . https://t.co/DP7soaxQeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is well worth watching - to actually see how the fault has moved is amazing. https://t.co/usnTxIOvHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing- makes you actually understand what a faultline is and what happens when the earth moves. . I https://t.co/HCCks7ftUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great view of the changes along the NZ coastline post quake... https://t.co/kUqhB7SZ9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomBaxterGB Unreal!!!  How can a company get away with this?  Do you know anyone who has received product from them??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquakes in the Upper South Island/Lower North Island of NZ in the last couple of days... https://t.co/uIowAxJpzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquakes in the Upper South Island/Lower North Island of NZ in the last couple of days....https://t.co/uIowAxJpzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jasonfox1976 @Channel4 @billingham229b @ollie_ollerton @AntMiddleton333 will be light relief from stressing about earthquakes back home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile she is in masterton. I am in the UK and have been worried about them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile mum's mobile isn't working. Am on Skype with her while trying to text &amp; call her &amp; mobile not  working. Dads Vodafone fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighwaysYORKS why does an overturned vehicle northbound require closure of all southbound lanes???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the world is becoming a cross between Far Far Away Land under Rumplestiltskin and The Hunger Games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofLeeds what the hell is going on? Got surrounded on the a64 by asda and had abuse hurled etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia @Biggazdobx @runnersworlduk I don't understand what the word "moderate" mean??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Biggazdobx @Independent yep. Left handed is another big one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this bad??? @Corieltauvia https://t.co/8tnD905YH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia prickly hedge. Recovery is quicker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lucieno7 @andreahewittnz @PerpetualGuardn yep the commentators failed to notice Andrea didn't have them on to start with!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Male Privilege Is Why We Laugh At Lochte And Vilify Douglas https://t.co/GpoFhHkpp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSportOlympic Open Water Selection process is crazy - its not just top 10 at one meet, top 15 at the next. Way more complicated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1aurenboyle you are still a star and always will be - don't ever forget it. Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford under $500k is not affordable for far too many  people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport where is the swimming coverage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The free market at its best. . .  https://t.co/7gqw21OtvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really interesting read on what it takes to be the best at your chosen sport... https://t.co/VbItL4WtaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World is a very scary place.... https://t.co/149Yp7nb1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zohocares Why is our email not working???  Wont send to and wont receive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a 20min distraction from the hatred in the world. Interesting stuff from European Space Agency  https://t.co/cEX8qsFkqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expat debt will be chased in Oz https://t.co/5OfgB6On7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustNormNow @EGXCinfo @RossBrierley you and me both mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seaningle have a tale to tell about a coach using homophobic slurs &amp; abuse.Is frequently complained about -NOTHING has ever been done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an important message to get across and would go a long way to addressing the rape culture that exists https://t.co/xzEeXBnneG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News disappointing #isobeloakeshott. You are the epitome of "the sisterhood" in action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GO HELEN!!! Helen Clark makes pitch for Secretary General job in speech to United Nations https://t.co/OD3GRc2r7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia oh dear!  Rome's prestige in ruins as ancient city drowns in rubbish, rats https://t.co/d6eXwu7jfT via @@abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia I don't have your mobile but I will pick you up at 12.30pm :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#turboswimwear @turboswimwear DO NOT BUY FROM THIS COMPANY!!!  8months and no product.  A joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turboswimwear. 8months to make a swimsuit and deliver a swimcap that is IN STOCK? Many words spring to mind. DO NOT USE THIS COMPANY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bestboomer same. Who is stuck in the dark ages???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidesaddlesally totally agree. She's the one in the dark ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare line hanging low across road in BostonSpa.not my house or street but it will hang someone, cyclist, car. But can't report it 2 u!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia the mini heat wave bit is a little suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattfrei we are talking about you- how many languages do you speak and to what level?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boyan Slat's high school project raises millions to clean up world's oceans https://t.co/8UCPUTAIRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News what is this??? It's not news!!!! @jonsnowC4 what ARE you doing??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia so that's the problem! Best not run 10miles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corieltauvia Best we stop drinking at Sam Smiths Pubs....Landowner 'blocks' temporary bridge plan for Tadcaster https://t.co/jSKW2lRSQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An all round great guy who will be very much missed.  Always a great competitor in the pool and a great addition to…https://t.co/wbMz4dKyTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Severe flood warning after Tadcaster bridge collapse https://t.co/C0x3KbYLGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well it's wet. Boston Spa bridge threatened. I suppose we will hear it if it goes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said Rachel.  https://t.co/UkwWlP2FHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#channel4news how wonderful is @PoppyNoor!!! Spoke such truths so eloquently and simply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#channel4news how wonderful is poppy noor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News are you seriously thinking I should feel sorry for bankers? FFS loads of people suffer this WITHOUT the pay!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonsnowC4 I am going to have nightmares tonight of that woman! Political commentator?????? Where did you drag her out from!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#channel4news crikey that woman is scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone else who manages it without resorting to surgery. https://t.co/Xib95MOB5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about this when something goes wrong in the NHS. https://t.co/wES7aTHred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News wouldn't it be better to focus on the issues for &amp; against war instead of turning it into petty personality games alone????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VodafoneUKhelp And the online chat has been "unavailable" all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VodafoneUKhelp I have been trying to get hold of someone and we have been on hold for five hours. Sort it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very good read. https://t.co/OfZMPAxCUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpderaad twitter jp! What's become of you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant - its the first follower that changes a lone nut into a leader. https://t.co/6etF7iHPCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Northpowergrid why is the power in Boston Spa really low - lights really dim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoho you are rubbish. Your service is non existent and your product is crap. Wish I had never been introduced to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport What happened to the Stockholm Mens Triathlon Highlights at 5.15pm today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So True- Lauren is without a doubt one of the greatest distance swimmers the world has seen. Only one woman faster e…https://t.co/zaTrvDu3BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And again @1aurenboyle - You are without a doubt one of a very small group of the greatest female distance swimmers the world has seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @1aurenboyle you are an absolute star!!!  So proud!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks remarkably like it could be his own Winners Bible.  Read the book by Kerry Spackman. https://t.co/BFKuHHjoXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear it being said- look at the root cause. (And what causes it.) https://t.co/GCd3e5nB5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you make a service so shite and then offer people the opportunity to pay for better.  And then also charge 20quid…https://t.co/VRCQpytGrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Schools Back in the Pool and Reduce Drowning | PledgeMe https://t.co/6QNi95wwsW via @pledgeme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly true in too many organisations! https://t.co/gFfcA3EIRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News @jonsnowC4 employers lay off staff &amp; employ immigrants because they can pay them so much less. Employment law is the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News @jonsnowC4 how about asking why employers can pay so little which only poor immigrants will work for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very interesting read.... https://t.co/JSn60XpRGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryGibbonBlog I'm a kiwi. I feel marginalised and discriminated against. I have faced racism. Technically I am white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very interesting read on gender and education. https://t.co/2ShL06Oqvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krishgm "This is appalling behaviour...."  Yeah no shit Krish - they are politicians! What do you expect????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraKhanInspire great item on channel 4 news. You are awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c4news commercial imperatives eh? I would rather have heard victors story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rushanaraali fantastic performance on @c4news- you are a strong woman &amp; I salute you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@guardian: I’ve seen the secrets of TTIP, and it is built for corporations not citizens | Molly Scott Cato http://t.co/Pl5Kc9kEKS"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to find out the truth behind TTIP, the dirtiest trade deal in history? Watch our video now: http://t.co/CsISDALcR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So  the customer does still have power to make a difference....
https://t.co/krwCsTbSJJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>