<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC We haven't seen anything yet. Watch what happens if Trump gets to replace one of the liberal SC justices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter @JuddLegum "Cheated."  They whinge like small children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans in Maine had better be burning down the phone lines to Collins. https://t.co/57a7VEnAR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_donaldson @RonColeman Best not to concern yourself with the opinion of a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC Why, yes, yes it does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stranahan  have no problem with that in theory, but it'll never happen.  Defunding and let them go private is the best solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJ This is wonderful.  Hope the Republicans in Congress don't let us down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegInsurrection Hope there is a way this woman can be disbarred or disciplined for failing to properly represent her client, the U.S.A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor @Phil_Mattingly @evanperez Still waiting to see one single legal argument against the validity of the order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courrielche It'll be a happy day when I never have to hear or read that fool's name again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor @nytimes The NYT has been wrong on almost every single prediction about Trump.  This will likely be no different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor From the article, it isn't clear if the "attorneys" were actually retained by any detainee or if they were just "volunteers."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harlan @verge This may be the stupidest boycott campaign in the history of leftist stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @kimpriestap This is going to be a bummer for all those college students who were hoping to become baristas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto The lawyer is an advocate.  His statements are not evidence. If evidence exists, the lawyer should produce it or shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very important information and provides context for the Trump EO, but will be completely ignored by the hys… https://t.co/b8fhuvbsTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor Americans won't be denied their guac.  We're just gonna have to ramp up production in S. FL and HI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanWagoner @BeladonnaRogers Reminds me of my Catholic grade school class saying the rosary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey @SherryTerm @hotairblog I'm one of those pre-Trump GOP voters. Doesn't mean I was happy with GOPe, just the only option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kausmickey When all you've got is nothing, you go with nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto Getting what you asked for is a bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["2 simple rules: buy American &amp; hire American." - @POTUS. Turn illegal #DACA off @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kausmickey Maybe it is and Trump needs to speak a bit more about this to reassure us, but Sundance makes a great argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarshallFSmith @stranahan @TrumpinatorSpks Hope this is real. If not, it should be.  Commit violent felonies, face serious prison time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC On the other hand, as Alinsky wrote, "Make the enemy live up to its own book of rules."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonColeman Before the fools in the media start scoring, they should wait to see how China likes the new "two Chinas" policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Soviet media, at their best, were never as good at fake news as the American liberal media. https://t.co/Kt1CmdjkIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey @BillKristol @GeorgeWill Will and Kristol are not toadies of Trump, but they are card-carrying members of the establishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wary seems desirable:

Leaders Abroad, Joyful or Wary, Face Uncertainty of Trump Era https://t.co/JCZWmjIBOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtracey Millions of Americans are easily gulled by the MSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlaBabbVOA She's made a fool of herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: If You Thought I Was Kidding, Think Again! https://t.co/MN7MshB5h0 via @powerlineUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobProvince Twitter helpfully offered to translate this from Haitian Creole.  Why does Twitter hate Missouri?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanMaue Not only would the new administration not want to delete the databases, they would want to keep the data as evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor Journalistic malpractice of the first order, but Politico et al. plainly don't care; "evil banker" story is too good to check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaSuhler @CahnEmily It would be a great honor and privilege to be in the same room as Marcus Luttrell and Rick Perry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor This smacks of the worst kind of politically driven prosecution.  "Feelings based" not "fact based."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC The hatred he feels for this country knows no bounds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonColeman @USATODAY But, you're unlike other trademarks, so it's all good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtracey To ask the question is to answer it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII Yep, definitely looks like a criminal conspiracy to me. These people need to be arrested and charged immediately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harlan @christianbal4 Jeez, he just wants to BUY one.  It's free enterprise. Give the guy a break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit Brennan is a partisan, likely behind some of the anti-Trump leaks. He cannot be believed or trusted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Strange Trumpian Glee https://t.co/D44uCVVKA5 #KlavanOnTheCulture via @pjmedia_com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobProvince Two fine beer choices. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmartosko @tedlieu He's not disrespecting Trump, he's disrespecting his office and the country he allegedly serves.  He's a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter @BillKristol Lewis gets exactly the respect he deserves, given his disgraceful statements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hits Back at John Lewis https://t.co/rJvomvBBoM via @powerlineUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian The fewer people like him attend, the better for America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmartosko Lewis has repeatedly disgraced himself and his legacy.  Trump is absolutely right in his criticism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey This is a nothingburger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRiehl No wonder he's begging for a truce. CNN's tents are on fire. The cable ratings speak for themselves:  https://t.co/N0wrgNbRIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat They're not the least trusted name in news for nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobProvince Sort of like a .300 Win. Mag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATLSAHM @kaijubushi @RobProvince Honestly, I'm not worth a damn with chopsticks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heavyhokie @RobProvince @nytimes Lol, and they thought the pickup truck question was hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWBennett Most Americans rejected Hillary also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC Yes, I'm sure its just a coincidence that Ford is making this move RIGHT NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stranahan Hmmm. These leftist institutions seem like hate groups and possibly agents of a foreign government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harlan I just want to congratulate the Italian police for some nice shooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey This makes me want to burn a copy of Robert's Rules of Order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardinals150 @EdMorrissey So, this is how the electoral sausage gets made. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey Live Texas EC feed here:  https://t.co/fKv5nycFla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBloom451 Let's just say that if the attempted assassin's last name is "Princip," we could be in trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielmalor Sort of how we all became intensely interested in Art. II, Sec. 4 of the Constitution during the 2nd Nixon administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbarianinSF @NolteNC Yep.  Instead of abolishing the EC, CA needs to split into 4 or more states.  That would REALLY be fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allahpundit Not an expert on Art. 5 of NATO charter, but I doubt this or a Russian retaliation would trigger "collective defense."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyman_brian "Protestors," also known as "losers."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC California can only exist in its current form because the rest of America isn't California.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhinderaker @powerlineUS Well, about 50 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobProvince That's a fine rifle. Mine's chambered in .270.  Most accurate I own by far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doobydoobydo @RonColeman @DailyCaller Earnest is an insufferable hack and his boss is a small, petty man who failed utterly as president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AngelaDale143 Sorry, Levin, I suspect that very few Swamp Dwellers are Eagle Scout Civil Engineers from Texas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AngelaDale143 Not to mention, extremely accomplished and successful and head of a major American multinational.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AngelaDale143 Heard Levin's screed. Disgusting.  Tillerson is a TEXAN, UT Engineering grad, Eagle Scout(!) and fine American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmartosko Dear Democrats, please choose Joe Biden in 2020.  Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAO_ 1971, $1.60, during the Nixon wage and price freeze.  I survived!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikki199x @asamjulian I took high school civics in about '71. Now I know who those people were sitting in the back of the class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC Once I see some actual "journalism" from those folks, I'll worry about "destabilization."  Meahwhile: Lol!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD @KurtSchlichter the Russians also made sure she scored a huge profit on the cattle futures deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NRA @JohnKennedyLA You can count on Louisiana voters.  Of course, it's the middle of duck and deer season, but sacrifices will be made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdMorrissey Great work, Ed.  Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich Sure, we should be skeptical of GS alums, but would you rather have the smart guys working for you or not working for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich @MarlowNYC @daveweigel @brianstelter @jaketapper "In the future, everyone will be a Nazi for 15 minutes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii This is a great article and explains real issues that need to be addressed if illegal immigration is ever going to be stopped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBaldwin Shorter Kelly:  "If Americans don't listen to our propaganda, then pretty soon they'll be having dangerous thoughts."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtracey @RepAdamSchiff Surely,if the evidence is "overwhelming," Rep. Schiff won't have a problem producing some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmartosko @PressSec Gotta believe that's fixing to change in a big way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit I say we give Pearl Harbor survivors a pass to feel however they damn well please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceofSpadesHQ @jaketapper Because, Ace, they still don't accept that it's a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I will just note in response to the media that it's nice to once again have a president who doesn't hate me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradH0101 @KurtSchlichter I would support CA secession on the condition that CA allows breakaway regions to stay in the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAO_ He can invite the inmates to come live with him on his new private estate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian CNN has long dominated the fake news space.  I guess they're jealous of the competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto @peterdaou Mr. Daou should come out to that big red bubble in the middle of the continent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii I agree, plus recounts present opportunities for mischief for the Dem machines in Milwaukee and Detroit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhinderaker @powerlineUS From now on, all references to any MSM outlet should begin, "the far left," as in "the far left Washington Post."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBaldwin Wow. That's actually encouraging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fud31 @ArthurSchwartz Isn't Schneiderman due in federal court in Dallas shortly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian Stein is an egomaniacal loon who wants to drag the entire nation along on her delusional quest for relevance.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>