<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@minionOX @harrym_vids don't get me wrong, love it. Just not sure people getting carried away with nostalgia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWClynes @harrym_vids not as a daily car for family. Rather but beaten up series 1 and 100k on silly car!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrym_vids I agree it's brilliant but when has new model come out and you not thought it's better?? Nostalgic trends.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amspeedracing @RaceCarsDirect will do. But going to finish existing projects first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amspeedracing @RaceCarsDirect these are fantastic. Would love to develop mine into this spec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutoPap @McLarenAuto shall we start the no invite club?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStevenKane @BentleyRacing @TheGuySmith @ollyjarvis you need to jump higher!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrym_vids @fletchdale Nothing worse than seeing someone on phone behind you taking photos. Seen accidents from this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baylissrally I think it will sell for more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton only if we take boxster!!😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops would have thought drink or drug drivers worse. https://t.co/dlYN58Vut9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton I guess you also dirty dancing and grease fan?? Buying a boxster soon? When's coming out party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @mattfoers toppy but great spec. Absolutely love my one. https://t.co/mUdQXg3kqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattfoers @nplumpton @scottyparker911 not on a board!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DionSpeak worrying for owners!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottyparker911 @nplumpton @mattfoers give him a break, he's old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredAtom @aSUPERCARDRIVER @McLarenAuto did thruxton in the rain just after picking mine up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2months to go till back racing the Rover!! Great to be invited back by @GoodwoodRRC .Racing with @timharvey7 again. https://t.co/WhsxGmQVrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tatbels when they start the bikini washes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tatbels small flat in Brighton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gordonshedden fantastic place that always has fantastic powder. Make sure you have a baseball steak at the keg!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DionSpeak never! It's keeps as owned it so long. This was the replacement for the 50th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to start 2017. These 2 picked up and registered today. Happy New Year to everyone. https://t.co/e5D60dRGh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldburybuilders was sold to buy p1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartg917 @Seatz37 only 30kgs more on a 2 tonne car! Doubt you notice the weight but you notice the power. 0-60 in 4.4 for school car!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartg917 maybe a lot but still think it's worth it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldburybuilders strange fact, i used to deliver papers to his house!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartg917 pick of the range? Should try a Turbo with the Performance Pack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton bit gutted to see they give them out on the standard cars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheChiefuk all good thanks. Just busy with other things at moment. Good Christmas to you and family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaffMunson fantastic!  Just just noticed glass garage door, very nice!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@me_ste where is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntAnstead @fresh_partners bad ordering by sounds of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most exciting drivers in f1 at moment and THE most exciting new car on the market. https://t.co/fZzkYDegVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWClynes @mjmclassics drop down size for winters? Just bought merc so need to find some wheels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please @PCMidSussex !! https://t.co/FGy8u0hIvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaffMunson congrats!! So keeping coupe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_foxx @StuartMcKay723 @TurboTerrific9 yes. Prefer raw cars, no need for hyper gt that is slower than my p1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke_chappy only race car being announced tomorrow. But road one will happen and I would like it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steps down?? He went to high court last week to stop stepping. Just say sacked https://t.co/5pQJN8xwwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrgrahammilne @LandRover_UK I have email from my dealer to say it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldburybuilders @LandRover_UK This is rangey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise that if something is fixed under warranty and the fault occurs again it's not covered. Shit service from @LandRover_UK again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PetrolHers @OmologatoOro @MonkeypennyMiss put a 1 before the 3!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurboTerrific9 @harrym_evo @Beefmeister no room for luggage either so best take the mistress!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrym_evo @TurboTerrific9 @Beefmeister tbh all modern cars too fast for roads. F1 was built without compromise, this is to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaytonKingman @sammooresphoto @astonmartin 2+years away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADelicious1 sadly these numbers were all taken!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Beefmeister why isn't this the ultimate road car? Only 25 track versions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be the best car made since the f1. https://t.co/pEXPBAO0CQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@me_ste FF! TDF a lot louder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlietadman lack of details aswell. I.e. 993 RS and gt2 with no explanation and 70k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fletchdale @Porsche911UK @yournotmyfather  @F1Barca really bad plate. That's the car at Octane. 2 out of 4 cars Reading got been flipped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ttsls great colour for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaytonKingman @HolidayInn serves you right for staying at a holiday inn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimates not really realistic on many lots. Is that to make sale look more successful or to attract people to the… https://t.co/NrTu5tImwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Touringthecars @tomwookieford guess not with 105]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwookieford not great street for cars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaquesLondon @chrisratcliff not a car I would want to buy....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurboTerrific9 @SupercarOwner @torquespeak @autocar good but value for limited numbers rather than how good. Sad low mile culture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fletchdale @torquespeak @autocar although what cars we £100k now £1m?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fletchdale @torquespeak @autocar great shout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SantaCruzLad @danny_macaskill @RedBullUK @CutMedia1 just someone who appreciates the skills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not stop amazing skills. Worth watching to end to see outtakes. https://t.co/lRMWXNrGRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torquespeak @autocar pick 2 cars now at same price that will be £2m different in 20 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottyparker911 @BertieMorgan @N13lCl @nplumpton @HabsyP @mattfoers yes! 918 is better built, p1 is good, p1gtr is ultimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattfoers @BertieMorgan @nplumpton @N13lCl @rollstrolls love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for coming along. Great morning. https://t.co/wdzsrEqo9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RSdriver00 @evoNickTrott CRT subtle cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my new hero! Badass Pilot Buys Own Fighter Jet | AARP https://t.co/PQAvND2TIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @Porketh @RobHcarnell dog years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @Porketh @RobHcarnell I would debate more but at work! Not as old as Neil so still enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @RobHcarnell yes, not the actual money but what it buys. Security for family going forward. Oh, and a f1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @Porketh @RobHcarnell more do than in a lot of alternative careers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @RobHcarnell do it, money is important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nplumpton @RobHcarnell @760SJ @jp_foxx don't bother on most but want to keep these original]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobHcarnell @760SJ @jp_foxx yes but it's waiting to get protection film and then maybe off to Scotland for while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobHcarnell @760SJ @jp_foxx no plans. Generally post when new cars and have time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@760SJ @RobHcarnell @jp_foxx in fairness Tim is now employing people and driving cool things most days. Don't think that's bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartMcKay723 @RobHcarnell @jp_foxx unlike Porsche and Ferrari. 3 test days in 918. Test drive in R. Ferrari f12, 488 and Lusso drives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobHcarnell @jp_foxx no. I have never been invited to drive 650, 675, 570. Asked for p1 drive before they sold out but was refused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomN1994 is a pouffe also offensive? https://t.co/RBqKvGxa7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats, amazing season and well deserved. https://t.co/1ztkbE8aFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalphsSurfShack @PCMidSussex decided against it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldburybuilders not my house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartMcKay723 @jp_foxx just in case you haven't worked out how internet works..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_foxx depends spec and miles. 900k max knowing where I can buy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_foxx loved it and did 2000miles in it. Just wanted p1gtr so sold. Looking at another one now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_foxx you know answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_foxx keeper. Sold gt4 as it was out gunned by my other cars. This one is properly exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vroom_photo yes but wanted convertible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ngoffy @PCMidSussex they follow me on twitter and seem to like cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ngoffy @PCMidSussex never run front plates. Look at all my cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealmushy @PCMidSussex how many what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vroom_photo 50th sadly sold as thought 991 RS, R and turbo s enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's here!! ME64RRR!!! So chuffed how it has turned out. First R in UK with custom stripes. Huge thanks to… https://t.co/khZByHa30j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertovery @Missionmotorspt @octane_magazine superb photos. You always find a different shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henryhopefrost thanks, amazing to be part of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fletchdale @JamieOrton71 @DickieMeaden @JZMPorsche @perfectionvalet wish it was new gt2rs so people wouldn't buy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@actionjack84 @Missionmotorspt @GoodwoodRRC @benjjwilliams @PawnSacrifice @BenB_7 @Tankslider @harrym_evo great day, good to see you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>