<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading our spineless PMs comments in the stuff article.  What a gutless coward.  Remind me again why @BillEnglishMP thinks he’s a good PM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Farrar’s finally delivered the polling results then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evinshir @pmbillenglish I want him to condemn it, but I’d like him to express our government’s position either way. Saying nothing is weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On issues with international importance Bill should either make a statement, or concede he isn’t ready for the responsibility &amp; stand down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English  was handed being leader of the country, and wants to win that role later this year. The job comes with responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has our feckless PM made any comment about Trump’s Muslim ban yet or is David Farrar still polling on what he should say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jowrotethis No kidding huh. Some folk seem to think if Trump gets impeached the crazy would decrease. Pence is worse, he’s a true believer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missgracenz that’s not tiny!  Golden Bay Air have one with only 5 seats, one person gets to sit beside the pilot :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teradar will they let you have a hoon on the BB guns at the side shows after you’ve drunk all that?  A&amp;P shows are the best huh?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sdoull Shakib al Hasan still, surely?  Double ton after being put in to bat, outweighs all the bowling efforts. A KW ton pushes him close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainobrien feck, would you want to play on if he’s rushed to A&amp;E in the ambulance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, @lakestreetdive are pretty feckin’ phenomenal live!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney asking cos I think I remember you tweeting about their sauces once..  (I blame the 3x mojitre)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney you tried culley’s chipotle corn chips before?  Epic. https://t.co/kCzFFc1lSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney was that the video where the head sharpener tests the blade by cutting into his thumb nail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFromHereNZ I think some of the time it is, there may be a fee I’m not sure.  They post on Facebook what is happening week to week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisIsPPM @JuddApatow @realDonaldTrump is he though? Without his tax returns you don’t know what he’s worth or to whom he owes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFromHereNZ canine solutions in Seaview has a big indoors doggy area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XTOTL wait, Te Awanga Hall, Te Awanga, Hawkes Bay?  We’re over in Haumoana at the moment :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m the only person awake so far on Boxing Day.  Pup not impressed. https://t.co/qpGiSX2tW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen or it might possibly be better, will decide after 2nd, 3rd, 4th &amp; 5th viewings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert Rogue One is pretty good though huh?   Up there with Empire for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonhaislip best wishes to your livers from 2 listeners down here in Middle Earth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altonbrown lol, please excuse my phones auto-correct :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altonbrown the Peking fuck are ok but weird, I think the cheese &amp; black pepper just out of pic on the left were good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @NZTAWgtn @GrowFromHereNZ I dunno, it’s been a massive boon in the arvo if you live j-ville north on SH1 :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altonbrown I’m not in Auckland but the best cheap eats from around the world are in Mercury Plaza I’ve been told.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn evening!  How come the KPL trains are going so slowly through Tawa, in the tunnels &amp; alongside the motorway in to Welly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike so closer to Te Awanga or up around Clive might be ok?  Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought I was pro at googling but failing to find any info on whether Haumoana has any swimmable beaches. How will I cook down this summer?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chetibby or read Dirty Politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbwilson is the story following local body (esp Wgtn) and by-election that Labour’s got (ground) game?  And it works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardboock you’d think McMillan was the aussie’s batting coach, not ours ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This commentary pairing is god awful.  #blackcaps #shutuppup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris is that a border terrier?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike do they still have a vege nasi goreng for $6.50?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike that looks like the Oaks Satay Noodle House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek ever been tempted by a rocket mass stove?  Mac would probably be a decent fuel for one of those!  (No idea if allowed in NZ).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek does macrocarpa have similar creosote buildups to pine when burnt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conclusive evidence?  No hot spot, snicko only matches hit on elbow.  Robbed.  #blackcaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress unbelievable huh! And Sexton’s swinging arm with initial contact to the head goes completely unpunished!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Naly_D tried giving the tenancy tribunal folk a call for advice?  Do @rentersunited know what tenants can do in this sort of situation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson have to wonder what they’re expecting Cane to do there.  Even if he just stood still Henshaw would fall onto his upper torso.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great 50 given the calibre of batsmen falling around him &amp; who got nowhere earlier in the day!  #blackcaps #jeetraval]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall depends if you’re talking about the province bit or the water bit.  So,both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chetibby I think a lot of the buildings up that way might be all of a similar vintage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird weather event just blew past the northern end of Tawa.  20-30 seconds of incredibly strong northerly wind. Then perfectly still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XTOTL read the day the costumes stuck today - love it, looks like my niece gets a book for chrimbo :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewsos I guess if we consider this election part of a trend, then we might want to make that very, very soon :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_ng and by plenty too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON Not sure if you’ve already got the news elsewhere but looks like WWE has cancelled the Dec 5 &amp; Dec 6 NXT shows in NZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m going to see @lakestreetdive in Auckland in January and this is very choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aw_nz @kyhwana check the SSID overhead calculator from revolution wifi. Seems like &gt; 3 SSIDs on 802.11b/g/n might be a bad idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aw_nz @kyhwana yeah I get that, but not sure how that expands to 8!  All that time spent broadcasting ssids might give perf hit too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aw_nz @kyhwana 8 SSIDs?!?  What the hell for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hodgman @prairie_home and if you have the capacity watch it on YouTube.  Even down here in Middle Earth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cold Sunday morning, I’m under a blanket on the couch having a cuddle with the pupper while A Praire Home Companion streams on YouTube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyhwana do you use ubiquiti gear too?  I’m a fan of their power/price though no idea about how robust/secure it all is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wandaharland @BillBailey is on the twitter, you could ask &amp; see if he replies in the affirmative!  Good sir: is your show child friendly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler yeah it was a number that streamed by in Twitter the other day.  Seemed high, was around 1/13 a year or so ago I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler is it something like 30 million African American men have been disenfranchised now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS elites fail up, not down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @hadyngreen in terms of availability Boundary Rd have a serviceable light beer at most Countdowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chetibby is stuff cheaper or are people buying less stuff (for the ones with big decreases)?  I’m assuming it’s the latter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskeall That’s buying the saw, paying shipping &amp; GST by the way. Only reason my bud didn’t do it is b/c it was 110V and needed adapter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskeall Prices in NZ are broken. You can buy an almost identical table-saw in US &amp; ship it here yourself cheaper than buying here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskeall All that service stuff would be nice indeed; but I’m convinced people purchase online due to price first &amp; foremost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen We went over Christmas &amp; the beach bar wasn’t open, only poolbar. All bog standard really, very basic. Sunset there is great tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen For sure! When we went we stayed at this avg but still ok place called Castaways. Buy 2 get 1 free cocktails was the clincher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen so happy ;)  Did you guys get a holiday home or at a resort?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lingerie_addict @mizjwilliams John Cleese talks about that a bunch in an interview with either Adam Savage or John Hodgman…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to let the try happen there than infringe again.  Would be penalty try anyway &amp; risk another yellow card.  #AllBlacks #ARGvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Marshall can refer to law 20.10d.  If ball is at No.8′s feet but scrum not moving the ref will call use-it.  #AllBlacks #ARGvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missgracenz well, it is a breakfast pie, I’m not sure steak &amp; cheese should be eaten after 5am or before 11am :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missgracenz B&amp;E?  Potato Top?  Ugh, Chicken?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_mate13 @davemeltzerWON Jesus. Hard to believe RoH could possibly pay enough to justify these guys risking their bodies like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XTOTL holy cow, 5 already!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainobrien think that was clipping leg of going down?  Would have loved to have DRS for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chetibby really?!  I always figured that of all FPS style games it would translate to controller perfectly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chetibby do you play PC or console version?  If PC I’m on every other day or so if you wanna ‘toon up. More chance of winning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress you seen the doco on her on Netflix?  Was pretty good watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney it’s pretty much a where’s wally situation trying to find Benjen. If we spot him at all it’s just a guess based on half a tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @LewSOS Cully’s are great, and I’ma let you finish.  But Huffmans make one of NZs greatest hot sauces of all time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do most people get a community work sentence if they knock a police officer out? Is that first sentence leniency, rich privilege or normal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amscraig and nobody knows how to, plus even if you did it’s not as much fun as just building an AI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amscraig I watched an interesting computerphile clip on YouTube about AI. The basic problem is you need to work out how to program morality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotdang, Burger Fuel’s latest special is very meaty &amp; cheesy.  https://t.co/UFbkgVsEJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen @publicaddress @chriskeall @nzben @ow 1Gbps at your house kinda just means bottleneck is wifi, then backhaul &amp; Trans-Tasman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realkingregal We hope so too! Given your love for reptiles I hope you get a chance to check out our Tuatara’s if you haven’t seen them yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKingRegal excuse me, King Regal, Sir, are you coming with your NXT charges to New Zealand this December?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress would a manager of chemical programmes exist without meth hysteria?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonhaislip @stonebrewingco You mean you’re late because Alex is busy SAVING LIVES!  He’s a veritable hero of the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike I think there’s one opposite the sound shell that was ok last time I was there (3 yrs ago!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslevin I think there’s an opt out in the t&amp;c splash, then hidden somewhere in settings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson plus all the work off the ball means you’re not clearing rucks, setting defence etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson trouble is if you resort to that immediately it tells your opponent you’ve given up competing on skill. Then they over did it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson they look good when they focus on simple rugby.  Seems like they’ve distracted themselves with intent to niggle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffcannata I raise you with the Shinsuke Nakamura entrance from the Takeover show yesterday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graemeedgeler thought that was a kinda iffy future profit once they sell their stake, and ignores cost of issuing the bonds used to buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Naly_D its cheese &amp; onion dip if you’re doing it properly &amp; it’s delicious.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>