<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@pascalmeier74 @BMJPatientEd @bmj_latest @RosamundSnow1 oh dear, that is terribly sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas 游때 lol, you're a darling to me as always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generally I find people to be human beings with health needs, vulnerable in illness, not NHS tourists. A disgusting phrase if I may say so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yasmeen_9 what does it mean Yasmeen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francismaloney5 thanks Francis 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what the US Supreme court will now do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got told off for not smiling so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joo_Gaza good morning, may freedom and peace come soon 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning 游땕 https://t.co/JME0l5hbLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a constitution for a reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pascalmeier74 congenital absence of heart probably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itxaP this is one of the greatest determinants of ill health. Very sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parthaskar @irishayesha @DrK_W1984 in theory it could really help but I worry it'll just be a separate business of no wider social benefit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishayesha @parthaskar @DrK_W1984 no, we are seeing a major disruption beginning. The end of the contract as we know it? Probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@trutherbotblue: There are two kinds of people. Those who can extrapolate from incomplete data." 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishayesha @parthaskar @DrK_W1984 but they can't see their NHS list privately. Which will create an interesting dichotomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parthaskar @irishayesha @DrK_W1984 what is new is running a private clinic alongside the NHS surgery. Will they cross subsidise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WelshGasDoc you would have to be a contortionist to do that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodyaberdein I did it too, still do it, and for what it's worth I think it should be actively encouraged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWMacPherson @ElsTrovo @grahamfarmelo @YoorWullie I agree....but it still made me laugh游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlwenOlwen wow, yes. I have such a desire to travel just now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theveindoc @drmanohar04 I am interested in the model and if they are cross subsidising their NHS practice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OccPalGaza this thread made me sad. I must say I have always found your observations to be balanced and humanist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@thinkalot: Yaaay! https://t.co/P3XGF9RTQR" hurrah for law, sense and decency 游녪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelle_simons but 1 in 5 people in Italy? Really? 游 Let's hope not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwardle Mark, I would be really interested to have another conversation about outcomes with you and compare notes. What do you think ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrRobinHosking @BTCare they don't talk to Openreach, apparently.*sighs loudly*. Plus I don't have a spare 2 hours 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry about that Had to get it off my chest. 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wouldn't be so bad if we consistently had 1 MB. We don't. It drops out daily.@BT_Openreach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try working in the Grwynefechan valley with 1/2 MB.Rural communities are disadvantaged.@BT_Openreach @Kirsty_Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the sheep want to enter the digital age in the Grwynefechan@BT_Openreach @Kirsty_Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that @Kirsty_Williams will continue to support the Grwynefechan community in their quest for decent broadband @BT_Openreach. Help us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of clarity and customer care from @BT_Openreach is causing havoc for businesses, families, medics, farmers of the Grwynefechan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that the Grwynefechan community want is a straight answer from @BT_Openreach as to when their fast broadband will connect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanShrew that's dark. I love it 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Rebek17: The last shift at Ebbw Vale. #photography #steel  https://t.co/gNHnLcD5SC" historic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas lovely, make sure you relax!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartberry1 yes same. I think that would really take things up a level. Let me know how you get on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartberry1 great. Have breathe easy here too but I would like to expand it a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas sleep is ......I'm fine though. How is your Dad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toates_19 yes it is sadly. There are many reasons why, but it is true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartberry1 that's great. Is there access to ongoing support beyond the initial course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I ask myself, 'What would Capt Janeway do?" 游때 https://t.co/Voksaz6nt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francismaloney5 I'm fine 游땕, thanks for asking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francismaloney5 good morning Francis 游땕. Hope you are well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perceived risk leading to fear has no correlation with the actual risk of an event.This is a problem for humans. We are irrational beings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@IhabGaza: In such ugly times, the only true protest is beauty. https://t.co/pibzcTOpZf" how true 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Alan_W: @RslewisSally and thinking laterally to fix the system on behalf of patients" yay, 游녨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorcaldwell there has to be a better way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@DrKristinaKing: @RslewisSally TIME being the key word." Yes yes yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorcaldwell I totally agree Gordon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should time in GP be mandatory?I don't know, but it sure is a useful thing to do .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time in GP also gives a greater appreciation of risk management holism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time in GP also offers experience with tackling undifferentiated illness, thereby improving rapid consulting skills and lateral thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time in GP gives a helicopter view of the system, an appreciation of the importance of population health and generalist skills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrPaulDavidson we should shout this out and salute this man游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francismaloney5 in good ways Francis游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parthaskar @ralanshirley @doctorcaldwell Partha, I think this is about whole system understanding and generalism. Both important concepts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look. I don't care if some think this is histrionic. There are some pretty horrible things being normalised across the globe. NOT OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@SpellingPatrol: #RejectedCandyHeartSayings https://t.co/mkKn2MLOzQ" 游땘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parthaskar I think most are 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sujayrjadhav just discussing this today...will be a game changer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markallan2020 yes! It felt like the planets had briefly aligned ...Hope your day was good 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet Secretary announces Strategic Parthership with @ICHOM_ORG . Fantastic news for patients in Wales! @AneurinBevanUHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More humour needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yasmeen_9 and so it begins, then it grows 游땩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Super_Dave_71 @ketaminh both of course! 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebHazeldine yes , I know and I am so sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was my Wednesday attempt at a joke btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fairly certain America already has  the most stringent vetting procedures going They took my inside leg measurement at border control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebHazeldine if we are going to collect patient experience info for example, there should be a mechanism for acting on it in timely fashion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squirrelrhiw me too Alex, me too. You at Confed today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebHazeldine a v reasonable question. Data collected for all sorts of reasons, often well-intentioned but sometimes not well thought out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebHazeldine spot on. We need the right data accessible to the right people, presented so that it is useful....then used!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas ahahaha, yes, exactly that! 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas either that or hysteria has set in! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas you have to laugh about it 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And my car has broken downWhich is nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrRobinHosking oh no! Hope you are ok. Take care!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrRobinHosking and you 游룋]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oggsky thanks Mike, your ears will be burning! 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve value in healthcare we need a whole system view, patient involvement and...better data, not more data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow I am talking about #VBHC at the Welsh Confederation with the legendary Paul Buss and @muirgray . Come and join the debate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefanoNistri @ACCinTouch @RickChazal I am pleased to see this. The medical and scientific community  asserting its values 游녪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@mikegalsworthy: @sianbennett12 @Scientists4EU  I choose atheism, compassion and pragmatism." Yes please, me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas hugs, it will be  fine x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmcefalas take care 仇]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tranquility starts with the mind I suppose. https://t.co/CEMKk513wV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello and good Monday morning 游깫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Corneleusthe2nd @FalconGrip if true, how sad and I stand corrected on the example given]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theveindoc yes. We need to pick our moments for indignant rage to be really effective. Constant shouting gets ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theveindoc yes, I understand what you are saying. The difficulty she faces is that silence can look (rightly or wrongly) like complicity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theveindoc yes, but if your friend says and does something really bad should you not say? He clearly cares little for her predicament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendean1979 this is true 游땕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After all that, something to still the mind 游땕 https://t.co/twQUbcKeSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priyesh123 it will be tested to the limit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrRobinHosking so it would seem. I know that emotions run high but still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how quickly debates on here degenerate into shouting and swearing :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HassanRaja789 I don't know. It makes me very sad.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>