<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekSnider Smokey Robinson is the cure for what ails us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. It's all better now, right? Smokey and the Miracles have a way with such things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone's tense, consumed by politics. It's important, but it's Saturday night. Pour a glass, put on You Really Got A Hold on Me by Smokey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThrivingDev personally, I choose a space mission over self driving cars. I've been in lots of cars, but I really want to go to space, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With two of the finest journalists I've ever worked with. @CdnPress @CdnPressStyle https://t.co/rw2SFZxVD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlkibler @catherinebnn It's like we're barely worth worrying about (we hope).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @allisonjones_cp GO train riders, myself included, may not have nuclear qualifications, but I've met more than one cab driver who does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crudereporter @rosskay I do what I can with the limited brains the good Lord gave me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosskay Would seem a strange play, since it took them so long to red flag the market in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CourtHeelsCP24 Yes, yes I am. And to declare you now the coolest person at CP24. Sorry, @cristina_CP24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver sales (homes changing hands) stats: Total sales down 39.5% YoY. Detached: -57.6%, Apartment: -24.7%, Attached: -32.4%. @BNN #VanRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_bonnell @BNN CORRECTION: 0.6% drop is month over month, not year over year. One year change is +15.8%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @BNN I've always been skeptical of the benchmark, while it makes sense to smooth out distortions, who's doing the smoothing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @BNN Benchmark or average.... the basis of the new Fight Club. Think Brad Pitt and Ed Norton would sign on for the sequel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InfinitusCap @BNN 20%-plus drop is classic definition of bear market in equities, but as with all thing real estate... people will argue..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benchmark Vancouver detached sale prices falls to $1.47M in January, down 6.6% over the last six months, 0.6% over 1 year. #VanRE  @bnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average Vancouver detached sale price falls to $1.5 million in January, down 17.5% from peak of early 2016. #VanRE #RealEstate @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cmdr_Hadfield And a flying crab trying to eat them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hainsworthtv One must love themselves before they can love others... or some such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 .... indeed the marginal buyer, active in the high end of the market. @davio9999 @crudereporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davio9999 @crudereporter TREB argues that 66% of foreign purchases are homes under $1 million. Others will suggest they are ... 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is a “blunt instrument for us,” Bannon told Ken Stern for Vanity Fair last summer. “I don’t know whether he really gets it or not.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewinning haha. Probably the several hundred other realtors I'm surrounded by in this baquet hall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TREB sets sights on supply constraints as it lays out 2017 forecast, says role of foreign buyer is minimal &amp; tax would be misguided. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ipsos poll commissioned by TREB finds 40% of foreign buyers purchased home as primary residence, 25% to rent out. @bnn #RealEstate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ipsos poll commissioned by TREB finds 4.9% of GTA home sales involved foreign buyers from Nov 2015 to Nov 2016. @bnn #RealEstate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat down with Canada's top diplomat today to talk diplomacy and trade with @realdonaldtrump in the White House. https://t.co/tF143JFxKF @bnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton on diverging energy policy with US (pricing carbon); we have to remain competitive, it's not all about energy costs. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton on Mexico; says Canada wants NAFTA to work, but focus is first and foremost on what's good for Canada.@BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton says a protectionist US can take actions not aimed at us, but could have unintended consequences for both counties. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton says Canada's corporate tax rate is competitive and can remain so even if US cuts its tax rates. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton on softwood dispute: we are looking at support package for industry if we get into prolonged dispute. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmbMacNaughton says Canada has engaged with Trump administration frequently, and "for the most part" positively." @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levinepmc @BNN True, but they are pretty to look at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow and TSX both shed 100 points at the open; Dow breaks below 20,000. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin's Russia in biggest Arctic military push since Soviet fall https://t.co/JebGC4bATe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susurrou very hard to get an audience with the man these days... it really comes down to him liking the cut of your jib.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some things you hope are above money... but I guess even the great Marcus Aurelius needs to make a buck. https://t.co/YzON3w6SWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this music in just one binder! Will digital ever become easier to carry around? https://t.co/ulEj9gdcrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People are far more determined to see their ancient enemies made miserable than themselves made happier." - writer Adam Gopnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wm_Elder In the Last Waltz... Robbie Roberston is a great player, but when Clapton gets in there... a different level altogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wm_Elder I'll have to check that out. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wm_Elder @BNN It does often feel like the jurisdiction with the deepest pockets gets the auto plant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benben416 @CTVNews I'm actually one of Tory's targeted outsiders. I live in the 905.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benben416 @CTVNews John Tory's building a wall? I've been at the orthodontist with my kids, and clearly have missed something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump advisor says Canada probably won't get hit in trade talks as trade relationship fairly balanced. Loonie, mean… https://t.co/U0EoJL1DQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freshii boosts range for IPO, could raise $125 million... https://t.co/8lwxIVSmAF https://t.co/lUd4WN9YIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Felt a little self-conscious as I talked about possibilities for upcoming federal budget with Michael Wilson waiting in the wings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eggsforsupper It's not Hawaii, but the Canadian dollar has strengthened quite a bit against the Mexican peso in the recent months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world waits... https://t.co/Fnp4CAj5tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the week... Poloz bests President Trump when it comes to loonie pressure. Still, Poloz did talk about Trump unc… https://t.co/hHvyne0Kxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcbluecon A little shy of a 1/5th of a cent. A full penny drop -- like on Wednesday -- it quite a big move for a currency in one session.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiqHewson @ctvqp @BNN Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day's loonie action.. so far. https://t.co/taUnr4PoLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiqHewson @ctvqp @BNN Scare mongering? I think a weaker loonie would be very welcome among policymakers in Ottawa, particularly the BOC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump vows "American first," and "protection will lead to great prosperity and strength." Loonie does thi… https://t.co/n491VTd5LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partisan politics aside, this is a fascinating read about the nuclear codes given to a U.S. president. https://t.co/qqBZrh7eh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're getting orange juice in 1st class... before take off! Now that's living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poloz asked if Canadian business will get sideswiped by Trump protectionism... "We simply don't know." @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC's Poloz: Loonie holding its own against USD means Canada losing competitiveness in US market. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC's Poloz says new economic models account for missing $30B to $40B in exports; too much focus on US developments before. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC's Poloz: Yes, a rate cut remains on the table. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC: US fiscal stimulus to have small effect in Canada, offset by 3 things including loss of competitiveness if US cuts corporate taxes.@BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC entered meeting "particularly concerned about the ramifications of US trade policy" adding "they are simply unknown at this point. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper @ThatEricAlper Great bass player... but a picture of The Smiths with @Johnny_Marr cropped out... sacrilege :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@APeninsulaMan @BNN Hhhm. Can't see why it would impact me emotionally. The only skin I have in the game is a house in Brampton, ON.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday night. https://t.co/hNRdc4ZfBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hainsworthtv @theCHIVE Are they running Hainsworth photo galleries again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaTrichur My place in our old hood cost me $210K in 2002 -- 3 bedroom condo, 934 sq/ft. Good luck to the kids starting out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaTrichur Mortgage Free! You mean if I had stayed in our old hood I could have been too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRabidoux ... modest incomes plus lure of cheap money got too many people into trouble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRabidoux My family moved to Brampton in '77. Always very much a blue collar town (as was my family)... 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRabidoux Hometown proud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alandrummond1 You boys having a wild night I gather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC says few Canadian firms making concrete moves based on Trump winning White House, as uncertainty remains on impact of Trump policy. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOC: Some Cdn businesses optimistic about Trump's infrastructure &amp; military spending plans, while others concerned about protectionism. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of Canada says more Canadian firms expecting strong growth in U.S. economy, citing outcome of the U.S. election as one factor. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#brampton winter trail. https://t.co/6qAqLfBK8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBonnell Watching Mariah Carrey not even attempting to  fake lip synching, with family and friends. Happy New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're into Motown you're into this man. Bassist James Jamerson. Best of the best. https://t.co/ZYVrr0gU1k https://t.co/fwkl6WNmG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your gym is flooded with New Year's resolution 'posers' remember to be kind... they subsidize your workout the other 11.5 months!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil and gas extraction fell 2.5% in October, following four consecutive monthly increases. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing output contracted 2.0% in October, the largest monthly decline since December 2013. @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Widespread decreases in manufacturing output and lower oil and gas extraction were the major contributors to the GDP decline. 2/2 @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[StatsCan: After increasing for four consecutive months, real gross domestic product was down 0.3% in October. 1/2 @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikalfaro @GOtransit a flashback to "Billy keeps feeding lead pencils to the hamsters so you're all not having gym today" school years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikalfaro @GOtransit haha. No, it we one of those train-wide announcements in which we were all scolded because someone held the doors open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm 45 years old, don't need to be lectured about another passagers' bad behaviour (holding the doors) on  @GOtransit like we're in Grade 1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlkibler @timhudak We'll definitely have him back in the New Year. He currently holds the title of the only @bnnhousemoney repeat guest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BNN in which Jeff poses the question... Can Donald Trump inspire millennials to procreate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CPnewsboy My former boss, mentor, and style consultant (ties by KJL). A big loss for journalism, but well deserved. When's the party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking in the bright side... the pollen count is nil. https://t.co/V4vPXBj850]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen Rogue One. I won't be that guy who spoils it for others, save to say I'm a very happy boy.  #StarWarsRogueOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hulkcharts The other caveat, it's 50% of new 'insured' mortgages in Q3. Uninsured mortgages originated in q3 not part of that calculation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hainsworthtv Did Chris Pine block you as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... I paused for a second, worried that it wasn't real and we were being punk'd. Didn't see interest free loans coming. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a reporter (and not a columnist) I won't offer an opinion on BC's loans for 1st timers, but when I saw the release... 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C's release on loans to first-time buyers: https://t.co/Et2LwD0LhH #VanRE @BNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_bonnell "After five years, buyers can either repay their loan or enter into monthly payments at current interest rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mortimer_1 I thought they were going to tinker with Land Transfer Tax rebate. Didn't see interest-free govt loans coming, that's for sure.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>