<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. I went to Iran in 2013 and wasn't Prime Minister of anywhere. Think I'll avoid visiting America any time soon. https://t.co/gPhUvEN2Qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on last night's Graham Norton and really loving Harriet Harmon. Can we have her as Labour leader please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko My profile pic is me and my #poppelganger2017. Best TV show character ever! https://t.co/Z1BShmr3L0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh, I'm so pleased that massive downpouring of sleet managed to coincide with my walk home from work. &lt;/EnormousSarcasm&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure if I'm more offended by the blatant lie or by how terribly written it is. How are these people in char… https://t.co/F1ahoNJZRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best decision I've made in ages. https://t.co/Ao0tYIVvDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is rhetorical. *puts on oven for chips*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contemplating dinner. Do I go for the healthy option I'd been planning, or do I make poutine (albeit with regular cheese, not curds)??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook 'suggested posts' can often be annoying, but a tiny sausage dog in penguin PJs just brightened my Thursday! https://t.co/VlgDXFVXg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magic_treehouse I'm pleased that 3 Cardiff ones did (including mine) but it's still not a huge comfort :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4 Me in Paris! I love feeling European. I felt physically sick when I heard the referendum result. Pot colo… https://t.co/MVBNe4b7bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twin Peaks @OriginalFunko Pops pre-ordered!!! :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many times do dead cows feature in The X-Files??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh Eve is on Spike. Bit of X-Files to end the weekend? Don't mind if I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to 'If You Tolerate This...' It feels worryingly apt in current political climes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[381. The Ark - A Virgin Like You #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[382. Black Box Recorder - The Goodnight Kiss #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[383. @suedeHQ - Breakdown #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[385. Radiohead - The Bends #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[387. The Ark - The Most Radical Thing To Do #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[388. Simple Kid - The Commuter #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[389. @divinecomedyhq - Becoming More Like Alfie #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[390. @amandapalmer &amp; The Grand Theft Orchestra - Massachusetts Avenue #Top777
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've reached the half-way point! Songs 390-381:
https://t.co/DpDRBBwdmz
Countdown follows... #Top777]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great time seeing Gruff Rhys and Set Fire To The Stars. Even got a bonus James Dean Bradfield sighting! I love living in Cardiff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can people please stop making adverts that feature knocking and/or doorbells? It makes me paranoid there's someone at the door...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh @TheLastLeg coming up with bonus David Tennant?? That's my kind of Friday night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intriguing!! I do rather like the idea of an X-Files-inspired comedy with @mradamscott. Partly because I miss him a… https://t.co/kd9opw8Hr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiGarside @MarkSadlerActor I found someone at the top of Pen Y Fan!! I'm turning this into a drinking game *has a drink*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSadlerActor @EmiGarside Just found a guy whose profile says 'must have own eyebrows and teet'. I'm assuming he means teeth!! Ha ha ha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSadlerActor @EmiGarside That's a good motto in general.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiGarside Ha ha ha ha. So many of them put that!! Also too many photos of men on bikes. Instant swipe left (I'm proper harsh).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiGarside He's also Crump from Drive!! Though it took me a while to realise that - he looks really different in different roles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just managed to accidentally throw my glasses into the bath. This probably means I've had enough to drink, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[391. @BatForLashes - The Wizard #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[392. Amy Winehouse - Back To Black #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[393. Sinaptic Gap - Flamboyant Child #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scousepie I'm fascinated by the description of 'non-violated' video on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[395. @spacetheband - Hell's Barbecue #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[398. Murry The Hump - Cracking Up #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[399. The B-52's - Rock Lobster #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[400. Catatonia - I Am The Mob #Top777
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's blog post includes perverts, mushrooms and me playing the flute. Songs 400-391:
https://t.co/gr1inVK5R9
Countdown follows... #Top777]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's pictures!!!! Love them. https://t.co/9Xq1qPamyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm simultaneously drinking beer and watching The Man In The High Castle though, so not completely broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm voluntarily doing some ironing on a Monday night. I think I might be broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pitythebackseat Probably pink and The Lego Movie :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now to change my bed sheets, light some candles, paint my nails, watch a film and drink more wine. #SelfCareSunday #Hygge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh, just had a lovely soak in the bath, complete with ace music (shuffle chose to be very Jarvis heavy) and some red wine. Lush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for the lack of Top 777 blog post this weekend (if anyone noticed or cared!). I'll try and get a mid-week one up if I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lex: Did you think I'd just roll over?
Fine: No, not you. Not without a bone.

Bwa ha ha ha. The HoYay just got less subtexty. #smallville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laurem_ipsum I feel like that too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god, that baby on the ceiling's going to give me nightmares. #Trainspotting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The poll's still set to run for a bit, but I'm calling it for Trainspotting. It probably is about time I actually watched it. Thanks all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode III is the only Star Wars film I've never seen (in case it seemed a really random choice!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never done a poll before, it's quite exciting!! Most are films I've never seen before (the exception being Moulin Rouge).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being characteristically indecisive, so Twitter, help me decide which film to watch tonight...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiGarside Definitely not wrong - especially if you're on a train! It's surely one of the great perks of trains over buses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shows that end with a cliffhanger and then they never make any more episodes. Aghhhhh!! Why had I forgotten this?? #CarolineInTheCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easyqueenie It's loaded for me now - I've copied and pasted the list on Facebook. There is a Log Lady!!! :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to view the new Twin Peaks Funko Pops but it seems like the site's overloaded with the excitement! Please tell me there's a Log Lady?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo!!! Not seen them live since 2009. Excited! https://t.co/GVt1v0ZdTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching a Caroline In The City episode where there's the new and mysterious world of the Internet and Cyber Cafés. Feeling old. #90s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesssssss!! Me too. https://t.co/CznUm1GMz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaDownie I got them all on DVD for Christmas. I'm re-addicted!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seem to have spent most of this weekend watching Caroline In The City (being the stuck-in-the-'90s cliché that I am). I regret nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[402. @themachines - Simple Joys (4 Roy &amp; Pris) #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[403. The French - Porn Shoes #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj
(I'm expecting to get some interesting bots following me after this tweet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[404. Martha Wainwright - Bleeding All Over You #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[405. The Beatles - All You Need Is Love #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[406. Minuteman - Quality Time #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[407. Muse - Plug-In Baby #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[410. @TheDecemberists - Grace Cathedral Hill #Top777
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post - Songs 410 - 401:
https://t.co/eG7nzvfuMj
Countdown follows... #Top777]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to a weekend of doing very little. Roll on 4:30pm! PJs and wine are calling me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bunch of flowers!"
Not watched Unrepeatable in aaaaages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[414. @mansunband - Taxloss #Top777
https://t.co/9c7StaCsaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[415. The Hot Puppies - Theda Bara #Top777
https://t.co/9c7StaCsaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[419. MC Mabon - Be Di Be #Top777
https://t.co/9c7StaCsaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post - Songs 420 - 411:
https://t.co/9c7StaCsaN
Countdown follows... #Top777]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep getting tempted to re-install That Dating App. So far resisting it though. Partly because I'm low on phone space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaDownie Oh my god, they sound amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonypdickinson If I have to hear 'Brexit means Brexit' one more time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to watch The Man In The High Castle instead; which is worryingly seeming less and less fantastical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The news: Theresa May's hinting we'll leave the free market and Boris has met with Trump's people. I've not got enough wine left for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kankurette Hot bees, bored in the trees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[421. @JensLekman - The End Of The World Is Bigger Than Love #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[422. Easyworld - A Stain To Never Fade #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[423. Catatonia - Dazed, Beautiful and Bruised #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[425. Radiohead - Creep #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[426. @racehorsesmusic - Mates #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[427. The Wannadies - You &amp; Me Song #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[428. Ooberman - Serotonin Smile #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[429. Right Said Fred - Deeply Dippy #Top777
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post - Songs 430 - 421:
https://t.co/PxGpBQU9dN
Countdown follows... #Top777]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmiGarside Creepy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_you_are No Wales and no England. Just Scotland, Northern Ireland and the UK!! Bizarre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also unsure about their grasp of the alphabet. Assuming it's in the place of 'Great Britain', as N. Ireland is also separate. They tried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filling in an online form for an American company that seemingly got ahead of themselves with the Scottish Independ… https://t.co/10eZbBH2dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've even got a soft spot for the lack of functioning locks in the toilets. Part of the charm innit? #savedempseys]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>