<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Stanley &gt; ...heat your gaff*

*When you're at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correct, you can not have a public movement. We've been over this quite thoroughly last century. Grab a history boo… https://t.co/2hDX2ePZDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only there were some signs before the election. It's amazing Trump managed to keep his real POV and intentions quiet all that time.

:-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this is all pretty terrifying: “Trial Balloon for a Coup?” @yonatanzunger https://t.co/TxKIwxz6UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T2: Trainspotting was good. A satisfying epilogue. At times not quite worthy of a full sequel but never unwelcome. Enjoyed it a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any response from Irish government to what's happening in USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cramforce @EamonLeonard @conroyp Correct, from a Google search. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cramforce @EamonLeonard @conroyp so that's good :). I've also had trouble with the back button in chrome, Android… https://t.co/rjXrQ13Oxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cramforce @EamonLeonard @conroyp Hey Malte. The lack of a canonical link to the original content is a big issue, b… https://t.co/BfcHdCTMGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conroyp Cheers. I'm sure they'll refine it but more an annoyance as it is. Surprised it got released tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Amp feels like the wrong way to solve a problem. Is it opt-in for websites or do they just harvest content? Can I opt-out as a user?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's a good no-nonsense Android radio app? I've never liked TuneIn. Feels bloated and lacking where it counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool! https://t.co/3QmIaJOsl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck. https://t.co/3lDtFbJ37V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conoro Love the @AdamBuxton podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow, they finally released some ebook/Kindle versions of Robert Anton Wilson's work. Been meaning to take another look at Cosmic Trigger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I missed the humour when I watched this. Thought the film was good but unenjoyable. https://t.co/4m2AvKVm8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sucks that we leave it to organised crime groups to profit so massively from the sale of this stuff. https://t.co/33r4EDQB8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tadywankenobi Nah, they've moved to @POTUS44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True story. https://t.co/YICJpZXmdT https://t.co/xn9a1ns3WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally What's been bad and how is it going to be better? That's unclear.

But certainly, things will be better from today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally Pessimistic and divisive? No, didn't you hear? He's going to make everything better. Because everythin… https://t.co/SlyvVbRuaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful cinema. Congrats to all involved, and happy birthday @LightHouseD7. https://t.co/f139y14Qrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsmelo aye, that's what I went with – and just what I was looking for! Adding it to my regular tool set.

Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feylya ohh, command-line. That could be perfect, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know a good app (OSX) for parsing and querying large JSON datasets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mystery.. mystery.. myst... Ah, never mind. Let's just wrap this up, yeah? Don't forget your sentimental montage on the way out. Kthxbi".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed that last episode of Sherlock, although they just seemed to give up on the story 10 minutes before the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the “Santa Clausification” of MLK, Jr. Leaves Out - (he also fought for economic justice and against war) - https://t.co/eMdbEJlg3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La La Land was great! Beautiful, lovely, fun, and engaging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched "Manchester By The Sea". Good film. Longer than it needed to be. Serious drama stuff. Could do with a unicorn chaser by the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prendio2 Who the fuck is that guy and why does he have your first iPhone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@forbairt (although I'm sure I could figure it out ;-))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@forbairt That's probably the only thing I do with it! It is useful though. I'm not really sure how to set a timer manually anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched Silence last night. Masterful filmmaking. A real treat to see in the cinema.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmulley @suzybie @Twitter I've seen "faved by someone-you-know" before. Today there was a tweet without any note. Maybe just a blip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzybie @Twitter Noticed that today too. I recognised the author but I don't follow them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TouchingVirus and for instance they put the 2D version of Rough One in the biggest screen, 3D in the smaller. Warms my heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TouchingVirus ... Man Who Fell to Earth, and Goodfellas is out next week). I was worried I'd miss out on some big movies but not at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TouchingVirus MUCH nicer cinema experience. More emphasis on *good* films vs blockbuster films. Classic screenings (have seen 2001, ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightHouseD7 Absolutely. Silence tonight, then difficult choices between La La Land, Monster Calls, and Manchester… https://t.co/9F5fRi0sFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a regular cinema goer, best thing I've done recently was ditch the megaplex monthly sub and get a @LightHouseD7 membership instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo isn't really going away (at least, not yet) https://t.co/aDsCht1NzS via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyhoy @ideasasylum yeah, that crossed my mind as soon as the tweet sent ;-). Happy where I am for the moment but it is a near-term goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyhoy @ideasasylum Often think I'd be happy working 3 or 4 day weeks and earning 3/5 or 4/5 what I do now, but th… https://t.co/Bb4TyMR9Xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyhoy @ideasasylum Unfortunately it can also be assumption that person earning $1m doesn't have to work much at a… https://t.co/oHDLacWW5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dclay Girl on a Train, because I haven't seen it and it looks good. Otherwise Star Wars because it's good fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iHelping out a colleguebcwcolleague who doesn't use vim-mode, when you're used to vim-mode, can be a little confusing.:w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, yeah, that is much better. Same story, better told. https://t.co/I3nRjQHbZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davebolger @paulmwatson OTT outrage is fuel to the fire for these assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson Fair enough. The article just doesn't merrit the outrage imo, nor match the choice scrnshots. But that… https://t.co/Gxt4k8AghS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Man Who Fell to Earth in @LightHouseD7 this weekend. Nice one!

https://t.co/wYEVCaOrIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson it's reporting on an "offensive, influential, and reactionary group" which exists and is "outrageous and frequently offensive".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davebolger continues "confrontational, outrageous and frequently offensive" in second paragraph.

Where's the endorsement bit I'm missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davebolger but these people exist, and those terms exist. Article mentions "offensive, influential, and reactionary" in it's byline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should we also pretend they're non-existent?

Anyway. I should know better than to wade into this nonsense on Twitter tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure they're controversial terms and definitions but clearly described in TFA as offensive, nationalist, confrontational, and outrageous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiestantonian @IrishTimesWorld Search 'Irish Times' on twitter for the outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiestantonian Glossary of terms used by the alt-right, which didn't to me seem to endorse or encourage anything. https://t.co/53LCbtIKc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worker and Workers. Client and Clients. Job and Jobs.

Nice.

"Hm. Workers sounds bad. Lets change that to Staff."

Staffs.

(╯°□°)╯︵ ┻━┻]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson Cheapest, lazy way to pass that "apartment has heating" requirement. And still €1250/m for a 1 bedroom… https://t.co/pI4YIVGuJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage heaters are a bloody insult to tenants. Never would anybody buy these things for a property they intend to live in themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiestantonian thanks for the all clear, laddie. I think I nailed it!

FFFRRREEEEEDDOMMMM!! https://t.co/laKFoh1uTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feylya @AmericanGodsTV – Ian McShane! Cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's now over 10 years of my listening history, which I can export in a neat json format. That's cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last.fm is great. Love that I can forget all about it and it just continues to do it's thing. Never intrudes or oversteps it's usefulness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My year in music, via Last.fm: https://t.co/aJIbeqy57L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my flat a lot but living under a family with two young kids, wooden floors, little push scooters, and a tendency to tantrum, is shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll meet again,
Don't know where, don't know when,
But I know we'll meet again, some sunny day. https://t.co/YgcUnLGOrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastPassHelp Is it possible to disable the pop-up and use an unobtrusive system notification icon instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastPassHelp thanks. Popping up on non-password forms isn't really the issue though. The pop-up is annoying all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @LastPass "Matching Logins" pop-up on Android is infuriating. Can it not use the standard notifications system? Is there a setting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffrey_way ah, gotcha. Yeah. Thought you might be an arrow keys holdout in vim. Took me the longest time to switch but haven't looked back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffrey_way don't you use vim/vim-mode? If you can get used to hjkl and other keys for nav, it really is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steve228uk well. Good luck to 'em I guess. Must be fun to be so sure of yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steve228uk like, a tracker/ad blocker? I use all the time! Great!

But "better, FYI" and "protecting you from unethical website" – hrm :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steve228uk think so? Definitely something unlikable and condescending about their whole message. I do wonder if it's just an image problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who decides what's ethical on the likes of https://t.co/8XihpLeci1? Pretty sure I hate the idea of outsourcing that decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE yeah, a reboot fixed things earlier. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @VirginMediaIE having broadband issues again this evening or is it just me this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dclay and yet... there's just something about the guy I can't help but trust.

I'm gonna give him a loan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember dreaming about how cool a live action Transformers movie would be? https://t.co/uxaYsr6uks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matfinucane oh, display port? I'm sure Apple would like that very much &gt;_&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matfinucane dp cable?

Have tried unplugging and replugging all cables. No use. It not an all-the-time problem but it is frequent enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcoTroisi I've tried that in the past without any luck.

I rebooted. Lost the focus I had all morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MBP not recognising external HDMI monitor after waking from sleep.

Anyone have a solution? Only one I know is a restart and I hate that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciarancoyle sure I'll pick up the road anyway, see how I get on. Haven't seen the film yet either. Heard it's a right aul laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciarancoyle I could do with a book. Good one of his to start with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a long time since I've seen Blue Velvet. Looking forward to it tonight, with an appropriate amount of trepidation, in @LightHouseD7.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would they do if they did care? Angry tweets? Designated protest zones? I figure Americans don't believe carin… https://t.co/sp5PGQbn9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Childish Gambino album is really good. https://t.co/Z09fTuWOvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's be fine but writing tests after the fact is dull as dishwater. Red/green TDD is, by comparison at least, lots of fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front end devs: do you use TDD?

I find it great on backend but my front-end tends to be more an emergent thing. Maybe lack of discipline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feylya I've been happy with the OnePlus Power Bank. They ship to Ireland. https://t.co/sUS0KWqb9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duggan ah, OK. Cheers. That's less interesting than it could have been :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Gilmore Girls something to talk about now? Isn't that an old show? Out of the loop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A QR code button in the Twitter app.

"Finally!!" said no one at all. https://t.co/kpXIYPvcDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson and actually more like 5 or 6 clicks before I found the greyed-out non-obvious "Go without highlights" button :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson I think that Highlights thing used to work better? Now it's 2 extra clicks and an install prompt befor… https://t.co/WisdeTQKFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidan_walsh it's annoying alright though. The directors cut was/is great, but now there's a third and I suppose it's a toss up between them]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>