<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PetaCredlin1 Time to put Turnbull straight, u came up with clever Mr Harbourside Mansion not Shorten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm History will not be kind to you Mal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm Gee $1.75 million, that was money down the drain.  Worse Prime Minister ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm Peta Credlin gave you tag Mister Harbourside Mansion not Bill Shorten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull really showed his arrogance and his delusion of self importance on 7.30 tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fehowarth yes he looked very uncomfortable, stiff shit eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS what would you really know about everyday familes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No you are beholden to big corporations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He always has to mention Lucy, she must wear the pants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nettythe1st @fehowarth exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teakingw @fehowarth He can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BowlofCherries @fehowarth that made me laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking shite as usual Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thefinnigans @TurnbullMalcolm I am sick to death of this moron treating us likes fools.  Time to quit the job he does not know how to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suthernx @ChangeAus @Change signed and shared with facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@64AnthonyP @YouTube I thought he died years ago, obviously not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebazzi Is that poor woman still in Nauru?  I saw tweets yesterday that she was being moved to a Qld Hospital.   What is the truth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet He has obviously never looked in a mirror..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bruhritto_ @MSMWatchdog2013 @vicenews We dont hate you, it is just Trump and his supporters.  I have American 1st cousins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf picked up grandkids when it was 40c, fed them tea and sent them home with mum after work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelpRefugeesOZ Where do they get their info from, the sky or out of their arse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brigidglanville @DailyLifeAu I couldn't believe my ears when I heard her say "I am pro-life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clementine_ford @ItsBouquet About time.   Thank you Doctors who pressured for this it must be hard on you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Loud_Lass Oh no don't tell me they have let Bernie out again. Ignore him Sassy he is completely bonkers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS do something for this woman.  My youngest daughter was lucky to survive pre-eclampsia.. https://t.co/wITdAVitVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LennaLeprena His father was born in Palestine...His mother was born in Australia.  I don't know if Joe is a dual citizen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GissiSim @vanbadham I have already had a run in with someone saying he was a Muslim..  RWNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MohammadiRashid @secupp @MichelleKIRO7 @deniseoryan @wendywidom @PMOIRAN Let us know Rashid when you know for sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef did he get the exemption for not criticizing Trump??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MohammadiRashid @secupp @MichelleKIRO7 @deniseoryan @wendywidom @PMOIRAN Is this for real Rashid..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anne_margaret @NannanBay Yes I have said that all along.  He just wanted to please his ego and up date his CV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GVakarian11 What are you on about.  the man is not a Muslim.  You don't want to accept what the Canadian PM says that is your problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm @JustinTrudeau A 'White Extremist Terrorist Attack"  call it what it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm #notmyjob  Time to get another job Malcolm, you have been a failure at the job you have now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnews Please call it what it is "White Extremist Terrorist Attack"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmahusarmp Piss weak poor excuse for a PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre @POTUS yeah that did enter my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh @VicPain1 @ChangeAus @Change signed and shared with facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebazzi and fuck the rest of the LNP MPs too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billshortenmp Thank goodness you have finally come out and said something, the PM we have is piss weak get more MPs to speak out please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottMorrisonMP Mr Morrison you are way out of touch, the Australian people DO NOT agree with the Trump ban, you do not speak for ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelwerner @dodona777 @guardian Not in my name you don't Morriscum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelpRefugeesOZ I have made an error in a Tweet and made a mess of it trying
to fix it.  The important thing is I support the Refugees...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNent @fehowarth a'blemish' more like a 'stain']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuskarSurbakti Auskar please call it what it is "A Terrorist Attack"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNCLE80075178 @MinhKular It wont be a terrorist attack, he will be mentally ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in my name Ms Bitchop https://t.co/muhfgUliTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane I am jealous, she is beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fehowarth I have never 'hated' anyone before this bloke came along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraceySpicer me too, thrilling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Onya Roger, what a beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plabg @BellaFlokarti @woolworths Navels, not in season atm here "its what the customer wants" Woolies will tell you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myknittingwool @davidbewart @gwendabgilbert @AustralianLabor Turnbull will not admit to it if he did a deal, treats us like mushrooms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMCimino @Qldaah and so many ALP voters supporting him, me included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrOzAtheist I am leftie tried mouse with right hand, couldn't do it too awkwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrOzAtheist @leftocentre that reminds me of the pic of Abbott at a 'puter, no sign of moniter and mouse on wrong side 4 a left hander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au honestly you need help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au what a load of shit, you really sre a stupid man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au I said lefties care about everyone else.  There is good and bad in every group even your right wing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au so I can blame you for everything Pauline Hanson says in your way of thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au and that has nothing to do with me.  I was not the one that said it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au and I or Jenko never mentioned a 10 yr old boy get that through your thick skull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@equityliberty @MinhKular Channel 7 has gone dowhill when it comes to reporting important news.  Dont watch it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson We never mentioned any 10 yr old.  Go and reread our tweets then apologize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerrySerio @smh That is what most of us are worried about..he is a loose cannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson go and find out the population in  States that are almost total

- 
red and compare the pop from the blue squares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson No even we out of office exPresidents are still addressed as President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinsonso right is the same every where too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson I think you have had enough to drink today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7_jenkinson @Bernie_au exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson that has nothing to do with lefties here in Oz, dear oh dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7_jenkinson @Bernie_au I blocked him last week, I dont know how I was seeing his tweets.  Left of left gave him a run 4 his money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson I am fine I think for myself and have both eyes open.  Go away and learn to think for yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson WTF has that got to do with me, idiot.  I have nothing against Mrs Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson I suppose u are a fan of Blair Cottrell and his UPF mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson left care about every one else, right only care about themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bernie_au @7_jenkinson I am not 1 eyed like u if u happen to see Tweets last night they were support r Adrian Piccoli NSW LNP Mp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7_jenkinson @Bernie_au Ignore him, always has to have a shot back never comes up with anything original.  A LNP RWNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBongiorno @BevanShields Gladys' first mistake.  even ALP voters want Adrian to stay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will believe this when I see it not before https://t.co/70PowJMrCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Justin, I wish Australia's PM had the same attitude https://t.co/2XZx5MaWoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about airline crew on Emirates and Etihad planes are those who are Muslims allowed into the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AagjeSchouten Is it true Aggy that KLM are refusing to carry Muslims to the USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiccoliMp I have never seen so many ALP voters backing a LNP MP Adrian, you did a great job and r held in high esteem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiccoliMp @MSMWatchdog2013 You will be missed Adrian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @earthma23 Abbott please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt I was willing to give her a go, but not now after dumping Piccoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @ray_wilton Yep, bugger what the people want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denniallen and I was willing to give Gladys a go, not now stupid woman, best MP gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GladysB sorry error held not hled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GladysB why would you get rid of an Ed Minister that is hled in high esteem even with ALP voters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillemBosch @AagjeSchouten Thank you citizens of The Netherlands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randlight Me too Mari I have time for him too..  Shame on Gladys if he goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jouljet @thenewred1 You are right, we have nothing to be proud of 😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @EducationHQ_AU I was willing to give Gladys a go but axing Piccoli would be a BIG mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiccoliMp I am an ALP voter Adrian but I am a big fan of yours a good Ed Minister for NSW, I really hope you keep your job mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best news I have heard in ages https://t.co/Zr78TKgZSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Confused_Maud simple person not a simpleton, easily pleased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep I wondered when it started because we did not 'celebrate' when I was young..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Confused_Maud every time it comes on I wink and say 'simples' at the end to the Meerkat, getting silly in my old age 🤣🤣🤣]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>