<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_timpeake @NASA stayed up late &amp;waved as you drifted overhead.  Greetings from Wellington NZ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderMaps congratulations on breaking into the European market. To infinity and beyond!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde I'm looking forward to the end of it too #moveon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StationCDRKelly @Space_Station so great you had the foresight to get the mask up there. Well pkanned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two oil pump pulleys, old and new. Spot the difference! Now we see what's missing from the old one! https://t.co/5CJxUdeyqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde I have been added to a twit group called "young, cute &amp; happy". Since there has CLEARLY been a mistake,  can I remove myself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie and now happy birthday for today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie Happy birthday for tomorrow! !!!♡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my American and Canadian friends: this is my egg separator. It is 46 years old and says: "With… https://t.co/nKGtwQMi1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passionately Lunching ladies!!!
#passionateconf https://t.co/tEJR7gRMR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger, literally,  moonlighting as a mtb mechanic #karapoti #lessthanaweek https://t.co/k2rNpOiuK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde sorry that's old school. BOC gases nowadays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde no idea $ but oxygen tanks try NZIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderMaps awesome to see this new development!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving my beautiful shell collection it's annual wash. The smell is heavenly! #seashells http://t.co/qSmBwud00C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My very first ever pair of jandals! (Aus:thongs) http://t.co/scNc7DCSRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Potsto got a new friend for Christmas #vegetepals4life http://t.co/zLXf7M5cQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas in the compund! http://t.co/QVchkCOdob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASA_Marshall @NASA any chance of seeing anything in tge southern hemisphere?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 of my fave little Christmas decorations: the box of baking and festive pie on a ceramic plate. Both… http://t.co/0patYpIxQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie stawbs in the blue pot, spinach, buttercrunch lettuces, courgettes and carrots (not showing yet). Mint in the green pot! Yum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde Fusion is the combination of any two or more cooking styles, one is usually Asian but not necessarily so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde Tapas (Spanish)are little savoury plates to go with drinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolynstuart Hope you have a safe flight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie nowhere.  Here for a conference.  Flew over hail to Chch and drove here. Not enough clothes for 5 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie It was all over the place!  Storms&amp;rain then sun but COLD!!! Blowing a gale in Dunedin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger over the moon at the Moeraki Boulders http://t.co/zw4s4cMaBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turoa chairlift!!! http://t.co/rURq1FZ9N2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright baking for Spring! Gluten free chickpea and veg muffins #onefor therecipebook Vintage… http://t.co/7NRSIYcrp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did I do on my day off? Proof reading a Master of Architecture thesis of course! Very interesting… http://t.co/VGZtRxpEaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The definition of absolute bliss #catslife Hardy relaxing from the stress of it all. http://t.co/zMfFbM4TOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New sign writing for our business name change! http://t.co/noeZqWpSOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy World Vegetarian Day! We are celebrating with dinner of spaghetti with mushroom and chilli… http://t.co/OEJ6CCniKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the breakfast tray this morning: an icing heart leftover from Saturday's experimental cake… http://t.co/fCueEsrupx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie Too funny! Hope you said yes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dynesmcconnell Just as I remember it 25yrs ago! We're pumped for you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting new term: TV3 report describes Auckland as an alcogenic environment. #newjargon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the new Arise CD "God Alone" with my potato friend.  Disturbingly like Miranda. http://t.co/eAvmSi7kME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby broad beanies #knewthemfromseed #livinggreenly http://t.co/BovsDm5P2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Government love me and want me to be well so they are giving me free mammograms! Thanks NZ!!!… http://t.co/T0o36JTUAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie Thanks! Never usually win anything #livingintheoverflow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the tickets @StudiocanalNZ!  Date night! Woohoo! http://t.co/vQAMj4u9ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudiocanalNZ wellington,  penthouse cinema!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving the new podiatry chair http://t.co/kE8b9ceQGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraWardThomas I think it was me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderMaps Always wondered how you spelled that. Good work Thundermaps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True: "You don’t argue people into the kingdom of heaven. You love them into the kingdom of heaven"  Ps Rick Warren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A treat for the eyrs: You Could Grab A Bargain Classic At This Massive No Reserve Auction http://t.co/bMOvUyiaey (via @CarThrottle)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger putting up a new ceiling. Live using a gib sheet lifter! http://t.co/DmT1L7Hh6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is full of info, good and bad. But follow the right people and be prepared for the gems to come #trueforlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go again! Roger's club car begins with a small engine! http://t.co/kdJQ7RrfG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy in their work and keen to pose for a photo! http://t.co/0ejSTPY4e3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty soon this is going to be one sweet ride! Look out Targa! Roger's on the build! http://t.co/cXRALGE9Os]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind and rain are no match for these guys!  Painting the electric cable towers. #braveryonthejob http://t.co/32wc9uyPpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the jungle! Short plant is eggplant, the rest are Russian red tomatoes and cherrydots.… http://t.co/Mfd0U8C2hL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless this mess! Looking forward to seeing the end of plastering and painting. http://t.co/Y6UH70ySo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a MORE POWERcleaning day in Area 51 compound, including safety equipment and 4 compressors! http://t.co/gR3ZaPpVYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cleaning up a roadcase for peoplecare. The right protective gear is essential! http://t.co/69cXdQuiCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weloveallthat not in NZ. It's already tomorrow over here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top of the mornin' to you all on this beautiful St Patrick's Day! 'Tis a great day to be Oirish and no mistake!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodness me, the plywood is starting to mount up everywhere in Roger's worshop http://t.co/RyYqlAl9gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for muscle and classic car spotting today! At Oriental Parade with Roger Rowse xx http://t.co/2tIBfsIdUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A festival of wind and water for birds! http://t.co/gJHBpfspSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the day your life could change! Make God the centre of every decision and live in his overflow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde Gmail autcorrects "Kilbirnie" to "chilblains". Go figure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God wouldn't give us a purpose without making sure of our success so step boldly despite the naysayers! He trusts you so listen to Him!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got to move it move it, MOVE IT!!! Can't wait to move it to Vision Sunday!
Are you coming too? It's going to be incredible! 
#seeyouthere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders must be worth following.  Followers are worth treasuring!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the latest single by @ARISEchurch here for Free! #arisemusic http://t.co/FFeuVAbBtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde Totally agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't judge a person by their exterior.  They may not seem much, but in times of sadness,  weariness or trouble, they are always there x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is everywhere!  Post Vision Night walk back to the car. Ordinary signpost + streetlight = little miracle http://t.co/gvnxNdCDpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danieltiaiti congratulations!  So many will be saved because of your relationship with God!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have joined Men United! Awesome institution devoted to promoting screening&amp; treatment of prostate cancer in the UK #proudgirlsupporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhoodie Welcome to Android World!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect today I am renewed. Enjoying the overhaul I get every morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the day to step out, acknowledge&amp; encourage that person who has been yr quiet supporter all along. Notice the unnoticed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThunderMaps Great to see an Aussie connection.  The Victorian CFA could sure use you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Re-Ignite Your Passion for Ministry by @rickwarren via @pastors http://t.co/dEFKjpe4Uo #pastors via @pastors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Annamarietnsb I'm prob in the wrong country for this company!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Wellington Anniversary Day! Do at least one thing that makes you truly happy. Let yr heart sing and yr spirit soar! God's got yr back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Pastor John at Planetshakers city church! http://t.co/wn773QpIyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suz_suz_suzie oooh take care Suz. If this carries on you will need medical help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Absurdly Simple Life Hacks That You Can Use Right Now http://t.co/3vNOmBHz6e via @lolacoaster Love the tennis ball!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde @dynesmcconnell Oh goodness yes! Happy birthday to you Dynes with many hugs &amp; blessings for the year to come xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is loving driving a manual again! #incontrol #behindthewheel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I surround myself in thoughts about what I want: to be happy and fulfilled in Christ. Speak encouragement, be open, love every1!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a beautiful day - I'm living in the overflow!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde o well that's ok then :) just sounded kinda lonely. I njoy a bit of solitude too. Chatting with the Holy Spirit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde didn't it give someone the opportunity to bless you with a free coffee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcarusForde In prayer for you dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never believe that others are somehow fundamentally better than you. God made them &amp;you to His plan. Different yes, inferior no #Hiscreation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a day to organize and streamline home and business.  Actually looking forward to the work..God's hand is all over this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJohnSparks Me! @CeeDub67  thank you and happy new year! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matariki12 thought you might like this! http://t.co/SdWyEok7oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok now that's what I call rain! Flooding from the downpour #lifeinthepark http://t.co/Sp9XO2hwDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says you can't garden in a loft? 8 tomatoes and 1 eggplant say differently! #goodlife http://t.co/50GgNkQcc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014 will be a year of building &amp; growth in my life, spirit, marriage, business &amp; most importantly my relationship with God #declaringit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringing in the New Year watching Bridget Jones' Diary. Great film about fresh starts &amp; coming back after epic fails. Happy New Year to all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night we had Dad teaching his daughter to drive up here, this morning a guy teaching his son to drive a forklift!  #ChristmasinthePark]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>