<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s an adaptation of Daphne du Maurier’s My Cousin Rachel coming up and it looks *thrillingly* OTT. https://t.co/6bLNkacoul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your subconscious takes a bit of time to catch up with your feminism: https://t.co/NqjvMcMJ8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paolo Sorrentino has made a short film for Campari, starring Clive Owen: https://t.co/288DMIC8Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alibelle Oh my god this makes my blood boil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahswiv I knew there was a reason I voted for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuckinghamAlice Ooh no. I'm using the HA and then the Rosehip Oil, which I love. Maybe I should give Vit C a go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat @Tell_StreetLink DONE! Thanks for the reminder - something I keep meaning to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuckinghamAlice The micellar water is nice; cleanser also nice but nothing out of the ordinary (I prefer cleansing oils).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuckinghamAlice I like using the water gel as the next step after hyuralonic acid (from The Ordinary, ofc) in the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Good Point. 
(But Damien Chazelle is still only 31) https://t.co/ReGtaHRjdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like Ewan McGregor but I’m still not sure why a Frenchman couldn’t have been cast as Lumière https://t.co/UJYpXztmBc #beautyandthebeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScarlettCayford @TunworthCheese Literally 1 day to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahswiv @TheLooseKannen Ah yes, definitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLooseKannen @hannahswiv I may be a total running nerd but I loved Two Hours by Ed Caesar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone after a Magic Unicorn Garden? https://t.co/Ow8KwxrGqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like something @ScarlettCayford would enjoy. https://t.co/HI1Quv72If]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usain Bolt no longer holds the triple-triple gold. Dammit. https://t.co/kPOPyY1hSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliceelizabethk This feels like the thin end of a terrifying wedge, although I hope I'm wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliceelizabethk In what kind of "land of the free" are its leaders insistent that women can't have choice or control over their own bodies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #globalgagrule news makes me feel so so angry, and so powerless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may not have loved all of Sherlock S4, but @TheeNerdwriter shows why its good bits are still great: https://t.co/mNijpCFfRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@picturehouses @The_Shiznit Last Five Years and Singin’ in the Rain both popped into my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally saw Goodfellas this weekend and, well, I think I left it about 10 years too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, are you listening? 

#womensmarch2017 #womansmarchlondon #trafalgarsquare #iamwoman https://t.co/SqQPGVGsRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite signs from today's march (there were so many great ones) #womensmarchlondon https://t.co/lDDC1a03xW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, T2 Trainspotting has been given 4/5 stars by The Guardian and 1/5 by Little White Lies. Now I HAVE to go see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we really going to do 00s’ fashion all over again? This seems like a really bad idea. https://t.co/kCDNqcsiYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted to skip gym class and sit in sauna for 45 mins. Brrrrrr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I’m feeling a little blue, I go and hang out on @elclimo’s Insta for a bit. Works a treat. https://t.co/u1VpRhOYA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuttycow I really really want to see that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woody Harrelson is shooting a film, live, on Thursday. Because, why not? https://t.co/iWcOqxEsWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally jumped aboard the matcha latte bandwagon... and, well, it's literally just grass-flavoured milk. https://t.co/CPBS8EtNLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyjunesmith Dear god, I can't get past the second verse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I caught up with the final Sherlock last night. It's a bit... overwrought, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganJGibson @jamieklingler @ScarlettCayford @hannahswiv I can't do Friday/the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScarlettCayford @jamieklingler @hannahswiv @MeganJGibson I am so in. This book is my manifesto (of sorts)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophLouiseHall @ScarlettCayford are you through yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyrutter I love their Hyaluronic Acid. And their Rosehip Oil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 30th birthday will be spent watching Hamilton. Huzzah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daniellagraham @hollyjunesmith That's a good point. More visibility is a positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyjunesmith Totally agree. What a way to make everyone feel like they *must* be miserable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat I had almost that exact same conversation last night. This is serious stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected, but I love it. 
#Crossroads #Britney4eva https://t.co/Ii1HYD8s2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be doing Dry January, but I'm still really enjoying @DropWineApp's newsletters. May just start stocking up for Feb/my birthday...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished reading @NaomiAllthenews' The Power and absolutely adored it. Smart, well-written and compulsively re… https://t.co/QmIonxrpkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wonderful. @Hemmo on swimming, IVF and the choice “to keep moving instead of standing at the edge of life, peering in.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahswiv This is a great idea. I just *know* that my 2016 book list is going to have been so homogenous (white women, last ten years).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 2017 resolution: Be more Meryl Streep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So buses leaving from Waterloo are packed already #TubeStrike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weird and wonderful world of Korean beauty. Anyone any clue...? https://t.co/mabE7rPZkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW your office is so cold that you’re warming your hands over the toaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat @thepooluk This is great, @hollyjunesmith. The advice "even 5 mins a day is better than nothing" is something I should heed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jellymalin Cafés that stay open late, for somewhere to hang out in the evening that isn't a busy bar or restaurant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've read too many think pieces about Love Actually to even be in the same room while it's on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoskas Bone structure to study for days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoskas Somehow her eyelids are very alluring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All off Christmas' thespian-ness came together with Andrea Riseborough and Toby Jones nose-to-nose in #witnessfortheprosecution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything's very misty. #witnessfortheprosecution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaDelPizzo @finkowska @PhelpsieSarah Seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat Fair. Christmas is the time for sleeping, and sleeping some more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat (TBF I'm self-medicating with caffeine and whisky)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitinahat But... Agatha Christie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best whisky tasting notes ever. Blood orange, salty rockpools, tarte tatin AND light chocolate sponge cake? What a… https://t.co/YNiRaXDPJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer we're at our parents', the more my sister and me revert to teenage type. Just us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_cornish so I should bother going to see Rogue One?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophLouiseHall Shhhh. He can never know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophLouiseHall I fear he would run away if I ever met him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goodreads 1920s Ireland with Hercule Poirot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first sub-21 Parkrun this morning on Wimbledon Common... and don't I look chuffed about… https://t.co/PLTySxMug0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp Hiya, how can I get hold of a VAT receipt for my order? Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penguinukbooks The Goldfinch by Donna Tartt - I can’t believe I haven’t read it yet…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mail has gone so far beyond parody it’s amazing it hasn’t imploded. https://t.co/HbKvbAOM05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's playlist: https://t.co/SgOQNgpDLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScarlettCayford @NotRollergirl @Czaroline ...I'm going to use that in everyday conversation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRollergirl @Czaroline Although I guess the insult depends who you're talking to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRollergirl @Czaroline See, that makes way more sense. It's meant to be insulting, surely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRollergirl @Czaroline For some reason I have it stuck in my head that it's 'third the tiny princess', but that can't be right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have just registered for the Vitality Bath Half Marathon Why not join me...  https://t.co/8xpwFE6xQh via @BathHalf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got bitten by a zebra. Thanks mate. 

#safarilife @ West Midland Safari Park https://t.co/vVWXPG4REQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this seems reasonable: https://t.co/Ep30qpxZ2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olifranklin This one is great, read it yesterday and now pressing on everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m worried that future history books will talk about pre- and post-2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABourdillon1 On a cheerier note, how was the NY marathon??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adjwilson Blind drunk in a rocket to Mars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like waking up to find out that the Big Bad beat Buffy... and the audience chose the ending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I might just stay drunk for the next 4 years. Anyone want to join me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please reassure me that there are enough checks and balances in the US system to stop him doing anything truly stupid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transpotting 2 trailer - now actually about trams. #edinburgh  
https://t.co/M1T4JKX3LL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mynameiscal I'm going to take all my friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a #HamiltonMixtape and nobody told me??!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mynameiscal I loved it SO MUCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrietnash Chop'd. £6.25 and just so... meh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a thuddeningly mediocre but expensive salad for lunch and I’m still angry about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, another film with a great trailer that eventually disappoints. https://t.co/rEDP7elHLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melted cheddar on a crumpet is so delicious, I reckon I could eat 10 of ‘em without breaking a sweat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirschplunder_ @melt_room I have been waiting forever for them to open!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burberry aren’t going for low key this year with their Christmas ad… 
https://t.co/9AeKgW6c3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trailer for #Logan, the final Wolverine with Hugh Jackman, has a totally different feel: https://t.co/TAHsz9a08W #xmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raaaather intrigued by Gore Verbinski’s A Cure For Wellness, starring Dan DeHaan and Jason Isaacs https://t.co/gs5dP7Tf1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus it means I can bore you all silly in art galleries.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>