<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part still to come. Goodell is going to have to eat all the shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those not from New England might find this remarkable. The rest call it New England grit.  #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of the game so far https://t.co/19RfJwEgqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a good game for those of us from New England 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @lannycardow does the sports https://t.co/ZOruwTuVhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then again maybe we need a left celebrity candidate. Teigen 2020.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is Chrissy Teigen the most compelling and effective voice on the left? I mean I heart her. But get it together… https://t.co/sNCle5w38A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZauxuULyeJ  All of this. https://t.co/AiSqaxnvya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 looking to be worse than 2016. https://t.co/9vQ60SrHGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson CNN in a cage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson the whole sketch was 💯🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Moose" + "lamb" is the best part of Spicer SNL skit. Dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice finding creative ways to make money in a tough media environment. #innovation https://t.co/Ex2Q6dvylj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the feels. "Audi's Super Bowl Ad With a Dad Contemplating His Daughter's Worth" https://t.co/pWsqTl3pxu via @POPSUGARMoms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson the arrogance was unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will also be another English test. Obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvanGiesbrecht Hrm...anything about DeGrassi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson Lose Michigan? Never!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received notice from Immigration I have to start studying for citizenship test. How many Qs about Drake will there be? Bieber? Nickelback?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry ad industry. Clinton didn't lose because her TV buying data wasn't good. She lost because she couldn't connec… https://t.co/tktxHIEv01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, Trudeau just found the best way to bury electoral reform: Beyonce pregnancy. Only trumped, by Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all seriousness. My world went by for two hours without knowing the most important news of 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait. Beyonce is pregnant. How was I not notified immediately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson Classical *East Coast* Elitist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson @HamiltonMusical Lol. If you defended Originalism with rap I might come around. Also, not a Liberal Elitist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson Agreed - intent and spirit of law, not exact interpretation! See we do agree. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson I know. But flip side is that if men who wrote law believed okay to own people (amongst other values) then grain of salt, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson And its not because of abortion issue - I get that argument - it is grey area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson Doesn't change my innate issues with literal interpretation.  #AgreeToDisagree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Constitutions original meaning said it was okay to own other human beings. So.... https://t.co/lpSu0t21Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyScully Clearly smart money was on muslim woman of colour...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoiler: white dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sports confuse me, but this is pretty smart.  https://t.co/1VP5TGP3jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FTR: Trump finding a way for people to care about Supreme Court nominee is the one good thing he has done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. All of this. "White Resentment on the Night Shift at Walmart" https://t.co/irLgP5TN94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got an invite to my dad's retirement party. 49 years with same bank. What a boomer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could also describe half the White House https://t.co/qBUjDPpXD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that this is audience ID. But tasteless to have petty shit like this out in light of QC, US, etc. https://t.co/qCyV58N0uO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimWalker9 "The demise of the dinosaurs was inevitable once the asteroid hit earth."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In summary, the word is shit. *goes back to bed*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration! It works! https://t.co/gtRMYicN22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Twitter feed nicely juxtaposing leadership... https://t.co/QEVl534PXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The champagne pour is the second best part next to Taylor's outfit. https://t.co/csjdZKuumQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agalbraith Pop culture overload! And her styling. I die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GUYS. NEW T SWIFT VIDEO. https://t.co/kzPlk8pHJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsburge I have no problem with some government money or policy, but I haven't seen any innovation. Gov't can't be only answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will take innovation, changes to current structures and rethinking the role of a "newspaper" &amp; "media". Something status quo won't do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or better yet, all media form alliance against Facebook to not share content unless they get better cut of ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I have digital spends that are almost 100% Facebook? Because its efficient, its cheap and its targeting is second to none.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian media needs to find a way to take back ad dollars from Facebook and Google. How? Make it easy to target and buy ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. It doesn't. It needs innovation. How about you put someone in charge of PostMedia that isn't a status quo, over… https://t.co/EHU9cAcFaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite example: Most of us get same (or more) for massages under insurance as we do therapy. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(4/4) So keep talking, but but the words into action. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(3/4) Need government, employers, insurance providers and health industry to work together. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(2/4) Stigma is first battle, but also need affordable access to mental health services. Still out of reach for most. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(1/4) Important to not only talk about mental health, but to work towards practical solutions #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe it when I see it. They make $$ from this. https://t.co/maV2a5oWxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUGE (yuge) miss opportunity. People gathered, taking action. One location. Data goldmine. Progessive base. https://t.co/VuIxLJDwae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gross man child is 36? Even Corinne is better than him. #TheBachelor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we supposed to like Nick from #TheBachelor I mean Ben was watching paint dry, but he wasn't a walking STD either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynne and O'Leary are earned media feud made in strategist heaven. Appeals to both their bases. Creates clicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robserpe Fair. I mean, arguably shouldn't have a career.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you ever wonder what the NFL prioritizes. Its not domestic or sexual assault. But, hey. Football! Sports!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of quarterbacks playing tonight is a noted sexual assaulter. Never sanctioned by league. One may have let air out of ball. Sanctioned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't sleep. Spent morning cleaning and organizing and watching #thebachelor Feminism is alive and well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you know he's using media? He usually tries to offend the media. Incites predictable outrage. I.e. lying during briefing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you still all fall for Trump's trick. He makes crazy statements to push bad news off front page. Don't feed a fire oxygen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been accused of not being to hide emotion on my face. Usually contempt. Michelle Obama, a kindred soulmate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is one thing history has taught us, its that patriotism defeats prejudice.....(spoiler: no it doesn't) https://t.co/rDppoPwHW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a drinking game for this speech? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp. Fingers crossed. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN getting its revenge by repeatedly broadcasting shots of empty Mall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we strike the word "destroys" from media vocabulary? https://t.co/ZbLXAg0WNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainly for this line https://t.co/QybZ1V4tEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best piece on internet this week? "Discussion Over: Nelly Was Bigger Than Drake" https://t.co/hJhW6NBuI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen Twitter just because I talk about wine and am online a lot doesn't mean I need prescription weight loss meds… https://t.co/K1pSbQNg4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvanGiesbrecht lol. God help my generation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOMORROW: I'll speak as a token American, token young female, token digital expert on #Inauguration… https://t.co/WYX9zHjk1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click bait President https://t.co/rLe5M5BdUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time my morning issues scan read: "Rap video".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obvious headline of week https://t.co/xZ5Wnfo0l3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First I've seen this Facebook Amber Alert. Smart. First platform many of us check in morning. https://t.co/7YK17imxdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there not a "serious cup of coffee" line at Starbucks. If you don't add goddamn caramel you can bypass the other assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson @sweetpetetweets "Got my nunchucks up here"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson @sweetpetetweets  Also, this dude lives in Canada. His fridge has Presidents Choice products.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does Taylor feel about this? She's team Selena. But also team Hadid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE WEEKND AND SELENA. OMG. Will Bieber and Weeknd have Canadian street fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a small baby in the office which means I have gotten none of the work done. #30somethingkryptonite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one outside of media cares about conflicts. Most Americans just hear this man has a LOT of money. And a LOT of power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This speech is why Obama could have beaten Trump. Emotional connection. Can't fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the tears. https://t.co/dzD1prrtLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were there people who thought Trump didn't have strange sexual proclivities. Like? Really? That's the best Russia has?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why you don't fuck with the CIA. https://t.co/AyvlQ09LFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrnr brings back Egypt presents. Mine fittingly has something to do with a God that hates sunrise (mornings). Fi… https://t.co/lRjzhnfbpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chazpierson the cognitive disconnance the media demonstrates is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up to a feed of "Meryl Streep Destroys Trump". If by destroyed we meant, played into his anti-elite, earned media hands. Then yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously my new go to shade. https://t.co/mdGQ2YE1dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the positive side (personally), Putin is really showing the value of communications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ode to Hooker Harveys. https://t.co/CvcjflQonR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/vB7Sd4l4X4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>