<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Driver in critical condition after a crash on Ash St in #Abbotsford @AbbyPoliceDept @BC_EHS https://t.co/8PmKAgRMRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRescue do you guys have a staging location set up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD say this is the city's 2nd homicide of 2017. https://t.co/yWi2dzCH7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD confirm they are investigating a homicide on the #StanleyPark seawall. https://t.co/Wp2f9E8gAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD investigating reported stabbing on the #StanleyPark #Seawall near Second Beach. https://t.co/LA0xxiQdja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LateNightCam that couldve ended badly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stabbing on Commercial Drive has sent a victim to hospital. @VancouverPD @BC_EHS @VanFireRescue https://t.co/ngoHNXiNE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@i_on_food_drink It looks like @raffertybaker filed his story on Jan. 31 of last year: https://t.co/fatI1SK7HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD at Vancouver's first homicide of 2017 in the #DTES last night. https://t.co/QLRBJNSGny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD investigating possible hit and run; truck hit parked car on Hastings and crashed into building near K… https://t.co/9ZxdRLBtOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD say man in his 50s dead from apparent shooting at the Savoy Pub. https://t.co/BeQpMeJzG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD dealing with a reported shooting in the #DTES https://t.co/1ipaJZcRg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD have arrested one man from the savoy pub incident https://t.co/R6YyHpOIf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD on scene for an incident at the Savoy Pub https://t.co/aqEublYZU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collision with @TransLink bus on Boundary Rd sends young man to hospital. No other passengers on the bus at the tim… https://t.co/PYHcng0puX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP gather shell casings off the ground. Vehicle and shooter have not been located. https://t.co/MhkTFBUFRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP investigating drive by shooting on 124 St. Shots fired into vehicle, occupants unharmed. https://t.co/5nzxcd8fvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh so that's where you went. @HeritageVan @WestEndBIA https://t.co/rxzIrYOHxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD have Victoria Dr closed in both directions from Kingsway to 28th for a 2-car crash https://t.co/DrSoi95yVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue says the house is not abandoned; homeowners were on site 2-3 weeks ago. Fire appears to have starte… https://t.co/eZdCV3hqfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue fighting a fire at vacant house on Yukon St https://t.co/5QQomcnr0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AbbyPoliceDept say one of the shooting victims is in life-threatening condition. https://t.co/WUd48GacIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue attacked a large fire in an #EastVan house early this morning. 2 men escaped safely after their dog… https://t.co/32XKT5vgMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue says the dog helped the two men escape by alerting them to the fire. https://t.co/UBNsbpHGZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 men and their dog escaped a house fire in #EastVan early this morning. House was under renovation at the time.… https://t.co/4yAYNdbNp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawrence Parry escaped unharmed from the fire with his uncle and their dog. He says he's blind and his uncle woke h… https://t.co/MuNQSbpXS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire has completely destroyed the garage and deck @VanFireRescue https://t.co/mMyjn7dygj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue battling a fire on Euclid Avenue in #EastVan right now https://t.co/l0ebhO0EGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BurnabyRCMP investigating targeted shooting at a karaoke bar off #Kingsway. https://t.co/UzI6HV9aNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people forced out of their home  in #Surrey after fire breaks out in their furnace room. @Local1271 https://t.co/X8hEIKhre9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP have towed the target vehicle from the mall on 120 St. https://t.co/gEA5mmcX0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passenger side window has bullet holes in it. https://t.co/NF3rGJomyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target vehicle now being towed away https://t.co/PyoYLiGhVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP officers gathering shell casings off the ground in the parking lot of the mall. https://t.co/0LgUAPEWwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP investigating a reported shooting at a mall on 120. https://t.co/dFhpBnv4jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@iaff1286 busy fighting a massive blaze at a scrap yard on Mitchell Island right now. Flames can be seen across th… https://t.co/VAQ1UQihTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large crowds gathering across the river to watch the fire. Smoke can be seen as far away as Grouse Mountain.… https://t.co/dvIR0Y9kW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire is on Mitchell Island at some kind of scrap yard. https://t.co/N0Y5wN8KM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large fire burning on Mitchell Island. Can hear explosions and popping coming from what looks like a scrap yard.… https://t.co/9CoqnWf35a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extra overnight security on hand at Trump Tower in #Vancouver on the dawn of inauguration day @TrumpVancouver… https://t.co/zw3HM4c9oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD confirm it was a pipe bomb inside the vehicle. 33 yr old man from West Van in custody. https://t.co/Uf8kkCVkUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PfenTwo i believe they examined it before firing at it. it sounded like they hit it with compressed air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD firing at the suspicious package after removing it from the vehicle on Cordova St. https://t.co/7MkPUsxIL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blubdha they obviously had reason to believe it wasn't suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD say they're unsure of what specifically was inside the suspect package, but officers shot it as a precaution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD just detonated something from inside the vehicle. https://t.co/K7wTbpbecS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bomb squad robot is currently examining contents found in the back of the car. @VancouverPD https://t.co/GgF2MMwGyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD still on scene with possible explosives in the back of a Mercedes https://t.co/muFWZojv08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD say the shooting is targeted. https://t.co/xaT3pvhpgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD say occupants of the house are not injured from the shooting in South Vancouver but also not cooperat… https://t.co/UCkqtPHHAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD incident at Knight/54th. Looks like bullet holes through a window. https://t.co/1Y4kSKr93z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people and their dog forced out of home after fire destroys porch in #Surrey @Local1271 https://t.co/EhsEvi0h82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AbbyPoliceDept say they’ll be clearing the scene of the shooting on Janzen Street soon. Forensics team focused on… https://t.co/3Ch1Svn4OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BREAKING @AbbyPoliceDept says 1 man injured in a shooting less than an hour ago. Suspect has fled. No word if shoo… https://t.co/WocdtSbYFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KamilKaramali we even win for trying to recycle https://t.co/UKOXHJJP1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRCMP investigating stabbing that sent 32 yr old woman to hospital. Attacker/victim were known to each other… https://t.co/U1LcY6AQ0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CoquitlamSAR wrapping up a long evening of searching in South Vancouver after missing #Burnaby woman found safe. https://t.co/NiA19sa7Tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man and woman in hospital in stable condition after a stabbing on Oak St. @VancouverPD @BC_EHS https://t.co/MMSJlv3jLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD investigators have not yet arrived on scene at the crash on Granville/16th. Avoid area if possible. https://t.co/abE1Bqw0Hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD have traffic blocked in all directions at Granville and W 16th after serious crash https://t.co/EyKhZkfi6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hornby blocked from Davie to Helmcken as @VanFireRescue deals with small fire at the #MurrayHotel https://t.co/n6ZGsx5TBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HomicideTeam investigating fatal shooting in #Richmond https://t.co/6N7OutTUuj https://t.co/Pu1X9iczhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RichmondRCMP confirm male shooting victim found on Ash St. late last night. @HomicideTeam will be involved in the… https://t.co/4qfpJMoBac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RichmondRCMP say 6500-block of Ash St will be closed for a while. Officers have tarp over an SUV that looks like… https://t.co/zh9RPpijI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@i_on_food_drink thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD officers say 1 victim was an elderly man; the other was a young man who got in a fight. Both with min… https://t.co/u6wld3cHdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two in hospital after reported stabbing on Granville St https://t.co/pVkiZGFMT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small memorial of flowers grows outside the scene of a fire in #EastVan that killed a young child yesterday.… https://t.co/4uj13TZ8xe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andwalsh im sure with some dedication and ingenuity, another larger 'rink' is not that far away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@New_Westminster offering free salt/sand mix at works yard on First St today https://t.co/Zfe5G3yha0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue really upping their sign design game this morning! #saltcrisis #saltgate #bcsnow https://t.co/93dneUHsbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 #PittMeadows residents had to spend a few hrs in a community hall on Harris Rd after a gas leak was detected by… https://t.co/9hGbSQQ8Ay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple #EastVan teens took advantage of some free ice time before bed last night at #TroutLake https://t.co/kVLL24xmhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RyanMacouver @Sheila_Scott I'm sure all the salt that's been generated on twitter today should suffice a couple rounds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no but really -- #saltgate #saltcrisis #bcsnow https://t.co/AHzy8efxzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine. #saltgate #saltcrisis #bcsnow https://t.co/6cpPFnnShJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and yes, with every ounce of energy I have left before I go to bed, I hope to make #Saltgate a real thing. #bcsnow #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CityofVancouver says most of their salt is gone and @VanFireRescue halls will not be resupplied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue says all 10 halls will be restocked with free salt by 9am and daily thereafter. They’re banking on the honour system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All is not lost... @VanFireRescue says salt will be restocked at all halls by 9am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batt. Chief with @VanFireRescue says halls 12, 14, 15 and 17 are out of salt. Unsure if there was a fresh delivery… https://t.co/GteFGByNax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands remain without power as @bchydro works overnight to restore outages across South Coast https://t.co/jSVGHwXjgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man in hospital with serious injuries after apparent stabbing in #Surrey. @SurreyRCMP have 43 yr old man in custody. https://t.co/rXWpHwPC45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the greatest hits collection: https://t.co/0ZdqMChRBN #cbcvancouver #photojournalism #thenightshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanFireRescue at their last fire of 2016. Early reports say possibly caused by fireworks, but cause still undeter… https://t.co/C7j7TdYvMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringing in #NYE with these peeps https://t.co/Myq3nQBijy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of residents forced out after fire at #WestEnd apartment building. @VanFireRescue https://t.co/mReomuFiMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ScanBC is he any good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people to hospital after crash on Ladner Trunk Rd in #Delta. Icy roads believed to be a factor. @deltapolice https://t.co/qjAQDqpuQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barn fire in #Langley is out now. 3 horses rescued, 2 cats still missing. @TOLFireFighters https://t.co/XYjygxrz2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crews still continuing to fight the blaze at the barn. Still no word on if any animals were injured.… https://t.co/TwQgxVXvar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TOLFireFighters battling 2-alarm blaze at a barn on 240 st https://t.co/PWPmmOuYbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@yaktrax did I even put these on right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightcrawler vs ice #bcsnow https://t.co/2h5J6Fecml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman in hospital after being hit by taxi that spun out on ice and crashed into driveway on William St @IAFF323… https://t.co/AlQ0sLlN7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning the late Christmas shopping parking game. https://t.co/SS0MFPBLfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with that, #MerryChristmas everyone! I’m off tomorrow… see you for full overnight coverage next week. #NYE2017… https://t.co/LOO9iNJFLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CityofVancouver EWS shelters open overnight for people to escape the cold weather. Creekside Comm. Ctr and The Ha… https://t.co/GoNitguxxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Witnessed 2 overdoses, literally within metres and minutes of each other last night, in the #DTES @VancouverPD… https://t.co/4gQ5qkeHgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driver of pickup truck safe after he was rescued from a water-filled ditch in Langley late last night.… https://t.co/gHpTHVOu5f]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>