<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Donald Trump Plans to Eliminate National Endowment for the ArtsPrivatize Corporation for Public Broadcasting https://t.co/bAtOhndR05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Lies About the Popular Vote, via @nytimes https://t.co/ePdUlZdcHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Havana, Castro’s Death Lays Bare a Generation Gap, via @nytimes https://t.co/5Rajkm6ayN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Rorty’s 1998 Book Suggested Election 2016 Was Coming, via @nytimes https://t.co/M314U6EUTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye, American neoliberalism. A new era is here | Cornel West https://t.co/udPA3FZvOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Zacherle, Host With a Ghoulish Perspective, Dies at 98, via @nytimes https://t.co/YCRF9f4WUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_FieldTheory great to stop by chatting with @_DavidCross and u valiant folks Friday evening talking public practice &amp; endurance art 6hrs2go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A NEW artist run space in Wellington! The First MEANWHILE Publication | PledgeMe https://t.co/BO8zehi5gZ via @pledgeme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobel panel gives up knockin’ on Dylan’s door https://t.co/YogTHrPK61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Foster Wallace, my teacher https://t.co/IiCv9GIF76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucywardle_ @rubyjoyeade @hibiscuslips @salientmagazine that's a memorable piece of writing thanks Ruby and thanks for pointing it out Lucy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally Mann’s Loving Study of Cy Twombly’s Last Years https://t.co/9gfnn4r1P2 via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Anxiety and Escapism at Rashid Johnson’s “Fly Away” https://t.co/64Vndh8t4F via @artfcity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Wilson, Mike Love, and the Psychodrama Behind the Beach Boys’ Sun-Streaked Legacy https://t.co/4awSPFJKcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henry Rollins: 'Trump fans are going to be very dangerous losers' https://t.co/JfdawXlr4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to hear of the upcoming publication of artist @_DavidCross 's book "Air Supplied" by @punctum_books NYC https://t.co/OEHD4JNd4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview Magazine - Benjamin Patterson, Ears Open https://t.co/e2dVDsujQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being Honest About Trump https://t.co/B9wtVzhCyU via @adamgopnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've curated a show Is it the beginning of a new age? opens 19 July @TheSchoolofArt @theengineroomnz do come along! https://t.co/QHlPTXT61x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw @JOEtheMORTON as @IAmDickGregory indescribably powerful and moving evocation of artist &amp; human rights activist by a virtuoso actor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn Went well nice turn out Amelia grt. Off to NYC on fri with Simon Morris and a Massey student posse! many miles to go before sleep!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about artist Daniel Crooks' artworks in the Bullet Time show with writer @AmeliaBarikin @CityGalleryWgtn this Saturday at 2 PM FREE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burt Kwouk, ‘Pink Panther’ Actor, Dies at 85, via @nytimes https://t.co/E1Uv3fcoN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noam Chomsky on Donald Trump: 'Almost a death knell for the human species' https://t.co/UJ1aUHkhwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iggy Pop slams modern music: ‘Why don’t I just die now?’ https://t.co/3bzeb6ImQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s the Thing So Many Americans Can’t Grasp About Bernie Sanders https://t.co/65SyRKAWHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re in an amazing black cultural moment. Cue predictable white backlash https://t.co/krjuQpjuN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Catch a Beat https://t.co/K3IfCtBgEw via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to help Louis CK out of debt? Four great reasons to watch Horace and Pete https://t.co/NdWEsDQor5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Promises Paul Ryan That He’ll Sound Slightly Less Like Hitler https://t.co/Zxb5FLI1SU via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Secret Shame of Middle-Class Americans Living Paycheck to Paycheck https://t.co/d2oGCbU1Jz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @arovideo @lumierereader there's a cool essay on the late great Jacques Rivette by the very much alive @jrosenbaum2002 in May @Artforum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The (Very Lazy) Sunday Routine of Vanessa Bayer of ‘Saturday Night Live’ https://t.co/5YryqZjhnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Bernie Sanders Is Staying in the Race https://t.co/bJ7zwMK6Rg via @JohnCassidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sons of No One Los Angeles Review of Books - Los Angeles Review of Books: The Sons of No One https://t.co/gdPk4VLE84 @lareviewofbooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to think of a comment but words are failing me..... https://t.co/yOqylpQ2qS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFMOMA's new extension – a gigantic meringue with a hint of Ikea https://t.co/54Rqhizkdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Borrower returns library book 67 years late – but escapes $24,000 fine https://t.co/PJNOjjYwaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep’s Twenties, and My Own https://t.co/PKc1CyYJbr via @@MJSchulman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s in a Name? Just Ask Frank Zappa’s Feuding Heirs https://t.co/EyUlGHtNij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganDunn90 your talks were awesome today and I've gotten great feedback thanks again hardest working art writer in Wellington!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Art Matters, Even in Poverty https://t.co/RIkIurfyiS via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galleries Scramble Amid Brooklyn’s Gentrification https://t.co/xFp2k6kotD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewPaulWood @vulture Franco a terrifically underwhelming artist but Saltz has his writerly moments for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Franco Is, Actually, an Artist. So Why Won’t the Art World Take Him Seriously? https://t.co/xKqdZDiyeD via @vulture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Beverly Cleary! https://t.co/7MVz02KkWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art of Secrecy #panamapapers https://t.co/KJehI6iGf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merle Haggard: The authentic and gifted voice of the people https://t.co/VxMmXOqdWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Performing, Writing" symposium in Wellington March 2017 CFP open until 1 July 2016 More info at 
https://t.co/PuhR7PxmOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders’s Message Stands to Resonate Long After Election, via @nytimes https://t.co/YhLzVOfzWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last red-roofed Pizza Hut experiences surge in dine-in customers https://t.co/TfwlJMeZkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free symposium event "Capitalism and Parasitism" organised by artist Etienne de France on this Friday at Massey: https://t.co/MOw1kfKMZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Whites Just Don’t Get It, Part 6 https://t.co/EwtO0RsYzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking Wellingtonians world's most active https://t.co/wV0vT0wayI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed Institute of Artivism / Instituto de Artivismo Hannah Arendt on @Kickstarter https://t.co/sCDXr9THnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Seizes 3 States, Sweeping Democratic Contests https://t.co/SISJmTLyrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Don Cheadle shake the establishment with 'Miles Ahead'? https://t.co/8YSAil6whg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s How Bernie Sanders Could Win the Nomination, via @nytimes https://t.co/72QI1nkIAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@guardian: Where have all the art punks gone? https://t.co/Xjsx56IykP” featuring the shittiest Simon Denny remarks I've read yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump Are Winning Votes, but Not Hearts, via @nytimes https://t.co/GERQ3l9yht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie’s Dead-End Math — and Why He Should Stay In https://t.co/ge0hn67wkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ry Cooder: 15 essential songs | via @TeleMusicNews https://t.co/c934d81aXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schjeldahl on Hammons: Laughter and Anger https://t.co/uSupmE0qIl via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How America Made Donald Trump Unstoppable utterly terrifying! https://t.co/yQvdwQdtdO via @rollingstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Artists Make the Best Curators? https://t.co/D43peVKgYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consolidating Power: Interview with Roar Magazine https://t.co/rL76Ct87mk via @profdavidharvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should All Research Papers Be Free?, via @nytimes https://t.co/TGr5PFALhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iggy Pop Life Class | e-flux https://t.co/GdY78vivTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Chicago, and the Lessons of 1968 https://t.co/uNSXYMbvkA via @jelani9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream Journals": How to Beat Writer's Block https://t.co/UjGRr4np7g via @mkonnikova]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trip Through Amazon’s First Physical Store https://t.co/uzEqEIF95o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Sees Michigan Win as a Springboard to the Nomination https://t.co/QXKbjTGYL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Rally in Chicago Canceled After Violent Scuffles, via @nytimes https://t.co/phu9D5d3qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riskiest Political Act of 2016? Protesting at Rallies for Donald Trump, via @nytimes https://t.co/FVMdpDcE2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communal Living, the 21st-Century Way, via @nytimes https://t.co/hMHbtVdHQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump University, Students Recall Pressure to Give Positive Reviews, via @nytimes https://t.co/lf23ttqfOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Print | Tony Oursler on David Bowie https://t.co/vVUjettSkR @artforum best thing I've read so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnjoyGallery @CIRCUITAFV in the very best way imaginable! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the 2016 Walters Prize nominees what a fantastic list, and great choices judges! https://t.co/h66kbmL9R5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Martin, Redefining Producer Who Guided the Beatles, Dies at 90, via @nytimes https://t.co/qbxTWrBqYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanyliu but it was certainly an amazing resource at that time to which I was addicted and in retrospect I am extremely grateful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynpepperell sounds like a great one. you might also want to check out Percival Everett's Erasure if you haven't yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringostarrmusic @RobynHitchcock isn't the news of George Martin's death a hoax?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hang in there @BernieSanders so fantastic to see the support in Michigan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human trafficking, exploitation 'rife' in New Zealand - Peter Mihaere https://t.co/aFXRxPmqh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring some art in the hood this past week always new surprises  @Kemi_Niko https://t.co/VsFj3LXCY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump has to be the all time ultimo big bastard performance artist but in no way do I want him as US president! #21stCenturyfascism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Mexico City, Comedians Punish Society’s Scofflaws With Humiliation, via @nytimes https://t.co/qHdGQmM6Ht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary | Eva Díaz at the 104th College Art Association conference in Washington, DC https://t.co/z41xzna8s9 @artforum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary | Anthony Byrt at the reopening of the Christchurch Art Gallery in New Zealand https://t.co/HuhBR1Whqp @artforum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Dylan’s Secret Archive https://t.co/scc1kVa6CT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders and the Case for a New Economic Stimulus Package https://t.co/c1uJVFOrLd via @JohnCassidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Simpsons' "Debateful Eight"! https://t.co/FvwtLDWIhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Unruly Pleasures of the Mid-Manhattan Library https://t.co/6TvgRKCetf via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Joy of Learning French, Part Deux https://t.co/TH1TtabFto via @theatlantic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always loved them! If you haven't yet: Meet the Shaggs https://t.co/ZGYOtYR9L8 via @susanorlean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary: Is Trump now unstoppable? https://t.co/R9bVY2elhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond “Infinite Jest” https://t.co/VuXcW7n7CX via @dtmax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louis C.K.’s Horace and Pete Is (Mostly) Good https://t.co/hewIsdbtwQ via @vulture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umberto Eco, 84, Best-Selling Academic Who Navigated Two Worlds, Dies, via @nytimes https://t.co/tfOq8neHo8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>