<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it say about me that I'm on the Wizard's side in "Emerald City"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call us racists all you want my dear progressives, you've made that term so devoid of meaning that no one cares anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The left is discovering to their peril that making ideas social unacceptable does not erase them from existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, that tattoo is an expression of your inner self? I guess your inner self enjoys working as a busboy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO I've written on the subject at length in my blog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reChristianization of the West is its only true hope. The secular must be desecularized. The rational replaced with the supernatural.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the left has made anything crystal clear over these last few years, it is that no compromise, no concession, will ever satisfy them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were all these brave "protestors" from Berkley when ISIS death worshiping fascists began slaughtering Christians across Iraq &amp; Syria?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the alt-right is is a symptom of the fact the modern world is broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO I normally am as well, but Glenrothes is my one exception]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO though for blends Glenrothes is excellently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO oh, that's simply mandatory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell the measure of a man by whether or not he drinks his scotch neat or on the rocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sad fact is that it is a growing reality that progressives don't wish to live with us, and we don't wish to live with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I disapprove of what you have to say, but I will defend to death your right to say it."

Whatever happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tailoring is a simple concept that too few people understand these days (hint: the sleeves of your jacket shouldn't cover your shirt cuffs)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junk food is a waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayHeard our generation already had gone to war. Does this person not remember Afghanistan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why are you making me hurt you!" https://t.co/9cqBd3BCjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srhbutts you know who uses violence to shut down free speech? Fascists. Look in the mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booked my trip to Rome for this October. What would #CRx Twitter recommend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #UCBerkley you know what real fascists do? Shut down their critics with threats of violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milo accuses the left of being intolerant and hostile to different viewpoints and they immediately prove him right by rioting #UCBerkeley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Article50 is triggered. Hooray!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In light of today's events, my column for @Poletical on the conservative case for #ERRE is a little outdated now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations dear lefties, you've been had! Turns out Justin Trudeau is an empty headed narcissist with no substance after all #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ERRE is officially dead. Dear progressives who voted for Trudeau: do you feel used?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glory be and praise the Saints, Electoral Reform is dead! #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lowly_Mouse @MPeters74 could be, and thus wouldn't be the first case of some Canadian white boy going all wannabe jihadi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPeters74 could be a convert. Or it could just be as simple as two guys going all Columbine on a mosque instead of a school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Innerfaith* bloody autocorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And CBC has confirmed the identity of the two #QuebecShooting perps. This isn't Islamophobia guys, it's interfaith violence #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a lot of details on the #QuebecShooting so far but it really doesn't look like these guys were either white supremacists or Islamophobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm seeing links to Quebec media saying the #QuebecShooting perpetrators shouted "Allah Akbar". Anything in English media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine you can be whatever you want to be! https://t.co/ttZ1lwyy6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The equation of the judiciary with the people is faulty. https://t.co/rXZqWwjIxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every generation must take up its Cross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modernity is filled with addictions meant to distract us from its emptiness: addiction to money, pleasure, and pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there are better ways to deal with the issue of terrorism than a complete travel ban. But it beats the Dems stance of "do nothing".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see the Magic Flute #Opera #GoBlackTieOrGoHome https://t.co/7bZllcvgly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how the March for Life never descends into violence and rioting, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran has banned Americans in retaliation for Trump's executive order. Americans hoping to visit Iran, all two of them, express unhappiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @POTUS should #TearUpTheIranDeal! https://t.co/eMEEueEb7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahnqir my grandparents left Russia for Canada just prior to the Great War.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahnqir my grandfather &amp; grandmother on the paternal side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau: any real rural Canadian will tell you what they need is a silly looking wool tuke &amp; a Tim Horton's travel mug #cdnpoli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau: talk to ordinary Albertans and they'll tell you what they need is six galleon hats &amp; rhinestone jeans #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau: what Atlantic Canadians really need is an illegal moonshine still in the backyard &amp; an EI cheque #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Justin Trudeau's next stop, he'll share how what Natives truly want is a hatstand for their headdresses &amp; a vanity mirror for war paint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 new unfollowers and 4 new followers (hello! hello!) in the last day. Via https://t.co/50lMuumEyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abortion is murder and you have blood on your hands. https://t.co/CVClps792X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What utter condescending tripe! https://t.co/zVQXO0UcIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hasn't mass Islamic immigration to Europe drastically raised the odds of terrorist attacks thought?" @FedericaMog #FreeSargon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Scott_ you might not like what it is, but it's there for all to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Scott_ I can recall two very detailed speeches in the last couple of months where she's plainly lain out her post-Brexit vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progressives are certain they are right, so certain in fact that they no longer feel the need to make their case to the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubinReport first they came for the gay Brits, and I said nothing, then they came for the classical liberals..... #FreeSargon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Scott_ why? PM May has clearly laid out what she hopes to achieve via Brexit. All that's left is the negotiations (which this begins)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the light of the Cross &amp; the strength of the Crown, may we be delivered from this new Dark Age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cselley been asking that since the last election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO @modestmanstyle ah, we all have our burdens to bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO @modestmanstyle it helps we really only have four levels of dress: casual, smart casual, formal, black-tie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Scott_ it is what it's supposed to be, a bill to trigger Article 50. No more, no less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Scott_ it's an enabling bill to allow Article 50 to be triggered, not a white paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO but what if I identify as an SJW despite giving the outward appearance of an anti-SJW? How anti-SJWnormative of you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phillip_Blond one day future generations will ask how so many stayed silent in the face of such injustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real women #MarchforLife2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget. Never again.
#HolocaustMemorialDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then they came for Sargon #FreeSargon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what they say, when the gods wish to punish us they answer our prayers. https://t.co/864x4RU4m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huWhiteDaily @LadyLSpeaks @GirlsOfEuropa most slave traders were other native Africans actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they say politicians don't keep their promises anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyLSpeaks @GirlsOfEuropa slavery is both unChristian &amp; also very uneconomical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LexiVictory @BreitbartNews not surprising. I remember reading some similar stats in Charles Murray's latest book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 4 new followers in the past day, courtesy https://t.co/50lMuumEyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO sure, I can ask next time we chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO yeah, I'm sure he told me once but I can't remember (his side of the family is Russo-Polish though so makes sense)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO the northern part (no clue what it's called)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessMorganTO my Dad was from Winnipeg, he keeps a list of famous &amp; successful Canadians who were born there and left as soon as they could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time ever, the left is afraid
https://t.co/vvHi7YfyoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the DOW broke 20,000 today for the first time in history. Guess we're still waiting for that Trump-induced stock market crash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time I can ever remember, progressives are not just angry, they are afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never fear a man who speaks plainly. It's the ones who smile &amp; nod you should always question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't kid yourself, fascism is just socialism with race taking the place of the worker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you truly want your legacy when you leave this world to just be that you once won Employee of the Month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will that promotion to lower management in your fifties come visit you in the seniors' home? Doubt it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does pushing paper in some office cubicle REALLY give more satisfaction than bringing new life into the world &amp; helping it come to maturity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, 95% of us will spend our lives in utter insignificance professionally speaking. So ladies, why not spend that time raising children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the clothes don't fit. Don't wear them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex is great. It's even better with your lawfully married partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne by any chance are you in favour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The modern world has lost it's taste for blood. We no longer fight wars to win them, instead we try to win hearts , &amp;  in doing so lose both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who play identity politics should be prepared to pay the price if they lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Realjmannarino sheesh, at least the lefties of old had some spine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first contribution for @TRUENORTHREPORT #cdnpoli 
https://t.co/GaYRcgVqGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan plus he sucked in the Star Wars prequels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aradwanski dear media, please stop publishing polls like this. Membership sales are really the only indicator in Cdn leadership races.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tide is beginning to turn.

https://t.co/g4CJhUjmw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So a female reporter for @TheRebelTV got punched by some lefty beta male while covering a lefty protest. Who are the real women-haters here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DennisWheatley1 @screw132 British gallantry at its finest]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>