<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's gobsmacking how many people are upset that @jk_rowling is speaking out against Trump and fascism. What books d… https://t.co/RsUsDG8XVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandycooklyn fuck em. Hope it goes well. Well done for seeking help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey geniuses at Team Trump. You don't get to pick and choose what media you engage with when you're president. https://t.co/zvEexd8F33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaAKL I mean, the long term plan was bleach hair to better use manic panic. Guess I'm going red instead of virgin snow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenitoWill oh I feel old now. My first album bought with mh pocket money was Warrant's Cherry Pie

#noregrets https://t.co/s9MRn9PKD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos good luck. Clarity is a good thing 😊 trust me. I hate having BPD but much happier knowing what is going on than not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I just spent several hours bleaching and dying my hair with blonde dye to end up... ginger. Definitely ginger… https://t.co/SpA38oMyvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I learned why hairdressers use chemical treatments to strip… https://t.co/1ETSqt3Lnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post bleach, pre dye. Oh dear. Ginger was not the aim. Yikes. https://t.co/Ajf6BNkNMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PizzaAbuser when he inevitably is impeached for abusing executive power or conflicts of interest in his business dealings, he won't be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PizzaAbuser I was thinking about this the other day. Assassinate him and he becomes a Cheeto coated martyr for the ridiculous right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Predictable but awful. https://t.co/cutRHs9uWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am having a horrible sinking feeling that bleach doesn't affect hair that is dyed dark.... Too late to back out now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelBlakema5 thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's talk about Theon. https://t.co/wU0rCox7dV @BryndenBFish @PoorQuentyn pls circulate #asoiaf #gameofthrones @LiIKimSeason_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profsarahj wtaf???? That's.... wow. That's really not good. I didn't think things would go to shit that quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZedAyySeeKay fairly sure it's intentional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My prediction? The Wall falls, the Others invade. Dolorous Edd sums it all up: "shit..." https://t.co/gWSvwdXVBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos the frequent elitism shown by upperclass male university students in MFMM at THE uni (i.e. Melb) is quite accurate. Still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos there's one shot that I'm fairly certain is the Vic Supreme Court with all the court signs covered up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Miss Fisher's house is in Parkville, not St Kilda. I cannot figure out where City South Police Station is IRL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos the offices of Women's Monthly in Away With The Fairies (S1) is Vic Trades Hall @VicUnions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos the gentleman's club in Murder Most Scandalous is actually the rear entrance of @VicParliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I love the locations - watching The Blood of Juana the Mad now (one with medical students.) This is shot at @unimelb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos can't remember which one that is https://t.co/BJ7JkGSYMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Yep! It's pretty clear by halfway through S1 that Cec + Burt are in for a penny, in for a pound because life is never dull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Yes. Phryne learns to respect the more demure ladies in the world, Dottie learns to stand up for herself and open her horizons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos very last episode, where Phryne is flying her dad back to England, Jack drives out then runs up to the plane and they snog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos they gradually stop protesting working for The Man (even if The Man is The Lady) and go along with Miss P's antics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos if you go back and watch the first episode, Cec + Burt pick up Miss Fisher as a taxi client and she continues to employ them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos trying to remember the order... have you seen the season where Phryne's Dad comes back to Melbourne and gets in strife?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Cersei's reaction to wildfire when burning the Tower of the Hand makes me think Book C would use logic of Show C re battle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos ready for married life - moving out of Miss P's house, not working anymore, being restrained and demure and all that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I love that Dottie gets slowly more and more feminist. Culminates in some brilliant stuff in S3 when Hugh pushes her to get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I know the stuff in S1 with Cec and Burt and their "red ragging" Commie buddies is on point - Nan and Pop were Commies :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos so then we have Dany the Mad Queen, Cersei killed for blowing up part of city too, and KL off the map, prob Dorne too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Dany arrives, doesn't believe that Aegon is legit, brings dragonfire to Dance and inadvertantly ignites her father's WF caches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Cersei flees to Casterly Rock. (Jaime meets her there and gets strangly.) Aegon takes city, with Dornish + Arianne as bride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Myrcella dies earlier in botched 'rescue' attempt as per Cersei's plans that Balon Swann thinks about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos when Jaime finds out, this is what pushes him to valonquar. Tommen either dies in wildfire or at hands of FrankenGregor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos yep. I think: Aegon storms KL. Cersei attempts to use wildfire in defence of Tommen, kills large portion of smallfolk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Have you seen the most recent season (S3)? THEY KISS AND OMG IT IS GLORIOUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos "I'd like to see you manage my sewing machine Hugh Collins!" 

Love it when Dottie gets all feminist on Hugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos to driving... and Phryne's reaction. 

Pretty on point for gender and sociopolitics in MFMM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos from my limited knowledge of pre-war Aus history, yes? Love the stuff like moron who thinks women are "biologically unsuited"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the US President is sacking the acting A-G for DOING HER DAMN JOB and telling him that his policies are unlawful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the A-G was condemned for his part, and has been shuffled off to an ambassadorial post (because as if #auspol does responsible govt LOL)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's put all this in context. In Aus, the Solicitor-General (Justin Gleeson SC) resigned because the Attorney-General acted above the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos cannot stop laughing at Hugh's emotional "I've burned my footy scarf sir!" So typical of the stupidity of the average Melb man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos for AFL though. Not for proper bloody football. A League has to struggle against not very thinly veiled racism - "wogball"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos it is also super, extremely Melbourne to be so caught up in drama about opposing football teams. Seriously. This place is nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's awkward compared to dying in the shower hung by the opposition's scarf?" 

Phryne putting things in perspective, as always :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethrajohnston yikes. Maybe tell her that you're not in a headspace yourself for visitors? Would she respect that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, like Miss Phryne, I'm a lapsed Collingwood supporter (until such time as they get rid of the misogynistic douchenozzle McGuire)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So? I'll just divide them up... girls for the West, boys for Abbotsford." 
"It's people like you that bring footy clubs down Dottie!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also adore this scene: "If Hugh marries me, I don't see why I should convert." "Because he'll want to take his kids to the footy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[b) the actual murder mystery is all sorts of intriguing, c) Jack's ex dramas, d) CEC + BURT C'MON...  https://t.co/IP2VBZ5mZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the reason I like "Marked for Murder" so much is that a) not much has changed with Melbourne's fervour for football since the 1920s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Miss Fisher binge is up to my favourite episode, the one with the footy dispute. "Marked for Murder." Some of Cec + Burt's best bickering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend just asked me this. I don't know? Is it? Bundarra's designs are gorgeous. @IndigenousX @mrngunnawal… https://t.co/RlcQGLxhwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb  But eventually we had Kitty Detente https://t.co/z5GFqVO2DH https://t.co/bNhLgTa5FO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb Alice was initially... not pleased about the new arrival https://t.co/S8qQkYWcTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb He was such an itty bitty kitteh when he first came home with me at 8 weeks old https://t.co/XCut6n5mvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb she's my baby. 8 years old. Bucky is 2 years old today https://t.co/PaELe8Bm42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrDTJames not taking that bet. Suspect it's the only judicial figure he is remotely familiar with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utter nonsense. Show us the receipts or STFU. https://t.co/RbYbMwQ1yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb trying to get her to stay still for one... argh. https://t.co/3793nmpcl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb I've my own fat cat. Ms Alice has a taste of gluttony - won't keep her nose of her brother's bowl, even though it makes her ill!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos also love that by S2, everyone has fallen into their roles e.g. Jack just going along with Phryne jumping off the pier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos watching S2E3 Dead's Man Chest (the one in Queenscliff with the doubloons and temperance society.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos as much as I hate the classist nature of Phryne's social peers, it is adorable to see Mr B taking the young guy under his wing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb @hpstorian @lizduckchong lovely floof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos the only problem with Euro setting is that there's no way to loop in the rest of the gang in Melbourne (e.g. Mr B, Cec, Burt..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I love that Miss Fisher is so popular throughout US and UK. Always on lists of shows to binge on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos dodgy old dad (who is hilarious) and Phryne + Jack get involved despite being on holidays...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I would love to see a Miss Fisher in Europe film. Jack follows her, Dottie and Hugh on their honeymoon, something happens with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos she has taken to being Australian like a dyke duck to water. She's marvellous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos they're apparently exploring options, like a Miss Fisher movie with Phryne in London (either as teen or adult)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos boo. This is the reason S4 MFMM isn't happening. Essie has her kids settled in UK and isn't willing to move them back for 6m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos I also absolutely adore Miriam Margoyles as the utterly posh and judgemental Aunt Prudence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos with both of them, it's the mix of good storytelling, acting and excellent production - use of Victoria's historic buildings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos Definitely one of the best shows that ABC has made in recent years, although the Dr Blake Mysteries not far behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOverRos you realise that Essie Davis is Tasmanian. ONE OF US. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A WOMAN IS DYING ON NAURU OF PRE ECLAMPSIA DO SOMETHING @TurnbullMalcolm @SenatorCash @PeterDutton_MP @ScottMorrisonMP #BringHerHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelloveslife we know pre-eclampsia kills. Border Force's failure to bring this woman to proper medical services is going to kill her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelloveslife they have an episode where woman dies of pre-eclampsia. Mum explained this was reason for her being i… https://t.co/zf3ZMCHy5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelloveslife My mum was induced because of pre-eclampsia with me. Didn't realise how serious it was until we were watching Call the Midwife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the things I love about Miss Fisher's Murder Mysteries is the way they handle 'war neurosis' (PTSD) in multiple episodes, esp S2E2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoners never achieve anything, huh? Yeah right. @kalpenn is doing awesome stuff. https://t.co/8BxUJJqx2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This woman is going to die and it is our fault. @TurnbullMalcolm do something you gormless vapid twat. https://t.co/Md0vF6GEC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A moron and a potato head. Not an ounce of leadership skills or moral fortitude between them. https://t.co/Cg84w9pByT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samishah exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous wings, eyes inspired by @mirrorsandhaze #metalmatte… https://t.co/sgC0rHayuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on this tutorial https://t.co/93UaHg9uXH But with a black lip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Miss Fisher can solve crimes in high heels, I can write essays in full goth make up. Experimenting with @KATVONDbeauty and @NyxCosmetics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anguslivingston that IGA is the greatest little supermarket ever. Heaps of awesome stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is horrible. https://t.co/RcHwrVGMGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is my right side. I'm wedged between the floofs https://t.co/3B8N4tzWpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My efforts to become less nocturnal are not being helped by my… https://t.co/M3u9XMYWvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminds me of Rob Anybody and his plan, which is to write PLN on piece of paper and then declare "Right. Now we nee… https://t.co/7nEfUlH0AE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>