<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TenNewsSydney @dailybailey10 So proud of 10 and warmest wished for the Wagga Wagga family!! xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TenNewsSydney @dailybailey10 What a fantastic thing Channel 10 did for the brave Wagga Wagga woman and her family, So proud or 10!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailybailey10 @CookIslands @TenNewsSydney What a fantastic thing  Channel 10 did for the Wagga Wagga brave woman and her family, So proud!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer Oh dear!! ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraUnited @ashsykes91 well done girls!!! âš½âš½ðŸ”lock in GF win!!ðŸ’“ðŸ’—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait come back and enjoy Canbera's heatwave....hahah xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frogsinspace Kristina was QUOTING the Washington @washingtonpost read the article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Many happy returns!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Listened to your conversation with Lou yesterday........Hobart is too far from Young during the cherry season!!!  Mxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimGavel and still doing an excellent job!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott I've got four tomatoes ..3 types, in greenhouse!! Finger crossed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott @sloaniealex glad tomatoes survived! Nic needs a sports psychologist FULL TIME on his team..twit!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott How are the tomatos going with minus temps??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wynrewardsseapr fingers crossed to win this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoldGadgets already done twice - still no delivery after 18 months....must be a sham!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGadgetFlow @BoldGadgets Waiting 18 months istoo long to wait for the delivery of 2 Bold Knot items,where's my refund or the goods please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run Away with Cirque du Soleil https://t.co/zdfDS8lHcL via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julianbabbott where's the photos of the planes Julian??!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott @sloaniealex @GibsMoore Friday AM husband and friend talking on driveway Arabana Street, when a Roo came bounding down the St]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2wgwmDVQFc booking GM5W4W - I have just purchased the water deal but no acknowledgement has been received?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait  Hey happy birthday! xx Mine was last Saturday!! Two dogs.....I'm jealous!! ðŸ•ðŸ©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait  How are you and that beautiful puppy going?  Goldie is just sooooo cute!! https://t.co/mQs8S8SDbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samanthahawley You must b talking about Canberra. ..correct that Federal Parliament!! ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott sausagss...ðŸ˜„ðŸ˜‚ should I say build a bridge.......etc!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nbn New Development Charge | the iiNet Blog https://t.co/zC9sNbngyH via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate reform - what's it all about? Check out this explainer: https://t.co/se7Lu8O0AJ via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @KimKardashian Do Americans really want Trump as President?Australians cannot believe he may be the leader of the Free World!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveKinlan @FatherBob But that doesn't make him a Saint either!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait @RadioNational Mel, I think you will make a great mother &amp; wife....someday!! xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitchell Pearce should be sacked!! What message does it send to allow him to play in Australia again after so many errors??!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidWBrown7 Why is it that the Nations capital is left of the map often when giving Capital forecasts??It's VERY disappointing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait I want her!!!  Still chewing everything??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Hello Mel, what kind of pup did you get, boy or girl &amp; what's it's name??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm Welcome to Canberra! As a 68yr old 5th generation Canberran I feel our PM should live in Canberra, thank you to you &amp; Lucy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait sure it is! Happy New Year Mel...xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Jason's efforts to fight kids' cancer. https://t.co/DnCHYSSAvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott what was the haunted  movie site u said was funny please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was the name of the haunted movie site u sais was funny please? @Margy21rob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GPforEducation: Over 1M signers stand #withMalala to fund 12 yrs of edu for all. Now is time to act. http://t.co/OJIkKlgKdJ #FundEducation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gallery http://t.co/njvwAKz7r4 via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Malcolm Turnball: 20 yo childcare worker allegedly attempts to rape a 2 yo and is l... http://t.co/gTBWaIcIpf via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl should have the right to a full 12 years of education. @GPforEducation please stand #withMalala http://t.co/L0sOaGj5UF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FatherBob looks aren't everything Fr Bob here in Canberra!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenfry @TheBumBumTrain saw u on The Project last night...good luck 4 coming Aussie tour!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASA Hope there is no VW involvement!!!??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait @ebie_hd hey Mel at Gerringong going home tomorrow thru.....Robertson!!! Might call in &amp; see ur parents....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sloaniealex @666canberra @JulianBAbbott  funny how the image you have of someone doesn't match reality! But your Okay @JulianBAbbott.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Pair of ECCO Damara Silver Sandals Worth $170 http://t.co/1vgs3BvXnr via @WomenFreebiesAU To wear on a cruise husband battling cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Pair of ECCO Damara Silver Sandals Worth $170 http://t.co/1vgs3BvXnr via @WomenFreebiesAU T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Pair of ECCO Damara Silver Sandals Worth $170 http://t.co/1vgs3BvXnr via @WomenFreebiesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus did he really have to chew gum throughout the press conference??!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help make it happen for BOLD Knot: Power Bank-Charger-Cable on a Keychain on @indiegogo http://t.co/fgJmuAkjbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinniesACT @666canberra that's what I think also....more stylish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@666canberra @FarzEdraki @Clarissa_Thorpe No...Farz by a mile.....!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sloaniealex @666canberra Vote 4 black dress but what happened to "The Hat"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deborra_lee Too big to bring to Canberra?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Hello Mel........bit wet down your parents way........they Okay? xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait  Hey...it snowed here today....melted by the time it hit the ground!!  Freezing cold though....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Hi Mel, going to Gerringong next month, do we call in and say "Mel sent us"!!?? How's Tassie going? xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoldGadgets Have you commenced delivery?  If not, when are you going to start delivery please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More expensive medicine? Ask the government what's really in the #TPP http://t.co/uNKzMEw6oY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help remove the corrupt and dishonourable Speaker of the House - Bronwyn Bishop https://t.co/q1vitSiV1i via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealHughJackman @Deborra_lee Great photo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing! Sleepover at North Bondi Surf Club #airbnb #nightat https://t.co/F5f4eDbrXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Independent review underway, though fight far from over! https://t.co/vv1dinpGqj via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds great! https://t.co/ps8VbAnGtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best bacon in Australia in 2015 is from Pialligo Estate in Canberra -  http://t.co/plTnVIULMc via @goodfoodAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tackling climate change effectively means no new coal mines can be built: New @climatecouncil report http://t.co/d6N8YDrWg6 #galileebasin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Did I see you among the MAD frozen  nude swimmers???!!! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait @GawkyMedia Hey Mel - passed thru Robertson this arvo on our way to Wollongong....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just passed by the Big Potato!!ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸŒŸâ­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Robertson on our way to friends Art Exhibition in Wollongong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait spelling should be "count"!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait cheer up Mel you are not that far away. ....close if you cpunr social media!  ðŸ’•ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimGavel might be a different story full time Tim?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Oh no!! You mean I won't hear you any more on 666.....boohoo!!  Glad 4 you though!! written any more plays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait How long r u in Tas? Pete's kidney removed 4 weeks ago massive cancer found by accident, annual blood test recovering well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Please Pope Francis give Australia a Cardinal we can respect in place of George Pell URGENTLY!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Hello Mel, my goodness you get around....how long in Hobart? You must like the cold??!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBAbbott Husband asks what's the cost of such a trip Julian?  We are sitting by the radio with laptop enjoying your trip!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canberratimes what about aged pensioners...
Tony?????!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Williams_297 speedy recovery Sam...fantastic game!  ðŸ˜Šâ˜ºðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call on the government to #ReleaseTheText of this top secret trade agreement before it's too late http://t.co/uNKzMEw6oY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCoffeeEvents @SasaSestic canberra the BEST PLACE IN THE WORLD!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton As a 67year old white Australian I cannot understand the white treatment of Black Americans especially white law enforcement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimGavel @Margy21rob @TimGavel let's hope both teams - Brumbies &amp; Raiders continue on their winning ways! Hello to Jen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimGavel  Will the Raiders win Tim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersCanberra @TimGavel Will they win Tim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersCanberra @TimGavel Go the Raiders!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessfeato @NRL @AlburyCity @SeaEagles @RaidersCanberra Go the Raiders!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nosdrachir49 @abcnewsNT @abcnews I live in Canberra &amp; can assure you lying is in Tony Abbott's DNA!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help make it happen for 'Flow Hive: Honey on Tap Directly From Your Beehive' http://t.co/6mZWvNrRSN #indiegogo via @indiegogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've signed up to ninemsn email alerts and entered to win a trip to New York to the value of $20,000! Click to enter http://t.co/C9jQadY1GO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-Course Dinner with a Bottle of Wine https://t.co/08Mp9AjRJn via @LivingSocial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mamamia @JamilaRizvi Sorry! I did mean to wish you all the best for your future life together!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mamamia @JamilaRizvi Bet Abul was a very proud father!! Hope he is keeping well........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait hope 2015 brings you the rewards you deserve,  health &amp; contentment!  Margy &amp; Peter ðŸŽ­ðŸŽ‰ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieTait Merry Christmas Mel &amp; have a great, safe 2015 Margy &amp; Peter xxðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayers for the Syd CBD hostages!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanberraUnited W-League - Great win Girls!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>