<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun walk with Kaitlyn Olson-Demarse this afternoon, sometimes the snow can be beautiful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know this will cause lots of drama but this is why I don't like bacon!!! see pigs are cute.... bacon is bad!!! https://t.co/oHbNVyehC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[roads cleared back to my plans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which 80's rock band are you? https://t.co/jnfMK0bU9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to have Anika on my team!!!! https://t.co/uGf4sdavzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning issued after convicted sex offender Jeffrey Goddard moves to Surrey https://t.co/qfRvWNTynX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 days only...dont miss this deal https://t.co/DxNW6PPdlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who wants to do this???? https://t.co/ibjRfSmy6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing deals this month!! Valentines special 5 tinted lip balms in a decorative box for $79 (until Feb 10) AND... https://t.co/H94re451kT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone with siblings - make this your status 

1. Who had the best grades? I think it was me....
2. Who was... https://t.co/wjUCNMuw31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This breaks my heart. What is wrong with this world? If this happened to my boys.... I dont know what I would do :( https://t.co/hhESB4lxgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New party just started today! https://t.co/6moVooJmYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiz: Only 1 In 50 People Can Identify These 16 Grammar Mistakes. Can You? https://t.co/AYZovjVbOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Year 2017 Party! https://t.co/TUrLT4mW1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which 5 Letters describe you? https://t.co/oaFqOQfRqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game! Not the outcome I wanted but exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good words to follow https://t.co/kPEmJtRp5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to party! 10 days to get your orders in! This months Kudos will sell out fast https://t.co/Zs7GrJV54X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$119 and all this is yours! Plus when you own a home business you can use it at tax time!!! Join now! https://t.co/d2z4y7oJHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Years!!! Got to ring in the new year with all my favorite people (a few missing). Hope you all had a great one too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 3 of my cold and still in bed!!!Please please go away, it is NYE tomorrow!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most amazing Christmas with the O'Reilly - Houle family. Thank you for having us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to spending Christmas with our other family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to all our friends and family. Hope you all have an amazing Christmas and new years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ugly Christmas sweater day at work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last party before Christmas and NYE!! Order now and get 3 day shipping for only $11.  There are some excellent... https://t.co/nHBqUwUnVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's a perfect storm': Surrey Christmas Bureau short on donations https://t.co/1blJeuvQY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016 https://t.co/sv4lQHRXwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016 https://t.co/1MoSNhy9sA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/nnhmMpUbZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the boys live the snow lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks amazing, who wants to do this??? https://t.co/7xigKXDJ3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this party only 3 days left.  2 orders placed and I have 3 half price items and $108 shopping... https://t.co/sVYm3xa5pj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh heated matress pad I think I love you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BB cream perfect if you want a light moisturizing foundation. https://t.co/BTlnXZ9dUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "WP-POM Christmas Party 2016" https://t.co/ZbJSsULCUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas party tonight...so much to do today!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TGIF!!!!!! So unbelievably exhausted! Not sure how I am going to get through today on 4 hours of sleep!  Will be... https://t.co/qhQrYHWoPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning!!! Now is the time to have your own online party!! All parties between Dec 1-14 will receive double... https://t.co/8kGpz9VtVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Binge watching Gilmore girls is done and all I can say is.....how can you end it like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 days of bundles... new one each day and only on sale for 24hrs! starts at noon today https://t.co/ahpaHfrlU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 shopping days!!! order now for Christmas https://t.co/hFTINug3Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[woke up with only a little sore throat, thank god that nightmare is over!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day! I am always so careful not to expose myself to things I am allergic to, but some how something got... https://t.co/vo4YYGgX0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 3 days left to get in on this party!!! https://t.co/D8nK0JAGxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's party time! https://t.co/JgAXyDy7Fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happpy Monday!!! Lets get this party started! https://t.co/roVlYlZ80h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look what came today!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[best husband in entire world!!! Rick Demarse thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for new presenters for my team! 20% instant commission on all sales (including your own). Kit is $119 and... https://t.co/XnrjYdWsCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOO HOO new products, new party!!!! Splash lipstick is here! https://t.co/VLf7LjFtu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at the mall with Kaitlyn Olson-Demarse watching her apply for jobs! happy mom moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is your life quote? https://t.co/3Lsj4XPBG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all my friends who want to join me for a paint nite... Groupon has a deal right now, one class for $25 and if... https://t.co/H6m3picmi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing weekend in Portland, Oregon so much fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Story of my life these days!!!! https://t.co/EZ3zEtb04C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kaitlyn Olson-Demarse grad photos tonight.... really... I cant believe she is really in grade 12! Where did the time go :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New party started! New products avail!!!! check it out https://t.co/7OYuWGehZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Demarse Kaitlyn Olson-Demarse know any dogs like this???? https://t.co/vRZgB20voU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as always an amazing night out with Rick Demarse and Jennifer J Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg Keith Urban tonight! Can't wait to see him and Dallas Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday Oct 9.... Delta pub. I think this will be my next paint day, who would like to join me?? it is my bday... https://t.co/9IKJ6xe1cV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 2 days left to get in on this party! I am also looking for people who want to start their own business! This... https://t.co/FSQxnDp0fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running out of days on this party! Instant lifting serum is the kudos but all products are avail on the party....... https://t.co/MTFZbajzTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 6 days left to get in on this party! INSTANT lifting serum!!! https://t.co/e0gnHwh2lO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[off on a date with my love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG love the instant lift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[beautified https://t.co/txro9Nswx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new website up and running https://t.co/XPD7OSe0v3 https://t.co/4sE7Y4uQ3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautified !!!!!  https://t.co/5G6TTuCvnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/EFVQergtSp

New party! just need to sell 69 3d... https://t.co/ZdOSVQV5vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for people to join my team! $119 gets you a ton of make up, website, and instant royalties! 20% of all... https://t.co/rgkIqrRVbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Party Day 2! Just came last night and I tried it out! wow, you can feel it right away!
It is worth every cent!... https://t.co/RXhQCTA4xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use to be stressed..... now I paint ... and wow I feel at peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sept 1 and the start of an amazing month of deals!!! this one... Instant lifting serum! $78 plus you get $18... https://t.co/HJ0IPIMn1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What 4 people hate me!! I dont think I can go on... who are they we need to fix this lol https://t.co/s3r8LillFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got: Left Brain: 25% Right Brain: 75%. Left Or Right Brain Test https://t.co/HJiQG5pO9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My goals for Sept! Join my team! We all love good quality make up..... why not get paid to wear it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ahhh first run since nerve damage!  very slow but I did it!   I promised Rick Demarse I would start slow and work... https://t.co/Ea2aLJTerf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only need 45 more points to make this party a success! That means I need you! Only one 3D mascara and and eye... https://t.co/vMLPPaeAAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shamrocks vs Maple ridge Friday 6pm..... Who's in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hello friends.... company I work for is looking for a receptionist... mon-fri 8-430. Must have some office... https://t.co/YrDpyeY6hV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aug Kudos is almost over! The colors are amazing and it is to support a great cause.  At $72 you cant go wrong...... https://t.co/GkwHIN3koT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what I got today!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay I dont want to jinx it since in is still early on Sunday... but what an amazing weekend! 

Lacrosse game... https://t.co/NLtlfwKSus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in this one? It is Thursday Sept 15 @ 7pm in Coquitliam at Char 631....34 tickets still available! https://t.co/Kqy1lzcz1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome day painting with Barbette Kaiser!!!  So much fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hmmmm left phone at home...... pm me if you need to otherswise will talk to you all later!  

OH... anyone want... https://t.co/EouBxWbGeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[only one day left to get in on this party! This is a great bundle to help support the children! Please buy https://t.co/dsfoXfnYee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One ticket left if anyone wants to join me this Saturday! https://t.co/dbmjWsV52U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this would be a good one...  Wednesday night.. https://t.co/iG4w8CQd6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2tVj7QB6Jn

Who doesnt want big beautiful lashes?????... https://t.co/7pekZYYd9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should do this to Kaitlyn!!! https://t.co/wWJQKKdwkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn your face shape and how to apply blusher correctly https://t.co/MWmTOEug6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please come and like my page :) https://t.co/SSnhVUed9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[August Kudos: Defend Innocence

One in five children is sexually abused before age 18. 
This is unacceptable.... https://t.co/EJaI9EcfWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[traveling to Vancouver, British Columbia from Toronto Pearson International Airport https://t.co/w2wyjs73aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new Quebec friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started with the Jeep! Then moved to the  minivan :-( thank God I am going home tomorrow!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>