<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@iParanormal_TV Sup with you big dog still rockin the IT game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iParanormal_TV Smokin weed and filmin vids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskWWENetwork Appreciate the reply, guys. Emailed them 3 biz-days ago and no response :'( Got any extra codes layin around there for me? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskWWENetwork signed up for 30 day free trial, locked out of account, charged $14 to bank account. Missed both ppvs this weekend. 0/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The For Honor Beta failed to interest me. 
The game seems very generic. I'm also tired of playing games with grinding/laning phases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at this unreal Gamecube @ #genesis4 by @borzooka https://t.co/8IcYjvAjxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanesmith30 if you pen adam curtis for a few feature docus, I will fucking shit my dick off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KinsZilla Hey I would like to own that instead so please bring it here so I can play it and you can watch THANKS, K.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Camd0zer "Is my car door locked?" Rips off door handle "Nope, fucken frozen."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bennet_Lim Been there buddy. You're a good dude %100. It'll happen,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horace once said "Rule your mind or it will rule you." 
Advice that has transcended time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRbeia Anxiety has your mind racing- your thoughts aren't as rational. Hurry up and wait. ): Hate it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSMsemphisss a bank account going from $5 to $0.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unkleofficial Quick question: Unklesounds Edit - Rabbit in Your Headlights. What is the guitar melody sampled in the beginning? Obsessed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh trevvy with the hot music choice on this fashion piece https://t.co/gEguv1c2LJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickyLumpkin Sorry to hear you're going through that, Rick. Our trials and tribulations ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rootkovska love the work you guys at Qubes are doing! It has interred my curiosity into the realm of internet security]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicahamburg I'd have said "the sound effects"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turtle40000 dlc are expansion packs if you think about it. But not released on day 1 lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cant wait for this dlc era of gaming to be over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheUltraLex I put on O Tannenbaum by the Vienna Choir Boys and pretended I was in a die hard traiker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarah_StarLight I want to be "the place"!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirScoots Well written! Good read. Interested to see how this further develops. Perhaps an arbitration? Ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EasyModeAj Thanks taking a look now. Waiting until next year to buy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EasyModeAj interesting, how long do they last usually? Why do they break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustmouret Haha undoubtedly. Meant more society in general. Really is fascinating to identify when it happens !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone done any 3D printing? I imagine the stuff you could make would be awesome -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustmouret You'll quickly learn in the coming years that perception is stronger than truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mauroranallo Snow is just finally melting here in Abbotsford. Merry Christmas Mauro- yesterday's Smackdown was LIT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakzeh Have you looked into network rendering at all? Looks pretty shweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynnieNoquez my favorite is when an open teams loses to a female team and they disband HAHAHAHAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love when I leave a render a whole night just to wake up and find I rendered in the wrong frames per second...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLGhazed success is just corrected errors over time breh~ stick with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobleLLumiya smoke weed and stay in corner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EasyModeAj YES THIS IS DOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KinsZilla its poetry so be in the mood!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KinsZilla Ever read Even This Shall Pass Away by Theodore Tilton? Always helps me carry on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobleLLumiya I dont want to live on this planet anymoree plz stop by any time after 1230 ill have my ppl call yours arrange killing ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo: @nickthiessen @ PNE/Playland https://t.co/9LaFKv9XZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobleLLumiya 2016 nothing surprises me anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredNurke @Sportsnet @Shawhelp gotta protect that lucrative TV curling deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sadokist I've been playing a lot of PCars Go Kart mode. its like deathmatching your apexes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard is an angry young man, today! :@ (6)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vansilli dooope. If you wanna blaze one and goto East is East or cannibal cafe lets make it a date!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spotted at a skatepark, 
built inside a tunnel, 
undernearth a highway. https://t.co/Bt4jfCHi83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From CS teammates 10 years ago to artists today. Unbreakable. https://t.co/OrWHKjRMN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidOtunga fly piece on the wrist tonight buds #bringgoldback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everyone on tinder named megan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfriesen I miss my old menno church sometimes ):]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilsonwteng Robert Shaw Chorale. "Christmas hymns and carols" and "a festival of carols" albums]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[%100 win rate on rocket league when listening to church choir christmas caroles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoPro needs to get into the dashcam game to rebound from the job cuts they just had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losing an entire day to sleep has to be one of the shittiest feelings ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some headphones? -- Taken from our '16 Show Reel https://t.co/64zJdtnbex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NRG_ptr You're a good d00d ptr! Certainly taking some time to collect your thoughts will be beneficial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boq_TV @Rantopadgaming @Tistergaming prove me wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassiedwn new tindy fashooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love this season https://t.co/g65pckQ42Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the trump knee jerk reaction anger is over already? ):]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeviathanLoL @RLewisReports YOUR HONOUR COMMANDS IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KYAN1TE People without windows in their echo chambers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else feel like CNN was drawing out the calling of states for the ad revenue? lol Called the election as Trump was walking on stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameSpuh National Treasure: Meme Map to the Whitehouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Read all about future announcements in my outbox" John Podesta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crymmusic I dont even know where im spending next week. Ill hit up katie too dont tell my mom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crymmusic tru. I trusted you to smoke me up when you visited ):]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians got the luxury box suites for this election. Bring the entrées!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant wait to see the viewership and social media analytics tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like im watching the soundbytes that will be in documentaries to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I PVR'd this election earlier so I already know who wins. I can promise that half of you will be pissed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have playoff-hockey level nerves right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win or lose this Donald Trump victory speech is going to be unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Big lead" - CNN reporting on a county with %1 of the votes counted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLGhazed [toxicity intensifies]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont watch baseball but this Edwards Jr guy looks cool as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sprawll Agreed, CS is a part of the soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westworld is %100 going to take it's place as flagship show on HBO after Game of Thrones wraps up in the next couple years. Incredible show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boq_TV Agreed. If it was a really long haul stream I'd usually sit for ecos or stompings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sadokist the new planking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sprawll Back on the WoW train eh Chadsy some habits die hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boq_TV I really enjoy standing while I cast. It also helps me project my voice deeper and I feel like I can take in more air/easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheUltraLex sorry to hear that alex doemestic violence is a shitty situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moxietv that is an excellent photo! wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sadokist @NedlohESEAtv @GriffinBenger @espn that guy was in connector griff woulda really started goin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[distracted by a cool map for 25 minutes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames Where can I get a high res version of the Japanese poster? Would look incredible hanging from my wall https://t.co/mOW65CfcQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know words.
I have the best words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearllycee going outdoors is overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that one sour teammate tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESL One NY with 6million uniques and 122m impressions. Very nice work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LexWFX this tweet could definitely use some punctuation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drex @NPR This has devolved way past "facts". https://t.co/44PLLzrbTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamikaziKitten Watching it is my guiltiest of pleasures. What can I say, I'm a fan of pro-wrestling style feuds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamikaziKitten so what Canadians arent good enough now huh, Isabelle? &lt;:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By far, this US election is going down in history. Whitehouse Wrestlmania #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very fortunate to work with the amazing people at monstercat! Shoutout to the TV in the lobby that's going to show… https://t.co/1Ygs3pqZLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sadokist Any Great Big Sea on there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can light up a club... but the real question is can they frag? @EminenceUnited https://t.co/uuidY1LAjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how long until nextflix adds a tiered system to their subscription service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NedlohESEAtv Agreeeeed. And they get the benefit of hype by creating more demand for tickets]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>