<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieEresman in all seriousness, I appreciate that you, unlike some right-wingers, don't leap to utter nastiness at the first opportunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieEresman everyone needs to eat your food's food if they want to take a shit more than once a month (that's me lightening up)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieEresman scarf &gt; openly proclaimed desire to eat other humans with whom you disagree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MelanieEresman that's funny, because I was asking myself if I was supposed to take a self-proclaimed wannabe vegan-eater seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieEresman tell that to the Chinese, who just cancelled 103 coal plants. The majority of the world/97% of scientists disagree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MelanieEresman that's a bit rich coming from someone advocating that we continue to burn fossil fuels until we can't breathe anymore...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelanieEresman the platitudes of someone who is unwilling to exchange a little inconvenience for the greater good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you describe yourself as wanting to "eat a vegan," you are not to be taken seriously. https://t.co/Zae7jUcVP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MelanieEresman the world will be underwater in a few decades, but as long as AB doesn't have a carbon tax, everything will be fine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood sorry, I should have been more specific: https://t.co/JfCAy5DGJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood your assumptions are, again, wrong. Carbon pricing isn't a bad policy, nor is it broadly unpopular. https://t.co/uqpxxncBnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood yes, the ultimatum that was irrelevant to the majority of Canadians bc they already live in jurisdictions that price carbon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood that's all fine and good, but the premise of my original tweet is Scheer's promise of a repeal rings totally hollow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood see, I can screenshot too! https://t.co/SzZldGMyiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood and the feds mechanism won't kick in until 2018. AB's plan was in the works long before that. Again, know your stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood those four provinces all adopted some form of carbon pricing before the feds got involved. Know your stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Henwood you're dead wrong. ON/QC/BC/AB alone constitute the majority of our population and weren't forced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewscheer except most Canadians will still be living in provincial jurisdictions that price carbon. This is smoke and mirrors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of @DrEricHoskins, who's spent his entire adult life supporting the vulnerable. This is the right thing to do. https://t.co/bGQBdWcx38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to my boy @channydang, incoming @westernssc president! We always knew you were on your way to great things. #voteusc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red team, three years running. Congratulations @tulktome and team on an amazing win! #voteusc #WesternU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope aliens are watching the ridiculous theatrics of #GroudhogDay, recognize us as an inferior species, invade, and save us from Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump has the potential to be one hell of a @CivGame leader in a future instalment. Starting next to him on a map would be the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophhelpard @lindseefperkins "what happens on this campus doesn't matter if you're waiting at the bus stop" omg flawless, iconic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ImWithHer --&gt; @sophhelpard @lindseefperkins &lt;-- #ImWithHer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile Donna, I really, really hope this isn't true. Democrats can't skip practices and still excel on game day. Fight, always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proudly donated to the @ACLU and @HRC tonight. If you, like me, are sick of this shit, then you should donate, too. #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dissent and the upholding of the constitution in the face of tyranny is not "betrayal." Beyond disgusted with Bannon's nazi administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is on fire and everything is horrible hahahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no no No nO NO. Progressives need to stop being such wusses and fight back at EVERY opportunity. EVERY. ONE. https://t.co/ES3uncuPzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Muslim rhetoric has life-and-death consequences. We need to stop being casual/flippant about hate. Hate kills. https://t.co/kCBPmvoRG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellieLeitch you continue to find new and sickening ways to demonstrate your inhumanity and repugnance. Shame on you, Kellie Leitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FACT: Muslims are the number one victims of terror and war in the Middle East. https://t.co/ZCc33aJ9hU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When conservatives wonder why everyone paints them with the same disdainful brush, look no further than your own. https://t.co/BIGiRufJg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crooked Conrad has been writing gag-inducing gush pieces about Trump for ages because he loves his billionaire buds. https://t.co/zG95yPOzVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the compassionate, love-of-life attitude in that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-lifers create poverty by forcing teenagers to keep unwanted pregnancies, but are opposed to social assistance for the poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ArleneDickinson was always my favourite dragon, but she's quickly becoming one of my favourites. Period. https://t.co/71KLDIezQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The application was passed from intern to confused intern, as all of State's senior staff quit earlier in the day https://t.co/yIzoWZA8Gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily reminder that progressives need to stop playing nice with people who aren't nice: https://t.co/TPTa8NWJsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is Jeremy Corbyn on the verge of having no one left to replace rebellious shadow cabinet ministers with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allieadamo that's because what people want to hear doesn't always equal reality. In student politics, personable &gt; competent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allieadamo careful my darling, you might end up with a B- in your end of the year report card for being too "standoffish"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Of course it is happening inside your head, Harry, but why on earth should that mean that it is not real?” #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westernu I know -- we worked on it together for a whole year! Very excited about all the positive changes, esp. the WEC. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of my MH heroes are the staff in @westernuWSS, many of whom I've seen drop everything to support a student in crisis. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is for you guys! ^^ @teamdibrina @teamjanmohammad @VoteTeamTobi #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice: learn the intricacies. What's funded, for how much &amp; why. Map the gaps. Know the frontline staff on a first-name basis. #WesternU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The incoming @WesternUSC exec has a responsibility to learn the MH system at #WesternU so they can help students navigate, expedite cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I trained up on MH first aid, alertness, and suicide intervention. If you want, you can too: https://t.co/uA22gPlwWe #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to learn to detect distress or how to intervene in a potential suicide? Check out these programs: https://t.co/uA22gPlwWe #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a friend discloses their mental illness to you, you don't need to know what to say. You just need to listen and care. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met @clarahughes at #WesternU last year. Her story inspired me that day, and her leadership continues to inspire me today! #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carepinglo I know I keep checking as if there's an actual notification but it's just accounts I don't wanna follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who say, "let's look at what she did to invite the violent online abuse. That's the real story" are repugnant and clueless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Neo-nazi punched*: "The left is disgusting! Violence is never the answer!"
*Female leader harassed*: "Give ppl a break, they're just mad."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top comment says "people when angry say things they should not." Funny. If you were the target of online violence, would you be so flippant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top comments on this are abhorrent, too. You don't get to tell someone to kill themselves because you're mad at them https://t.co/n0G7vjEtEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reaching out to someone struggling can change the course of their lives; I've seen it happen. So reach out, and help out. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigMacBride going to get you this for next Christmas or a birthday or something https://t.co/0jN7EO4lSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I won the election. I am legitimate. Also, millions of people voted illegally. All of them for Hillary. No investigation. Thank you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perpetuating this ridiculous myth harms the administration's case that he is unquestionably legitimate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny for people fuming over concerns about Trump's legitimacy to question the integrity of the election he won. https://t.co/VcExLIkb0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic and hypocritical, considering that Trump himself uses cheap Chinese steel in his buildings. https://t.co/Oy3R8STyrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noticing that @KellieLeitch has a pattern: bold tweet, big idea, little logical rationale, and no context. https://t.co/M8PvBC20z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says the man pledging to kill a trans rights bill https://t.co/SYmy77nDxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The line between spin and lying is not a thin one. #SpicerFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's @CanadianForces night at the ACC. Great time to thank a service person for their dedication! #LeafsVsSens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One VP candidate hates LGBT people; the other officiates their weddings. America picks the first guy. https://t.co/QzOUfGd8Jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is truly no downward limit to the lows these cretins will stoop to. https://t.co/1mh43HPkBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna spend the next few years looking at my watch being like "is it 2020 yet"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God have mercy on us all. https://t.co/3UuVc1E85M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoeBiden is literally taking the train home. We'll miss you, Amtrak Joe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellieLeitch behave like what, the government of a sovereign nation with its own interests? Honestly Kellie, you haven't got a clue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On what must be one of the hardest days of her life, @HillaryClinton showed up for duty. Proud of her. #Inauguration https://t.co/V2aipxVLwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to remember that the Wellness Centre came together in 8 months. Cool things can and do happen in one year. https://t.co/nr1oH3pyfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration day has all the fixings for a million-man lynch mob. https://t.co/mYMbBVWKJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must watch: @ArleneDickinson's scathing indictment of Kevin O'Leary as a potential PM. #DraftArlene https://t.co/VuapTUgEEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone, businessman or otherwise, who commits to a 50% increase in the GDP growth rate is lying and hoping you know nothing about economics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know where to start with this nonsensical, brain cell-killing video. https://t.co/fjG7jqBcZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In addition to this being poorly written, it's also a gross misrepresentation of our economy and fiscal prospects. https://t.co/MjumeMW80p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be wary of businessmen who say they're going to bring back jobs. Chances are, they spent their entire adult lives tapping into cheap labour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if this week wasn't already going to be apocalyptic enough. https://t.co/ZNfR0Q7kk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As another @WesternUSC election season kicks off, sending best wishes to all the candidates! It takes a lot to step up and run. #westernu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guydebort this perfectly captures my experience at the dinner table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessaseager Also, at least 8 of those letters have nothing to do with education. PC, MP, OOnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessaseager not inherently, no. But Kellie Leitch is a member of a privileged group trying to pretend that she's not to gain votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And each of those letters is an indication that you are part of the elite you claim to so despise. Fraud. https://t.co/Ktu2ZN3fbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This advice stinks of condescension. Older people banking on millennials being stupid, shallow, and ill-informed. https://t.co/PzVlfS1ze0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For only the fourth time in as many presidencies, it is being awarded with distinction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS just surprised @VP Joe Biden by awarding him the last Presidential Medal of Freedom of his presidency. Crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fortunate to live in a county where my government thinks I'm worth the money it costs to keep me alive and healthy. #ACARepeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton has graciously faded into the background and allowed Trump to lead unabated. He's still attacking her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I somehow doubt that Donald Trump is capable of scheduling secret meetings no one on his staff knows about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod Operation Valkyrie, hopefully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's something perverse about Trump saying he's doing Democrats a favour by killing the #ACA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump just admitted that he boldfaced lied when he said he would release his taxes if elected. Jokes on anyone who believed him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump thinks that Putin liking him is a good thing. It's not; Putin only likes people he can take advantage of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT SHOULDN'T HAVE ENTERED PAPER LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This news conference forgot to take its adderall.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>