<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This what happens when Supply drops 50% ! and yes it's hard to believe in Toronto with all those cranes but it's tr… https://t.co/7bdftk4b7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Bay Street Corridor, in the last 2 months, Sales up 20% vs last year while Inventory dropped 61% = Prices u… https://t.co/nsHJp5UoJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Waterfront Communities in last 60 days, Sales up 30% y/y while Inventory dropped 52% = prices rise 18.2% y/… https://t.co/flSXFzBxMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downtown #Toronto (C01) in January = 345 Condos Sold, with only 302 Listings = drives bidding wars, Price/Sales Rat… https://t.co/tht2zh7tLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto January Real Estate Sales up 12% to 5,188 with only 5,034 Active Listings (down 50%) = sent prices up 22% = Boomers Aging in Place?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January Toronto Condo Sales up 27% with prices up 15%, in Central Toronto 897 Sales with just 737 now Listed! biddi… https://t.co/qn6p8Zait8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you need when you online shop ? a credit card !  VISA new high $V $MA $AMZN https://t.co/1M2oLZPFIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised Productivity numbers have been weak =  Experienced Boomers leaving the workforce, replaced by ine… https://t.co/kDmc0N0YxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprisingly Condos prices are starting to play catch up in Toronto #torontorealestate https://t.co/lXoGKMe1tY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Hiddleston wears the House’s suiting for the new Gucci Tailoring campaign. https://t.co/lzyZMrCcPR via @Gucci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2009 and Q2 2016 both market bottoms. https://t.co/x1dvpU0hKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the 70s when the Boomers started forming households, with mostly US made products inflation went crazy.  Outsour… https://t.co/YlQDVax9IF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This what happens when manufacturing jobs leave and service jobs takeover https://t.co/YP6k6hN6f4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Retail Continues to Polarize as Stores Close, and Luxury Grows - the mid market is squeezed out https://t.co/67ZmlHn1Oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zerohedge FAKE NEWS: Beware, igores inflation... no kidding in the 80's when inflation was significantly high, income growth was too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to raise gasoline taxes! I don't think the Feds have done so since 1994. https://t.co/P9GAjV0tpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[361 sq feet - if this was a hotel room I would think it was small. But it's a studio apartment $449k #toronto #condo https://t.co/fkSnOLe7v8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is the bathtub really next to the kitchen ?? chop your vegetables while in the tub  #CrazyLayouts #RealEstate https://t.co/uHSWsUBJ48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marijuana shops are trying to look like the Apple stores https://t.co/2xrupo7nlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Schedule a tour immediately, condos like this sell on avg in 5 days.
Expect to bid higher.
50% have sold over asking" #torontorealestate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zerohedge yes a weak pound has done wonders for U.K. Exporters and loads of foreign shoppers on Oxford Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucows continues to push higher after last weeks acquisition of eNom $NAME. Under followed TSX name $TC.CA $TCX… https://t.co/w2rcKGRVnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Homebuilding ETF hits a new 52 week high $ITB https://t.co/uBkZgF4yKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Chemical are you wearing ? Great questions ask at the next  #Oscars https://t.co/JhKbaDu9Ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist user pay - on highways and airports more coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security -- a top priority of the new administration and the Banks !   $HACK ETF  #MAGA $XLF https://t.co/qtOmZ2ad31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After moving sideways for two years, are US Homebuilders finally going to get their groove back ?  $ITB $XHB https://t.co/Xw95xhqWmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at the start of new cycle the p/e ratios always look high. https://t.co/2yXLuVljyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai's Azadi Jewellery's 1st North American Store opens in Toronto's Shops of Don Mills [3D Photo Tour] https://t.co/gFe6tFeAVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boeing = Global Travel in a long-term up trend = Spending on Experiences with 3.4% yield to boot !  Nice quarterly… https://t.co/9mZ9EEzKNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will the retail investor come back to the Stock Market ?  $SPY $QQQ https://t.co/3g1U9qDDM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in Toronto, new Condo Completions for 2016 were only 17,538 down 47% from the from 2015 = lack of supply = GTA Dec.… https://t.co/lvYDgRMIep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downtown Toronto Office Vacancy Plunges To 4% = more workers = more demand for condos  #TorontoRealEstate https://t.co/mzX54gXCi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the main reasons Home Inventory is so low... boomers are aging in place, I expect the trend to Continue $ITB… https://t.co/3770vR50gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes some money flowing back into FANG stocks and technology $GOOGL $FB $TXN $AMZN $NFLX $AAPL $AMAT https://t.co/HCocFqtWhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The market is/was desperate for a new theme, any theme that doesn't involve Fed Watching $SPY $QQQ #trumptrade https://t.co/frjD6ZVHFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet Shares Could Top $1,000 in Year, Barron’s Says  https://t.co/DoQtYDNc3V via @BarronsNext $GOOG $GOOGL $QQQ new high today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely one of my Favorite  #realestate  blogs for #whistler   -- https://t.co/azMiRoW2rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ting's parent Company Tucows = New High today $TCX $TC.CA https://t.co/dVsnhK5jEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ting says existing city networks accelerate FTTH builds https://t.co/9k8aSd8JFI Two Canadian Companies working together $TCX $TC.CA $LTE.CA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Which show is better: Parks and Recreation or The Office?” the vote is close 

https://t.co/JqfCmKhnaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Properties linked to Malaysian money scandal sells in Beverly Hills, amongst many more. Love it https://t.co/LdEk4Xc2dM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California housing market posts solid performance in 2016, Lack of Inventory  https://t.co/XK1GOEAv3M via @RealEstateRama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zerohedge using your own data, it tripled from 1991 to 2007]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Week Tonight Season 4 Promo https://t.co/lrMqfoUrrD via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel Industry Eager to Partner with the Trump Administration https://t.co/dy05GCzQbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes the US Leading Indicators turned up in March 2016 - and the markets have been up ever since. https://t.co/9eF65P1Xqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gucci Wool a-line coat - as worn by Kellyanne Conway #InaugurationDay    https://t.co/Wi3ioMMXmr via @Gucci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anxiously awaiting Mr.President's first official tweet !  @realDonaldTrump @POTUS #InaugurationDay https://t.co/0xJDiHSQC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US ECRI Weekly Leading Indicators up 12.0% annualized, still very strong $SPY $QQQ $TLT  https://t.co/iuVAGrpyI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucows Acquires eNom &amp; Becomes World's 2nd Largest #Domain Registrar $TCX $TC.TO = new 52 week high, up 15% https://t.co/4GmBhEfusb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic Blue Hawaii - to a great earnings season - Cheers ! https://t.co/HZQUdUQl7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMEX card member spending grew 7% in Q4  ROE was 26% - 2016 full year eps $5.65 vs $5.05 adjusted $5.93 or less 13x p/e  $AXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Comic: After years of central bank dominance https://t.co/DIxn7CPkm7 The Market needed a new theme, that didn't involve Fed Watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Mid 1960s you say ? that's when the Boomers were in their 20's and renting and now Millennials are renting !… https://t.co/7VHJiCM3qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when people bought DVD's or rented them ! Digital Services and GDP  and Netflix $NFLX 

https://t.co/dyNmWLc8TH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix, just another thing Consumers are Buying, that is NOT in Retail Sales - careful what you track esp given Target's Miss $TGT $NFLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's would be over $1000 a share if $NFLX hadn't split 7 for 1 !!   Love it. https://t.co/JqTMmB6huZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Streaming,  Hulu opens beta testing of live TV service - $NFLX $AAPL $GOOGL $FB https://t.co/T5uBNrHDu6 via @TheStreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is waving adios to the longstanding ‘strong dollar policy’  $DXY https://t.co/bTGIAExPT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[410 Euclid Ave. https://t.co/mg8vh2VpYy an awesome Lifestyle Video to help sell an Elegant Townhome in Toronto $3.188MM #TorontoRealEstate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the California drought improves, reminds me of the turn around in the Great Lakes water levels, after hitting re… https://t.co/WIgl48x4nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marijuana shops are trying to look like the Apple store  #trends #retail  https://t.co/YrjlKOPJQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when supply falls, prices jump ! no surprise. https://t.co/8RZwBuTF4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennethwilcox @CityPlanTO conversion of multi family to SF is the core of expensive cities is common.  Lots of triplexes going back to SF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rents for Toronto condos rising at record rates up over 11% https://t.co/v5cHLPwwu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microtrenching is an alternative to digging trenches in the dirt along the side of a road -- Lite Acess  $LTV.V https://t.co/UoZVH6qHCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now the British Pound dives 1.2% https://t.co/UgnLtRJX1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex and during the summer they were raising money at Negative interest rates ! They should have been spending more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's Most Reputable Cities and 3 of the Top 10 are in Canada #CAN2017 https://t.co/Eu6YWzUXnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sacramento Housing in December: Active Inventory down 17% YoY - Boomers Aging in Place ?  https://t.co/VQfa62oJga via @po_st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta Dec. Home sales up, prices up "Lack of Listings" a common theme in Real Estate - Boomers aging in place?  https://t.co/tP6uYafgBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moody’s to pay $864 mln to settle claims tied to housing-market collapse - so it wasn't AAA Mortgage Debt ?  https://t.co/C335xiUha8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 inches of rain, 12 feet of snow finally end 5-year drought in N. California https://t.co/S74toGHNr6 via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[old data, but still holds true,  Rx Drug spending/cost not the real issue $IBB $SPX $PPH #MAGA https://t.co/bMQ9Zsjm6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What $1 Million buys in Toronto and Vancouver  https://t.co/9s6PYsqwIW via @Chatelaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending on Experiences and Internet Spending = crushing Dept. Store Sales https://t.co/v2u5q28vLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswmayer @TrentBlair19 Agreed,  on Shiller's use of  "cyclically-adjusted" price-earnings (CAPE) ratio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tale of two cities:   US December Retail Sales Data:   Internet Sales up 13.2% while Department Store Sales fell 8.4% $AMZN $XRT $SPY $M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year 2016 was about "Experiences vs Things" with Restaurant Spending up 6.0% while Department Store spending was down 5.6%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US 2016 Retail Sales, Household Formation spending: Autos up 4.1% Furniture up 3.8% and Building Material &amp; Garden Stores up 5.9%  $SPY $XHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after a huge success in the US,  McDonald's Canada testing all-day breakfast menu https://t.co/8iZs1Fauqv  $MCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFTH Plays acting well today during this Optical SuperCycle following $AAOI boosting guidance $FNSR $LTE.CA LTE.V https://t.co/upspkkXski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as long as they are made it America it's ok. https://t.co/3rA5qHfq5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Toronto active Condo listings down 53% vs last year.  #torontorealestate https://t.co/8jVVTqdYuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rye, a Grain With Ancient Roots, Is Rising Again https://t.co/eQEPIyY9wN - love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uranium prices on the move YTD.  Production cuts ? Or Demand ? Or a bit of both ? https://t.co/0ougQ5dZMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. fund investors, countering trend:  Massive Inflows into Bonds and out of stocks $SPY $QQQ $TLT  https://t.co/BEzedVNOw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Surges Ahead to Lead Canadian Luxury Market in 2016, According to Sotheby's International Realty Canada https://t.co/ox9l0oJTNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Toronto's Bay Street Corridor:Nov13-Jan8  Condos sold 124 up 85% vs a year ago, while active inventory fell 64% to 71 #TorontoRealEstate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto WaterFront Communities Nov13-Jan8  353 Condos Sold up 49% vs last year while Active Inventory fell 55% to 194 #TorontoRealEstate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says Major report on Hacking Coming in the next month  $HACK https://t.co/lDXD8laSGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another smart move by the #Gucci group, parent Company Kering  $KER.FR $PPRUY https://t.co/qoElHOMhdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The turnaround at #Gucci continues, parent Company Kering hits a new high $KER.FR $PPRUY Award season in full swing… https://t.co/6A1xU8lNWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India -  Housing sales plunge 44% on notes ban: Knight Frank  https://t.co/sW0C6l1UUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas new home sales jumped in Q4 but builders couldn't keep up - Lack of Land and Labour ! https://t.co/IrrE7lZ5fd @dallasnews $XHB $LGIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average real estate commissions dropping to low 5 percent range https://t.co/LKUNYjwlAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who’s Buying Downtown L.A New Condos? https://t.co/pO3YnRv6oL via @http://www.twitter.com/DowntownNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians are getting help from ‘bank of mom and dad’ to buy first home, with B.C. and Quebec leading the way https://t.co/u16nEUsTPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is another reason why Boomers are Aging in Place... contributing to the lack of Supply, in Canada and the… https://t.co/zOnyGB05Oy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>