<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHinck after the latest Fiasconauts, all I want is a duet from you and @KyleBosman as an Easy Update song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao that's why you get the neon joycons :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks @YouTube @patrickklepek is the best here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No John Wick: Chapter 2 hype on @MichaelPHuber syndrome, feels bad :(.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Klepek" confusion... @patrickklepek @thecalgee https://t.co/i8RRohPnj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NorthernlionLP can you share where you got those local Mexican delights? I need good tacos in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao No issues allowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennymackinnon @Entrepreneur @jboitnott no. 

The article worked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee @screenrant holy shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao have you seen Sing Street?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee while watching The Incredibles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao welp... took the plunge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao Monster Hunter now on PSP Go2!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee are you buying this fatichu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao also my favourite music of all FF is near the end of the game :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao hmm... you'd definitely know if you were at the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks got one result that makes sense by searching: citizen+restaurant+ottawa -"ottawa citizen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao the game of the forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks yeah, you're right :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao There's one other character kind of like that but not on the same level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao ah yes, Cindy. I'm sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao I really want to seeeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeministSpag not much. It doesn't really stop lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeministSpag ah yes I've had some fun with that where I ended up fighting like 15 guys at once. Great times :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeministSpag if you're strapped for gil you can do hunts pretty quickly, best way to make money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeministSpag I felt the same way through my playthrough, not selling did come in handy with some quests but for the most part you can sell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @TSN_Sports why restrict people who want to cheer for their nation's WJHC team by locking streams to the games behind a cable wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched @kubothemovie after getting the blu-ray day 1. I can now say that it's one of my favourite animated movies. Thank you #LAIKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Death Stranding adds @FredrikSewell as a skeletal rival to @theofficialmads. Please @HIDEO_KOJIMA_EN???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao @FeministSpag hardcore is camping out in the Bestbuy parking lot over night. Nudge nudge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFIX likes for infinity. https://t.co/P8u1TpqlU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip @amazonca, when you finally offer Prime Video to Canada you should at least release your original programming at the same time as US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMoore035 Please make a video like the Anchorman News Team battles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished FFXV campaign tonight. Definitely rough, but final chapter was one of the greats and most dungeons were exciting/intimidating. A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FFXVprotip go into Options, turn off music and audio device, go to Spotify, turn on Bloodborne OST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @dominioncitybc: all I want for Christmas is some Earl Grey Marmalade Saison in Vancouver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FFXV #TMNT #PS4share https://t.co/aySgRb6vn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BottleneckNYC dayum, people love their $300 art $.$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao me too me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao for sure... I'm like 30h into FFXV and only maybe 50% complete lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao at this point I think I just need Persona 5 in my life :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao IX is by far my favourite. Story, mechanics, music, characters, all my faves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao I do wish that some chars in FFXV could join your party permanently, and that the skill tree was more robust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao nope. I did not like FF12 with its Gambit system at all haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao combat and sidequests in both Xenoblades blew it for me. FFXV combat does take a bit to get used to but once you do it's great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao it directly compares to FF12 and Xenoblade in my mind, and i like it way better than either of those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao even if you "fast travel" the load times make it slow. But I love the combat and the scale of everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao it's definitely rough around the edges but I'm pretty obsessed. Main complaint is that there's a lot of time lost to commute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wombo combo #PS4share https://t.co/DXmQ2eTh2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPHuber @RealGDT WHAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp I'm just a bit confused because my co-worker got his delivery but mine hasn't even shipped yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp It says "Arriving today - Being shipped today"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp I have not, it's stuck on "Being shipped soon" which I assume is the default message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's my Pokemon shipping notice @amazonca ?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God of War should win Most Anticipated Game @thegameawards on 12.1 #TGAGodOfWar https://t.co/sXV9vxAspm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny O’Dwyer should win Trending Gamer @thegameawards on 12.1 @TGAdannyodwyer @intelgaming #DannyOdwyer https://t.co/sXV9vxAspm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwatch should win Best eSports Game @thegameawards on 12.1 #TGAOverwatch https://t.co/sXV9vxAspm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infiltration should win Best eSports Player @thegameawards on 12.1 #TGAInfiltration @INFILTRATION85 https://t.co/sXV9vxAspm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee what is that Sephiroth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee how can i watch this forever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks New pickup line "You have textbook beautiful eyes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @SlackHQ, I identify as a robot and thus wish there was a "robot" skin tone option to choose as my default skin tone. Please comply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao what do you think of Super Hyper Cube? Worth the price tag?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao what are you still buying?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeKentDraws @thecalgee hahahaha it's true. Can I just rank The Evil Dead series above everything and be done with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeKentDraws @thecalgee Also I might not have seen the older Halloweens? I think I only saw the remake..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeKentDraws @thecalgee 7 Jason Lives out of 10 Freddy's Deads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee @MikeKentDraws Nope, you have that one last one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao yeah I've seen a lot of people feel weird with the platformer. I haven't felt bad with any of the games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao the on rails Rush of Blood has some rollercoaster-esque segments and they haven't made anyone I've seen sick. A+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FenixSolutions @generaltao @pauldinelle @JaimieWistaff @jmk1ng @tomasbreffitt only if @MikeMcG comes and we go to Delicious Steak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronpepper proof that you don't develop much on a Mac :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennymackinnon That's better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks @jennymackinnon Where's the Halloween candy?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks not enough Halloween candy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao @thecalgee I wouldn't even describe that episode as dark... more of a grey with sunny periods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingdomcub @kimtrucks I can't stop watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao yeah I've seen the complaints, luckily it hasn't happened to me but our office is a big open area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao @PlayStation have you calibrated it through the settings menu? Also camera placement makes a huge difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao @KeepTalkingGame @ThumperGame Thumper is definitely my favourite PSVR experience so far. Still need to try Batman for myself tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee is that the eye of arigato?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee Blinky and the PAIN? #seewhatididthere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecalgee I think you linked the wrong insta :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickklepek the one it actually chooses to tell can barely be called a story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pensnpixels @thecalgee @MikeKentDraws Mike has to deal with a lot of zombie vegetables huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FenixSolutions @chelsea_mac1 I see that the mirrors are still in their rightful place on the floor ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FenixSolutions I think at this point that Knob Creek is older than I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaimieWistaff @jennymackinnon @FenixSolutions Whoa whoa whoa Fenix rebrand leaks. Plug the holes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickklepek it could be that PS4 connects to 2.4 WiFi. I wired mine in and it's 3x faster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrailerJones one way you can interpret PS4 Pro is Pro = Proceed. To move forward to the next step. Not saying it's good, just a diff pov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauldinelle @generaltao @jennymackinnon don't you always look like that though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennymackinnon I finished season 1 years ago! (not actually). I also got my mom into it and all my friends when I visited TBay haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennymackinnon About time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHinck that's too bad. Wiring my PS4 has changed my life. Haven't had any online lag or download issues since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHinck just watching the podcast, is your PS4 on wifi? My PS4 on wifi is substantially worse than cabled. 30mb/s wifi v. 90ish cabled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffcannata My favourite theatre in Vancouver isn't playing Kubo for some reason :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao yes yes by far yes. All of the interactions, physics, animations, so on point. The boy had the exact same reactions as I did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@protectdestiel @generaltao @teefury stolen art partially? https://t.co/2OqACinAXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtrucks whoa TF2 o.O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generaltao @Secret_Tunnel I don't have a reason why. Gut said 11th, it fell on a Tuesday. Perfection.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>