<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex Pistols Glen Matlock, One F, the Fury @pistolsofficial @RamonesOfficial @Buzzcocks @Smiths_Official @BIMMDublin  https://t.co/O6WIWLu8vL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or Elvis Costello...his aim is true.... https://t.co/OnDzWFjDBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yer always Lou Grant and I'm your Mary Tyler Moore...ooh-eeh-uhhhh https://t.co/UBiQbojYa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Mirror...Ire clearly dropped Woody too young...@ireland_rugby @Munsterrugby @MRSC16 @HarpinOnRugby… https://t.co/RrRit6urLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So why does Glen Matlock want to hit One F over the head with his Fender Precision bass? Pages 40/41... https://t.co/ybKiw7NoDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all Glagow fans now C'mon Warriors! https://t.co/Cq2KoKj2pC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPCR Untoward Incident Review Group has accepted Munster &amp; Conor Murray's assertions he wasn't concussed v Glasgow on Jan 14. Case dismissed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you get to find out the Jackman/Eddy/Patsy Absolutely Fabulous connection ... #abfab #eprc #toulouse… https://t.co/znvN3Iu3Kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab venue in Newport with their regular audience. (It is where Kurt Cobain proposed to Courtney Love) Anyone want t… https://t.co/lK9Fqfqpf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah look! Miniature goats at @TheGoatGroup Goat Grill in Dundrum #GOAT #goat_blog https://t.co/tp3fh3Fmxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AAGill ... #ClareHollingsworth ... hope there isn't 'third-light' sniper out there aiming at another all-time great ... @mediaguardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Sexton passed 2nd HIA in dressing room after RDS game. Injury/hit confirmed as neck. Free to train fully on Mon #LeinsterRugby #ERC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wha'bout ya Glentoran! Great goal Matt Burrows! https://t.co/wLcABQha2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Sweetnam for @LionsRugbyUnion ? Going/watching @Munsterrugby v @leinsterrugby   @IsFearrAnStar @IrishStarSport DS EXCLUSIVE i/view]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bundee Aki crocked...to undergo surgery on ankle...will be out until 'mid-Feb' #bundeeaki #connachtrugby #pro12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been #apollohouse..well done Hansard &amp;Co..security well behaved..food/stuff and pple in/out.impressed. Hasta l… https://t.co/eaxaxySBDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/txIV0kbUFl No prizes for guessing which reporter upset Jim Mallinder at Aviva (Indo &amp; Times rugby coverage today. I confess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are a racing fan you will know why this is being tweeted....16/1 nap....winner alright...happy Xmas Star rea… https://t.co/UMdpTagKmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alternate view of the Hartley/SOB tackle...not quite sure there would be many takers there TC...but the twitter… https://t.co/438ISxw8am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan Hartley handed six-week ban for his hit on Sean O’Brien https://t.co/vLNr37FCtW via @buzzdotie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six weeks for Dylan Hartley. Until Monday Jan 23...has him well under the wire for England v France on Feb 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Star - Comment: EPCR’s humiliation of Keith Earls was bang out of order https://t.co/wDsjumxr6k via @buzzdotie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sickened by EPRC's disgusting t/ment of Keith Earls today; how fnucking dare they, he was clearly upset about Axel Foley...more t/row's Star]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["..of it and sneer or sigh or fling them with great force at the dog. But together they make up the most precious thing we own." AA Gill RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...team effort. The power of the press is cumulative. It has a conscious human momentum. You can – and probably do – pick up bits... (more)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...restaurant reviews or gossip columns. But that’s not the point. Journalism isn’t an individual sport like books and plays; it’s a.(more)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Freedom of speech is what all other human rights and freedoms balance on. That may sound like unspeakable arrogance when applied to (more)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laine's belting delivery killed big bands shitty crooners (Crosbie Sinatra etc), opened door 4 r/r's holler (Berry, JL Lewis, Gene Vincent)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab Frankie Lane 1953 Royal Theatre poster d/stairs in Dublin's Lansdowne Hotel. Right then he'd be 1 of the bigges… https://t.co/0AOp7MGV4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Set The Controls For The Heart Of The Rising Sun...today's One F on how much more Ireland have coming down the line

https://t.co/fAFttgJ9wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unable to take prop pic of Above &amp; Beyond in Dublin but they are fair rockin' The Olympic  @aboveandbeyond… https://t.co/mbcunIqD4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest Sports TV graphic of all time? Aretha F sings the red, white &amp; blues and (cue outrage!) holds up the game!

https://t.co/nlVoJ7jleO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AkaPaulHoward did that come out during the Sea Sessions at Bundoran when he played there in 2010?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oblique? In-yer-face Queen were why we were rebelling (was Fat Bottom Girls/Bicycle Race the nadir of rock'n'roll?)

https://t.co/M65b6s0auO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AkaPaulHoward The Seven Seas of Rye - former Ire/MUFC midfielder discusses Fergie, PNeville,  Haaland,  Dunphy, Viera,  Quinn, McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at this poster! Not a bad sunny Sunday a'noon option #thelookalikes @Tonerspub ...am told band on stage 5pm

 https://t.co/3QN14sHx0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star GAA Awards....great night....top class event! https://t.co/jdEPjQHFRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Host grounds for the potential 2023 Rugby World Cup bid #ireland2023 https://t.co/QuL4IEvgWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff 4m @Roisinmurphy including 30 hat/costume changes; this 1 is sorta stone; couldn't get a pic of the 6ft… https://t.co/1IKa5lo1rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have randomly walked into a pub called Doubleday in Damen,  Chicago to find...Roisin Murphy on stage! Go Roisin,  go Moloko! #roisinmurphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland calling: All incumbent US presidents 'discover' Irish ancestry &amp; then visit us. Please don't elect Trump. #ElectionFinalThoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 10th b/day @HoZacRecords Doubledoor Chicago; top bill The Gories (pic) have filthy blues/punk thing! G8 sonic… https://t.co/wO6AZzK1Ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tara  Browne on Tour: look who helped make the news today ...... Ireland 40 All Blacks 29 ! https://t.co/cqfZkJFBli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Newsnight - best ever tweet in the history of tweets! This has made no so happy!

https://t.co/b47Sk2Qd8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Star plus! Rob Henshaw on how @ireland_rugby can draw on The Notorious for 'impossible' @AllBlacks  game @ChicagoBears Soldier Field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, evil spell check made me wrong...twice....sorree...so had to issue reprise...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tara Browne on Tour: at the piano (Duke Ellington, JellyRoll Morton) roarin' 20s speakeasy The Green Mill, Chicago… https://t.co/weHNdf2Q2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have They Read The New Today, Oh Boy...Tara Browne on Tour! #GoCubsGo #Cubs https://t.co/eL6Qj7uq0m https://t.co/1eeNeiaLIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tara Browne on Tour: We read the news today and Donald Trump is all over it! https://t.co/i2NLlmcCSV https://t.co/T3qYhmQvXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people here! #chicagocubs #worldSeries broke 108 year old curse too! Ireland to bt All Black's going back a… https://t.co/4TwBZhuCR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made it! Chicago's oldest jazz bar &amp; Al Capone/Machine Gun Jack McGurn hangout, The Green Mill- $4 a 3/4 pint, fab… https://t.co/jDTYBcWQDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does your race affect the restaurant you choose? We generally eat food we are comfortable with. Fist World idiots

https://t.co/MVeWvFsG1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is all Rocket From The Crypt here...@bandpicturethis rawkin' the #BuzzLaunchNight  @buzzdot.ie @IsFearrAnStar… https://t.co/enLKeymWXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olivia de Havilland as Maid Marion in The Adventures of Robin Hood (1938, Errol Flynn) is greatest tom-boy in film history..Just sayin']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PUNKFLASH! Santry Towels/Prince Runamok to release Boomtown Rats 'I NEVER LOVED TARA BRAUN' to mark @AkaPaulHoward's book 'I Read The News..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front Cover Irish Daily Star Inside Sport pull-out today...Anthony Foley 1973- 2016...'Farewell To A Legend' https://t.co/GtVj7SLUIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony Foley 1973-2016 RIP see Inside Sport pull-out centre pages https://t.co/BY4mFQ7tqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soi Guadalajara Oi Mexico! Fab The Butcherettes @theworkmansclub Dublin  Teri Gender Bender is PJ/Polly/Lydia Harve… https://t.co/n0UbylGkW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super super piece about Anthony Foley. ..now this a read https://t.co/0mOrNS65gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup me....there is nothing to beat Yes Minister ...sorree https://t.co/mEaCBkv3Qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deux Moulins, Montmartre under the famous Fabulous Destiny of Amelie poster..writing today's copy about the Fabulou… https://t.co/VgO8SOx71m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just two guys...one famous...in 2001...Axel had column in the @IsFearrAnStar @IrishStarSport and it was xlnt too...… https://t.co/xYYnTDeBZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensational Irish Star sports magazine cover from Rob Baker... have you had your @IrishStarSport Saturday supplemen… https://t.co/uSiBCVJJDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vapors in Dublin. They came, they saw, turned Japanese (once v early on) &amp; were done by 10:10pm. Punk's not dea… https://t.co/0NPVZ6emUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good stuff... https://t.co/dMFI1KniXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kirsty MaColl❤. Hope were lots of @Soho Square drinks tnite #KirstyMacColl #newengland #england2colombia0 #terry @billybragg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales &amp; Ireland to be ahead after 20 minutes...a 10/1 on-screen 'special' in shops today. Thank you Paddy Power!… https://t.co/wuxrjmIUkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Second Coming...Garry Ringrose exclusive...real story behind boy name-checked Irish rugby's future by… https://t.co/SVzIoX1UKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you been on Buzz.ie ??? Calling the Ryder Cup and the betting  https://t.co/HNTKDXit2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is 'disarming' the curse? https://t.co/vonvIEVEbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't all country at the Ploughing Championships....Rosser was with me... @NPAIE @RossOCK https://t.co/WpNMQRCmW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you about the Wellies of Greatness? #garyandpaulodonovan #robanddavekearney #PloughingChampionships @NPAIE https://t.co/aX0ysB5Loa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a brilliantly designed front page!

 https://t.co/rE8fDgsi57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we don't know about Joe Schmidt leaving - Irish Daily Star #Schm-explanation @dementedmole @HarpinOnRugby https://t.co/LdPsjCiibj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know about Joe Schmidt staying - today's Irish Daily Star #Schm-explanation @dementedmole @HarpinOnRugby https://t.co/qFQbVsI9zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite the Lights of Tetouan...but close....any guesses? https://t.co/k1Un9p8A34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah look for heaven's sake if it is needed that badly, tell Waterford Hospital to contact me - I'll stump up for a new Cat Flap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already!!! Already a best seller (see bottom shelf in pic)! @RossOCK @PenguinBooks @PenguinUKBooks @AkaPaulHoward https://t.co/smHnHc9TjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't start against Palace Jacko (my old HF buddy)!

https://t.co/BFGa0ISHtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard @nickcave 's new single 'Jesus Alone' 2B released on @kobalt soon (this w/end I think) - a complete stunner! Form! #nickcave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a finish...Eloise...Plan 9 Channel 7...New Rose...Neat Neat Neat!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE DAMNED Seriously this is shaping up 2b one of the greatest Dublin gigs of all time @mcd @DublinAcademy @DubCityCouncil @TwitterDublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eloooooooissssse! Melody Lee! Smash it up!  @thedamned is this the Dublin gig og of 2016! @mcd @theacademydublin https://t.co/qBr6lN5r7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Millar maybe?
 "Some people call me the space cowboy,
"'Cause I speak of the impompitous of love..." https://t.co/i1ngiwmnKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jefferson Airplane? Anyone know y (admit'ly xlnt) Somebody To Love is rated #279 in Rolling Stone G8tst singles and White Rabbit is #483?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tks to maths guy pointing out if Irel 'lost' fights they shld've won on unaminous decisions, odds go to over 1000/1. Less Paddywhackery plse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live commentary/ certain panelists/studio guests. Have U heard unchallenged @Rte Bolger i/view of Rio conspiracy? https://t.co/8SftAa2kzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rte commentary said all 7 shld've won. From Barnes tru a fight with 2 public warnings..analysis plse not Pwhackery https://t.co/JWFKzu6N9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Stephen.....you think Conlon shld have won. Okay. Were all seven Irish boxers robbed? https://t.co/keZMZkw33Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All seven Irish boxers were robbed? Conlon was cut in 1st Rd on my TV...was he cut on the arena where you are? https://t.co/1tTbdyockq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK maybe Conlon shld have won. But ALL 7 (128/1)? Is there any proper analysis out there anywhere? @rte @iaba less Paddywhackery plse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnes were 4/1 to gold b4 @Olympics. Not 1 of 7 Irish boxers dominated centre of ring in sport where being the agressor is important?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...being robbed in 7 50/50 fights are 128/1. Why am paying @rte TV licence for this rubbish analysis. Less Paddywhackery plse. Both Conon &amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV showed 4 clips of last Conon round. Russian landed 3 good shots in 3/4 clips, maybe Y he won round3? Maths chances of Irish boxers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ire have only won 1 gold in 120 odd years @Olympics but ALL 7 Irish boxers were robbed? Including a fighter who is given 2 public warnings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So let's get this straight @rte @iaba. ALL 7 Irish boxers Barnes, Irvine, Conlan, Joyce, Donnelly, Ward &amp; KT Taylor were ALL robbed? More]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please plse @Rio2016_en @rio2016_es @Olympics pan a camera to Main St Suva....bet an Irish bar witnessing 1 of the g8test parties ever seen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We @irishdailystar @DailyStarSport  flagged Fiji gold at 2/1 as a bet of the century. Magnificent! Tears! Joy! 43-7!! #Rio2016 #Fiji7s #fiji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishStarSport @irishdailystar told u 2/1 Fijians were sent by God, Presidential TV announcement with tears &amp; all 27--0 half-time in final!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If McG is complaining he doesn't get enough money....where those that leave the others? https://t.co/RfvbEv5W6t]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>