<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamBreastCancer @ePatientDave push back is welcome - it's why I love moving from word-limiting Twitter to Medium and blogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How might we empower people to participate in research or solve problems related to their own health challenges? https://t.co/IpvhmXxoeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The idea of a patient systematically, intelligently, and competently contributing to saving his own life is still n… https://t.co/MkFGXvSMIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SolidFooting Thank you! Didn't have time to fix my poor old site before posting, so the conversation's here: https://t.co/lUai3aN0Lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaTenaerts Love it - any chance you have time to write a quick response expanding on what you see as opportunities/challenges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAinDC Agree! @fastercures came to mind as I was reading the piece. What do you think of my question about models?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackpenner Yes, thanks to you, @ePatientDave and @philmartie - psyched to get more people in the conversation, too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How might we empower people to participate in research about their own diseases or conditions? https://t.co/B2UQGsHzLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveDolton Thanks for sharing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanessee Yes! If you're inspired to write more, here's a Medium post you can respond to: https://t.co/B2UQGsHzLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great - and I think answerable - question: which models work best? And for which challenges? https://t.co/wvcbL2kVvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I almost wish that every disease had a @DavidFajgenbaum to be part of the charge." How might researchers empower people to do so?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots to discuss about this @nytimesbusiness story by @katie_thomas about @DavidFajgenbaum's #RareDisease (just to get all the tags in)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilly social media guru @gmatczak, who actually listened to patients, dies https://t.co/nesYzTymQ1 (thank you @nversel for the tribute)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you resist "19-year-old Jill put on her most serious navy pantsuit"? And how e-patient is THIS: https://t.co/H6GxUjTEON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will spare you the live-tweeting of the @ThisAmerLife show if you all PROMISE to listen or read: https://t.co/p6xdSp55NE by @DavidEpstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time off = time to listen (again!) to one of my favorite episodes. Peer-to-peer health care FTW https://t.co/ZZXCTFpiur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this story! Perseverance - secret to Dr. Johnson's success. @SI_Invention  https://t.co/TTUGg0T0nq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to parenting an innovator? "I was tolerated," Lonnie Johnson says with a laugh. "I experimented with rocket fuel." @SI_Invention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be at @SI_Invention to hear @drlisadcook interview the amazing Lonnie Johnson https://t.co/VJ9IL962Pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmontori Reading the latest @Atul_Gawande essay, I was reminded of the ideas, data you &amp; I have traded. Also found: https://t.co/dWQzCLmpGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time off = time to re-read. Today: The work of being a chronic patient and the Internet, by @vmontori https://t.co/ui90c7knCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time off = time for reading. Today: https://t.co/357CtTgEnu by @Atul_Gawande]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Axarharebate @SVHealth20 Thanks! No West Coast travel plans but grateful to know you all are out there hustling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aviars thank you! You were one of the pioneers who inspired me to pitch in with the @HHSIDEALab and #hackredtape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Bush A Democrat and a Republican walk into a bar... I mean, HHS...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the innovative work that continues at HHS: the new class of the @HHSIDEALab Ignite Accelerator https://t.co/sdQxDU1f8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This is kind of emblematic of why we collaborate, to build this kind of systematic approach.” - Padmini Srikantiah… https://t.co/qZKaO6BjTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelFeltman As a DC juror I visited the U.S. Constitution and Bill of Rights on my lunch hour: https://t.co/iK4J3GjnEx @USNatArchives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_m_space @Medium Thanks for sharing that essay. I still believe there are discoveries &amp; innovations ahead if we li… https://t.co/i45oHreiIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DurgasToolbox got you covered here in DC - you keep loving on that boy and writing dispatches from *your* front lines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a break from the tumult and thank @DurgasToolbox for these lessons about health and care https://t.co/bKHOdFm4fg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bostonheartmom ❤ that you found help in the hours while I was offline! Thank you @ASlavitt and @AislingMcDL - Tami is a mama warrior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two reasons to go to @AislingMcDL profile page TODAY:
1) Latest https://t.co/dsO4IwqqiS updates
2) Balloons (happy birthday!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't read this until you are fully awake and braced for words like "astonishing incompetence" https://t.co/I9KQ5UfbVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your head is spinning from the deluge of news, read @MikeGrunwald on what really mattered this week: https://t.co/qkA8tpfWvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraRiggare @DurgasToolbox Thank you for tagging me, Sara! And Cristin, a tour de force, as always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patientslikeme and of course @ReginaHolliday paintings are everywhere - love this new #thewalkinggallery jacket https://t.co/piVBVNH033]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reconnecting with old friends and making new ones @patientslikeme today - the health revolution is happening here https://t.co/miMyj4CFPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbrigham thank you! You do amazing work for patients and the people who love them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreyOstrovsky Happy to say I'm staying in DC (just taking a few weeks off). Would be great to meet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Most Important Job in the World?” — @BryanSivak https://t.co/Vxjn9vRiCu https://t.co/jI9IvwJEH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HHSIDEALab is recruiting a systems architect to serve at @CDCgov for a year. Uncle Sam needs YOU: https://t.co/e6pc8nTtk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A conversation can be a potent analgesic - how might we scale this insight? https://t.co/9STPDf6kJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joltdude Instax as a matter of fact - anonymous woman asked to snap it and then gave it to us. Wonder for the kids, nostalgia for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Polaroid, snapped for us at #WomensMarch, prompted a great tech evolution conversation across generations https://t.co/5sqYHs8AhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryagneskelley thank you for sharing your mother's voice with us. Tears for you, here in DC ❤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch with my family today ❤ https://t.co/NWVKJxmm8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@annakyoung helps nurses prototype and build clinical solutions - @makerhealthco @MakerNurse https://t.co/I71SpTgGuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jordan Reeves, age 11, designs prosthetic hands – and glitter cannons – for herself - @bornjustright https://t.co/HZ98mUxGBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Valor is surviving ALS, hacking health with one eye @surfiving  https://t.co/AXcT4Uz5fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lynda Mitchell advocates for kids with food allergies @kfatweets https://t.co/7bmE1K0R38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory Cooper is using robotics to change what it means to be disabled @PittTweet https://t.co/SPwPFm58HF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoko K. Sen asks gently, with purpose, “What is the last sound you’ll ever hear?” @SenSoundSpace https://t.co/iy2DSfRCtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill T. Jones combines beauty + strength, art + activism - @BTJAZCo Love this performance: https://t.co/udUBLcIVTU?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ekeeleymoore is a mom/caregiver/activist who pushes the edges of what’s possible https://t.co/xaTdCM0yAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bjmillermd helps people live until they die https://t.co/Zr6J4IWyoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laurie Strongin brings joy to kids who are hospitalized @hopeforhenry https://t.co/Bw7s1dSX3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to share examples of awesome people...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMitchellAAFA @AllergyKidsDoc Awesome news! Have you seen this comparison of injectors by @Donteatmagnets? Useful: https://t.co/haDImZEH24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebGreenwood @gee_perry @ePatientDave thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CleverThought @YouTube Yes! A line I didn't expect to get applause. People w #RareDisease push edges, use every to… https://t.co/lpklmCKUJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eerie story from the 2013 federal gov't shutdown: https://t.co/VehErfRTxl https://t.co/hH39MtdRlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siobhanmaire I love that idea! Storytelling from all divisions, all corners of the globe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, @TheMoth, for sharing this organ transplant story https://t.co/Gj8ByY81IX (MVY -&gt; MGH in 1.5 hours!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing story of one procurement -&gt; transplantation cc @ORGAN_IZE https://t.co/ZkBE1xZZPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resilient people &amp; communities strengthen national health security - @PHEgov https://t.co/xJ5XoAkvIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight surgeons, engineers, designers, nurses, emergency response experts - the common thread: a can-do spirit https://t.co/0p6edZGdxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In gov't, I looked for people who lean into the curves, who innovate by instinct. I found them in emergency response and, of course, @NASA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quickmuse @_Continuum @KevinYoungR @TechCrunch Wonderful! Added it to my outboard memory of #InventHealth examples: https://t.co/LBSBrDK44Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bornjustright You'll recognize the pic that @VentureValkyrie used to illustrate this post: https://t.co/TTwEIIwnOX :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always on the look-out for extraordinary people - health hackers, MacGyver patients. They are the lead users of health &amp; human services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bornjustright @Enablehands_ECF @Enablethefuture AWESOME! Love the pirate hook. Go Jordan!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@N_Brennan Thank you for your service!! You've been a righteous, riotous, data-liberating, barrier-breaking (on you… https://t.co/J18L4fN0Vu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inclusiveness is beautiful: the audience welcomes @jenbrea ASL-style (waving hands in silence) https://t.co/W1u0Hdr5qU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to a 2014 interview of the incredible @jenbrea - truly a "Health Care Hacker" https://t.co/ruGdh5V6Eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@USDS @Medium Yes! Hundreds have answered the call to serve @USDS and as Entrepreneurs in Residence at @HHSGov - s… https://t.co/6eZT16Gffd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You’ll Never Be The Same Again” — @USDS https://t.co/WOe2QBWXE1 https://t.co/wnnpqoXUgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HHSIDEALab And why HHS practices health &amp; human services at scale - on a high wire - yet needs to create space for experimentation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HHSIDEALab Topics include: why I focused on Makers, not VR; #wearenotwaiting and the FDA; why CDC needs data scie… https://t.co/QhuGr9nxLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I take any chance I get to brag about @HHSIDEALab and my awesome colleagues. Latest: https://t.co/TTwEIIwnOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: @clathan asks why don't we have a vital sign for brain health? How might we leverage data? Caregivers? https://t.co/bbBzdk08ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: The U.S. Government Should Buy Gilead For $156 Billion To Save Money On Hepatitis C https://t.co/56zEDpwdom - @peterbachmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hjluks @BackStoryRadio @HowIBuiltThis @MaeveInAmerica ...and not just because I'm on the current episode: Tech Ton… https://t.co/NRa5Dwlmjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hjluks I love @BackStoryRadio (U.S. history); @HowIBuiltThis (startup hagiography); new to @MaeveInAmerica (immigration stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read reflections on service, on the @AIDSgov blog: https://t.co/B5WwqLpX1j https://t.co/UMX1Z7yCZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Life’s most persistent and urgent question is: ‘What are you doing for others?” - Dr. King (love your answer,… https://t.co/ZdcYwzYJvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DShaywitz thank you for having me on the sharpest healthcare podcast out there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;happy sigh&gt; I do love a good set of footnotes https://t.co/gJT2fiu9zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My message to innovators: We cannot let people who don't understand us defeat us. https://t.co/nJFi4Z4HJw #Medx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCartier2 When @SecBurwell asked each of us in the leadership to share a story of impact from our portfolio, I shared yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeattleMamaDoc @HHSGov I loved being part of the mission: to enhance and protect the health and well-being of all Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to keep asking for better design in health care and so should you. Read: https://t.co/jk4SL0FLf2 by @joyclee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like other #foodallergy families, we manage the risk as best we can. We take what we get. See, for ex: https://t.co/7kA7jAZ2H5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A generic, cheap alternative epinephrine injector is great news but note: it is not an intuitive, well-designed device. #foodallergy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, @Donteatmagnets, for this comparison of epinephrine injectors! #foodallergy https://t.co/haDImZEH24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joyclee @arstechnica My household got a preview when we renewed an epi Rx and got the generic auto-injector. Disap… https://t.co/tBnjxFctCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinclauson @HHSIDEALab @damonldavis thank you! These jobs are like ambassadorships, translating back &amp; forth amo… https://t.co/wbxJutRj1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the center of @VAInnovation you will find one of my heroes: @andreakippolito. Her enthusiasm &amp; smarts lift everyone's game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch up on and follow #VADiffusion - deeply embedded model for innovation in a federal agency https://t.co/0VcvXVlPVV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>