<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA['The world's doors were closed': Jared Kushner's grandmother on refugee life https://t.co/4d4hm9czIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arendt Explains How Propaganda Uses Lies to Erode All Truth &amp; Morality: Insights from The Origins of Totalitarianism https://t.co/gVzVgNr8IG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim ban feeds IS narrative https://t.co/dgAkGQarv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClareAliceMurph I'd seen it a couple of places and just asked Dr. Google. It is pretty awesome ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Haydn_Barlow I would suggest illconisdered (or at least some variation of Occam's Razor) rather than intentional stoking of flames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS America. I love you and everything, but c'mon. 
https://t.co/v0RvG8VKNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Ban Is Unlikely to Reduce Terrorist Threat, Experts Say https://t.co/4xdK90BkqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Qaeda and allies announce ‘new entity’ in Syria: https://t.co/LbQDLvHNXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Irvine talks counter terrorism. What more could you want? #CBR 07/02. Register here: https://t.co/8YMIByi2qm #auspol #ct #natsec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacist threatened to shoot up Central Coast shopping centre  https://t.co/jeA6Wvf9hV via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always. Remember always. #HolocaustMemorialDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Untold Story of the Bastille Day Attacker | GQ https://t.co/oe9B9v2Eae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop reading this ... you're meant to be on holidays https://t.co/IlzzbMg2b6 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold. Just gold. #brexit https://t.co/pjIfvLnyjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Minnesota’s Risky Plan to Deradicalize ISIS Recruits https://t.co/69wGyKvGIR via @WIRED #CVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colombia Port Town in Bloody Battle Over Former FARC Turf https://t.co/8c83GYrRwr via @insightcrime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistani Extremists Carve A Sanctuary In Southern Afghanistan https://t.co/XOhNLvBFez via @GandharaRFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registered for David Irvine's keynote address at the @CSU_CTstudies Canberra program launch yet? #auspol #CVE https://t.co/8YMIByi2qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon: Bombs struck Islamic State’s ‘external plotters’ in Libya | FDD's Long War Journal https://t.co/Od4klDUpbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Al-Qaeda affiliate claims Mali car bomb attack in Gao https://t.co/E2rXczpCw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friction deepens among Al Qaeda factions in Syria https://t.co/gzUwHDXbpU via @TheNationalUAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Irvine will officially launch the #CBR Terrorism Studies program on 7th Feb. Register here: https://t.co/8YMIByi2qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A conversation on terrorism in Australia, with @levijwest  - part 1 https://t.co/2RKCmPgmPQ thanks @Andrew_Zammit #ct #auspol #natsec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top cop lashes abuse of fatwas https://t.co/PBUhoM8jjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suicide attack hits Nigeria's University of Maiduguri @AJENews  https://t.co/Kn1cnooOPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickglavin need to be Canberra based with work permission, but not citizen per se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a vacancy: 12 month contract, teach &amp; research, terrorism studies program, distance and F2F students, CBR based. DM me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[does anyone know anyone in Aust. who speak with authority on FININT (financial intelligence) in the terrorist finance space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guardians of the liberal order now foresee its collapse https://t.co/H9QIhmJvfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Qaeda linked to more than 250 West African attacks in 2016 | FDD's Long War Journal https://t.co/fBYmIusHYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GameChangers 2016: Gang Evolution in Central America's Southern Gateway https://t.co/Ov8rRtbwIr via @insightcrime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hezbollah is the real winner of the battle of Aleppo https://t.co/nOPnoJ64LP via @NewsweekEurope #hezbollah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin, PayPal used to finance terrorism, Indonesian agency says  https://t.co/7XNdD5BrWO via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. intelligence study warns of growing conflict risk https://t.co/8fD6ahieM6 via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[doing a PhD in terrorism studies/Middle East politics/IR/politics? My program needs some markers and some guest lecturers. DM me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Strategic Logic of the New Year’s Eve Attack in Istanbul https://t.co/gSlRKcuweV via @warontherocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Qaeda affiliate leaders among 25 dead in Syria strike | SBS News https://t.co/5rH3jnGAB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatal Attraction: ISIS Just Can’t Resist Social Media https://t.co/zC9nrOfBrE via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prakash fled Mosul as IS crackdown took place https://t.co/ipe9WVL3Vb @mark_schliebs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nixon’s Vietnam Treachery https://t.co/09E3aLy312]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student evaluations of teaching are not only unreliable, they are significantly biased against female instructors. https://t.co/8IPPrlSbQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're living through the first world cyberwar – but just haven’t called it that | Martin Belam https://t.co/Mn0pAHgl9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian police point to Islamic State after 2016 spike in terrorism cases https://t.co/GcYb81VY3Y via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrest over New Year’s Eve threats https://t.co/4LR1EPI7Px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two-and-a-Half Years After ISIS's Rise: Global Jihad Spreads And Morphs - FPRI https://t.co/HsDe9UTWcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Abu Sayyaf: Blood, drugs and conspiracies @AJENews  https://t.co/N05Gyp2V6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd hand Bookshop gold! https://t.co/fUhRuKgC7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiaMBloom I prefer the 'Lone Wolf Terrorism &amp; Rise of Leaderless Resistance' by George Michael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Xmas reading list. @PeterRNeumann @brianfishman @petternessern  @caduceuscellars perfect paired with cricket. https://t.co/L2FquG1GOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intercept headed off disaster https://t.co/9XIjvjM3Ls #CT #ASIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me talking on the Melbourne Xmas Day plot: Explosive device suggests higher degree of planning: expert https://t.co/L03GYzbrtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing intelligence in a world of post-truth BS https://t.co/oQqtavIhJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CIA is delaying our books’ publication, and that hurts our democracy https://t.co/sH1vpovtoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban warfare on three fronts https://t.co/W1WUwHZnou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terror plan to hit Melbourne church service https://t.co/CPc0ArY9M3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well look at that. Who would have thought? It's like they have some sort of system? https://t.co/bqnAhnY5wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry appropriated Pagan Northern Hemisphere Winter solstice to all. https://t.co/MBKD8mX9QA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel broken White Spy (Black remains intact) captures something of 2016. There is a disturbance in the Force. https://t.co/WYOW2RoAme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark your calendar: Feb 07. Official launch of @CSU_CTstudies CBR PG program w/ keynote speaker David Irvine Details in the new year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Year after San Bernardino, the Number of Women Jihadis Is Growing https://t.co/I58s98wbIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The unnoticed trend that worries Europe's counterterrorism agencies https://t.co/m2Eu8BiQrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 years of terrorist attacks in Europe, visualized https://t.co/82J1epQQ3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent work - ISW's The Virtual Caliphate: ISIS's Information Warfare https://t.co/VbJ8VqPflD #CT #jihad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coming of the Russian Jihad, Part II https://t.co/GEKRVGZyLO via @warontherocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Colombia Traffickers Love High-Tech 'Narco Torpedoes' https://t.co/7Bi68UN2yo via @insightcrime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truck attack may be part of ISIS strategy to sharpen divide between Muslims and others https://t.co/9VIPDKnZab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on #ISIS and their system of social media facilitated individual/small cell jihad: https://t.co/Fcq4FivfoW #berlinattacks #LoneWolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Berlin Attack Is Right Out of the Terror Handbooks https://t.co/lIjcLm6EKq via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. to target citizens of Crusader coalition countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. German city of Berlin is a soldier of the Islamic State, and he carried out the operation in response to appeals...to target citizens of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Translation of Amaq claim if #Berlin attack: An insider source to ‘Amaq Agency: The executor of the vehicular assault operation in...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect video/audio bay'at from #Berlin terrorist to be released in next 48hrs or so. As a function of the #ISIS claim, there is a bay'at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful backgrounder on Germany &amp; jihadis https://t.co/KedYb4lFvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suicide bomber kills at least 30 soldiers in Yemen's Aden: officials https://t.co/xNSgHJAnHQ - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian police: ISIS operative Bahrun Naim detected in southern Philippines https://t.co/0Ibo9Ti5uu via @rapplerdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect says Islamic State ordered 2015 high-speed train attack in France https://t.co/LG1HC3ejXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. steps up fight to cut Islamic State financing and trade in looted antiquities https://t.co/XXZnZttyWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanks. 14 tanks! US airstrikes destroy 14 Islamic State tanks near Palmyra | https://t.co/OGdVo05DZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Leader in the Islamic State https://t.co/MFCepS2vQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Russia Wins an Election https://t.co/brCussauyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SA man charged after allegedly posting videos 'on how to kill Jewish people' https://t.co/K8oFUg0YE2 - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SA man charged with advocating terrorism https://t.co/K8oFUg0YE2 - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to Hurt the Taliban? Legalize Opium in Afghanistan https://t.co/aADw9XRyEp via @defenseone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Perfect Weapon: How Russian Cyberpower Invaded the U.S. https://t.co/TJ81gMXtEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Jihadi Threat: ISIS, Al Qaeda and Beyond https://t.co/cC4VqN4ESu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Tea with Hezbollah’s No. 2 https://t.co/bDr4hqridP via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-Aussie Khawaja caught in confusing Pakistan mix-up https://t.co/RirRSJT5Y5 - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7SongsCup Interloper, LMA, Point Man, Familiar Territory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dutch police arrest terror suspect and seize arsenal of weapons https://t.co/vRiPUdByYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CVE in the Age of Trump https://t.co/oIjlOKy3Nr #cve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hezbollah’s Struggle for Hearts and Minds on the Syrian Golan https://t.co/IipkpWCvZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Densus 88 seizes documents from suspected terrorist in C. Java https://t.co/PDaHmAEvJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian refugee graduates dux of one of Australia's largest Catholic schools https://t.co/Mr9py6Rjy5 - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7SongsCup #cainstakes but there is 10 songs on Ill at Ease...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspects in plot to bomb State Palace part of IS-affiliated network: Police   https://t.co/lYGL3Am3Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama orders review of cyber attacks on 2016 election: adviser https://t.co/HoQzv5Kj7l - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have though? Intelligence agencies collecting intelligence https://t.co/uixNSd4oHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney terror duo sentenced to 20 years' jail for foiled plot https://t.co/Gk3WJzwtar - via @abcnews #CT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hybrid warfare' of online propaganda and hacking pose fundamental threat, says MI6 chief Alex Younger  https://t.co/C3VXt8xdbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gang tactics used on extremists https://t.co/YdloKLoym9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>