<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LozzzaC Well... we are on a hiding to nowhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LozzzaC We _can_ hope... but should we?  ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LozzzaC Of course. Just getting my notice in etc. - we both know the lessons of previous visits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LozzzaC There's a chance I'll be in Melbourne the 14th April. Consider this your advance warning. ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spoonyman Hahaha, woops. I forgot my sarcasm tag.  Was merely engaging in the satire. ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spoonyman Brian Carlton from little island Tasmania = FAKE NEWS. Biased liberal sources, SAD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Liverpool dropped points as well.  ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Nope. Winter break all the way.  ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 *cough* https://t.co/T1j101HZgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy I've got enough vinyl that he'll know about it, but cassette and VHS will be a weird blank spot he probably won't believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy CASSETTE TAPE RICHARD. REMEMBER THOSE.  ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy Nirvana's Nevermind for me. Zeppelin and Metallica followed soon after. Had 'Master of Puppets' on cassette.   ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy You're well aware of my love for the Zepp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy THRASH mate. Early Metallica, Slayer, Anthrax. Proper headbanging. 

(not that I dislike any band you've named)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muppetbhoy Get some proper thrash into you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HeadbangingHarvey #Metallica

https://t.co/sR0MFjgNbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all the things /r/thathappened, this happened the most.

The architect's name? Albert Einstein. https://t.co/gqb5DOMu7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjwiss @KevinAirs442 25th Amendment has to come into play. The man is an unhinged lunatic, clearly mentally unfit for office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Under the 1949 Geneva Conventions,Â collective punishment is a war crime."

Invoke the 25th Amendment already.

https://t.co/jqOFEWQdv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Yeah, of course. Mind you, if I can do a sneaky "use Alicia's fuel card from work to fill up"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 @thurbs62 I have separately messaged as to his potential availability. His Twitter is... well, one step shy of deactivated. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 5.30. This one is 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Kickoff earlier this time as well so possibly 11.30?  Depends on the run away from the stadium but midnight at the latest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Well last time, Alicia and I left within 20 minutes of full time and were in our garage before midnight... cost... $40??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@priorpeter I'd ask you about Canberra but I know you're going with the ladyfriend. Didn't want you to feel left out.  ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell you what, when the Mouse House wants something to succeed they don't fuck around. Their marketing budget is obscene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CoryBooker How long until serious discussions re: the 25th Amendment are had?? Trump is _dangerously unfit_ to lead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aluminiumilism Murder at the tennis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Federer is G.O.A.T.  It's not even a competition. Be honest with yourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@se_collins Sarah Collins = FAKE NEWS. Very sad, liberal bias in all tweets. Looking forward to Britain visit with friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PG3_12 The funny part is she didn't say a word whilst filming it. Or after. There was _no screaming_.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PG3_12 Ignoring the ad, which is comical - why is the default response of the hysterical Twitter user "IM SCREAMING"??  ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Jurgen Klopp has a worse win ratio at Liverpool (47.7%) than David Moyes had at Manchester United (52.9%)"

But it's definitely their year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#KloppOut

Foreign manager doesn't get a winter break and falters... can't gegenpress for 50 odd games without issues. #Trolololololol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ally__cakes My pizza was better. Fight me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CCMariners Get out. Don't even bother with your coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst part about that Scum Cunt's red card? Perth still had a sub left. We were _thisclose_ to an outfield player in goal. #CCMvPER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're missing out @Ally__cakes... (@ Joe's Pizza in Gosford, NSW) https://t.co/cvfjy4PB98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Orange, shit. Same difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner You foolish man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counter-attack, ily. &lt;3 

#CCMvPER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at Bluetongue Central Coast Stadium for Central Coast Mariners v Perth Glory in Gosford, NSW https://t.co/7w7tFlzmkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner All about dem clicks and click $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Back in my day, Time was the shiznit for long form stories. Now it's complete and utter clickbait trash on the BuzzFeed level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenwaw @iron_tyson87 Ever since, _fuckin' everywhere_.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenwaw @iron_tyson87 We randomly saw some dude wearing it the other week walking to Joes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thurbs62 Has the prodigal son returned to the microblogging world?  :-o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner It's alright. CCM will be here to consistently disappoint and give you the grounding you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Oh you fool. You foolish fool. What have you done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gatty54 @Lukejbyrne Arnold wishes this team was CCM 2.0 - we actually won things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Danny beaten low and to his left.

I am shocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That counterattack. My pants. Sploosh. #MVCvSYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They don't take a backwards step do Sydney"

*literally 4 backwards passes ending at the keeper ensue*

Never change Andy. #MVCvSYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold's patented collapse/choke starts here. Come on Victory. #MVCvSYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Ally__cakes @Grogbottle_ Now this was a fun night. https://t.co/MYQwKIUwmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aluminiumilism 50 000??

Same person counting the crowd in that photo must count the crowd at CCM games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public holiday + Big Blue = altered schedule. (@ Oporto in Erina, NSW, Australia) https://t.co/dEHwJLBJzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Jurgen Flopp amirite? League Cup is only a Mickey Mouse Cup. Everyone out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 League Cup is just a Mickey Mouse comp., right? ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenwaw Well if you have no idea, the rest of us are fucked. I don't even think my Spotify has anything from 2016 on it. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A _privileged white man_ won Australian of the Year? Oh that's just got to piss off all the right people in all the right ways.  ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well then... Trump isn't fucking around.  ðŸ˜ https://t.co/3CECJZrl2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@brenwaw The Tool Shed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You appear to have surprised me, eating a carrot. We are now at an impasse." https://t.co/uorfb75U5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some pertinent advice for the far-left re: tomorrow. Your hashtag slacktivism means less than nothing. https://t.co/mKhYasDgia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A free (!!) tip for journalists/media.

"So and so reacted with outrage on Twitter" is not a story. Never has been, never will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slim_rusty Some of my favourite people don't even use USB. And let me tell you, they're the best people. Just the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slim_rusty Or just iOS in general. 

Copy and Paste? People won't want that until Version 5.... right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisIs_Alicia https://t.co/9CWrZFUldW

"It is the successor to Mickey Mouse Clubhouse."  WHAT?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spoonyman STOP TRIGGERING ME.  TWITTER IS MY SAFE SPACE - the Left, probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump inaugurated and the Patriots going to another Superbowl.

This is why we can't have nice things.  #EvilEmpiresUnite #NFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at The Man Nook in Gosford https://t.co/p3FB075MpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valencia does one thing and one thing only... the fact it continues to confuse left backs around the league amuses me. #STKMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Rooney is about to come on though.  ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Did I not say my mocking would cost us a win? When will you people listen to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Izzo is still fucking shit. Makes world class saves and lets in stupid shit 2 seconds later. Not reliable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Roy's chance conversion rate is fucking abysmal. Wildly behind the rest of the league.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner I'd wipe the entire squad aside from Tavares, Pain, Galloway and _maybe_ Izzo (as a desperate backup - keepers aren't everywhere).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner ...Neill do upon receiving it??  Sprint for 15 metres and then checks the run. Lets them regain their shape. Then back to Izzo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner "Mild jog" is what fucks me off more than anything. When Tavares was playing, he has a wicked strong pass to his left. What does...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner With our powers combined we couldn't be as bad. At least I wouldn't check every single attacking run I ever do. EVERY. SINGLE. ONE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner I was a left back during our time at Mingara. Just saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If not for insane goalkeeping and the post, Pogba would have scored 5 or 6 world class goals already this season. #STKMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner We do not speak his name. It is only to be cursed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Never said you wereCALM DOWN FARKIN'.

Zlatan is bae. Zlatan will score when he wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Not at all. Okon isn't the greatest, but Charlesworth is the real problem. Either go fans trust or oil billionaire. Fuck him off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner I'd say "don't you mean dirty traitor", but our pikey cunt of an owner won't fork out for anything, so... y'know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Wilkinson is running around at Sydney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Yesm.  Everyone coming back to the Bay, Year 1 gear if you've got it etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Strange man.

P.S. Are you coming to Retro Round next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Gin and tonic??  Are you some weird jazz guy from the 20's??  Or are you doing the whole "mature" thing??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoke people sound angry.

Mind you, I'd be angry if I had to live in Stoke as well.  #STKMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner If Fellaini scores a double I'll.... well, I won't really do anything because knowing our luck it will happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Fellaini is starting. My problems are infinitely worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 No winter break man, I'm telling you.  No coinkydink that you and City are starting to slip (HA) a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner I read that as 'rag' and I thought I'd discovered one of your fetishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Roy being carded and your weekend being ruined implied you had hope we'd get a result. I admire the optimism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4burner Please. My taunting here has sealed our loss and you know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iron_tyson87 Wait a second... I just turned on your game and you're losing??  But... THIS is your year??  And Kloppball!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I just heard @KevinAirs442 in The Shed... #HereWeHereWeHereWeFuckinGo #PERvMVC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>