<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenRHHW @MdmAbsentMinded This Bowling Green Massacre?? https://t.co/KICL3RBFV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_R_Walker @canthavepudding THAT'S a massacre!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nobby15 @TheWillowGhost @9NewsAUS From she who created the Bowling Green Massacre that was on the same day as the Cricket Pitch Massacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuentinDempster @BloggerMe3 @billshortenmp #ShillBorten just doesn't have the same ring to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol "Move along sir, we don't want any #Trumble" https://t.co/a1ht4UWMZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPascoe01 @juliecorb @JimmyKimmelLive Isn't it a sort of grain?...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@64AnthonyP @FlatEarthGang Could have been worst for him. The T-shirt could have said #TuckFrumble....#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_ComputRepair Jeez! Whatever happened to Bumble? He hasn't shuffled off the mortal coil has he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol BREAKING: Pauline Hanson accuses Iraqi refugees of committing the Cricket Pitch massacre.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trojanaras @FailGOP Not to forget the Baseball Diamond massacre......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dacollar1 @earthtoreform A Ms Consherway.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Britanniacomms Bet that's duty free she got on her trip on the Trans Siberian Express!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illchangethis @RBJRON @MichaelWestBiz @CEFCAus Get the kids down the mine!! That will increase profits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBJRON @MichaelWestBiz @CEFCAus Let's face it, to the LNP this is innovation....#auspol https://t.co/1E3sIF17mT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illchangethis @nobby15 @randlight Come on! Cheer up. He's achieved this in only two weeks! Three to go before we hit 100%.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@de_facto_Aus Interesting a US conservative commentator alluded to #Trump acting like her 3 year old son. Not a problem at 3 but at 70!....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janer98 Or does he work for #PresidentBannon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol #TuckFrump and #TuckFrumble too.... https://t.co/ZIfqbYeacf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annekbrooks @Magpie1954nBird Or you can annoy with and send this pick of 2 female fighter pilots who… https://t.co/UK1Tm88UvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol White House spokesman Shawna Splicer praises former Australian PM Howard John......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheWhoVotes @Ic206Bones Potential war crimes indictments?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoEdwardsson @HeleneBlanchard Thanks! A coffee stain on my shirt now!😊😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yackheather @ezlusztig Looks like the USA is going to have to start using this sign.... https://t.co/Kk3tD3FSXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janinesymons @Triplejay58 'Bowling Green' is a town in Kentucky where 2 Iraqi nationals were arrested for was crimes commited in Iraq.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Time to get #TuckFrump trending..... https://t.co/hxvXNqrByI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@64AnthonyP @PhillipCoorey I think as a mark of respect we need to try and get #TuckFrump trending #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol And to really piss off #PresidentBannon and #FauxPresidentTrump North Korean fighter pilots. #dresslikewomen https://t.co/jfs06b4WK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thematador66 @BloggerMe3 Very good point. It will be #PerisentBannon from now on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind He meant to say Germanphobe....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhysam @Linzz_1 #Trump's White House is obviously the first to have it's own resident drug dealer #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlohaMsLonesome @Triplejay58 Spicer? No! It's Shawna Splicer.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @Pammieoz @9NewsAUS Time for an #ANZUSexit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlohaMsLonesome @teakingw As confirmed by WH spokesman Shawna Splicer....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Who is the US at war with at the moment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markustonius @SuDharmapala A mere threrat to pull out of ANZUS, close Pine Gape and Exmouth Comms station would see #Trump pulled in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveFGriffin Hopefully by someone exercising their 2nd amendment rights? Or a military coup....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveFGriffin And rumble and dumb bell...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaineBlackadder Not only that but the use of #Trumble has barely caused a rumble in Canberra...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaIffland @upbeatme And the Exmouth naval communications base!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN Guaranteed to further enrage PHON voters. The Chicko Roll is their party's political cuisine...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happyloner @ForQ2 I'm amazed that 'sudden organ failure' is so common as a cause of death in Russia....Maybe the vodka?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@openpodbaydoor_ @mhmck @MdmAbsentMinded Thanks, that's what I thought but wanted clarification.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LesStonehouse @Smile__Petal Looks more like a Gumby than a Nob......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xSpycraft @belungerer Oh how the mighty tumble.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol BREAKING: White House spokesman Shawna Splicer mispronounces Aussie PM Turnbull as #Trumble. President Frump not amused...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@openpodbaydoor_ @mhmck @MdmAbsentMinded Sorry, what is KIA and WIA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Talk about ironic. It's taken the NeoNazi #Trump to reignite the offshore detention debate in Australia #Bringthemhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LelHulagirl63 Remembering his amazing skill negotiating with the cross benchers in the Senate when he was Treasurer! #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet @johnsalmond But he was up at 3am on Twitter......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhmck @MdmAbsentMinded Interesting timing for a Russian attack on Ukraine. Any comment from #Trump????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJopinion @johnsalmond @KarlRove @WSJ Correction: It's not 'Amateur hour', it's a whole amateur four years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VickiPlatt5 @TheBigShip Sycophantic LNP fawning.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol The headline that should have been: "#TRUMP TRAMPLES TREMBLING #TRUMBLE".....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@64AnthonyP @LarryShort777 Prime Minister Trumble??? Hell, I'm all a tremble....#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SumerSloan It's not only Pine Gap we host. There is also the NW Cape submarine communication facility. Critical to the USN....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjhelliar @demon_dave It's also been reported that PM Trumble makes the US President's knees tremble......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 @pinkbunny70 'Sudden organ failure' seems to be a major cause of death in Russia.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: #Trump will (for at least the next hour) 'respect' deal made with Prime Minister 'Trunbull'  https://t.co/cvNqfTznWu via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: PHON needs some extreme vetting: Rodney Culleton was never elected to Senate, High Court rules https://t.co/OiijxMDRq0 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevJohnst @TheNewDailyAu Agreed. And we've known it for a while...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: The car-making tragedy that must never be repeated | The New Daily https://t.co/qMxBoOKTKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Govt slammed by experts, rebuffed by industry, over ‘clean coal’ power stations | The New Daily https://t.co/Lkn6457p4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: Donald Trump unleashes on refugee deal again: ‘I respect Australia, but we have a problem’ | The New Daily https://t.co/tLNmWcHbIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: Donald Trump pulls the rug out from Malcolm Turnbull’s ‘dumb deal’ | The New Daily https://t.co/uf55uTWtZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European parliament leaders call on EU to reject Trump's likely ambassador pick https://t.co/xvLwLrYzPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: Turnbull tries out shirtfronting Trump as a way to handle the bully-in-chief | Katharine Murphy https://t.co/812JjgRork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol #DonationReform #FederalICAC: Dark money: $70 million in major party income is untraceable https://t.co/XWam8Beyfw via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: Springsteen had just the song to mock Trump-Turnbull call at Melbourne gig https://t.co/qLkgiuT1MC via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol #Trump defends 'tough' phone calls as John McCain expresses 'unwavering' support for Australia https://t.co/GoAiUb4gUB via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol: 'We are sorry': US media, congressmen stunned Trump has picked fight with Australia https://t.co/xQacqKNyfs via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol #ANZUSExit time?: Wake up Australia: the US alliance has never been our security 'guarantee'  https://t.co/45KOqTreiJ via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zippuli @Frankscan1965 His CV says he is younger than Mark Holden but he  may in fact be Mark Holden. At last making a mark as an actor....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrubbellAtMill @TurnbullMalcolm Hmmm....Is #Trump funding Cory's #BernaziParty????? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LelHulagirl63 @hayden45117324 @happy_dingo @mindychops Happy to help! Freedom of speech does not equal freedom of bigotry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happy_dingo @LelHulagirl63 @hayden45117324 @mindychops And with 1 follower this is what happens to trolls...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian @Bolwen How will the Poms take to a sausage sizzle.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DomV3 @Forthleft2 @theage @TurnbullMalcolm There is no 'Art of the deal' in international relations. It is subtley and empathy..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterPyke @BabushkaThe It's important Anzac day comes back to being a day of contemplation. Not jingoism..#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LelHulagirl63 Poor @hayden45117324 10 blocks and he's locked out of his account. I'll start...@happy_dingo @mindychops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Err @LelHulagirl63 what neurons? @happy_dingo is clearly brain dead. To be generous. @mindychops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His ex-wives are threatening to sue him for non-payment of alimony #ReasonsTrumpHangsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathywilcox1 @johngleeson52 That's a PLAN!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camillavalerie_ @4589roger That looks like a 4 bottle of Bourbon a day face.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJManring @AliasEleanor Given #Trump's age and diet. I suspect more like this....😡💩💩💩😡😡💩💩💩💩💩💩😡😡😡💩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucerossbrc 'Golden showers fill your eyes. #Trump awaits you when you smile.'(apologies to Lennon/ McCartney) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol A madman in charge of a gun infested asylum: Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/VIVH1edsGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KoparaFallsKid @TomthunkitsMind Thank you! I'm surprised after 8am stage 2 of major dental surgery!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahbrian @xskinn @JohnWren1950 It was $20K in Cabcharge. But you are correct. The old 'Treasurer for Sale']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@extinctsymbol Golf merely spoils a pleasant walk.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahbrian @xskinn @JohnWren1950 Hockey then can face his criminal trial for defrauding the people through misuse of Cabcharge #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Time to cancel #ANZUS: Pragmatic to pugnacious: how Donald Trump deals with Malcolm Turnbull https://t.co/IJGJmCxGlh via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Bishop is buying shoes. At the taxpayers expense...#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Or #Fascist: USA?Twitter diplomacy: Trump trades words with friends and foes on social media https://t.co/dhsmeRhOEY via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Brilliant article: Trumplomacy: Malcolm Turnbull learns Donald Trump doesn't 'make nice' https://t.co/PT9jZyxWId via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DagnyDelinquent Use your #ObamaCare to have your mental problems treated...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PinarooRay @PolAnimalAus @Rory_Medcalf I had forgotten about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizBuff46 There have been 0 Americans killed by refugees form the banned countries ever...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DagnyDelinquent @PhilipRucker @AshleyLeahy Is this how #Trump followers relate to your country's (for now) allies? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DagnyDelinquent @PhilipRucker @AshleyLeahy Aware that the tracking station for nuclear missiles is located in Australia? Close it and?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmannell @HelpRefugeesOZ @TurnbullMalcolm @PeterDutton_MP The story is big in the US at present...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>