<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@reefa_k @cboehm @TedDMeyer I thought OKC folded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun #DCU fact— Cristian Castillo is in b-roll footage of a PSA for @BeA_Donor that loops at the DMV. Drumming in the stands, not playing. 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EHolmes Go West, young lady. Congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a weird photo to pick, @espn. Weird 4-armed @M_Ryan02? https://t.co/cceNHQYM15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfntly What about cats? They are very opinionated and probably hate the same politicians I hate. And love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your breath. The city will be stinky for a few days. https://t.co/gcnwmg0NWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's feeling real. Surreal. https://t.co/3GWJ4yKAm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSist Also, see Pinchy, Stampy, Mojo, et. al.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @uber is either sitting at the drive thru getting dinner or picking someone up who can't decide on a 6 or 9-piec… https://t.co/zLAkhgpEnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #FancyBeerThursday entry was imported to DC from @ChucksHopShopCD. Sophisticated, tasty @NoLiBrewhouse Tandem.… https://t.co/Kp0KGK2hgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartfelt thanks to @AshleighAxios &amp; @kodiakstarr for your work. Often think of the @aigadc event when @petesouza d… https://t.co/YWtG30KB8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSist How dare you take that outside with the roads doused in salt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far theyve gotten married and divorced and changed names and gone to the end of the universe. https://t.co/a43FKRnctd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday. https://t.co/BgCYcIHC72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totes hillair. https://t.co/Xy09qnp370]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that S. Bijou has come to its senses, I hope @MeatsAndFoods will come to its senses and charge $95 for chilitos. They're that good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon I am a terrible host, but that was pretty cool. Good job #Periscope360]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen this movie before. It's hilarious. https://t.co/zrNV0mS6yv https://t.co/S2FNNYWqfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @Dcunited come in at #6 on @sportslogosnet best new logos of the year. @BSteelFC is 3rd. https://t.co/4qfh1f6E4N #DOOP #DCU #MLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping Edgar Martinez gets into the @MLB Hall of Fame. Gave so much to the game without the usual ego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one hell of a photo. https://t.co/iANQHy9Zgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanafry Is that Deuce's track at the end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @AmericanOutlaws @ColdAsBryan Yes. But it's also Montenegro's and was Albania's up until 2014. https://t.co/3s7sUTyiqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marvelle Wait...did you photoshop those tweets? Dammit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiltedvet You and @thepugdc have too many shared interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WashingtonDC_CM Here's to more in 2017! Thanks to @VigilanteCoffee for waking me up &amp; @Studio_Theatre for the great seats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfntly I'M CURRENTLY SKEPTICAL ABOUT THE KERNING OF THAT NON-ITALICIZED APOSTROPHE. #typesharting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We loved today's #FancyBeerThursday, an IPA collabo from @MikkellerBeer &amp; @anchoragebrew. A-O-K, esp @keith_shore's… https://t.co/ZiMjN4KZ2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boxbrown With the cessation of @tonymillionaire's Drinky Crow this week, I welcome Death's icy grip, and submit to his wishes. ~ fin ~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlight of biking in today— wind blowing me sideways, causing me to come within inches of crashing into a parked M3. WHEEEEEEEEEEshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfntly Get your Cheeto-mits off my jersey. https://t.co/pHjBOqORHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye's the trending story, while Rick Perry is the actual story. I'm dangerously close to becoming one of those "wake up sheeple!" folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hey, @Shutterstock, can you tell me how many times this photo has been purchased? Great stuff.… https://t.co/o6tBaGwita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EthanWhite15 @MLSist is over here crying like a proud papa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never thought I'd hear the lines "This white on white Maybach, I call it payback" on NPR. Fantastic. https://t.co/2WE9D1lks9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSist ROBE Issue #1 cover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon Vine hall of fame, along with @sonyakarate's masterpiece, "Pirlo Motionless at the Near Post" https://t.co/orNp5Pxv5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cboehm I heard #SWASUN turned down a SXSW gig for 2017. Too corporate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas station find in Windhoek. We can't have any fun in the US anymore... https://t.co/HhPCNLzL2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A co-worker just microwaved fish in the office kitchen. Goodbye cruel world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo selection. From 9 years ago. #flickrproblems https://t.co/MpRe2gQJSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerrinsheldon @kylesheldon @NolanSheldon A high-pitched fart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep one eye on the the main issue, one eye on what he's using to distract. It's critical to rebut both. https://t.co/9OeSywLlf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our flag is a symbol. It's power lies in representing something greater than the object. You can't destroy free speech w/ a lighter. (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, I'm officially back in the saddle, and pissed. This is outrageous. Be 100% aware of any attempts at chipping… https://t.co/g1qbeWvHfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepugdc The handsome gentleman in that photo is a fellow 2003 @StOlaf grad, @chapman4council. #themoreyouknow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jennifer_10_25 @kylesheldon He's also handsome. Magic and handsome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bout to swing through @MeatsAndFoods for some veggie chili and a dawg. https://t.co/eQDeL6Tjtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbridge @NationalZoo The orangutan ropes not good enough for ya? #OLine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was digging through my computer last night and found this gem. I should have made it a Matchday program cover.… https://t.co/bk2NulE0sS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cboehm @chestrockwell14 I think 1 in 5 tweets to each other are about BB. Like lighting votive candles in a Montenegrin chapel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hardywood Barrel Series for #FancyBeerThursday (due to Turkey Day). Nice rye flavor. @erleofmartin https://t.co/Ug2b58uRFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You advocate to block the wind farm that would ruin my golf course's view &amp; I'll tweet support for you to occupy a… https://t.co/DOKxBxn3eb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing that familiar Bruce Arena scowl again. #USMNT https://t.co/CGmP5VPRIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy's back. Go get it kid. https://t.co/QFp72j8g1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamilton's pretty terrible. So is our vice-president elect. Next topic please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon @NolanSheldon @kerrinsheldon Just kidding. I hate that show with venom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updated favorite Sheldon rankings (as of 4pm):
1.) @kylesheldon 
2.) Sheldon from The Big Bang Theory
3.) @NolanSheldon 
4.) @kerrinsheldon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon @NolanSheldon @kerrinsheldon Not very impressed with the silent Sheldons tagged here. I'm going to have to update the ratings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon @NolanSheldon @kerrinsheldon Of course. Kerrin is currently sitting in second place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily one of my top 3 favorite Sheldon brothers. https://t.co/O5MUUEc4Od]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alex_Caulfield @ChrisPontius13 Atta way Christopher. https://t.co/7j4mnIiTnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cboehm Big Al has a way with words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found a #NeverNude on Shutterstock. You are not alone, @davidcrosss. https://t.co/fkoenZNwwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip for citizens feeling sucker punched by election results: watch Cameo's "Candy" — https://t.co/c4PE7yrXnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Palin or Forrest Lucas possible Sec. of the Interior? Can't fathom the possible damage to our public lands.… https://t.co/IzDdgbrwPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alecko11 Yep— second time in NYC. Not close to a P.R. but it was a gorgeous day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alecko11 Dude! I didn't know you ran it too. Congrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattheweide Nope. Left shortly after my pap photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former #MLS / #DCU man Joseph Ngwenya is running the NYC Marathon today. https://t.co/vLzv0n8A4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to running the @nycmarathon this Sunday. https://t.co/1SQFviWt0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCU_Exile @chestrockwell14 @seanny_law Not even the most sophomoric of trolls could bring themselves to vote no. Well maybe a NYRB fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kottke That video just moved and sorted a membership. Thanks for years of content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSist "he said last night at Tramps, his favorite Georgetown disco." #filmanddiscoarentdead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelDanger19 @sporcle that was very entertaining. 13, for the record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Murray just sang "Take Me Out to the Ballgame" w/ Daffy Duck'th littthp. This is the most American thing ever &amp; I'm so proud. #FlyTheW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfntly Bragging about doing something different is half the appeal. "It was so...*organic*! The chef was impressed with my take on gluten."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Ive would be the most annoying dinner guest of all time. He'd talk about the subtle curves on the tines of his fork for an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLerner I legit hovered over the unfollow button tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well at least Christian Gomez didn't spit on anybody. #dcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cubs back-to-back, now #DCU knockout game. I can do this. https://t.co/coHkGN6kPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise, sunset. Swiftly flow the days. https://t.co/uuLK8wtFHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MNUFC @scottrainy Purty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaMBregman Patience grasshopper. Lots of baseball left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyapdavidson @michael_deforge I have books from both of you. Worry about what you do, and there are plenty of us to support it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyapdavidson @michael_deforge People have been mumbling "I could've done that." while skimming art for centuries. Inarticulate and lazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_wiebe #DCU isn't dead yet because @MLSist still has a couple of unused rolls of film sitting in his underwear drawer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This playoffs campaign is...not good. #MLS https://t.co/xmDQuYQjDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so it shall be— @brad_snook @DougCFSC @LisaMBregman &amp; Mahler vs. @APritch18 for the WS trophy. Let's go.… https://t.co/G1vpIrkw8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord have mercy. Those Cubbies are close... #FlyTheW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the #Bartman hour. Stay strong, Cubs fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @SeanDennisonMLS Reminds me of the classic @kylesheldon Mahler joint. https://t.co/sSSOLA3HVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swathes vs. Swatches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong. https://t.co/JbOWYOJX5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJentleson Was this a Cubs or Clinton tweet? Either way I agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about the poor Chinese steel worker? Doesn't he work hard? Doesn't he have a family?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erleofmartin Get back to work. https://t.co/3FGFAqnd8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylesheldon @RyanKras That's some gud mafematix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSist I assumed it was cat hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYCFC @dcunited You're still misspelling your opponent's name. #CmonBro https://t.co/qJepHmluNq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>