<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGingerRachel how does your hair smell? It it a natural thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGingerRachel maybe it's just the smell of red hair...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman haha nah, it's just my first choice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this mean people will finally stop calling P.Caps "the new doctor"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but everything begins again, too, and that’s always happy. #doctorwho #series11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ends, and its always sad.... #doctorwho #series10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just checked the wedding playlist, I am about to dance for at least 10 straight tracks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow my sister gets married. Tomorrow shall be a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara @fauxparse rooms been filled sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love White House Down because of how unashamedly Left Wing it was. I'd like to see the whole thing re-purposed for Trump's presidency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love them to make White House Down again this year, but the heroes are the people trying to take down the house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutumnAurelia I'd love one of these!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could be given help. It's cruelty to animals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate to think he's using the dog for money, or even lying about it. But if it is sick, he can't support it and I wish the dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am seriously worried about the homeless guy's dog on Willis Street. The guy has a sign saying "my dog is sick".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory, put Trump in the cupboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Last Jedi eh? I'm kinda disappointed that we now have 2 of the 8 Star Wars film sharing a last title word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've started having Breath of the Wild dreams...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never get sick of discussing films with people! I want even more opportunities to do so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked for a sauce recommendation at @subwaynz that would go well with a breakfast sub. I was just told "any sauce". Love the confidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyHayley_ @thatkatierose ahhh! Just offered it to someone who accepted sorry :( was a mad rush to get it sorted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems to be just as hard to find a new flatmate as it is to find a new flat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still looking for someone to take the other room in my Haining Street flat in Wellington! Any leads would be much appreciated :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewatched Dredd yet again, freaking incredible film. I'm still hopeful that someday we will get a sequel #dredd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the way that Resident Evil Revelations structures it's game like episodes of a TV show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimsEloise Michael Jackson, Elvis Presley, The Beatles... Toby Keith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutumnAurelia @skasocks it's my favourite film of all time :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tenani Team Carey? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicScale I'm also curious to see if they'll offer discounts if we've previously bought games on the VC, rather than rebuying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicScale ahhh gotcha. It's quite telling that the best Wii U games I played were the HD remastered Zeldas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicScale We've had HD Twilight Princess on Wii U.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington! If you or someone you know is looking for a flat, the other room in my place is available. Get in touch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tenani sorry but what the fuck is that tower of bread supposed to be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara is that because you're not American?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I better be able to buy this in New Zealand! https://t.co/S1OeYsJzZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to be social this evening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bySaraMichelle and Star Wars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bySaraMichelle Encouraging unrelated news, Domhnall was the 3rd most viewed actor on Letterboxd in 2016!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know a lot of the world doesn't agree, but I truly and deeply adore The Hobbit Trilogy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilzg2000 When the new series hits I'd be down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilzg2000 Youtube! The trailer was good, I'm so keen for new episodes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilzg2000 Yeah it was just a big time sink for me. I enjoyed the episode though! Obviously not the best one ever but it wasn't trying to be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a fan of how loud the wind was last night :Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mc_or_mac one of the  best cinematic moments ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe we're only 2 months away from Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just put in a huge amazon order for blurays/DVDs..... so glorious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara Isn't that just the natural state of being for a human?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roman_nvmerals I got hobbit on the brain!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGingerRachel about 73% of time time I have no idea what you're tweeting about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bySaraMichelle she and Ingrid Oliver need to start a club...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ameliabeing I'm starting to think he may have been created in a lab....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara Your shower regime is interesting. XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watching The Extended Version of the Battle of the Five Armies and it's already so glorious!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we all lost stars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am shit at beer pong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimsEloise should we just start preemptively smashing everything in the world? The element of surprise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara or lay siege to the houses of the friends who can’t hang?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara more-so looks very sad to me! https://t.co/LceG4e3O2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara mine shows a face on the brink of tears!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara that was not meant to make you sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara I didn't. I am the correct human in this world = there was no EQ here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara so now you can move to Wellington? Kthanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there was an earthquake? Did not feel that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-watched Sweeney Todd. Definitely the best film Tim Burton's made! One of my favourite screen musicals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a car with wings... yet it somehow does this! https://t.co/iy5M0nAC38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's spread our wings. FLY AWAY! https://t.co/UsGMf3hjsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to Wellington...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_zeltik if only there were a new Zelda game coming out…. oh wait..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, the new years cut-offs are hitting me full force this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like that your body (or my body) puts me right off alcohol after a big night so that I don't touch it again for ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapas at the Machin's! https://t.co/W0bQLfFkhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could not be more ready for a new series of Doctor Who! #doctorwho @bbcdoctorwho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nadineee what a charming person they are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did also die laughing last night. Sadly I cannot fit the reason why into a single tweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 2017! Big plans are a foot. First days plan: kick this hangover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year so soon!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiclara reasons?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxPattyx so that's a thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year party!!! https://t.co/j3UzBHiYpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhAliceZelda worst night to do that!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley I love talking Doctor Who with people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley watched it as it came out! Clara is my Bae. Class is fun! Very different from doctor who though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley I will hold my opinion until I see her in action (I loved last season btws)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley did you love the special???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley I'm counting down!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when you find those people who you could text all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman You’re our only hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy beach! https://t.co/HJN1CztgQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Debbie Reynolds for inspiring me to continue tap dancing while growing up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetpjeb23 follow me so I can dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinGoolsby you better get on that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For goodness sake, this freaking planet!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She gave me a high 5!!! https://t.co/2yAncaLPT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor Who time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost some followers today due to my obsessive Christmas photo posts XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional MACHIN Christmas tipsy darts tournament! https://t.co/CUNkOryEdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the second year running... you had one job Dad! https://t.co/FSke5cEYWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Round one complete! https://t.co/wXbdGp61uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Round 1 https://t.co/74XAeXnGzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS CHARASMAWRIST!!!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>