<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not hard making your customers happy. Showing appreciation for their business is the perfect way to keep them… https://t.co/fgoH7ny9xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a customer is easy. Keeping them is the hard part. Be deliberate and constantly train your staff. https://t.co/eM0qV3egxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those in Canberra (or near by), I will be having another half day round table event in March. Limited spots... https://t.co/6DJtY8eUgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NAB wow. Awesome time to go down. Still waiting. Merry Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes being a business owner you may feel like giving up. You may feel like you have nothing left to give or... https://t.co/9enlS69Rm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ato_gov_au greatwork with your system this morning. website is out for days now spend ages typing in number to b hung up on automatically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/Dwx6fP7m3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra it was supposed to be sorted 72 hours ago. Sheesh. Telstra is a great advertisement for Optus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra Wait. So you want me to let you know how your inefficient and crap service works out after me, the customer, gets it sorted? Ahh no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra because they haven't started working on it yet. Pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra seriously?? When you say you will fix something in 24 hours, 72 hours ago... saying it will take "another 24 hours " doesn't work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hidden in Plain Sight" https://t.co/XkiljLdLNZ by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start 2017 with a bang. Book a 1 hour mentoring session with Justin this year and know exactly what you need to... https://t.co/qq18WyM0FO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start 2017 with a bang. Book a 1 hour mentoring session with Justin this year and know exactly what you need to... https://t.co/ekO1SWgSVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thetempleskincare's photo https://t.co/W4fsKMVYQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out "The cycle of a sale. Get greater/easier sales and create referral machines" https://t.co/mTA7lIv2u6 @Eventbrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/vsUEQLFW0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop wasting $$ on campaigns that "may" increase your sales if you haven't yet tapped into your past and present... https://t.co/gu3EENXhl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long to go now for my half day sales seminar. Learn the easier ways to close the sale, up sell and get repeat... https://t.co/1szKIZINjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those people waiting for the details of my half day sales training seminar on the Gold Coast on the 26th of... https://t.co/3MikJDIkHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple awesome job with my new iPhone 7 #hypeaboutnothing https://t.co/tUOrtrMzb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/MBgjWfqtrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyDomains what a crap company. Got new domain and you released my contact details to 3rd party companies. over 60 unsolicited emails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out "The cycle of a sale. Get greater/easier sales and create referral machines" https://t.co/mTA7lIdrCy @Eventbrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to grab your tickets to my upcoming half day Sales training event. 
If you have staff that need that... https://t.co/LxCqjIur3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just put up the event details for my upcoming half day training on how to sell more, how to close the sale... https://t.co/k1cvYhxzmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my new mentoring clients has launched her new product for horse riders globally. Great idea to keep the... https://t.co/P3zwpGzZtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of funky sayings out there in business land. A lot of the time people think they are doing things... https://t.co/GefctclKCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to do a radio interview (around 1.10pm) with Chris Smith on 2GB (873am) on bad customer service trends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["4 Types Of Unfortunate Customer Service Trends" https://t.co/ZTMZbYHXar by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day ahead with a stack of new mentoring clients having their first session. Love seeing what people are... https://t.co/N3CgKpwoiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple maybe if your developers had to pay for their new phones they would make sure they live up to the perceived hype. Same old same old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple very underwhelmed with your new phone. Compared with a 6s side by side tonight and in all aspects no difference. Big Bang but fizzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billquiseng thanks for the retweet Bill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Does Your Service Suck?" https://t.co/sXSlcp8J1Y by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra as was I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra send I via post. Wanted to k ow when I could pre order and trade in current phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra have "new phone feeling" and wanted to pre order iPhone 7 but in store just in case you guys say my current one is "damaged" if I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra yes I was. Finally got on to someone but to be honest mate, your company really needs to train your staff as they don't know anythi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra hey Telstra, if your Rouse Hill NSW store shuts at 9pm why won't anyone answer the phone? Service please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out my latest article
"Word Of Mouse" https://t.co/OoyaoPJlVu by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smartest way to get your customers referring #referal #leadgeneration #ravingfans https://t.co/eJD4aat7eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have been wondering how my mentoring program would work for your business, send me a private message with... https://t.co/WGQBekqJPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From T-shirts to tech, make referrals easy for customers https://t.co/TPsQrOYHdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/vuncwtO00o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's little rant... Well not really a rant, more of an encouragement. Enjoy and share. https://t.co/nmUnXk8yf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's episode https://t.co/e7GsCJIX0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Herald   Conference Keynote 2014 https://t.co/3C9CkOp8O5 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to give a successful presentation. https://t.co/JeNGyLjoaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How to give a successful presentation.   " https://t.co/Ioj9G9FIvP by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ReferUs. The new and easier way to turn your customers into referral machines https://t.co/MrtZq1uIce via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andreabeatss hi Andrea, would love to show you our new start up ReferUs that has totally changed the way a business gets referrals. global]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[excited. Share with anyone you know who has a start up, want to start a business or has a business that they want... https://t.co/QGgZV8fw0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's a better way to get your customers referring" https://t.co/GQiyu4fq92 by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mastersau wow. Your rouse hill store is the best advertisement for your competitor Bunnings. Pathetic service one again. #consistent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had some amazing new mentoring clients sign up this week. If you are looking for some guidance or someone to hold... https://t.co/FCMSxBNWpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GM_amchamnsw @Green_Dot @AmChamAU @amchamnsw thanks for having me speak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[looking to get your business to the next level? https://t.co/zvEnMXAokB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you need a bit of guidance and direction with your business, why not have a look at my mentoring packages.... https://t.co/wTFzFiQUMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite 4 letter word. https://t.co/hlf44tYMup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's edition of The analogy series https://t.co/tZmCW1YoNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don’t forget to train your staff." https://t.co/K17otr5MD8 by @jherald on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune in in 20 mins for this weeks Facebook Live segment https://t.co/81RXEd4Xwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My introductory 1 month mentoring program was launched yesterday. It's been great connecting with new business... https://t.co/edJrNKkqSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If success was easy everyone would be successful https://t.co/d8EiOpemhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you constantly come across people asking you if you can recommend a speaker for their conference then why not... https://t.co/8M9ZBC7tPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Perception is Fact" by @jherald on @LinkedIn https://t.co/7tfrClgLt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest article for Hair Biz magazine just landed https://t.co/mbNoUp3O9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first episode in a weekly series called "The analogy series" https://t.co/dm3rINC9FK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find the right people to do business with. https://t.co/RfbeuFbnpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How desperate you are to succeed will be proved by how hard you are willing to work for it, regardless of how... https://t.co/uBosk6Fj44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[big things happening with https://t.co/4Da4ekyEHS right now. Loving the whole blowing business owners minds about what you can do these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garyvee hey mate. love your work. thought you might like my story.  https://t.co/autBc0Klei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's filming https://t.co/GJIrWE7orW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart business owners have mentors as they know the power of someone else's success in their own journey. Make... https://t.co/r096trjLV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now there's an easier way to get your customers referring for your business. Make it easy for them https://t.co/w9MK39w4Uj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now there's an easier way to get your customers referring for your business. Your business on all of your... https://t.co/QasrV0PkYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aplusk now a way for businesses to turn customers into referral machines = massive reach https://t.co/4Da4ekyEHS https://t.co/P7fMu4PE2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, after many many requests, I am launching a new mentoring program called "Total Business Mentoring". As my... https://t.co/Ynw9wIup09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's episode https://t.co/phTYaiXF01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next episode of https://t.co/bjIEMNNkYu is starting in about 20 minutes. Tune in on the Facebook page and feel free to ask questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day today with 2 new business owners starting with my in my Entrepreneurs Mentor Club (love working with... https://t.co/lyu6EFzFaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay true to yourself and your beliefs https://t.co/xmV3rJo7PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come and listen at 12pm as we talk about sales and selling and cut out the BS https://t.co/Rwhg1asXKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra you send me forms to ask me to prove that your crap service has affected my business. Ummm maybe see how many times I have rung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra you are a joke. Not only have I been waiting for 2 months to get my internet and phone sorted, when I seek compensation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to go live. Come and join us https://t.co/nj3jQIWVdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Rich and i will be discussing the topic of Triumph over Troubles in business. If you are having issues or... https://t.co/8YH1lqPAjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do want your customers to be referral machines for your business? Check out https://t.co/4Da4ekyEHS and be on all of your customers phones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting recognition globally for https://t.co/4Da4ekyEHS https://t.co/ZzCkxmeiNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/MAWTseoFVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are curious about how ReferUs can be the best thing for your business, we are holding a free webinar... https://t.co/oHdGejcca1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra and on the system it says a level 2 tech needs to attend. So trouble shooting over phone is useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra last week but they told me a tech would call to do some trouble shooting. Bit bizarre as they have already been out here 3 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy day with back to back Entrepreneurs Mentor Club clients. Big goals being scored by them so excited to see... https://t.co/PQ0C5yj3Xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra just wondering how many times I need to request someone to FINALLY fix my internet. Seriously get your shit together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/aL2GY073Ge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great episode today about "the idea" and what to do when you have one for a business https://t.co/m3729lrGFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday everyone. Just wondering if you could do me a favour please. Due to the huge response we got last... https://t.co/lqLMXCJicj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have had a lot of people ask me how they can Refer me. well it's really simple. Click on the link below and my... https://t.co/3ZYwKlD1Ol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>