<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[always the first option https://t.co/FEAP8e6y77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway I have no idea, but if you DO happen to locate it, share ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway it's so worth it, I wish I could rewatch the first time &amp; like hear all the jokes again for the first time omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 it's a tough skill to master]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 lol whats a book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway I only watched at first FOR Phil, but after watching every episode like 80 times, that entire cast is brilliant,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 oh absolutely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway Have you watched NewsRadio?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do I not have a shirt on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 yes, it has a nice ring to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 LOL I'M SO UNHELPFUL. How about "how to stay committed"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 they can figure it out,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 well played, well played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway He is sooo missed. Unbelievable talented. One of my 1. inspirations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 hmm how about the influence music has on your life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 we can make this work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 small world, small world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 there's a loooot of different methods, cuz everyone copes differently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 WHAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 would you like me to call nine eleven?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 well yes that could be a thingo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 we were meant to be, but not in an incest way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 how to make friends with freaks online :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 I wish you could sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 have you looked up speech format? I think it can be pretty loose, like not absurdly structured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 OH MY GOD, WHAT ARE THE ODDS?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 it's not good for your skin &amp; stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 ohhh okay, thank god holy hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 evil is also my middle name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 omg, always wash your makeup oooooff ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 pickles, OR, the impact of the internet on youth, OR, WAIT YOU HAVE TO WRITE AN ENTIRE SPEECH BY TUESDAY??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 oh friend, idk I think you look so good with longer hair but thats just moi ðŸ’¯â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 ahhaha not that often, have you seen me! Ahahha!!ðŸ˜ŠðŸ‘‰ðŸ‘‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 Im sure its GREAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 you silly little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza know of* heck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so thankful &amp; happy to know who &amp; be a fan of Phil Hartman, wow :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza I'll be here all week, folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 :( Try to sleep it off as best you can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 it's pretty af tho at least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Told you. https://t.co/r8zWWqSGwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 ikr, it's so irritating!!1!1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 ehhh it can be subtle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 yes, but you dont have the witch overall appearance I would say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza she finished it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 its like "meet ___ ___, an openingly gay player!" Like ??? I dont care ??? Sex has nothing to do with sports lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobotRepair97 but its the whole "personal vs. professional" stuff, like your personal life shouldnt have anything to do with how you PLAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in the mood to write some poetic type stuff that makes no sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza maybe I should work on that now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to write some Lorenzo related thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza I mean ya that has happened in other points in time, still does happen, but omfg I cant understand that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that a lot of parents didn't like to show any physical affection towards their children in like the 40s &amp; 50s is so fucked up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway I need to make myself tired enough by staying up later agghh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pussboi420 FUCK OFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt SANDtoro, son of a beach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uhmm okay, how does a BABY manage a Twitter account?! Explain that! https://t.co/u7NuyJar0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway bored, yes. I won't be asleep for a while tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pussboi420 is that like a grape with a lisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my tweet tonight are complete nonsense, so things are usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway OHHHHH I'm sorry, but yes thank you, ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gross Incompetence is my middle name, today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexander Hamilton, Come Quick! Your Son's Been Shot! Jk, where's the money you took]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designerskyIine life is an adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designerskyIine revelationary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justfadinaway oh, thank you, I'm alright at the moment if that's what you're implying;D ðŸŒ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designerskyIine emerging from the sea=emergency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewSantoro excuse me little one, do you feel like going live again tonight maybe? ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess I'll be awake for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@designerskyIine indifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to take all my emotions, put them in a blender, and make it into a smoothie, &amp;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhaha is that even a question :) :) ahhaha !!1! :) https://t.co/yTTiuEwLiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambientbIue That's some deep web material]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not gonna get my hair cut for while. I wanna see how long I can grow it until it annoys me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambientbIue Kennel Kink? Someone research this, pronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs darn it all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who got me pregnant again https://t.co/PUUObWCYII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs I'll slither away if I must]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs it's alright, I have fleas anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs nice neighborhood! Im gonna sleep on your lawn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nail polish is obnoxiously sparkly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houdini by Foster The People&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntrovertPizza it is I, a witch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really enjoy looking like a day-old pastry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No offence but I hate when my family yells throughout the house, like fuck off, walk downstairs to talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently you can re-watch Periscopes from months ago ON the app itself, &amp; wow crying Lin made my heart hurt https://t.co/vX90lOoNhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0h_snaaap tell him yes, then link him to a website that has pictures of something random af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a protest chance stuck in my head for days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The International Sanctuary Of Screwballs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs dont knock it till you've tried it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah, that might cause some pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs it's always a goodtime!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Shabnam pronounces Iran as "Eron"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracka Lacken? https://t.co/yansqIkDhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was on the Titanic when the "sinking" happened, but here's what REALLY happened: it flew away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisntphangs is that like the Titanic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot for a moment, but reminder that Sarah is my long lost cousin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Floobs, boat https://t.co/qNV5pZW3gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont even wanna eat right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frozen Wooly Mammoth Shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowmexico]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>