<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Already my 5th time putting legs in cold water tonight. Going to be a long night! Wish they'd sort these medical allergies out! #transplant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drawing of bobby the dog for my lovely friend. Wish I was more productive at the moment but really struggling wit… https://t.co/4e1dgH3Lyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look who's been drawing today! Ha https://t.co/kPt3XtwQUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to focus on drawing, needing breaks. Too many as my head just isn't focused at all with these reactions to medicines #cysticfibrosis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain feels like it's on fire after flushing my sinuses &amp; forgetting to put the #neilmed formula into water. #cysticfibrosis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionnualaJay I just don't buy it, only get for the husband &amp; pretend it's not there. Have had it once this month. As makes me bloat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep as allergic reaction so irritating &amp; sore that I'm having a freezing cold bath. Absolutely horrendous this time of year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No sleep as allergic reaction has returned! #needabreak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzzarca every time I have another disabled bay user pull in front to steal the parking I'm waiting for :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are awful when it comes to hospital parking's &amp; stealing spaces. Lose my faith in humanity every time I come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs up vomiting &amp; this allergic reaction is definitely rearing its ugly head again. Need sleep:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the petsmart app. I have discovered that when Eric's home alone, he likes to sit in the window howling. Usually quietest dog going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dodgeyhodgey22 well done today, so proud of you xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally heartbroken that a wonderful friend had a transplant call but it was a false call in the end. #shedeserveseverything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sproglet8 @BeaHappyCF @Dodgeyhodgey22 but it's also very exhausting &amp; taxing on emotions at times &amp; need a thick skin for it all xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sproglet8 @BeaHappyCF @Dodgeyhodgey22 was approached by papers, then Welsh assembly &amp; media as was happy to raise awareness x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeaHappyCF @Dodgeyhodgey22 @5WrightStuff aww that was @sproglet8 not me ;) she's my twinny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzzarca thanks. I have my mask on, which is just making breathing difficult as so hot &amp;stuffy. But so many people coughing so can't remove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat in full waiting rooms bring out the anxiety in me #transplant #cysticfibrosis #immunosuppressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHSOrganDonor @sickchickchic @CMFTNHS @Leic_hospital @Tor87 thanks for involving me xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nhsorgandonor's photo https://t.co/hl860zrqoa follow my instagram takeover at @NHSOrganDonor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 9 of allergic reaction &amp; higher dose of steroids to settle it &amp;my swelling is only getting worse! #transplant #cysticfibrosis #allergies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADEKplus thank you so much, things are great with lungs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hulmerd @cftrust I had a double lung transplant, that's the reason why!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrieOnTwit this time last year you were filming us leaving hospital for the first time! Woohoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all down to my amazing donor who saved my life &amp; gifted me with lungs that work. Am so grateful, despite having a rough month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have gone one whole year without needing intravenous antibiotics for a chest infection for the first time ever! 
Take that #cysticfibrosis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a dr describes your allergic reactions as tolerable &amp; you ask him to define tolerable: "well you're still breathing!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotmalejim do you find it makes your limbs ache like mad if their up. Also get burning hands &amp; feet (get it a lot but they burn extra hot)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotmalejim so I think the times have stacked up on eachother &amp; caused the high. Feel awful when mine above 12 let alone 24 :( #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotmalejim I'm on 30mg at the mo, been fine on it previously but had to take steroids at 2 different times yesterday as had a reaction,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em indeed. Felt like it was too good to be true. But glad I had a good spell. You ok? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodavidson65 thank you, trial and error at the mo to know how long to stay on higher dose of steroids, reduced too quickly K paying price]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idavidson56 how does this magic work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotmalejim yeah true, still not happy with it being in the 20's though, unusual for me &amp; I thought I'd done everything to avoid highs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High dose of steroids to combat allergic reaction is really affecting my diabetes control today! #cysticfibrosis #transplant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. So the whole, freeze your nips off &amp; apply cream to calm skin exercise was pointless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. Calamine lotion. Sit freezing for an eternity until you dry, only to realise skin ointment applied earlier in the day repels water! ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Rubbish ways to spend the day. Needing a cold bath because allergic reaction has inflamed skin so badly, then draining bath to apply..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running out of ways to settle my allergic reaction. Tried everything, just so sore &amp; itchy :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dodgeyhodgey22 wow, that's amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em either as will make my body store more fluid. Just exhausted at the mo xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em wasn't, so I've had some to get to sleep through pain. I'm ok, just resting in bed for today, steroids don't help with swelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em I can have oramorph for back pain but immunologist told me to not take in case that's what was causing reactions, but we know it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em prolapsed disc in spine (or 2) so pain really out of control at the mo. You ok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em really struggling at the mo, reaction flared up again yesterday so back to high dose steroids &amp; too sore to move &amp; have a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed a walk with the man &amp; dog child today. https://t.co/RiuhCcXixn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching @SwissArmyMan &amp; the dog let out a massive fart right at the ending. It's like he knew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BottyB we rescued her last year. Her name is Polly &amp; she only has 2 front legs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuddles with these two this morning https://t.co/l3YMjWK4fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling very mehh today. My bodies not letting me do anything I need to recently #cysticfibrosis can be such a pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Eric hasn't a clue on why I feel rough so getting as close as I will let him. My skins on fire pup, no cuddles… https://t.co/DI7OSNJk4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Eric could understand that my skin is on fire so his warm little body against me is just too much to cope with #needspace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em yeah &amp; may not work as can't stop the meds to get out of system to test, so may not show the reaction. Fingers crossed x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate allergies. Now have to triple my steroids then work out how much to increase my insulin by to combat steroids #cysticfibrosis #diabetes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Prickles54 oh I'm sorry to hear that. Insomnia is the worst x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em it's the meds, having tests at the end of month to see which ones. Went a good 2 months without an ad reaction at least x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awful nights sleep due to an allergic reaction. Now skin so itchy &amp; on fire it's too sore to move :( #transplant #cysticfibrosis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kakey89 do daily yoga &amp; exercises but pain is worse than ever. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kakey89 I try to do that &amp; also bought an exercise ball to replace chair while I'm drawing as will help with cor strength. Also trying to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kakey89 tell me about it. I have fractures down my spine &amp; compressed discs &amp; was taken off pain relief to control it recently &amp; struggling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cwtchesSouthUK I was on oramorph for it for years but it's been stopped as a precaution for allergies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need suggestions on ways to deal with bad back &amp; hip pain as restricting me walking the dog #cysticfibrosis #osteoperosis #transplant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a good day, I didn't internally combust by eating watermelon. My antirejection meds are also calming my food allergies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lomquiche @vickser22 @BBC all a major part of trust in team though, then feel lost when it's not there anymore. Im loving being home though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatySalisbury exactly &amp; counting carbs for insulin doses takes the fun out of sweets too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have lit a rosemary candle in a bid to get my brain focused on art today! https://t.co/eg9deQ0V2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebiggj aww, sorry. Very emotional December all round for us to be honest. So have had a bit of a break from everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TheDeck would love to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chez_Em they move away from me, which I really don't mind as means less risk of catching bugs ;) hope you are ok xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TheDeck we had minzi, but sadly she passed last year. Then we rescued another called Polly. Who is albino &amp; has no back legs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TheDeck thanks. Looking forward to seeing more of your designs. You must do a hedgehog next. I have plenty of cute photos of mine. Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TheDeck yes, little Eric. Their just the best. Such amazing detail on cakes. https://t.co/KK4hkA8Eav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TheDeck oh my word! These are just everything!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimmyreo I'm ok, but mehh but ok. Hope you are alright this not so fine monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMattBe you should see my wood carving skills. Trained printmaker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeaHappyCF one day. Will get he husbands go pro set up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewartdarkin it's not about he stuff though really, just glad to still be here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatySalisbury thank you. I thought t was handled wonderfully. Very proud to have been a part of it. If only they played across England too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatySalisbury I was eating way too many sweets last year so stopped but I do miss them (hypo treats)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lomquiche @vickser22 @BBC oh I'm sorry. It's diffusing it as they become a crutch almost &amp; such good support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebiggj glad you saw. Did you see the 2 minute video with Eric &amp; minzi as well as the half hour episode? It was emotional to watch for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendycaroline91 isn't it just. How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMattBe @WalesOnline ha. Will leave the music making to them. I'm happy with my pens &amp; art x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilyfharris if only. It gets so frustrating a people drive past while im waiting for parking &amp; steal the spot as I look ok. :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now getting stinking looks for wearing a mask in the waiting room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lose my faith in people when I'm trying to get a parking in hospital. 3 stolen from me then late for appointment :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMattBe @WalesOnline wonderful. But no, I'm not musically gifted at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CfAdventurers @CarrieOnTwit do you know the answer to this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost my keys in the field whilst waking Eric, luckily found them as was getting way too cold &amp; dark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of a lovely person Richard, who finally got laid to rest today after losing his fight with #cysticfibrosis #transplant breathe easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lomquiche @vickser22 @BBC have to be a caring soul in that line of work. My cf team are like family, weird not being in constantly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still a chance left to watch #bbcgreatestgift on iPlayer. Episode 1 is only available for today #cysticfibrosis https://t.co/mplqCtm0vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lomquiche @vickser22 @BBC yess, you have to work with what you have. Coat hangers were my drip stands while doing home treatments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodavidson65 thank you, few niggles the last few days &amp; am sure I'm brewing a virus. Hey ho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodavidson65 yess, definitely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatySalisbury aww yay. Yes, they made me cry but in a good way. Hard to see the donor side but amazing to see the positive message put over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewartdarkin can't top lungs fir Christmas though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewartdarkin usually have a few a week! Just got spoiled with clothes &amp; art equipment. My birthday was on the 19th too. So got lots x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewartdarkin indeed. First Christmas &amp; new year not having to go into hospital too &amp; actually have hadv2 weeks off from appointments too]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>