<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA is weekend league down. Can't get a game says this game session is no longer available]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA trying to complete the lacasette league challenge but no defenders for TFC available in market place at all? Suggestions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody please tell Hargreaves to stop saying the word exceptional every 60 seconds. Driving me crazy #ChelseaVsEverton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful send off to John Giles from Eamon Dunphy.. immaculately said. Giles is etched in to the very core of Irish soccer history. #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English FA should re-hire Hodge again just so they can publicly sack him 30 mins later. 4 years and still didnt know his best 11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PennyDreadful - Billie Piper's scene recanting her daughters passing. Emmy worthy doesn't do it justice. Absolutely incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassing utd team. The premier leagues AC Milan. Mid table side with a powerhouse name. #MIDMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is LVG still in a job. Zero progress. Fortune spent. Dire football. Get rid #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe Alan Rickman has passed on. I absolutely loved his performances in too many movies to mention. A QUIET GIANT of the screen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utd Chelsea... the most obvious 0-0 draw in the history of football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great insight into peps formula on sky just now. Pinpoints exactly what utd are doing wrong. Too rigid. #skyfootball #MNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieHolt22 he needs to improve his footwork big time. Watch the fight back. His feet rarely move. Any decent hitter will tag him with ease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man utd absolute dirt again... 200m spent to look nothing more than an average side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Pesci quitting acting was a monumental loss to the film industry. He was a genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New fifa update]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hector Bellerin channeled Sonic the hedgehog just there... he drops several rings on route.. unreal pace. #ARSFCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pigeon_island absolutely fix that... Murphy clearly stops trying as he turns that bend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FIFA16 is so shockingly bad it's bordering on unplayable. The passing is so terrible. You can't play a pass unless you telegraph it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[De Bruyne looks a serious player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeShaw23 bones mend luke... rest up.. eyes forward.... you have a life time of ball ahead of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope your head is warmed up Shane Long because it's going to see a lot of the ball. Republic of Hoofers #IrlGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly shit performance from utd so far despite the lead #AVLMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pearson sacked due to breakdown of relationship with mgmt a.k.a wanted investment in squad, was offered 10 quid. #clowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian_sport the owners should be ashamed of themselves. Milked to death when retirement should have beckoned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This utd side do not deserve champs league ball. Absolutely woeful with the exception of one month #CRYMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke Shaw doesn't want to play ball. That wasn't even remotely hard enough to come off on a stretcher #CRYMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunderland are the jammiest dogs of all time here today. Two absolute fluke goals while being battered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barca are back with a bang... Messi is the best player to ever kick a ball. He has absolutely everything. #BarcaBayern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double those Messi first goal odds Patrick @paddypower double them good and proper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanPetrov19 super stuff so far Stan on #SNF. No sugarcoating. Just honest and on the mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Stan Petrov on @SkyFootball right now. Totally frank on his views. Not holding back at all. Love it. #cityvvilla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower crash bandicoutinho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fudge are utd losing this game.  Chelsea are the most boring league leaders of all time. #CHEMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a surprise. Annie power falls at the last saving the bookies 200m. Never even address the flight. Stitch up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have cooked a joint of meat for longer than @Cristiano goal drought. #whatwhereyouworriedabout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does any striker in the league get service as bad as benteke. Literally one pass he has had to his feet. #villaarepoison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtois English is impeccable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonyxperia any sign of lollipop update on the z3?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youreceived servers are an embarrassment!!!! Absolutely every single day there are issues. Every single day!!!!!! @EASPORTSFIFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsport Hamilton needs to up his game. His commentary is awful tonight. No animation at all. Poor form #cityvcska]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30m for Shaw and he offers practically no chance of an assist. Poor #wesmun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs playing some lovely stuff #MANSPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously what is the point of these fixtures. Worse than a training game.  They should introduce a handicap system. San Marino +4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA absolute embarrassment &amp; sham of a launch. Cannot even play your game.  #Fifa15servers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA literally every second day your servers are down. It's beyond frustrating. Your product just isn't reliable. #fifa14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishmanmick yeah it was sublime. Sterling was moronic with that pass. Looks like pools now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely harsh to drop Mata today. Totally unjustified. Rooney in form back in to midfield. RVP should have been benched.  #LVGbottledit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice block of wood for Rio.  #utdvsqpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the end of Pardews reign at Newcastle. So disorganized at the back. #bringindavidmoyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joey7Barton that there is exactly why he shouldn't start. Can't even square a ball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now for 6 hours of pure couch mesmericness... #DeadlineDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTSFIFA why is it taking 30 mins to pair with an opponent in FUT. Ffs you have had a whole year to sort these problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danroan @RobbieSavage8 raises questions of the clubs scouting dep far more I would say. Not good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ones who selflessly strive to make us laugh while battling their own sadness are the definition of a giving heart #RIPRobinWilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Hart has nothing to worry about. This new lad has barely got to a single shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine how good arsenal would be with a world class striker up front.  A real battering ram 25 goals a season player. #ArsMan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_McCoy absolutely astounding enthusiasm to keep winning races..... Where does it come from AP????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker the same could be said for another Irishman @AP_McCoy who at the exact same time was breaking yet another record. #giants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_McCoy congrats on putting Pipey in his place Champ! Old codgers these days need to be brought down a peg 😛]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themichaelowen Tony McCoy has just won again breaking M.Pipe's record of winning horses trained. Surely worth a retweet. #thechamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell Bill.... An institution for Irish football coverage. Have a wonderful retirement #rteworldcup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mascherano is absolutely wasted as a barca centre half. He is a quality holding midfielder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowards challenge from Neuer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higuain off. Contribution zero. Get khune out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higuain is a poor poor forward. Needs 5 chances to score. Shocking effort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Byrnish1981 Oscar is not obligated to jump over his challenge. Left leg in there and missed the ball. Pen for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stone wall pen that.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieHolt22 very little Ollie I'd imagine. No keeper expected to save pens. It's a free opportunity to be a hero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Injustice seeing a side win a game like that. Horrid horrid horrid Brazil side. Hope the Germans Muller them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zero enjoyment watching this foul fest.... Constant break in play #BRAvsCOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benzema is an extremely average forward. How many chances does he miss per game? Rooney would be slaughtered for these misses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English Media: this is all Wayne Rooney's fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many Passengers. Sterling, sturridge, welbeck, Henderson all anonimous. Rooney only one having a go. #EnglandvsUruguay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Hamilton can't tell the difference between Sterling and Sturridge. One looks like a Jockey George. The other is Sturridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeCarrick @carras16 they mean you are two down. Put on a second striker instead of a like for like change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VDB has a lot to answer for. Never once changed shape. All like for like changes. No plan B. Left pacey players at home. @GuillemBalague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#dunphy we are a nation of swearers Eamo don't worry about it. Ha. Poor bill facepalmed himself silly with dread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenmoran51 shocking. They need to sort out the qualification parameters for these woeful sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenmoran51 undeservedly so in my opinion. He knows details even of the obscure players impressively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Kerr is a top notch co-commentator. Never recycles Same old cliches like many others. #refreshing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenmoran51 just realised its Jonathan pearce. Ha. Still a bit slow the lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does Jonathan Clarke not get this. The shot off the post wasn't over. The rebound was.  Is he thick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely top fight analysis by Paulie Malignaggi. Great insight throughout the fight. #Signhimupsky #FrochGroves2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely zero to suggest England have changed a lick style wise. Same old kick and rush football. No clue how to control possession]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuillemBalague @TelegraphTop read Guillen, You are wetting the appetite nicely for the season ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of this season can't come quick enough.Too many passengers in our side. New faces on and off the pitch required. #MUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hernandez is a below average footballer. No way he should be starting for man United. Having a mare he is #MUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xabi Alonso has absolutely bossed it out there for me. Magic he has been #realvsbayern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker only one man to blame. No style. No urgency. No guile. No fluidity. No direction. Utterly predictable. Moyes out !!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How absolutely shite are Utd. This is embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forrest Bale. That kid sure can run.What a goal! @GarethBale11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishmanmick depressing as fook bro.  Last game in Europe for a long time that will be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishmanmick I agree. The boys think he was clearly unfit. I think he was just toothless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Rooney is having possibly his worst game for Utd ever tonight. Absolutely horrific he has been. Not good enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond a joke at utd now. Making every side we play look world class. Average squad getting average results under an average manager. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ever ever a stoppage!!! What is jim watt smoking? There was no call to make. Let them fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nomeadome ive been off the grid social media wise. Got tired of its all consuming nature. So went jason bourne on it all. : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nomeadome you ladies have it easy Naomi.. Id kill for a DILF comment &amp; I dont even have any kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_McCoy as a gambler i can't even fathom picking 4000 winners. Who knew all i had to do was back you AP! Why did you keep it a secret? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rioferdy5 birthday greetings from dublin big man. Ice those celebrations till sunday night or i'll snitch on ye]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>