<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr @michaelfink @talopine @annetreasure But cycling is often about discovering new routes anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr @michaelfink @talopine @annetreasure They're complete rubbish.  It took me a few tries to figure out the Capital City Trail in Melb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr It wouldn't be on Weibo without the Chinese government censors allowing it.  🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theremonstrator All Israel needs to do is offer to build a Trump Hotel on Palestinian land.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Corday Although the Australian government doesn't seem that keen on our own scientists or science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjhross Who will be the first to go with an AFL analogy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bortflancrest Does it matter?  The real question is how hard and far he would kick his pet if it didn't please him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn The Sound of Music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, he has a lot in common with the Australian government. https://t.co/7vZF4wzoK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going by his appointments so far,   Trump will ask David Duke to organize the events. https://t.co/gXvSIkM7U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nolamjames I feel your pain.  I have been up late the last two nights getting work done.  But then again, I feel happy doing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These types who hate PC and just want straight talk, but who won't actually do straight talk. https://t.co/Akf9WYSSQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenCuzzupe Fuck that.  I'm traumatized again.  And what the fuck is King doing picking that fucking game.  Cunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Trump would then make Martin Shkreli responsible for distributing the cure. https://t.co/nkkqC8N4kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImogenDunlevie I loved this book about Keating.  https://t.co/vz4PQFeobn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natsouthby I know how you feel.  I can't bring myself to follow another club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nolamjames People who sous vide a steak can get in the fucking bin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennvalencich Roque Santa Cruz was also one of the great names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rm_rm_rm_rm_rm @NABFW I wonder if Serena being African-American makes Court even more bitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImogenDunlevie Obviously few people from minority backgrounds go to his restaurant, Maude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn And of course, he leaves others to deal with the consequences and fallout of policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lhjh70 We will see if people fight as hard for freedom of speech as they do for guns.  #USConstitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natsouthby This is turning into the US's version of the Cultural Revolution.  Ideology over reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on issues like Safe Schools and SSM, I would say that @TurnbullMalcolm is being craven. https://t.co/nIPWXKjZhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lhjh70 Another boost in subscriptions for the NYT coming up.  Trump could single handedly save newspapers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3.  I Know It's Over
2.  This Charming Man
1.  There Is A Light That Never Goes Out https://t.co/gvmwOD5Hfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triumph of the Will.  Of maybe that should be Trump-umph Of The Will. https://t.co/GAl2ngd3rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If true, it is terrifying how quickly law enforcement agencies fall into line with draconian and unfair rules and l… https://t.co/riBr8i6W2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dunkingdad And when Trump trashes the US economy and standing in the world, they'll blame Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside I loved the US when I've visited, but I'm not going over while the nutbags run the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottrdare Imagine if they give Brown and P*n*h* seats to run in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natsouthby Sometimes I think they're letting him sign things so he can feel important, but they file it away, never to be acted on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see the Trump branded military hardware. https://t.co/XD9jMwYT4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet they dump the "Manchester" part of the name and it will just say "United". https://t.co/EMxRxsGkK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBakewood @JoshCPinn @JRRivett to negotiate as individuals.  Unionism can even the playing field for workers, especially low skill ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBakewood @JoshCPinn @JRRivett Agree.  People have a right to negotiate as part of a union.  Not everyone has the ability or interest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn retrain them for different work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn wind down the industry gradually.  I still think of the workers and their families.  You need to look after them, and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn Take coal for instance.  While pure market theory would say, "Let it die", I would support government intervention to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn @SteveBakewood @JRRivett Although the private sector was co-opted to serve the Nazi government's aims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn On social policy, obviously from my tweets, you know I'm a progressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn I also believe that governments need to intervene at times, and that essential services cannot be privitised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett @JoshCPinn The more I think about it, the more it's probably just force of habit.  I generally believe in the free market, but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn @JRRivett That be me.  I think of myself as centre-right, but politics has moved so far to the right that I'm a de facto leftie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett I'm sure he would have a different view of torture if he was mistakenly identified as the terrorist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aptronym It would be the world's funniest joke if he didn't have the nuclear codes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon, USA will mean Union of Soviet America. https://t.co/HCnDnYCMon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Supermercado99 head who said he had to make the choice between career advancement now or the risk of having his reputation ruined later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Supermercado99 I read an article a while ago about a young GOP up and comer who was offered a job in Trump's team.  He spoke to an older]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we're going to see a lot of Trump supporters, from voters to GOP heavy weights, who will find a bullet hole… https://t.co/CZkoq0AgY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr I suspect Trump sees the popular vote as losing a ratings battle, but the GOP will exploit his obsession to make voting harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an each way bet from May. https://t.co/lGuM79Ta7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lhjh70 Small mercies.

And if it's Trump, very small mercies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's going to accidentally tweet out the nuclear codes, isn't he. https://t.co/SHs6vcMvoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bortflancrest Ah, there are so many loopholes to that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bortflancrest Ah, he blocked me ages ago.  What did I miss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside And the Roberts Labour Day rant has appeared on my timeline and it is even more stupid than I could have ever imagined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside I don't have to know what he is going on about to say that he really is THAT stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thiscassgirl And if you're like Ray and tweet only every few days, try not to be as petty and small minded as him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernardi also forgetting that Saudi Arabia and the US are best buddies. https://t.co/Bk93AOinRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss 11 baked cookies today. https://t.co/n9ytnJhMRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neatly packaged charcoal. https://t.co/sooimMbzTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will quote this article as an accurate report of what happened. https://t.co/M3DsGWLi9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like the Soviet Union. https://t.co/36qBTSsBtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profsarahj @nickorloff He did say his views changed after he left parliament.  Maybe they should get out of the Canberra bubble more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickorloff @profsarahj Although what is it about politicians who suddenly have their epiphanies after they leave politics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett Early on, very few people were willing to say they backed Trump. But as his momentum grew, more were being open about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett The other factor is the difference in what people are willing to say in public compared to what they really think in private.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bookshopaddict @JRRivett opportunity.  What big data does is to pinpoint those fears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRRivett Big data probably just confirms what good sales people have always know.  Fear is a bigger driver in decision making than]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDsD Wait 30 to 40 years and it will be as unequal as it is in the West.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is now:  https://t.co/bnND5Q4ONU https://t.co/y4pdOOsnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside @JoshCPinn That would be awesome.  Your work in losing weight was one of the most inspiring things I've seen on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theremonstrator Because it's not terrorism when it's done by white people in the name of "patriotism".  #FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn @Strauchanside You can disagree on a lot of things but still be a decent human being when it comes to important issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn @Strauchanside That guy trolling you is just scum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmcahill @BenCuzzupe The Patriots?  WTF?!?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside @JoshCPinn If you feel that opening up to the world helps you, then that can only be a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside @JoshCPinn allows me to see the context of things you say, and allows me to offer support, even if it's only words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strauchanside @JoshCPinn I've never met either of you, but reading your tweets about your struggles gives me an opening to your world,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjhross Surely his memoirs will just be a collection of his tweets.  I will follow him if and when they impeach him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_FMI Not to mention the world famous Trump quality.  😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDsD Pre-cook if it is chunky pieces.  But if you slice it thinly, you should be fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelbourneBitter And sadly, that will just encourage the lunar right nutbags here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelbourneBitter Happy birthday!  Hope the evening is better than the day at Highpoint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theremonstrator His worry that others must be cheating is just a reflection on how he plays the game of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theremonstrator Quite ironic and hypocritical considering his use of twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natsouthby @DanielCherny Losing to Sri Lanka and South Africa, defeating Pakistan, and losing to India isn't going to look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natsouthby @DanielCherny After the disaster in Sri Lanka, I think Lehmann will be very worried about what could happen in India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarah_Records A friend described them as being like the Christian Taliban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjhross Oh FFS.

Still, kudos to the Dogs for their reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Piers Morgan would have been all for it with James and Lily Potter being bleeding heart do gooders. https://t.co/LFbbRStFbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisfladgate @WlTTSJW who is really making them?  Pence?  McConnell?  Bannon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisfladgate @WlTTSJW Trump doesn't strike me as having enough political knowledge or connections to make his cabinet appointments.  So,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the young girl in the red top knows the US is doomed. https://t.co/6PQbObklwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WlTTSJW It's like he sees the popular vote as the ratings and he can't handle that he lost that to Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ichymochek @Strauchanside Yep, Malcolm Blight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshCPinn Good luck, stick with your support networks, and you can get through this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian Taliban is the perfect description. https://t.co/3hsapQme63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sonja_Hood @MGliksmanMDPhD And now she probably sees him as he really is.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>