<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked if Crosby tried to sell a call, Dubinsky said: "I'm sure everybody else can make up their own decision on that one." Gold. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pens_Girl62 was a great game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacketsfan77 3 of 4 pts vs Pens is just fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great comeback now win it in OT! #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Jones is good at hockey #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goalie interference. That shouldn't count]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_cynic that'll show em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boone Jenner is out there just wrecking people. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big game. Beat the Penguins! #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaebberwock @D2_Derpinator what site is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;Looking for phone while holding phone&gt; awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna listen to this soon. @CamBNewton is a good guy https://t.co/9F6qUyRFko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins it's $10 a month. Jesus these clowns just want to fuck over everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The data loss prevention features Microsoft has built into Office 365 now are pretty sweet. https://t.co/eXlQFKH3lC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gothlaw @seriouseats this is also why you gained weight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, those huge financial firms don't need any oversight. From 2008.... https://t.co/TM4wVfSW8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All these people that thought Trump would "bring back jobs" may want to see what he's actually doing, rolling back Dodd-Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#draintheswamp wtf https://t.co/ZbSAFeFr8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TribeAndCBJ looters are not protestors. They are criminals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is truly the dumbest thing he's ever said https://t.co/lBxZ2kFmof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins how does he still have a job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm totally fine with this as long as that means Churches pay taxes but of course they won't be required https://t.co/V54CGY00PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoForeman @gbdawkins Bannon said that repeatedly and I guess many didn't believe him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins I laughed when I read what they were doing. That's probably not the best reaction but here we are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZoForeman what could go wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fastest natural hat trick in NHL history = 21 seconds. Was Steve Mason in net? https://t.co/kNY1jdr0yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why in the world when anyone want to sync their calendar with @LinkedIn ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WindingDot unsaid, the driver of said car is also "suspicious looking"']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@treed1919 "CBJ are having their best season ever." And done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, the one day of the year a fax machine is still relevant. #GoBucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's juvenile but so is our "President" and these are hilarious https://t.co/yI4AGF6puk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Score 6 goals, win, and Torts is going to be justifiably pissed. That defense was u.g.l.y. in the 3rd. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonL is that bad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh.... guys? What you doing? #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dgmcdowell @gbdawkins isn't this nomination more important long term than any Senator's career?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derdrache agreed but obstruction in general worked for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derdrache why? It worked for GOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dgmcdowell @gbdawkins you don't think it's easy to explain to her constituents why she or anyone would oppose a hearing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derdrache doesn't matter. This should be payback for Garland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dgmcdowell @gbdawkins it's not sure her. Many Dems laying down right now and it's disgusting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of these whimpy ass Democrats. Grow a spine! This is why GOP wins dirty. @TheDemocrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairecmc he shouldn't even get a hearing. #Garland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins @TheDemocrats yes! And yet there are Senators like @clairecmc who think he deserves a hearing. Fuck that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was freakin gorgeous. 5-zip #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dominating the Rangers. #WeWant10 #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell. No. Block at all costs https://t.co/yg085wtv62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rudy Guiliani is currently kissing Trump's ass. He should just move in there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BarackObama should have done the same even though it wouldn't have lasted https://t.co/66ijMrv16R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sickayduh hopefully he has a rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good! Resist everything https://t.co/pmbUdQmpFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like Trump has already been "President" for 8 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WindingDot would be a good start though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins @texaninnyc Pence is awful but he's at least sane and I believe would fire Bannon and follow the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateMajLdr you're cool with all this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DSmithScenes yes. Sadly none of this is a surprise. Going to have to much worse before it has any chance of getting better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DSmithScenes would anything be a surprise right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DSmithScenes until the next day and the day after that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gothlaw any Democrat that doesn't stand up needs to be run out of the party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems this is embarrassing. Get it organized and together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats can't even get Pelosi's mic to work. Jesus. We are so screwed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins it probably is to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blakeells this is awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamjordann @SarahWoodwriter @Gallup so he won? Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump watch out for the stairs!!! https://t.co/Q7qj8XSB37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov @POTUS fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derdrache the police?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D2_Derpinator @SpeakerRyan his head is still stuck in Trump's ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetSematary @AymanM @KellyO we're gonna end up in another Revolutionary War, aren't we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sit here longing for the days of Ronald Reagan.... wtf is going on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shining City Upon A Hill https://t.co/Qj23J8SMQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins @DamonSilvers this is a lock em up I could get behind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we sign up on the Muslim registry yet? Sign me up! I'm also Jewish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jblanx @jwbul287 yes that's my point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwbul287 @jblanx does more harm than good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwbul287 @jblanx I haven't heard anyone say we should just take all refugees without screening. That's never been the case but a ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fivefifths the immigrant crime list is already the brown people list so probably not long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwbul287 they screwed the pooch by denying re-entry to existing green card holders. That's a huge deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just know @realDonaldTrump has been up all night in a rage fit. I'm the President, stupid court can't stop me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You couldn't make this up https://t.co/JRHTUbWy1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbdawkins it's so funny, nearly all their replies are still about Harambe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This crap is a distraction from the real news today - Muslim ban and lifting Russian sanctions https://t.co/LMn9ssyKBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fearfuldogs I don't think so. When they believe he's brought God back to the WH, they'll clearly believe anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_VanLinge the only redeeming thing about this movie is Buscemi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_VanLinge ha! I just flipped it on. And the hair is so bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mac_b_from_tn what happened to trading a chicken for a doctor visit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I totally understand this. One of our dogs is slowly fading and it sucks https://t.co/tWz12ZgNKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kat021171 the dumbass thinks demonstrators is a bad word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh, yes. What should they be called? https://t.co/eX5YZhTwym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["President Trump has brought God back to the White House." 
I just can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I'm sure that phone call on Saturday will be the first time Trump and Putin spoke since Inauguration Day. Sure it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that ref blind? Honestly. Was in the net twice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metroscapeGuy nah. Need the break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limping to the All Star break. Hopefully they recharge. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willnevin @TWEsq all the cool kids will be in the camp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWEsq rafts. Large, beautiful rafts. The best rafts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude. You can't go after Bob like that. Hell no. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_VanLinge @Pchopz_ please not JR. He should be Cleveland for life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Preds look like crash test dummies taking these hits so far. #CBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonL and then wrecked himself. Oww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gothlaw @POTUS @eshap the town idiot @seanspicer is already walking it back]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>