<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CroweDM @DeniseBeale Government make up 7.6% of all 457 sponsorship (table 1.06 https://t.co/nJCARP6YRu)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksonhtaylor No idea how many people subscribe to the newsletter you flagged my blog with but led to &gt;500 views. Cheers for the shout out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighEllis Please let Mark Cuban know. https://t.co/WOEXVJTQI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shauncrowe There was two weeks on "power" and how to weld it effectively. Colin Barnett missed that fortnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shauncrowe I did POLS1001 at ANU and I remember it very clearly ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redrabbleroz Yes but it fosters additional legitimacy which is ill deserved. The Liberals should know better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics 101: How *not* to deal with a political insurgency. https://t.co/v9EAzxYMRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutless, power seeking stooges. This is business as usual in politics and people are sick of it. What do they belie… https://t.co/CEvGyp4tE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said @cosmicpinot. ANU Vice Chancellor to staff on Trump Muslim ban. Our Prime Minister should take note. https://t.co/2DvBy2lRVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ I saw Robert Reich endorse Charles Krauthammer. It doesn't have to make sense anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull refuses to denounce Muslim ban. Morrison almost endorses it. Bishop asks for exemptions. The Turnbull Government in a nut shell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJRHiscox @tomwestland I worked at DIBP till 2012. I want to go back when the time is right and when I think I can make a difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJRHiscox @tomwestland no doubt. Up to the individual if they think they can make a difference. I don't think there is a right answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RHT_ebooks @tomwestland well there are many who take relish and if everyone else leaves, it only gets worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwestland and do good when the opportunity arises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwestland I can understand people not wanting to work for immigration, but good people need to be there to mitigate the worst aspects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CallamPickering Yup. And the wall + tariffs more likely to induce emigration from Mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@historyben Well, we have problems. Humanitarian migrants being the most entrepreneurial here in Oz is mostly because they can't get a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redrabbleroz Yes, you're right. ESTA distinct from what was changed to the Interview waiver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redrabbleroz Can you point me towards reporting on this? I'm confused about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@historyben One shouldn't exclude the other. I think positive examples can build support, just as appealing to hardship can as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffPolHist @SachaBlumen I'm too drained to think about this today. Within a week, what a turnaround for American leadership and idealism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffPolHist Not difficult to see a 120 day refugee 'freeze' (ban) extending for a longer period of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffPolHist Problem with these arguments: what is the tolerance for failure? If it's zero, *only* acceptable solution is to ban migrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_a_w cheers for the shoutout in your column.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer I'm not across that level of detail. But breakdown is about 50% universities, 30% TAFE, 20% other from memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Yes, most definitely. https://t.co/SiIemr6xni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Vast majority is post-secondary but there are also a relatively small number of school students.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Worth about $20 billion to the economy as an export service. Propping up Australia's higher education system by itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattCowgill @jasemurphy @tomwestland This is why Trump won.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattCowgill @NickMGreen @tomwestland &lt;slightly frowning face&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen @tomwestland I'm probably never going to visit that website again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article notes international students in Canada equal to ~1% of population (U.S. &lt;0.3%). Australia? 1.95% or 470,810 https://t.co/7EgHNXEAvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwestland I lasted three minutes before closing that tab. Just think of the emigration if Trump causes a Mexican recession. Oh the irony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwestland wth is this website? The first comment is advocating an offensive war with Mexico to raise US exports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 Rodrik is the best at clearly explaining what's going on to interested lay audience. Did you see his latest paper on migration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion Would fight domestic inequality. But locking out the median Indian IT graduate exacerbates global inequality (on the margin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RHT_ebooks eventually. About 10,000 of 12,000 people now in Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for Australia to recommit on Syrian and Iraqi humanitarian migration as US steps back from global responsibili… https://t.co/IBKCFCYTS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is coming to Australia under the Pacific seasonal worker program? My latest @devpolicy blog https://t.co/YAUa0w0Azr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New from @m_clem, @hpostel: Working temporarily in U.S. raised daily value of Haitian workers’ labor by factor of 15 https://t.co/949fxQlqHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodyavirgan Ah cool, cheers. Keep up the great work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodyavirgan Hi Jody. Last week, the 538 stream re-populated in the "unplayed" section on my Podcast app on my iphone. Was that deliberate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasemurphy Sure, 11m people. But what about the other 120m+ in Mexico whose currency is now permanently exposed to Twitter rants?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raycaryl @MsLisaHerbert Yeah I agree Ray. The system is well placed and will likely grow in the future. Australia can learn a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raycaryl @MsLisaHerbert If I was not on Twitter, this is the topic of a policy paper I'm writing at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudiEdsall Congrats btw on your degree, saw on FB the other day. Massive effort. Look forward to reading more bylines in the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudiEdsall Mark Waugh, 173 at MCG in Feb, 2001. Skipping school was the best decision I made that summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent in-depth reporting from @MsLisaHerbert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top down, bottom up? A few comments from me comparing Australia's Seasonal Worker Program to New Zealand's approach https://t.co/JIr8DxB0ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @rodrikdani paper on tension between global and domestic inequality, w/ implications for migration policy… https://t.co/7Fjobh706f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattCowgill @matttburke it'll get worse as the population continues to age and power over everyday regulations shifts further.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of notes about Australia migration dynamics and the economy https://t.co/YO4P1HflXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer how many fruit pickers, nurses, doctors, IT staff, students, backpackers do we need? No-one can predict accurately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer It's impossible to accurately pick a number. Should be informed by economic and labour market needs. i.e.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer But that doesn't mean we shouldn't have the conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer I think it's harder than people think when they say less migration. The system isn't setup for governments to pick numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Yes, I agree. But international student numbers went up as Federal government reduced government funding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer 4th. Could reduce permanent migration numbers? But that only accounts for 40% of new migrants and hurts temp-perm movements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer 3rd. Backpackers are between 5-15 per cent. They are bilateral agreements. If we cap/limit, what will happen to Oz overseas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Should this be closed and force Kiwis to get visas like everyone else? It would upend 70 years of open access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer 2nd. Kiwis have made up about 5-15% of net migrants over last decade because of open border arrangements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer But as soon as this occurs, universities don't have incentive to compete for students, changing behaviour of HighEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer OK. Students are about 30% of new migrants. Could cap # of students. How would they be divided among unis and TAFEs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Negative gearing, better oversight, more density in inner-city. These are difficult politically but not otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer I'd argue reducing migration is complex, has large unknown consequences and difficult to achieve but others would disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathan_pryke @CainTess Doesn't account for students, but the total numbers suggest Phils is not a major destinat… https://t.co/XYNeTZdTYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CainTess @jonathan_pryke Knowing how tourist visa policy gets made in Australia, this is unlikely for PNG in the near future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer but stopping migration won't fix housing policy, because the issues are much broader than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer I think Melb is doing better than Sydney. Demand side policies and zoning etc are much more important than geographic size.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer physical constraints aren't fixed. They are choices we make, even if not actively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kolappan_pillai Maybe. But what if a higher base has scale effects, such as networks+efficiency which assists workers also? Hard to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog post: Getting beyond common sense arguments about Australian migration https://t.co/xwfrJxaKqb https://t.co/l6E3nb7lbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer For certain things yes, but mostly no. It ebbs and flows over time. Lots came back from o/s just after GFC for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Yup. You can't stop Australians coming and going. We've got ~1 million citizens living overseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RHT_ebooks Life of Pi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer @mikejanda @carringtonAU If you scroll to the bottom, there is a breakdown on Net Migration by visa https://t.co/R6iyCaejTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikejanda @carringtonAU True. But confusing for readers who aren't across this? Eg: We don't talk about total GDP when analysing GDP growth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer @mikejanda @carringtonAU you get counted if you spend 12 of 16 months in Australia regardless of visa category.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer @mikejanda @carringtonAU temporary migrants are included in net migration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikejanda @carringtonAU latest Net Migration figures show about 176k, towards the lower end of past decade averages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikejanda @carringtonAU temporary migrants are included in long term arrivals and departures. The graph was flow data, the table was stock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 Don't feel bad. It doesn't achieve anything, wastes your own time and gets you down. Lose-lose. There are other ways to engage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The changes to citizenship policy implied from this Peter Dutton op-ed clash heavily with well-established norms  https://t.co/L6AenjGAej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For example: There are more PNG kids in Australian schools (2,500) than PNG students at Australian universities (1,700)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest for @devpolicy on PNG international students in Australia. https://t.co/RGo4Joyb8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redrabbleroz Pathetic behaviour. When will LIberal Establishment learn they can't outflank far-right on their own turf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleasedontatme 'it's going to be more people packed in'. Left, "progressive" NIMBYs are the worst NIMBYs going around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NusantaraEcon @MattCowgill If you want to do it the hard way  https://t.co/KtD1mM63t7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanineOFlynn Have you seen many instances of this in your research on government procurement/contracts Janine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 Never read the comments. A completely self-selected group with skewed incentives. Doesn't reflect anything at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudiEdsall But.... freedom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chalk one up for the haters. Hopefully the freedom crowd will note the implications of this. https://t.co/g09HXCvVFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thmcmahon s501 mandatory cancellations from late 2014 I think. Bipartisan ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 @SP_luke I missed it first time. Thanks for rt LB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer I agree completely. Visa cancellations have nothing to do with that. It's about appropriate migration policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Sorry, wrong link on previous tweet. https://t.co/J7Zh1YtiEV and https://t.co/9lDObTwIGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer Yes proportionally but the magnitude of the increase reflects deliberate new powers. See for examples https://t.co/aFFralVAmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian visa cancellations. Order of magnitude growth from the Coalition due to new legislative criteria… https://t.co/NtbxGyYDft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasemurphy Yeah it's just magazines from what I saw. I tried to sign up but it's only for US at the moment.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>