<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sethreznik sorry bud, you’re term limited out of bsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[time to see who gets primaried https://t.co/hl9qRnaJxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellismads it’s just amazing how bad it all is. and senate ethics gets involved too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellismads here’s wayback machine from a week ago :/ https://t.co/24FOKi4gpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellismads the Senate Democrats just updated their site to reflect that Schumer, not Reid, was in charge this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re all cowards for not retweeting this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natashavc what in the goddamn fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is also the one year anniversary of me trying to add a video to my snap story and it still hasn't processed https://t.co/8uahRloNjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year ago tonight Bernie Sanders came to a virtual tie in the Iowa caucus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I hear "proto-fascist" all I can picture is a little amoeba with a Hitler mustache]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArunChaud of interest https://t.co/HZiUQOzRER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryWebsite this kid gives me a lot of hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whyofcorso I had a very mild version of this when I was a teenager https://t.co/E3pafAyGll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beingbrina my hope is YC is playing it up. my fear is YC is going to light their money on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Adam Schiff (D) doesn’t want Democrats to win https://t.co/gxrkYbM9x1 https://t.co/jmfdlW08qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCaskill is 5 for 5 on Trump cabinet nominees so far https://t.co/lGxEZt3ofV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieWDC +++++++++++++++++++ and PETER THIEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes there is so much money and momentum waiting to come out for the people who lead. no one understands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbloom this is a wonderful tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mollykatch they could raise more with a different kind of program but go for the short-term high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mollykatch this: https://t.co/flLUzSadO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noisy_summer the only thing that will stop this is directive from party leadership. don’t hold your breath: https://t.co/flLUzSadO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markg0077 she was 8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETodes you can’t do the math without knowing the total number of donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETodes @politico @DanielStrauss4 that is an entirely different equation and the real measure of small-dollar success or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ETodes @politico @DanielStrauss4 yes, 73% of donations. it doesn’t say the percentage of *money* that came from contributions of &lt;$200]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @DanielStrauss4 what is the total amount of money from small-dollar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people talk about the number of small-dollar contributions instead of the amount of small-dollar money, they’re hiding big money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[73% of Perez’s donations being &lt;$200 is meaningless. What’s the percentage of dollars &lt;$200 raised @DanielStrauss4?  https://t.co/ki4qJevRzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeredithLClark yes! it is now a must-have protest accessory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And 2 favorites from the 2012 Occupy general strike. https://t.co/FNHzCB9GV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one @sarahljaffe shared, from the 2010 Greek Uprising. I’m told it says, “We are the Rock, they are the Sci… https://t.co/OwtAdbuMGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a folder of protest signs that I keep. Seems a good time to bring them out. This is from the Wobblies. https://t.co/xEM2W79vKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noisy_summer my man looks like A.C. Slater got stung by a hornet’s nest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like Jason Chaffetz to explore the idea of launching himself into the sun https://t.co/c8dvAgpiWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still can’t get over the fact that we have killed 2 of Anwar al-Awlaki’s U.S. citizen kids; 16-year-old Abdulrahman and 8-year-old Nawar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not an accident that U.S. keeps killing al-Awlaki's children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget, Robert Gibbs said Abdulrahman al-Awlaki "should have a far more responsible father" after we drone st… https://t.co/GvHRhbNdQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noisy_summer ok that makes me feel a tiny bit better BUT STILL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noisy_summer ok but the more I think about this it's terrifying. It's a baseball bat! Do the machines know what's coming????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always wanted to help primary a chickenshit Democratic senator https://t.co/SIX5LonplX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7im @MikePenceVP fake account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ActBlue is the best fundraising tool out there. $1.5 billion raised! https://t.co/dUDf71e1d5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn’t build the arena to accommodate a hockey team. One end mostly doesn’t have seats. https://t.co/i6LF3yMBBS https://t.co/LJFCYazIeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPP finds the American people see Joe Flacco as NOT an elite quarterback. 22% Elite, 41% Not Elite https://t.co/Lq3gZvn0RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dope Ohio Teen Gets Her Dying Wish: Tasing a Cop https://t.co/B0c8MCpXBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She’s joining that darth that escaped from philly https://t.co/TecilVNh9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseberney Jesse what on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doh. Plouffe left before inauguration. Good. https://t.co/KzYCnuUbeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericming5 oh dang! wow. thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sethdmichaels Seth this was a great tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This website is free https://t.co/mslxl0aC0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coxn I got that one on Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not great https://t.co/yrmoRnRay7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliacarriew yep. This is a once in a long time moment for them to secure the organization's funding for a decade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$10 million in 24 hours without an email is insane. With email the sky's the limit. Sustained email campaign could do $100 in a week or so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But they haven't sent an email since Friday :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They could do another $50 million in the next week https://t.co/8Likvx3DR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good work Chuck https://t.co/wg3osMTlPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's entire business model is to be a scab https://t.co/A4bxCJ958Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebruenig yet. It is very very feasible and can happen almost immediately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Casey and Elizabeth Warren are the only senators out tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libbycwatson @Bro_Pair the most surprising thing to me is there has been ZERO advocacy from any left groups about principle of all no votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libbycwatson @Bro_Pair OR is a c4 so they can't. Shitty. Any number of other groups should but aren't right now. Don't get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan_munz @speechboy71 LGA is objectively worse in all respects though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicoleindc time to eat the rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any idea why about 5 blocks north of the White House going east/west are blocked? We can go south on 17th all the way but not horizontal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidFo58626738 @mcuban fuck that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democratic establishment is getting completely blown past and will regret it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pelosi and Schumer both said "the Statue of Liberty is crying" but it's people who are deploying to the streets https://t.co/NiadnDVcvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryWebsite did you see this https://t.co/3oo2acymug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw Jackson sure looks like a part of the conversation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnknefel all those militias created to resist the Feds would go to the front lines for them too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's time to reclaim the Gadsden flag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mw_ebooks that's pretty bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @kombiz or travel for any number of days from days 1-90 and then want to go back some time again in days 90-180.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @kombiz ah it’s for visa renewals which expire at 90 days https://t.co/Bl2XCUfrnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kombiz it’s the interview suspension for repeat visitors only https://t.co/PndxrDJf0H

still bad, obviously, but not as huge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LAURENSTARRETT fun fact, the unsubscribe link leads to a page to sign up for email, not to unsubscribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @DCCC should send out an email apologizing, clarifying, and giving direct donate links to Planned Parenthood. @repbenraylujan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancesWithTamis first time i brought a girlfriend to meet my grandma, my grandma farts and runs to the bathroom with hands on her butt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshBaxNYC I’m really at a loss on this. so irresponsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanMcElwee raw small-dollar money to the DNC has dropped 50% since 2010]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseberney @emmaroller I’d be way less mad if they split contributions with PP or gave emails or something. This is just swindling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But DCCC telling its millions of people that Planned Parenthood is eliminated in their city is a brand new low. https://t.co/XquZwacdtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single one of these emails takes away money from Planned Parenthood itself because the Dem organizations can’t raise on their merits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is House Majority PAC, pretending to be Planned Parenthood https://t.co/abBEzsUxuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic orgs have for years pretended to be Planned Parenthood for money. E.G., this is actually the Democratic… https://t.co/MtQQx5dcIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is unacceptable. You CANNOT straight up lie to people in email. You can’t scare people for money. https://t.co/eCUteWzpVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samknight1 awesome, thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COMPLETELY fucked up, @Dccc https://t.co/eCUteWzpVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[let’s get these guys a bail and legal fund https://t.co/BdCHRlW3R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The subject lost (badly) but it did lead to a whole segment of “How else is Bernie Sanders pandering to Juggalos?” https://t.co/kix9DQ5jAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all this talk of political Juggalos, please remember when I made a joke about ICP in a Bernie subject line tes… https://t.co/p4TsZEcy3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is unsustainable for me. Feels like I’m getting suckerpunched every time I log on and then ask for more. It’s just too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewnazdin that is 2 too many steps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knows of a good Twitter list for national political journalists that isn’t a firehose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManWithoutPants I don’t think this is wrong. Rybak is the only one making sense in this article. They didn’t offer more than “not trump"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bookmark this for when Priorities helps 2018 senate candidates who support sessions https://t.co/piV69R96mP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>