<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter O'Mahony's current mood. (Looks like his mood all the time in fairness) https://t.co/RJwSPr8PH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darron Gibson, 29, has played in 103 league games in English football - 25 fewer than 20-year-old Dele Alli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off Thursday night, Tommy Tiernan and First Dates on RTÉ 1/2. Off Sunday night and REPEATS of Tommy Tiernan and First Dates on RTÉ 1/2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday night, watching #roomtoimprove and living the dream. https://t.co/J4B7MVN58J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming urge to buy a Kia for some reason, can't explain it. #kia #AusOpen #sponsors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa Nadal is such a class act. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fourteen years since Federer's first grand slam title - remarkable durability. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis, bloody hell. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed back from the dead! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fraser Forster could fit Steven Davis in his pocket. https://t.co/xiiMTGIMY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbconlon I can offer you a tiny bit of football chocolate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbconlon Errr...advertising wouldn't be my area of expertise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cadbury's have taken things up a notch in with football-sized chocolate ⚽️ https://t.co/e59aN7ZnDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevByrneBox Vegas weather update badly needed for @AidanDonoghue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late getting to Colm O'Rourke's Sindo column with this outrageously sexist remark. #GAA https://t.co/4rdMJRSK6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blount-force trauma.#PITvsNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Super Bowl XI team is the... https://t.co/zBHdBQkFfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So close to the Hail MaRyan. #GBvsATL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fail Mary #GBvsATL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Jeff_Reinebold with excellent analysis on the touch screen for Sky Sports. Really good insight. #GBvsATL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankfully Atlanta's Mohamed Sanu has "Sr" on his jersey to differentiate himself from his one-year-old son. #GBvsATL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty tough on Connacht to be eliminated despite getting more points than Toulon, who qualified. #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre season or not, that's a terrible result for Kildare. #GAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Sean Spicer just Conor Lenihan with hair plugs? https://t.co/7RI6rYvzov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They spelt "Rooney" wrong. https://t.co/xWKslehDzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobby Charlton is finally able to pick his nose in peace again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROOle Britannia (or ROOle Bet365).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand Stevie G tweets to come...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve McClaren has forced poor Donald to get soaked. #WallyWithTheBrolly #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% white faces in that choir. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT - DONALD TRUMP'S HAIR IS FLYING PAST MY HOUSE. #Inauguration https://t.co/7CtOksNz10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbconlon Haha no need to tell it like it is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbconlon "aim ballon"?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's me in the green bib under the red balloon. Dizzying heights of fame. https://t.co/ru6tqto0SP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is well worth a listen. https://t.co/5bwmW26nf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickARoyle I listened to that too and was surprised it was rated so highly. Possibly not, a lot of good stuff on basketball too though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger nooo the pressure! Kerry's @AidanDonoghue will back me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbconlon yeah! Will drop it over to you if you want, definitely worth a look. Much better than I expected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@endabolger yeah was surprisingly good! Expected the usual match by match stuff but was very interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished this - up there with the best GAA books around. https://t.co/AyDYhWQQM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha "this is playoff time, you're not conservative...and here comes the field goal unit." #PITvsKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-time classic in any sport. #GBvsDAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For the first time in quite some time we have Munster flags flying high on foreign soil," say Sky, week after they won in Paris. #GLAvMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OdhranMahony imagine! Cracking match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it really necessary for Sky Sports comm to apologise for a player swearing during a rugby match? #GLAvMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hull come from behind to beat Bournemouth. What would Marco Silva know about having to 'dig in', eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not one for hyperbole, but this year's Prem Goal of the Season could be the best one in history. Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tik a boo, Andy Carroll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONAN THE DESTROYER #LEIvMON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;Weekly moan about Mark Robson's commentary&gt; #LEIvMON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deryckfay Ha, I couldn't possibly say!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump discusses plane costs and the fact that he's a germaphobe... https://t.co/vqxwQt3hAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Tower followed by Trump shower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never has Phil Neville said something that wasn't immediately obvious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like after confession, when you were given three Hail Marys. https://t.co/zfIq0vfcBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickey Harte has a pop at those on moral high ground. Mickey Harte, the Pioneer. https://t.co/f5GRdz5Eg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Kerry championship includes teams from Spain, according to Joe Brolly. https://t.co/bDFtkHy8WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donaldgmcrae knew nothing about Emile Griffith before reading "A Man's World". Extraordinary stuff, particularly t… https://t.co/dfVvpxmN1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never change, Tony Pulis. https://t.co/741oLMTTIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He's all aboard the maximum train." Darts commentary is the BEST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALLY PALLY WALLY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will when you learn how to spell. Deal? https://t.co/flbRjTOLdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jones writhing around like a freshly-caught fish did for Feghouli there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickARoyle Ridiculous stuff. He looked a beaten man and yet was still firing in the 180s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MVG "Still has to apply the gloss to this masterpiece." Not sure if the great artists cracked open a tin of Crown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressions of the Isle of Man coat of arms are all the rage lately. Dundalk's Dane Massey still the pick of the lo… https://t.co/hvzGycJ2qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tony_Cuddihy Hard to credit that within a week, Mkhitaryan's goal has been put in the ha'penny place. Phenomenal strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football can only go downhill for the rest of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickARoyle get something in that fuckin frying pan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In tears after watching the Kevin Bridges "house rice" bit. Hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearsecorcoran yeah, seems they have a ruthless streak - no messing around, despite perceptions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late getting around to #pulllikeadog - fascinating insight to the O'Donovan brothers, tough lads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royle Family 'Que Sera' scene is all-time classic TV. Would need a heart of stone not to be moved by it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PadraigMcKeon Unfortunately my Gaeilge isn't as good as it should be...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough choice between not understanding TG4 commentary and listening to Sky commentator prattling on... #MUNvLEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like binge watching Black Mirror to get you into the festive spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gareth Barry just hoofing it every time he gets possession.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Joe Brolly just spotted the Sindo legal department. https://t.co/FtTcYV5TSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slightly chilly for Packers-Bears later. Real feel of -22C. ❄️❄️❄️ https://t.co/rvLHwdvbJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RFU boss: "I think Dylan's got credit in the bank." Jesus. https://t.co/Kp7o363ji8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Utd still haven't scored more than once against a team currently in the top 10 in a Premier League match this season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ui_Maine ref steps in to SHTAP the fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely guffawed at this paragraph in Ken Early's Euro 2016 diary in the @SecondCaptains annual. Brilliant stuff. https://t.co/8FHJJs4xf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a chest-beating republican by any means, but Joe Brolly v good in today's Sindo. https://t.co/wCmtxv3mwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone else should do a thread about how awful Donald Trump is. That'd be great. Maybe he'll read it and leave politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spare change for Jose, anyone? https://t.co/fBlaL0vOit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schweinsteiger: Never has a player's reputation been enhanced as much by his absence. Totally past it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster's Darren Sweetnam has a previous career as a hurler - and Anthony from the Royle Family. https://t.co/w0m68mGalE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football in the McGloin. https://t.co/WUDCC4VJkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simms: "holding the football is important for a quarterback." Can't beat NFL analysis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corofin boss Kevin O'Brien: "That performance probably wouldn’t be good enough in a semi-final." After 14-POINT win in Connacht final. #GAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits think he's stealing your look, lads. https://t.co/C56nBCisbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will do well to see a better intro in the Sunday papers. https://t.co/9HxepNnRDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven of the 23 Ireland players used had 10 caps or fewer before kick-off. Makes the result all the more impressive. #irevaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take THAT, Australia! https://t.co/WpwVg5xe2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simon Geoghegan will end up on the wing again at this rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noriordan @NewsNeil13 was first NZ game v Ireland post Lions - lads threatening to hang Umagu by the laces off their Dubes. A bear pit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsNeil13 he came on late but had an underwhelming first few caps, to say the least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsNeil13 was actually working in the bar behind East Stand before and after but got to see it- different buzz alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was at Lansdowne Road for Rory Best's debut - didn't think he'd get 100 minutes for Ireland, let alone 100 caps. Incredible improvement.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>