<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[After Berkeley: A Right Wing Call to Self-Defense https://t.co/xfIlO21KwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rebel’s first “Guns &amp; Gals” event! https://t.co/5PeCoezkde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelliekelly23 I don't blame trump for doing that. I would do the same thing if I had the same opportunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm honestly what on earth were you thinking with this deal? What did you expect was going to happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah that's how you handle the fallout from this deal with Obama, ignore the people who criticise you. Resign now!!! https://t.co/W71GkVMiv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captain Kirk Meets Ashley Judd - F*#%-ing Hilarious! https://t.co/iHd2sHYto9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieJuliezac3 @TeamTAbbott @TurnbullMalcolm if only he was like that in 2002, he would have been PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliMauritania @PrisonPlanet just because our prime ministers a pussy doesn't mean we are. We don't even want this clown as PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @HumanHeadline it's also the dirtiest word in nsw. Mans monis, Kiernan loverage were out on bail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thongdam07 @theboltreport @SkyNewsAust by sticking it to Turnbull he is sticking up for oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and we also support trump at a grand scale. Our prime minister needs to resign immediately https://t.co/ORugSRaPnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @sandro_au not to worry. Our prime minister is a complete moron. The news of his phone call has made everyone laugh down here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It more than made my day! I'm going to be remembering this day for a long time. The 2nd of February, the day turnbu… https://t.co/8BR4CP20MK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob carr Donald trump has every right to be angry. Turnbull is a complete moron for making this deal https://t.co/I2xPICoona]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theboltreport @SkyNewsAust @PrisonPlanet watch this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigel Farage: The European Parliament is terrified of Trump https://t.co/Yly7WsJhdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Last Laugh - Liberals Mocked Trump... Until He Won - Fox &amp; Friends https://t.co/FWat9uNMHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abolish firearms registry, says SSAA https://t.co/HlUCLGK9cU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Young Turks Are Falling Apart https://t.co/p1uNfdgPUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stinchfield | Dianne Feinstein Forgets Her Own Immigration Ban - 1/31/17 https://t.co/Bf9kguhKsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone verify this story? https://t.co/smO41tk7xK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @sunshadow7 we're talking about getting rid of stupid laws like this. Pay attention https://t.co/vEzqZyoS2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunshadow7 @christobel_wood gotta ban cars because you'll get drunk and run someone over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Dumbest Anti Gun Quotes By Politicians https://t.co/L2c9esSEur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @sunshadow7 then why do you propose laws that take them away from the law abiding people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @sunshadow7 watch this video to see why that statement is so stupid https://t.co/1xvswUiCbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theboltreport @SkyNewsAust no, maintaining the status quo will be a gift to labor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood because you never asked me that question also when you do answer mine you get a straight answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @sunshadow7 that's completely wrong, being able to protect yourself and having the means to do so is a human right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cement71 How about sharing the video with his constituents, he resides in a marginal WS seat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood I don't care whether or not you accept what I do or don't. so stick that self righteous attitude where it belongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bolt Report Editorial 31.01 https://t.co/xSOBHbQ8aF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @DavidLeyonhjelm are you going to answer the question or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HBangwaller @DavidLeyonhjelm you mean that one blimp caused by the mass shooting compared to every other year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christobel_wood @DavidLeyonhjelm here's the real question do you think that an appearance law makes you safer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @theage ! Any tips for how to get rid of the crummy media? #fakenews https://t.co/l5I5cbPGqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CamEdwards have you seen this video? It's absolutely hilarious how this guy gets shut down https://t.co/jsLwXuW6Sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sad Downfall of Shia Labeouf HE WILL NOT DIVIDE US https://t.co/FKWcgpsYEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec Terror Attack  - What They're Not Telling You! https://t.co/MvXrFLu1q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government rethinks new draft gun laws - Tasmania Talks https://t.co/0GZFXFymQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firearm laws, pensions for millionaires and dealing with the government https://t.co/jhxGSumuvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Contributor Reports Fake News From PARODY Twitter Account https://t.co/KiOdYNLjkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth About Trump's 'Muslim Ban' https://t.co/qfyklY4N3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bolt Report Editorial 30.01 https://t.co/o8ghGE6Dnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIGHT AFTER ATTACKING SANCTUARY CITIES, LOOK WHAT MIAMI JUST DID FOR TRUMP! https://t.co/1loRHqEUP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson meanwhile in the real world people like us deal with critics all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson yes, the echo chamber. Can't live outside the box]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson you have a volunteer here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson can't wait to see her reaction when one nation wins more seats in parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson I like it when they have a meltdown though. It's always hilarious to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shockresistant2 @Greens it's the way they work. If they can't ban it they regulate it out of existence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxidious @ohnoitsreality @JaneCaro although she down plays one and uses inflated numbers for the other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro what evidence? Not once has what you proposed ever worked https://t.co/M0i6FgcKLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah and I own a large acre property on Mars. You are a joke! I wouldn't vote for you if you held a gun to my head https://t.co/SsbDp3zCFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we have the very first stupid thing she's done as premier. Not looking forward to her reign as premier now https://t.co/agCzHOyrT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson @BillDobell @JaneCaro she's irrelevant as far as I'm concerned. However she has no right to speak on my behalf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson @BillDobell @JaneCaro not to mention she compared marriage with prostitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapitson @BillDobell @JaneCaro she publically referred people who are like me as not being a normal person. She's a shit stain on society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about you piss off @janecaro . Adults need to talk https://t.co/ZjbU1EDQ8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night of the Living Dead Liberals https://t.co/Zeqx3AecZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herman Cain: Americans are waking up to the media's bias https://t.co/1uLZogfDIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I hate affirmative action and quotas https://t.co/eAU73oqAjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the Hell Happened to the Left? https://t.co/d17Nl06Q54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March For Life Hardly Gets Any Media Coverage https://t.co/5IHof5QyOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Have Been Suspended From Twitter #FreeSargon https://t.co/ntyL3sPRz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innocent Celebs Almost Ruined By The Media https://t.co/uo4gJZeOdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Didn’t Wave Goodbye to Media When Boarding Air Force One - And They're Upset https://t.co/2gteXUwwyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FACEBOOK IS DONE! THIS NEW APP JUST KILLED CENSORSHIP AND RESTORED FREED... https://t.co/KBIMFOVdcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Actors Who Treat Fellow Cast Members Like Trash https://t.co/tJGF8fiOpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Marcus21 I fixed the problem and uploaded the video now https://t.co/aTQu934M0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's what happens when you take away the rights of citizens to defend themselves, place politically correct… https://t.co/tJSJ51gJEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big question on new gun ban is why? https://t.co/8mVWjcX3G1 via @theadvocatetas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Doing Dog Tricks for Free Candy https://t.co/8QiUxtgDu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lab Equipment Mistaken for KKK Meeting on College Campus https://t.co/LQVMFbr5RV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The judges who voted against the will of the people should be thrown in jail for treason https://t.co/UlrS6CvQc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Good Teachers Want School Choice https://t.co/oZBXl4Arw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Crowd Shouts "CNN SUCKS" in Wilkes-Barre, PA 10/10/16 https://t.co/9qGJZcKePD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainstream Media Publicly Shamed by 20,000 Americans https://t.co/gVBE5uRG7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof: Trump's Inauguration Felt Across The Galaxy https://t.co/TzvYzqzONz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RUSSIANS SEND HELLISH FAREWELL MESSAGE TO OBAMA THAT LEFT HIM SHAKEN AND SHAMED https://t.co/ZHqf12M0uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSM Booed Out Of The Inaugural Parade https://t.co/LnCUnQnmCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IDIOTS REACT TO TRUMP INAUGURATION https://t.co/E3aJFgADn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet crime is completely out of control in Melbourne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victims Of Trump Protestor Violence Speak Out https://t.co/PwNAWuNgH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Journalist Loves To Be Under Globalist Tyranny https://t.co/DSaxk8POOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider Secrets of the Mainstream Media https://t.co/YnsRERdRb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man actually mans monis had an extensive rap sheet and should have been in jail. He was out on bail during the Lindt cafe siege]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man @diversion2006 it's mans monis all over again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man I'd like nothing more than to get on with my life and be left alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man at least with social media we can have a say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man only two weeks. We have to put up with 20 years of talking heads and keyboard activists thumbing their noses at us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Browndogg_30x Or he can do something better, step down and let someone with a spine take over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man it's an important topic as well as is the right of self defence. You can't just scurry away as you only hurt yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mondo_dismo @Coalition_Man @jewelsparkle3 that tends to vary quite a bit. The May issue States don't tend to issue… https://t.co/IGQAOtMcIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhondaForbes @colleenwilson20 @DavidLeyonhjelm you should also condemn this act as well https://t.co/4npHYNIZi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coalition_Man @jewelsparkle3 @mondo_dismo which part of the US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLeyonhjelm it's a good point but it's not the time for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumanHeadline @anthillis yes, how dare he points out how the mainstream media exploits tragedies for their own agenda like you do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coward News Network Hides On Top Of Building https://t.co/tCX0rBOz1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[African &amp; Sudanese Refugees - Immigration and Ethnic Crime in Victoria - The Bolt Report https://t.co/NhDEVMyJnw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>