<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't release and process trapped emotions from the body properly and regularly , then your body is... https://t.co/IVudM0wiaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be apart of another fabulous local event, at Shaz Butterfly's Terrigal Psychic Fair this Sunday. 
I... https://t.co/pKAaqvzvIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My good friend and business coach Sze Wing Yip is running an awesome online webinar this Thursday night filled... https://t.co/fR7K5htS6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be good! âœ¨ðŸ’«ðŸ’•â˜ºï¸ https://t.co/utdS31Jauv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save the date!
The last 6 months has been an amazing time for growth and expansion with in the health and... https://t.co/n4DJC4DHLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all my awesome conscious minded entrepeneurs friends......check out the brand new Gratitude website, that has... https://t.co/IbX9ZdmdMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So looking forward to this!!! Anyone else fancy a weekend in the Blue Mountains with some awesome people who... https://t.co/EqVVGnrcE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you keep affirming this year 2017 will be the best year ever! Want to make this the best year of your life,... https://t.co/5THnwE1vsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of Lisa Brennan and her charity Snuggle Coats making it onto The Project tonight!
If you have any old... https://t.co/1C7GEylWOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My good friend and fabulous business mentor Sze Wing Yip is running a fabulous free online meeting next week to... https://t.co/HyA56Z286P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My good friend and fabulous business mentor Sze Wing Yip is running a fabulous free online meeting next week to... https://t.co/XtxiBYXqJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these 5 top tips for Empaths, on how to stay emotionally balanced , Thankyou Deepak ðŸŒºðŸ™ðŸ»ðŸ’– https://t.co/prdjfW8oCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please watch, when you know how the body truly works , it empowers you to make changes. ðŸŒºðŸ˜Š https://t.co/gxvlntoBLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many fabulous free workshops at next months Embrace Life Festival in the Blue Mountains, and I especially... https://t.co/kAhiKF2C4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling out to all my beautiful  friends who have a business here on the Central Coast who would love to join a... https://t.co/biVlY4KBcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving my friend Rut's morning kundalini yoga practice she is sharing. A true inspiration at how anyone , even us... https://t.co/Xpzm1laT8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been feeling the call for yoga this year? Great new yoga classes and times going on next door with Carrera Jones... https://t.co/i4BzNkYngD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth behind many many modern day autoimmune diseases that unfortunately most doctors won't find for years!!!... https://t.co/ERQHjlcNfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man Anthony Williams , the Medical medium is the Bomb!!! His books and ground breaking information on the... https://t.co/P7GO0l6oBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful encouragement this week from the Angels!! ðŸ’•âœ¨ðŸ’«ðŸ‘¼ https://t.co/FhKLXLre7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your sensitivity truly is a gift and an essential part of who you are. Love and embrace it today .... To help you... https://t.co/IwomvsCH6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking off another fabulous year with the Embrace Life Community in the Blue Mountains! A great weekend away and... https://t.co/zu16iGGNqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all my beautiful Earth Angel friends and clients, this book is a MUST !!! And the book I talk about all the... https://t.co/eqURzHZb1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of my friend Lisa Brennan, and her charity Snuggle Coats! she has her first write up in the SMH paper!... https://t.co/s9cNrMJKRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's message from the Angels is from the Angel of Peace ðŸŒ¸ðŸ‘¼âœ¨ðŸ’• https://t.co/Xm6EMQL33C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AN oldy but a goody ðŸŒºðŸŒ¸ https://t.co/Df1OTWsfjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Angel card ......The truth about "letting things go" ðŸ‘¼âœ¨ðŸ’« https://t.co/QKo05JNVDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend this 4 day class for any mums out there concerned about their young daughters self esteem and... https://t.co/KOvVwOy1mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to another fabulous weekend in the Blue Mountains!! A whole weekend of fun and Intuitive... https://t.co/j77BLH5r2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited the beautiful Embrace Life Festivals that I love being apart of and being the Central Coast ambassador... https://t.co/ou2HTRNobk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year message from the Angels for 2017 ðŸ’–ðŸ‘¼âœ¨ðŸ’•ðŸ’« https://t.co/LoUPUgQyCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angel card and flower essence for today! ðŸ‘¼âœ¨ðŸ’«ðŸŒºðŸŒ¸ https://t.co/tvhPhKLHtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How chronic stress affects your brain and can greatly deteriorate your health and happiness .
This is why daily... https://t.co/qABOEIZpPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this article by Melissa Matthews on the Joy Of Christmas ðŸ™ðŸ»ðŸŽ„âœ¨ðŸ’– https://t.co/97sh3Wl07y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's just under 2 weeks now til Christmas and I can feel the craziness vibe ramping up. 
Things to do, buy,... https://t.co/JJvc4YPmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morining beautiful Bloom family and Earth Angels!
Just a little reminder for any of you who are already... https://t.co/KopIvZIXcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How amazing is my beautiful friend Rut Frohlich, 
Sharing her love of kundalini yoga, supporting others to... https://t.co/OHctmt54Gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016
I love my job!! ðŸ’•ðŸ’–ðŸ’–
I love my clients, my friends and my beautiful family, Thankyou to you all... https://t.co/7I93spYnJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yearinreview2016
I love my job!! ðŸ’•ðŸ’–ðŸ’–
I love my clients, my friends and my beautiful family, Thankyou to you all... https://t.co/JKjpfrQvQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all my beautiful friends who have a health and wellbeing practice or business AND truly wants to be apart of... https://t.co/vDHanhadfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please help my beautiful friend Lisa Brennan, she started an amazing charity "snuggle coats" , where she turns... https://t.co/HpJQY7AN8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What another beautiful day today, spending it with all these gorgeous, amazing souls. 
So constantly amazed how... https://t.co/qPkDmbr6uI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angel bumps are around already, many spirits around today already, anxious to get messages through to loved ones,... https://t.co/9Z61BpAAVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch just gets better and better downstairs! Yum! ðŸ˜‹ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/ad3IAxOMDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have been doing hearing the call, doing the work, its time to break free and Bloom 
Today's messages from... https://t.co/FoW7WE9o11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you Marisa Finestone! Truly magical way to start the day! The cool salty breeze, blue skies, turquoise... https://t.co/qM1D2z5Fe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous article to help explain why so many are feeling such huge emotional shifts, lows and old issues... https://t.co/WFb0GkReVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend coming along and attending  my friend Sze Wing Yip workshop this Saturday on how to embrace your... https://t.co/OPlQyPfTZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So blessed to spend the day with this amazing group of Intuitive Readers, who do an amazing job of bringing... https://t.co/ffSug9peV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How great is the line up of music, sound healing and workshops at this Saturday's Northern Beaches Embrace Life... https://t.co/8C6lQMEPh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this article! Time to switch off the stress hormones and activate the happy ones!!! â˜ºï¸ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ƒ https://t.co/8tPmWszJG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self care is a long term plan ðŸ’–
If you have fallen off the wagon, all you have to do is, remake the decision to... https://t.co/vZ7l3aXlsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Precious messages from Spirit ðŸ’–ðŸ™ðŸ»ðŸ‘¼ https://t.co/F2zghjuTMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend booking a 30 min healing with Melissa Matthews next Saturday at the Northern Beaches Embrace... https://t.co/aLHEXCgZcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all my beautiful friends who are interested in learning more about kinesiology and how emotional stress affect... https://t.co/I1INvVSFH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The transformational healing power of sound and music is so amazing and Devine. The energy and vibration resontes... https://t.co/Y3lCBuqHeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many fabulous free workshops to check out at the Northern Beaches Embrace Life Festival, next Saturday and I... https://t.co/xRmZKzsQm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you fascinated by crystals? Want to experience their powerful healing ability? Book in for a crystal healing... https://t.co/25QalNvdKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An evening with spirit this Friday, with Shaz Butterfly! A great night out. ðŸ’–ðŸ’– https://t.co/EzaCbPVwoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How gorgeous is this beautiful raw cake now at available at work, 
Looks like the perfect signature cake for Me... https://t.co/0B5v1SIZlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your love and kindness Empowering others or Enabling .... 
Time to awaken and re evaluate ðŸ’– https://t.co/UWElA2IAMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to short, guided meditations regularly, especially first thing in the morning is one of my favourite... https://t.co/I6bgWykMjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 2 weeks til the Northern Beaches Embrace Life Festival!! 
The thing I love most about these festivals is the... https://t.co/2E4MqLLIqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be co hosting this class tomorrow with Carrera Jones, only a couple of spots left!
For all you... https://t.co/YJzgKWjh60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hour workshop this Sunday !!
Receive , Breathe, Believe! 
With Carrera Jones ðŸ’–ðŸ‘¼ https://t.co/N0TkXyPPet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Keep your positivity flowing!
Thanks Marisa Finestone for nominating me. ðŸ’– https://t.co/7pwK4AAEHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude Online is an amazing platform that I am so honoured to be apart of. This community truly embraces and... https://t.co/a3gMFMFq1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This month I have dedicated my writing to honour the beautiful messages I have been receiving from my Guardian... https://t.co/sppCEON08K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The card of today is "Transformation"!!
Time to celebrate you!! https://t.co/wEjU1ZJ2pJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you craving space! 
Check out my latest article on why alone time I'd essential for earth Angels and Empaths.... https://t.co/UwuYlcHJF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you lovingly speaking your truth! https://t.co/zhIWzGkJJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you craving SPACE!!
A self care essential for Empaths and Earth Angels. 
My latest whispers from the Angels... https://t.co/ttyJh8VTF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your sensitivity is really increasing at the moment, honour it!! It's a gift!! https://t.co/Mf2q3JiezZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/O49AWDt5ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you feeling the call to start balancing your giving and receiving?
Learn how to restore your Insanity to... https://t.co/esQqLbn8ZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you lost your ability to allow and receive .....
Are you stuck in the cycle of doing, giving and controlling ? https://t.co/ytEF0cyRGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you craving SPACE!
A drama detox?
An essential self care practice for earth Angels and Empaths https://t.co/yV1pxNRC89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you craving SPACE! 
An essential self care practice for earth Angels and Empaths https://t.co/g59MGdUj7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a ball tonight at the Northern Beaches Embrace Life Pre event night!!
Grounding in the energy 
Last... https://t.co/HUCkF8yuOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to finally be collaborating with the amazing Carrera Jones from yoga with CJ! 
Learning how to be in... https://t.co/aWRJNUaRbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/jTZ7pJ1mNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day for early bird tickets and online bookings!! https://t.co/GWNJkMFkCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the restorative Yin restorative yoga classes with CJ and highly recommend them for anyone trying to recover... https://t.co/4AJ4dk94Mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/ZeQTauMO0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/RS4IEy4Krg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early bird tickets for just $12 still available til Friday!!
Kids Free!! 
See you there! ó¾…ó¾¬ó¾†¯ https://t.co/lbF5yAUqSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh space!! Such an essential key healing ingredient for Empaths and Earth Angels. 
Time out and space from... https://t.co/6kqS6fTXk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone who hadn't seen this amazing Louise Hay movie "You can heal your life" I truly recommend it! 
You can... https://t.co/pgjcIUf68u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all us sensitive Empaths ó¾¬ https://t.co/8oKGuzv21d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Festival is going to be HUGE!!! So excited!! ó¾”—ó¾†¯ó¾”–ó¾”  https://t.co/BMUVQIL9FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Lucy, she is this years Ambassador for the Newcastle Embrace Life Festival and has done an AMAZING job... https://t.co/t7HQ6aVPLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So here is the line up and program of events at next Sunday's Newcastle Embrace Life Festival!
Yoga, Kirtan... https://t.co/YyGo2m29R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace Families at Newcastle! https://t.co/nUlCNlLCWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun Fun Fun again in Newcastle!
Music, yoga, holistic therapies, Intuitive Readings, healings, free workshops and... https://t.co/e6iOS0bb4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tears are just a sign, that you are melting the ice around your heart AND a soul in a human body. ó¾¬ https://t.co/d3n3BjesCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend booking a healing with the amazing Melissa Matthews at Newcastle embrace festival!! https://t.co/j02QjhUZIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to another brilliant day in the Intuitive Readers room at the up coming Newcastle Embrace Life... https://t.co/v53cM6Qp8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommend booking in early for workshops, readings and healings. Especially recommend going to my awesome... https://t.co/OBIlDR1xxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/ba4zPyunCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling the call for some Deep and Meaningful Life Purpose development?
Check out Katrena Friel's amazing up... https://t.co/eTYjOLzx1e]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>