<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said @MegaTJP cyber bullying is such a stupid petty pathetic thing to do to someone https://t.co/XnHwN5Rvrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWERollins my thoughts and prayers are with you dude, hope you can make it back for mania, theres no way the MAN deserves to miss out again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cashmeoussidehowbowdah and the fact it's became a worldwide phenomenon of a meme is exactly what the fuck is wrong with this world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick of seeing #cashmeoussidehowbowdah memes and shit, she can't even speak properly, it's exactly what's wrong with this world ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OneMillion subscribers for @WhatCultureWWE congrats to the best wrestling Channel on YouTube @LessDefined @KennyMc1985 @suzieadkennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OneMillion subscribers for @WhatCultureWWE congrats to the best wrestling Channel on YouTube @adampacitti @AdamTheBlampied @JackTheJobber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adampacitti @AdamTheBlampied @JackTheJobber @KennyMc1985 still  can't believe I met you guys, congratulations on 1… https://t.co/yuRJFNOIsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best wrestlers in the world, In the ring, on the mic, on commentary, he's one of the VERY BEST in the wo… https://t.co/CbFWQfzBB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some pics of an incredible main event of WCPW Edinburgh between @GallowaySpeaks and @joeshendry https://t.co/qf4BmnntMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GallowaySpeaks entrance at WCPW Edinburgh 3/3 https://t.co/ORMJgbfACs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GallowaySpeaks entrance at WCPW Edinburgh 2/3 https://t.co/c7JTuRqQWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GallowaySpeaks entrance at WCPW 1/3 https://t.co/tl7ndHNo1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKirbyProEgo arrive, sable bomb a dickhead, leave like a general manger https://t.co/RcltmgnDKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some pics of the incredible @roxxywrestler such a great and entertaining wrestler and one of my favourites https://t.co/FC13uamaNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great pics of the amazing @MooseNation69 https://t.co/RHtHDNXHFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great pics of the iron man @Joe_Coffey https://t.co/YJC0X6c8Ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple greats pics of the HUGE and amazing @Johnny_Moss @Liam_LZRS https://t.co/a3g2S6oysL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 of the nicest guys I've had the pleasure of meeting in my life @AdamColePro @TheLethalJay @MooseNation69 https://t.co/eiRWkGtz92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most epic face off ever @adampacitti @AdamTheBlampied and @JackTheJobber was like I'm outa here see ya later https://t.co/SiOmNU4zGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaNeeverKnow is one of the nicest guys I e ever had the pleasure of speaking too https://t.co/5df1OHZ8Ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a picture with the lovely, beautiful, kind and friendly @suzieadkennedy such a lovely person https://t.co/USrwHpqo3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeaconDispair @CJDLB i meant he got physical at ICW, as he down something physical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right I'm going to try and go sleep, hopefully my nightmares won't be too bad #RoyalRumble  #RoyalRumbleNightmares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJDLB @DeaconDispair he's been at ICW progress and OTT in the past 6-8 weeks and for physical at ICW, rumours are he's been cleared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeaconDispair @FinnBalor it was said 4-6 months we are in month 5 right now, actually into the 6 month from summerslam last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinnBalor dude you let us all down, where were you? Why didn't you come to save us? Why finn why? Why just why? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one predicted that, no one #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roller coaster of emotions in the last 12 hours for me has been unreal, I dono if I wana cry or scream or throw up #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going so many feelings right now, through no Balor and wyatt god eliminated and orton won, what the fuck? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roman reigns WHAT HAVE YOU DONE? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is my boy finn Balor, I'm so upset I actually wana cry #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This royal rumble could have been the greatest in history, but the fucked it, and that's coming from a huge reigns fan #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tye FREAKING DILLINGER I like legit 1000% percent lost my shit cause tye Dillinger got called up at the #10 spot #RoyalRumble #Perfect10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going into the #RoyalRumbleMatch I'm 5-2 and my voice is nearly gone, probably will be gone at the end of the match #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cena proving he's one of the best and nicest men in wrestling EVER #RoyalRumble #5StarMatch #WWEChampionship #ClassAct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's gota be at least #5StarMatch if I've ever seen one, maybe even 6 stars? #RoyalRumble #WWEChampionship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWENetwork hey the freaking stream sorted guys FFS it's all over the freaking place #RoyalRumble #WWEChampionship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWENeville deserves this more than anyone, he's worked so hard for so freaking long #RoyalRumble #KingOfTheCruiserweights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's is why Dean Ambrose is freaking awesome #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sort the freaking stream out FFS @WWENetwork it's lagging and cutting out to hell #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackTheJobber good is an understatement, when are you guys coming back to Edinburgh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took around 200 pictures at #WCPW #WCPWEdinburgh this evening, will upload after #Loaded has been broadcast tomorrow evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackTheJobber @adampacitti @AdamTheBlampied @KennyMc1985 I've got loads of great pictures if you guys want me to forward them to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackTheJobber dude I screamed and shouted so much I've lost my voice, so great meeting all of you, especially you after waiting so long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took around 200 pictures, some really top quality ones too of @WhatCultureWWE @WhatCulturePW would like me to forward some of them to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible night at @WhatCulturePW #WCPW #WCPWEdinburgh met @adampacitti @AdamTheBlampied @JackTheJobber @KennyMc1985 after years of waiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met @YaNeeverKnow at #WCPW Edinburgh, he's such a nice guy https://t.co/9nE5dE0b7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met the beautiful and lovely @suzieadkennedy I'm so star struck right #WCPW https://t.co/lrouQWDwZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringside at @WhatCulturePW Edinburgh right now https://t.co/HOwfUykDvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love for pro wrestling has helped me over come aniexty, depression and I'm on the way to @WhatCulturePW #WCPW Edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossOnRasslin don't worry King Ross as a loyal subject I shall get a chant started for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an incredible match, nearly in tears at the end of it, can't believe nakamura lost, congrats to the #Glorious new champ #NXTTakeOver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great  #WomensChampion #Fatal4Way #NXTTakeOver @NikkiCrossWWE definitely the star of the match by far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit!!!!!!! Seth freaking Rollins #NXTTakeOver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane match right there best of the night so far #NXTTakeOver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great first two matches at #NXTTakeOver not really had time to tweet about it yet, cause the #NXTTakeOver action just don't stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My picks for this evening are roderick strong, DIY, Nikki cross, Tye Dillinger and SHINSUKE nakamura #NXTTakeOver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @ShinsukeN on wining the #NXTCompetitorOfTheYear you sir are THE KING of NXT #NXTTakeOver #NXTYearEndAwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy that @ShinsukeN won the #NXTMaleOfTheYear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointed I thought @itsBayleyWWE was gona win #NXTFemaleOfTheYear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southyb7 aye I'm watching it live dude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWEEmberMoon should be the number one contender after this match, she's the best wrestler in NXT today #NXTTakeOver #Fatal4Way #WomensTitle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to @ScottDawsonWWE and @DashWilderWWE for winning #NXTTagTeamOfTheYear you guys have redefined tag wrestling over the last 2 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to @ScottDawsonWWE and @DashWilderWWE for winning the #NXTMatchOfTheYear you guys have redefined tag team wrestling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to @JohnnyGargano and @ProjectCiampa for winning the #NXTMatchOfTheYear you guys reduced me to tears at the ending of the match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you freakingf kidding me? #NXTBreakoutOfTheYear should have been @WWEEmberMoon by far, she's been far more impressive than those 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good episode of #SDLive predictable ending though, great to see @NaomiWWE back on TV though and @BaronCorbinWWE was great too #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now @NaomiWWE in the title picture is more like, she deserves the #SDLive women's title more than anyone on the roster #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was a complete and utter waste of @NaomiWWE time and talents, she deserves so much more than she's getting #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCena and @AJStylesOrg are incredible in the ring and on the mic, this could be the feud of the decade easily #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaronCorbinWWE is such a well spoken man, he's great on commentary too and amazing in the ring, the man has it alll #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomPhillipsWWE is a better commentator than after about 6 weeks than @DavidOtunga ever was or ever will be #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the #UNDERTAKER entrance theme never fails to make my hair stand on end, and give me chills and goosebumps #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a freakin incredible match between @WWERollins and @iLikeSamiZayn kudos to both men #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great if somewhat unusual match from @joeshendry who better win the #BattleInTheCapital next week in Edinburgh cause I'm coming to see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another incredible match from @CodyRhodes I hope he's gonna be at #WCPW when it comes to Edinburgh next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here we go with one of the best wrestlers in the world today @CodyRhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GallowaySpeaks with another amazing promo, NO ONE cuts a better promo in wrestling right now than him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wanna talk about wrestling then join my Facebook group called let's talk wrestling https://t.co/yEIVfF4ZoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was a waste of time #SDLive was so predictable it was unreal, disappointing cause it's usually #Raw that's predictable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm well and truly stoked for the #RoyalRumble this year, it's stacked and for once it's unpredictable #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooohhhh scratch that things just got interesting #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go again, the same 5 guys again and again, why did I stay up for this #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 2 night of watching wrestling at a decent hour with the #WWEUKCT staying up till 1am to watch #RAW is soul destroying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit, that was an incredible MOTY candidate from @WillOspreay @BeaPriestley @KingRicochet @teamTblanchard #WCPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow o wow @Johnny_Moss and @Liam_LZRS are one of the most entertaining tag teams in the world, and @Johnny_Moss is straight up scary #WCPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTMatchOfTheYear
#DIYvsRevival 
This match had me crying at the end of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTCompetitorOfTheYear
#ShinsukeNakamura]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTMaleOfTheYear 
#ShinsukeNakamura]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTFemaleOfTheYear 
#Bayley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTBreakoutOfTheYear
#EmberMoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTTagTeamOfTheYear
#DIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTYearEndAwards #NXTTakeoverOfTheYear #Toronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting here bored out my mind waiting on #WCPW to start, this 8 o'clock start time sucks. Ive sat twiddling my thumbs for about 20 mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My only question about the #WWEUKChampionship is what tier of title is it? Is it a world title or is it more IC and US title level?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read that jimmy snuka has passed away #RIPSuperfly #RIPJimmySunka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an incredible night of wrestling, British wrestling is stronger than it has ever been  #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the crowd In attendance know about Tyler bate and #MoustacheMountain he should have been introduced as from there though #WWEUKCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone in the #WWEUKCT not been mugged or in a bar fight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if Tyler bate will get introduced as being from #MoustacheMountain #WWEUKCT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>