<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Grr...early start!!! https://t.co/OHGqMSTiGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me a wanker, but I'd be playing "Hack-a-Manny" by now. https://t.co/QaoUZ6vaVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gabriel_Lynn It's been fun Gabe. A ways to go and I have ran out of money but should be able to wrap soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billy Ray and Mr. Duval must have missed Justin Thomas's round yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew "Beef" Johnson has played his way into being in my fantasy foursome. The man's love for life is catching!  #pgatour #BEEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best leave right about now if you want to be there for the tip! #GOAWAYSNOW https://t.co/wIWMz6GMbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gabriel_Lynn It looked pretty good really, especially as I was GoogleCasting my laptop rather than using Youtube app on the Roku,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see an all @BCBOA crew working the #GNAC game up at @SFUClan tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/C9b1Wv9s2E host Howard Tsumura moonligts at his second job as a play-by-play announcer for the @SFUClan https://t.co/us5uWS7e7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFUClan @SFU_WBB Why not throw the Clan game up on the 120" screen! https://t.co/axna7VSfQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@t_hankey Karma...blades one out of the trap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@t_hankey I don't have a playing partner that would even think about looking for relief there. Play it as it lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@t_hankey If I cant see it on my 65" TV...even after they zoom in, it probably is not affecting his swing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm. I'm thinking that taking relief Justin Thomas style could knock a stroke or two off the ol 'cap, Drip irrigation system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those that missed it... https://t.co/tmSNOr1GX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htsumura Great segment Howard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scoop! @LangleyEvents coming on board to assist with keeping BC High School and University Sports in the news!!… https://t.co/1lRFehGDBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFUClan @NCAADII @htsumura @provincesports @SFU Yes it's only February but this is likely to be the best Tweet I'll see all year! Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get on the air quick Bmac...local media going down like flies. https://t.co/gMqMQbZ7bZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little dramatic but January is starting for our local media as 2016 ran for celebrities. Not well at all. https://t.co/w688VhXAcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably wrong to comment on Twitter which has assisted in killing actual reporting, but I must say, I do look forw… https://t.co/oiyo1spXNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I'm re-tweeting Kim. Us sports guys lover our stats. https://t.co/lbppd8gTMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to read about Jordan Herdman 

https://t.co/nsZKT16DiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen a few of these sticks over the past four years! https://t.co/zMv4TR9Mb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doug_pauls @JjHerdJordan @SFUFootball @sfufbalumni @SFUClan @GNACsports I only caught the end. It replays Monday midnight on NFL Network]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh. Sad news. https://t.co/7VxgBSipU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htsumura @KitsNation @bcboysbball Kits has another Luka??? Awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gabriel_Lynn @SFUClan Gabe. Your passion for what you do shines through in every project you produce. And it just keeps getting better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never like a loss but not a bad performance from the Clan against a hot hand. 47% shooting  but only 22 from 3 and need to clean up the RBs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeakSFUSports @WWUAthletics She is fun to watch off the screen, Give her half a step and and she has been punishing the Clan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some nights there is no answer. Taylor Peacocke is having a hell of a game for the @WWUAthletics absolutely killing it from the field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes. Peacocke is killing it for the Vikings. Someone from the Clan needs to A.) Guard her and B.) Guard her some more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for the record, I'm not talking about Dellavedova, the bane of Gonzaga's existence for four years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try not to have favourite players but it's pretty hard not to cheer on an Aussie point guard who has a ton of grit to go with great skills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vikings defence is a little more than I have seen the Clan deal with. Hope they keep moving the ball and wear WWU down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this guy! https://t.co/IbMPZAtLHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htsumura Gotta say, would really like to see Coach Kinnear get a title.Just another one of the good guys in BCHSBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraydonEpp Truth Braydon! Hope all is well with you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Howard, Frosty, Z and Gabe behind the scenes. Lots of memories with those guys. Miss West gym like crazy!! Dang...forgot Jess!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard Tsumura has the call - solo tonight - for the SFUClan Womens BB Game tonight! https://t.co/toi1brSIEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htsumura Oak Bay have been knocking on the door for the past few years. Maybe this is their time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really getting homesick now! https://t.co/kg6uFQYYfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet 100....1000...what's in a zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Pitt!!! RT @QKF13: .@PMSSMarauders boys extend their lead to 9 over @carsonsecondary, with 5 minutes left in the game #noregretsbball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear TSN Sports. Watching your 4K broadcast of Raptors/Timberwolves. We need more of this. Way way way more. #4KFTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longbomb @htsumura Feeling your pain. Back to work after a week off. No fun when there is so much to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFU_Volleyball I don't have favorite players but,,,ah, who I am fooling,,,one of my all time faves!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htsumura @longbomb Still one of the best team names in BC!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmondsburnaby They are 8-2 with their two losses to the #2 and #9 teams in NCAA D2. Tough crowd!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmondsburnaby If raw means a ton of talent, athleticism and ball smarts combined with a high energy motor  then yup, I have to agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beingozi Your very welcome. Keep the motor running on BOTH ends of the floor and good things will happen for both you and the Clan! GL Ozi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sfuclan WBB with great execution on in-bounding the ball  four times in the last 5.7 seconds to hold off the Nanooks and win 79-77.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ozi is one of the best pure freshman I have seen suit up for @SFUClan WBB in some time. The girls gets buckets. The girl gets boards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the perfect day for my @SFUClan toque! (Thanks SFU!) Going to be a white winner so get yours soon at the… https://t.co/NIPcoTgZf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luka_KSTL pleasure to meet and chill on the sidelines over the years. I have really enjoyed watching you grow your skills. All the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my new teams RT @kssowls: @htsumura @bcssgva @VolleyballBC @bcsvball Go Owls Go!!!  This is how much we want another gold (or two)!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronh_pm @garyahuja1 Lord. Meant of course, hope our paths cross again. Text before coffee is not a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatsCoachBrown Wish I could give back 1/2 of what I have received from guys like you sharing your time, energy and knowledge with our kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garyahuja1 how poor paths pass again Gary. You truly are one of the good guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatsCoachBrown @1DealDude @garyahuja1 lol.. Thanks guys. Like you guys, love HS hoops and will be supporting the game from Kelowna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @longbomb photo bomb!! https://t.co/RPVaeb9iNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always nice to go out with a win. Going to miss this place. Go @SFUClan https://t.co/vp8VKCcJ7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ladies warm up as I prepare to shoot my last @SFUClan event. Going to miss this place, the athletes and especia… https://t.co/gARk2oXSCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thing that bugs me about the glorifying of "posters" is, no kid wants to be "Len" so they stop contesting  and give… https://t.co/JIyhX92LqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is talking about guys like you @doug_pauls The guy quietly workin his ass off in the background to help the kids… https://t.co/Qsk4kLu8Q3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? Hope these show up in time!!! https://t.co/epMReXVWjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottNotInVAN This is what Al Gore invented the internet for!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFU_Volleyball This is the best news ever! I'm so happy for you all!! Now it's time to make some tournament noise!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really big moment in the @SFUClan #NCAA history. So happy for the well deserved recognition for the senio… https://t.co/qKyIb963aN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeakSFUSports @sfu_mbb I thought he was solid in Fridays game, especially on D. A little confidence and I see good things ahead for Tyrell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWU is a great rival for the SFU crew, but it is easy to cheer for them as they reach the Final Four! Reppin' #GNAC… https://t.co/aBmuvZenMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to the @SFUClan MBB team and Coach Hanson on the big win #NCAAD2 win today! https://t.co/CWXkx8twqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My bad. I got it wrong. #GNAC got it right. Now about the West Region!! https://t.co/9Zala4v0HM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GNACsports :) Hmm. That's why I'm a photographer and not a journalist. Reading and research not my strong suit! My bad. I can breathe again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry @GNACsports, you blew this one. Emma led the Clan to the #GNAC playoffs.  She was 2nd in league scoring. She… https://t.co/jgwG6WO6K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And all around great guy too! https://t.co/EjOQf7XFxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanBallReport I thought you were that place!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get it, but no, I don't get it. Two minutes of silence are two minutes of silence. Period. https://t.co/F59cFCNwkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RidleyScouting I know eh. Rafe (kind of a hero of mine) would often talk about the ruling parties main mandate was to stay elected. Truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RidleyScouting I suppose I should be concerned about electoral practices and reform here before worrying about the US. Interesting though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharpie time @SethDavisHoops . I hate to say it, but it is what it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RidleyScouting I guess as it's only for President it's not so bad, but still seems odd. Why not just use popular vote instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Electoral College system is interesting. As I see it,  you can win the state by one vote, yet still win 100% of the votes for the state?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brexit no voters kinda going "uh-huh. Been there done that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear all north bound border crossings are getting very busy with long lineups coming into Canada. https://t.co/IeDqpHYqht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the delay on calling Florida? The drama is long over. With this amount of support for Trump, America is screwed regardless of result.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like game 7 all over again. Except there are no winners in this one. https://t.co/ojU6qltXVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a positive note, ISIS is officially shaking in their boots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafe Mair Axiom #3? You don't need to be a 10 if your opponent is a three; you only need to be a four.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MHStewart The payback for electing a black man and having the audacity to nominate a women. #RealAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking the sweat stains are starting to show in that white jumpsuit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never want to hear Seattle whine about not getting calls again. And I'm cheering for them! This is embarrassing for the #NFL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Although basketball is not extremely popular in Canada". Tough start for the author but a good writeup in the end!… https://t.co/WK0sBAlIa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I missed the replacement ref taking over again. What a gong show down in Seattle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Miller, after three years, makes it into my good books for his team play tonight. More heart than half the Canucks. #Stecher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And of course one hour after the #GNAC WSOC game is moved/rescheduled, the skies clear. We need Coach Renney on rad… https://t.co/6M0X4sjBzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the #GNAC soccer cancels because of inclement weather, Coach Jones @SFUClan jump team carries on with just anoth… https://t.co/KnDXJFy7ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@l_hommedemars @GNACsports That was likely discussed but it's soccer Saturday already for BC Soccer. Maybe insurance issues too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you think the weather cannot get any worse. My first soccer rain out ever! https://t.co/Et9IzILI80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful day for the beautiful game @SFUClan Fox Field. Looking forward to the #GNAC WSOC Championship. https://t.co/3WNrUhSKNS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>