<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@guan @pearkes @TheStalwart Would that be ready in time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearkes @TheStalwart It's more Islanders losing Barclays ... I guess it's back to the Nassau Coliseum?  Is that still a thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA consults on future guidelines for portability between trade repositories (an #EMIR thing)… https://t.co/21cR9fJqFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA updated the #MiFID2 Q&amp;A's

Transparency: https://t.co/SvAqUgufGR 

Market Structure: https://t.co/R65Y4JygqU https://t.co/99oSM3FtSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staffordphilip Very true. She also demolished me on using a double space following a full stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, my editor will be happy.  Thanks, in no small part, to an impressive voter mobilization campaign by @pearkes… https://t.co/LfFmsWIdZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreachyPreach isn't it more that spending 75 years transferring power from the legislative branch to the executive branch has some downside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@odtorium that's what the ($) is for, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I riffed a bit about ESMA's UCITS share-class hedging opinion ($)  https://t.co/OhXxIOMuxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Luxembourg https://t.co/LtGquI3c1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kadhimshubber @MayfairCynic this is great, the proof is basically the 'it's raining dogs and cats' bit from Die Hard 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give it a hard time but Twitter can be wonderful https://t.co/jh2I54DWC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is breaking in an unexpected way https://t.co/ZjqfeDI7DP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder what Grizzly Adams would look if he wore a suit and talked FinReg? Well, wonder no more https://t.co/G85iFnGGoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobcat escapes National Zoo enclosure; Public asked to report any sightings  https://t.co/HAJaCzXQFx https://t.co/lIp0uwJohc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasforth @celestialweasel @dsquareddigest honestly, I'm not sure either side of that conversation realizes that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobcat Missing at DC's National Zoo https://t.co/sIFwzyoCEo https://t.co/QSNluZt1S7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quantian1 Canadian Gold Maple Leaf Coin probably ticks the box for progressive goldbugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do as we mean, not as we say" is not a recipe for successful executive orders https://t.co/42ZTjGReuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are all the "Seventeenth Amendment was a huge mistake" hot takes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreachyPreach give me time, it will come to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communities that supported a thing to be worse off because of that thing ... where have I heard this story before? https://t.co/CIUqrnNzDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good short thread on the 2 for 1 regulatory thing https://t.co/momORe2syr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, this is not good governance https://t.co/frfVf8kEa1 https://t.co/7z5RUKaynp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far as I know, the inner sanctum isn't interested in FinReg. Which means, I think, that the CHOICE Act remains the template]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, this is basically the closest thing we have to an official Trump #FinReg plan https://t.co/OCBIXc9863]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ApwFA just so happens that we've got a pretty sharp tool that does just that https://t.co/32IUrdWoMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;-- Not a fan of prop planes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... When I'm gone
Somebody else will have to feel this wrong ... https://t.co/NPOpp1tkK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, I need your help in settling an ongoing argument I have with my editor.  Which is correct:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCMstrategy I agree equivalence is the only real option. Though, I also think it's a pretty bad option as well.  Not sure how sustainable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCMstrategy Don't think UK will change too much of MiIFD right away, longer term it really depends on if the "equivalence" route is sought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stand corrected, upon further reading, there is a welcome change to the pre-determination rules  (in yellow) https://t.co/QpkcALUQNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@odtorium It was pretty well telegraphed, ESMA felt duration hedging was more really a more investment activity than hedging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For background, here's a piece from last year on ESMA's work on the #UCITS Share Class Hedging Rules  https://t.co/2TUGkRIllV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overall, nothing that surprising here. Very much in line w/ last year's ESMA consultation.The transition/grandfathering was the only unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asset managers must focus on 3 key areas of #MiFID2: transaction reporting, fee transparency &amp; product governance
https://t.co/IHaBRbomIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA rules out all share class hedging, save for currency risk hedging ... so, farewell duration hedging and whatnot https://t.co/ZX6meM2aMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[existing, non complainant, share classes: Closed to new investors in 6 months &amp; additional investment by existing investors in 18 months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom! ESMA just dropped it's opinion on #UCITS Share classes https://t.co/8HokN6e86N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the quant traders sitting on a gold mine (a MiFID 2 Story) https://t.co/ZCmxAwowYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantLewis1 @tomashirstecon that is a big  "if"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA has written the EU Commission asking for addtional supervisory and sanctioning powers under #EMIR https://t.co/arbfUDGmZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a good get https://t.co/XyynZfsI5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MiFID2: Taming the Beast https://t.co/IHaBRbFY7f https://t.co/5mnzSwCian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't have bums in our town, Marge, and if we did they wouldn't rush, they'd be allowed to go at their own pace… https://t.co/o1WTwNcouu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brumblehag wait, you're telling me a business model designed to exploit the grey area of regulation &amp; circumvent labor law isn't noble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaGabor @GavinHJackson I'll give you the math may have changed but I really cannot see it going through until pensions get exempted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaGabor @GavinHJackson possibly but I remain unconvinced the FTT will get off the ground with the current group, let alone the EU27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaGabor @GavinHJackson the FTT? https://t.co/lLQ4gY9c0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe’s zombie tax on trading kept alive by election season #FTT https://t.co/xGbaTzJfGP https://t.co/e40IAGUntK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LorcanRK dude, that looks nicer than my apartment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanWeldon so, be honest, what kind of cheese is showing up to your house in about 50 minutes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kadhimshubber @GavinHJackson ahh, sorry my mix up ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kadhimshubber @GavinHJackson wasn't it the visa interview waiver that was suspended, not visa waiver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreachyPreach @northumbriana Always a fan of Burnisde's look  #mustacheTwitter https://t.co/gqFsZJoR1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate is a bit strong but we do think it's hilarious. Same with noisemaking toys. https://t.co/Na7kStkBfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to #ETF's it's BlackRock &amp; Vanguard's world,  everyone else is competing for third place… https://t.co/Aijs8DJWEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active managers are not happy with the FCA https://t.co/eNXHve0n1x https://t.co/35fYhUBcZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, McGill &amp; U of T are going shoot up the global university league tables over the next few years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Smokes. It wouldn't surprise me if 'Idaho' turns out to be the best book I read this year https://t.co/SMeoWdK6xJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTabrum I'll take the over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guan @felixsalmon @Welptheresthat @NickTimiraos @jaketapper bigger question is what happens to US bank accounts for those denied re-entry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guan @felixsalmon @Welptheresthat @NickTimiraos @jaketapper yes, I know it's a mess. Always can mail checks, if it comes to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixsalmon @Welptheresthat @NickTimiraos @jaketapper well, not really. It's Pretty easy to repay loans from abroad. Much harder to collect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhopkin Yeah, think it will be bundled into the general chaos/confusion and (probably) not a particular issue for Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhopkin you talking about US preclearance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTW It's times like this when the lack of Saltines &amp; chicken noodle soup in Dublin becomes a more acute issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanderwagner @ewankirk @drlangtry_girl plenty of room in Ireland, though the weather is sort of rubbish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to alarm y'all but I'm dealing with a pretty serious case of man-flu https://t.co/6vlVpRPtCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;This is horrifying.gif&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA Chief fires a warning shot that EU third country equivalence shouldn't be a one way street h/t @dsquareddigest… https://t.co/GTDbeRWQwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsquareddigest  very interesting, suspect that's as much a shot across the US's bow as it is the UKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFTC chairman vows to loosen US regulatory straitjacket https://t.co/3R18BcC4vU https://t.co/nr4Rv0GcMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorsen if the org is a collective I think it could still be dicey but not my area of expertise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorsen I think there's a difference to setting up a platform vs collectively negotiating a content deal with a platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorsen it's also collusion and probably illegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry y'all, two men worth a combined $159 billion think everything will be just fine https://t.co/IpKUasKpNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa, if true (no, really) https://t.co/KoVAtsmPim via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course there was A Hamilton Ticket Resale Ponzi Scheme https://t.co/MF5JJko3DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL House Party premiered at the Sundance Film Festival https://t.co/FD1E9Y2ilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PortiaCrowe they tried this Ireland a while ago, it did not end well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStalwart @M_PaulMcNamara nothing but finreg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternate take: British press corp fills out form incorrectly https://t.co/un1G16GV0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBuddhaSmiled all we need to do is put in on a blockchain and Boom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, want to read about the US (finally) moving to a t+2 settlement cycle? Go on, you know you want to… https://t.co/4nvn2EeAMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamishmcarthur Point taken, still I think fact checking is getting to the counterproductive stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much this  https://t.co/mw540mExni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monthly collection of good links featuring
@lisaabramowicz1 @jwg_group @IIF @DuncanWeldon https://t.co/glNqVBFEb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monthly collection of good links featuring @odtorium  @alexandrascaggs @therealrobison @DavisPolkReg @jasonzweigwsj 
https://t.co/glNqVBFEb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinHJackson @odtorium @alanbeattie I think it's pretty straightforward for UK lawyers to take the bar exam in the US (typically NY)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreachyPreach @DuncanWeldon maybe but, frankly, it was worth it just to have this https://t.co/CZs4rv04g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESMA publishes new Q&amp;A on Alternative Performance Measures Guidelines https://t.co/ywNS5kWoIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GristoMill For sure, I'm all about harmonization (within reason) but the idea of a binding  international framework is sort of silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear: There is ZERO chance of creating global regulatory standards for financial market access that supersede national rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, that's one way to solve for #brexit https://t.co/1eddCtLmMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ucits KIID has failed, trade bodies tell Brussels ($)
 https://t.co/ory97rm6kD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: 10 best things we read this month. Including pieces on Trump, Euro Clearing, Tackling Invasive Species &amp; More https://t.co/glNqVBo2Mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_C_Klein @sindap Yup, for example, there's generally no tax on interest payments to EU mutual funds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia itching to export financial services (#ARFP and whatnot) https://t.co/g8jr24UPLO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>