<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[British Army: Stop Putting Down Healthy War Hero Dogs Just Because They're "Old" https://t.co/vWzxHcYBSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep Trophy-Hunting Out of Botswana! https://t.co/WASSDtDEDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refuse application for pet rabbit breeding shop in Lincolnshire https://t.co/PGxYDqBEMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help end the export of captive-bred African lion parts in South Africa today! Act now https://t.co/3cg4x8HAHa via @HSIGlobal#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zimbabwe: Stop Export of Wild Elephants to Chinese Zoos https://t.co/m1VAphRl0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Roger Moore to PM: The Day Has Come to Ban Animal Circuses | PETA UK https://t.co/vheHEUL8VT @petauk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatia Praised for Banning Fur Farms https://t.co/AvELqn0RUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to factory farming? Torturing pregnant horses. Click to add your name to stop this horror! https://t.co/AXvqhKap7m@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urge Texas A&amp;M University to Close Dog Laboratories: https://t.co/REeX9N4Qan via @PETA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help change the law to prevent the sale of sick and underage kittens  https://t.co/xTSiYF0KDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring Back Vegan Semi-Sweet Chocolate Chips! https://t.co/imlHTcxXu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop South African Airways from Transporting Ivory! https://t.co/56zRyv9scC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puppy Kicked and Thrown Down Stairs - Abuser on the Loose https://t.co/qHdEpiZWtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just voted for Soi Dog Foundation: Love Will Always Triumph Over Evil inCharity Film Awards https://t.co/vBH8vsRXiQ via @CharityFilm_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed this petition to help stop tiger farming - please sign and share https://t.co/WuUu1L7xsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Juma is dead. Let’s ban the use of animals in all @Olympics ceremonies, now. https://t.co/gpEr8GLK3p via @SumOfUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petrochemical giant @INEOS is planning to flood the UK with fracking wells. https://t.co/nOTCaPESlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lion was found dead, hung from cables in his cage. Urge Indonesia to close Surabaya's ''zoo of death'': https://t.co/Ob2taK8o13 via @PETA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Dade City's Wild Things: Tiger Cubs Belong With Their Mothers! https://t.co/mJ39d7LEZ2 via @peta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backyard Brains: Stop Mutilating Cockroaches! https://t.co/KNtb8bRIMq via @peta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pawtitions I think that the bigger picture needs to be considered here. What of the rights of the animals used in the food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Ban driven grouse shooting https://t.co/soxYxF0H2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's #StandTogether against hate and #PostRefRacism in the UK now by demanding better from our media. Sign &amp; RT: https://t.co/h1BV9UM5Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bear Necessities: Tell the USDA to Ban Bear Pits Now https://t.co/ujT55LOvKe via @PETA@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Dog Taken Out by Hit-And-Run Driver Who Fled Scene https://t.co/j43EkuhACx via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Covering Up Corporate Threats to Great Barrier Reef https://t.co/bDikCj4Qib via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dam could destroy the heart of the Amazon rainforest. Please stand with the Munduruku people to #SavetheAmazon https://t.co/TsAtWoTwfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog With Artery Exposed by Six-Pound Chain Deserves Justice https://t.co/fjc0yDW3s2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Easy Steps to write your MPP/MP https://t.co/RNeTrGT9KP via @CdnChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rhinos and elephants of Selous are under threat. Help stop poaching @wwf_uk #SharedHeritage https://t.co/EJ7PJsPBlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog With Choke Chain Bolted Into Neck Deserves Justice https://t.co/YmEtHuLkk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition To End Organized Horse Fighting Forever https://t.co/s9Oik3kSTH via @network4animals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punish Men For Burning Girl Alive Due to Rejected Marriage Proposal https://t.co/BbjC6vtnM1 via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free SeaWorld Orca Who Beached Herself After Show https://t.co/50KV1Gb4nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quail are one of Europe’s most caged animals! Will you join me and help #EndTheCageAge? https://t.co/wUxzMkXsln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenage Girls Arrested for Throwing Bunny Against Wall Must be Prosecuted https://t.co/0DyWJLgZOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice for Harambe the Gorilla, Killed by Zoo https://t.co/3dATzyUTvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish regional government moves to outlaw bull spearing https://t.co/4OXUctAtnR via @travelmail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out https://t.co/IAZ4dEBb0w for this awesome product! Inflatable air-lounge - in just 5 seconds! https://t.co/EPSPBSIkwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm becoming a PETA member for 2016! Join me in taking a stand for animals today! https://t.co/dHdJrzi1vA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help! Our forests are being destroyed for biomass https://t.co/RTq9p8e015 via @RainforestResq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Tiger With Terminal Cancer Imprisoned For College’s Football Games https://t.co/wq6HBvy5Lj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World’s Fourth-Biggest Oil Company Vows to Go Big on Green Power https://t.co/qFPN2Za7Vd via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing Up: Vertical Farms Evolve to End Hunger https://t.co/bwtr3urpsL via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman Charged With Killing Dog to Fake Miscarriage Must be Prosecuted Vigorously https://t.co/RHJWbxhSQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Veggie Burger Jumps From the Freezer Aisle to the Butcher Case https://t.co/DnPk1JvyX8 via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Ever 100% Edible Six-Pack Ring Feeds Marine Animals Instead of Killing Them https://t.co/X6yuinVN4G via @ecowatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Third_Energy want to frack Ryedale against the wishes of the local community. Let's put a stop to it https://t.co/lk14kE30hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Study Predicts an Intolerably Hot World https://t.co/RIuDUWa6L0 via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones stop killing the damn wolves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog Starved and Infested With Maggots Deserves Justice https://t.co/TIji7alU7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With 100 #elephants killed every day, @Yahoo must tell @Yahoo_JAPAN_PR to ban bloody #ivory from their site https://t.co/Y3bcwBGUAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop McDonald's From Supporting Endangered Dolphin Deaths https://t.co/XNQ2jc3uWR via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fight to Stop Illegal Bear Trafficking in Southeast Asia https://t.co/kkvAZMuSTS via @NatGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strengthen Protections for Grizzly Bears https://t.co/PkNXiaganP via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell FWS Director Dan Ashe to Respect Science and Protect Wolverines https://t.co/KOGnbgtsJm via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No More Delays—Commit to Recovering Endangered Red Wolves https://t.co/OWMc7vCxsk via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service to Protect Endangered Species https://t.co/OSPhyYANVo via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice for Baby Bison Euthanized Because Tourists Put Him in Their Car https://t.co/22eCFHhAfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Mohan's court case to be heard on May 20th https://t.co/PVkCmrfj3i via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice for Cat Shot Twenty Times https://t.co/sNmhQRYdIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panama: don’t evict Ngäbe families  for the Barro Blanco dam https://t.co/k3whn3gUnj via @RainforestResq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat 2 TBSP of Coconut Oil, Lose More Weight: What No One Told You About Thermogenesis https://t.co/KUsTDbRfc6 via @@theheartysoul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crisis in Chiloé, Chile as thousands of marine life wash ashore | GREENPEACE New Zealand https://t.co/TU0BZOUZvG via @greenpeacenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fur looks best on its original owner. Help speak out against stolen skins and cruel fur farms https://t.co/461IMdx4hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greedy coal company is forcing farmers to crawl to get to their land | GREENPEACE New Zealand https://t.co/cQYL15POMn via @greenpeacenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PETITION: Ask Sweden to ban ALL wild-animal circuses. https://t.co/ZQQZBdfzkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fort McMurray Blaze Set the Stage for Even Bigger, Hotter Wildfires https://t.co/bXTy7LTHPf via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['An Inconvenient Truth' Then and Now: What’s Changed for Our Climate Since 2006? https://t.co/C0QJOqFgMh via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spread the Word https://t.co/OZbCtv2w29 #voteleave via @vote_leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me and urge France to keep the foie gras farms closed. End force-feeding. #EndTheCageAge. https://t.co/PEt69mM5R5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Who Starved Young Husky to Death and Left Dog to Rot Must be Properly Punished https://t.co/22DoabQU4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vietnamese man arrested with 4 frozen tiger cubs https://t.co/hhlAuyzqUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tears roll down Yani the elephant's face moments before she dies https://t.co/kuq1sWZABl via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retire Cancer Stricken Elderly Dolphin From Marine Park https://t.co/20cPiN3nwP via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee children should be with their families. Join @Unicef_UK's campaign #refugeeswelcome https://t.co/0M0oh5pyPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punish Person Responsible for Mass Poisoning of Stray Dogs https://t.co/SieU0iB5WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lion was found dead, hung from cables in his cage. Urge Indonesia to close Surabaya's ''zoo of death'': https://t.co/Ob2taK8o13 via @PETA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists Devise Successful Strategy to Stop Mass Wildlife Killings https://t.co/jl3Ol2o6uu via @TakePart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The killing agency: Wildlife Services' brutal methods leave a trail of animal death https://t.co/jwxTqJm4cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - We have reached 4000 signatures! https://t.co/8KOYX40GjY via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @USFWS to strengthen protections for grizzly bears as a part of any delisting: https://t.co/wDD7JKB98f via @endangered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now You Know... So What's Next? https://t.co/xUbrMi83T1 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop the Slaughter of Thousands of Wild Horses https://t.co/BI2zfxErhS via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save Ramabhadran the elephant at Thiruvambady Temple - Kerala, India https://t.co/hNwOWyiQQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAVE the Pack Animals at Havasu Falls in the Grand Canyon https://t.co/qKq4cZObk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK &amp; EU parliaments (law) - DEFRA: Ban ALL antifreeze preparations unless they contain a bitterant ... https://t.co/kwQUqYuDpi via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room for Debate: Declawing a Pet Should Be Illegal, Period https://t.co/BhYOcb9tGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the TripAdvisor petition https://t.co/d0WInnZXSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish : Stop Scotland's Secret Cat Slaughter - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/3G7J8jLebH via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fat-Busting Vegetarian Collard Greens Soup https://t.co/Fm5DOB2nAC via @happy_foodista]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frysfamilyUK - where can I get your produces in the UK? I have searched a few Tesco, Morrisons, ASDA, etc....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@forestserviceNW: protect wild Oregon rivers from nickel #mining, support 20-year mineral withdrawal! https://t.co/JWnQiceWQV @earthworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPOSE MAXIMUM PENALTY FOR ANIMAL CRUELTY OFFENCES! บทลงโทษสูงสุดสำหรับคนที่ฆ่า 'ขาว' - Sign the Pe... https://t.co/zPzRrDqTis via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut down the Xiongsen Tiger and Bear Mountain Village in China! https://t.co/4gtfbDCjfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabbit and Chicken Tortured to Death at Animal Park Deserve Justice https://t.co/yKOP3MkbyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude Dances to "Uptown Funk" Like Nobody is Watching. The Crowd Goes Wild! https://t.co/v6lTIWlxKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Action Plan against Wildlife Trafficking will help victims of illegal wildlife trade. Act now!  https://t.co/zGyIWGxoFw via @ifawuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Must Apologize for Posing With Abused Tiger https://t.co/lNZW5f0fAS via @ForceChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunting Wolves Hurts Tourism https://t.co/AWlGg9Js8f via @TakePart]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>