<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nycjim Doesn't Trump trumpet that his name is magic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I love it. #craftivism and the #pinkpussyhat🚺 https://t.co/PWd4cKrEyM via @SummersAnne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooray, it's @PodSaveAmerica time. #friendofthepod from Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbrella Fark. There really is no hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The short-fingered vulgarian from Trumpistan is awake. https://t.co/AfGj05iuEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @Eugene_Robinson I will but I have to pace myself or I'll collapse in despair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHamamdjian @ddale8 I agree (from Australia). Did good work during campaign and continues with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aflwomens @CarltonFC @CollingwoodFCW @BriannaDavey @darcyvee That was fantastic. Thanks to all who made it happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenvogel @StateDept @politico Curious to know what son in law thought about decision not to mention Jews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AFLWBluesPies is an excellent distraction from Trumpistan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinrileyau I like the idea that it's free and a celebration of first game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outersanctum01 @DaisyPearce6 @iTunes She's very good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for these women https://t.co/TXQKl10Afr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a great occasion. Go grrls https://t.co/4lfpeYs4K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew. https://t.co/AimDjggDjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenJ @realDonaldTrump Or being a duckwit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been busy doing home tradie work for a couple of hours meanwhile #DressLikeAWoman becomes a thing but really Trump should #actlikeapresident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Australia tonight we have @aflwomens playing first official game of AFL. Historic.@CollingwoodFC v @CarltonFC  #DressLikeAWoman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpistan govt stragety is a firehose model. Spray out as much info as possible including conflicting info &amp; no-one will be able to keep up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man with a drug-induced orange confection on his head, a double chin and a portly body is telling women to #dresslikeawoman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @nytimes It's not working very well though https://t.co/0hy6pbLqhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon @KellyannePolls @HardballChris From what I've seen, if she opens her mouth you can conclude she's lying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara He's probably struggling to put a coherent sentence together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The chief Duck is awake in Trumpistan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But no free speech in AG's office. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then there's this https://t.co/emIuZB2rb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryl_kernot It's getting increasingly hard to know what's news, what's fake, and then there's Trump's lies and alternative facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pete_savin Thanks for your photos. They're good therapy in this trumpety time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a sad, sad man thinking this word salad has any meaning. https://t.co/Yyp84nt9Za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardaedy @Colvinius Trump and Bannon watch too much television]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the bigoted red/orange haired politicians ... the answer is no https://t.co/Rl4walIlO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know the world has gone mad when you agree with Prince Charles https://t.co/jrC9q9Hf39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpety media strategy: firehose spray of shit so no-one can work out what the facts are, or even if there are fac… https://t.co/MjwtmNa7ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still waiting for my $550 from Abbott ... Turnbull says company tax cut would make you $750 richer https://t.co/dZGLebifak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention Malcolm Turnbull, the Australian quisling https://t.co/ieZ9JgUGzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara Do you have a crooked media list? Is this the same list as the fake news mob?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started reading 'A G-Man's Life' by Mark Felt (aka Deep Throat). Who is going to stand up to the Trumpery White House? Sally Yates did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-feminism = lying for a malignant narcissist. https://t.co/1oB4zBieSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a clown. Sad! https://t.co/HCo35aotlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary https://t.co/xUoRGVHuKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBaumann @MarkDiStef She's on the shortlist of public officials speaking out strongly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janemerrick23 Australian @cathywilcox1 And @FionaKatauskas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well whose job is it? You're a poor leader and a SAD! man. https://t.co/wxDin0AJZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt @murpharoo @guardian Another Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something a 12-year might say https://t.co/zUHM7R0APJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I was foolishly hoping @TurnbullMalcolm would condemn Trump's actions. Instead he sent one of his thugs out to… https://t.co/YUVerYuNp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julie Bishop says 'We have a very positive relationship with the Trump administration'. How would she know, her ide… https://t.co/dJ5h6cMtQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architecture therapy https://t.co/9UzWWJ5ner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon @natalietran @TurnbullMalcolm Is Turnbull's silence trade-off for Trump accepting Australia's Manus/Nauru refugees? Evil if so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is breaking America. https://t.co/gKBwkJRsoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good from @mgordon_fairfax about @JuliaGillard https://t.co/DhS8s3pzLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More architecture therapy https://t.co/uLJQe0mmkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoodCornish Brainfood my fave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer @jonathanvswan And good they're concerned with the big problems not the fluff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iiNet thanks. Won't need to change my provider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architecture therapy https://t.co/PE4RrCfvTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case there is any doubt he's a bully ... https://t.co/8EElOHezYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Trumpolini (ht @simon_schama) taking lessons from North Korea's dear leader? Sad! https://t.co/thMd90kzSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @EmolumentClause @NormEisen @ZephyrTeachout Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 @sydneyswans membership card has my favourite player @Danerampe on it. Hurry up footy season, I need a distrac… https://t.co/rjfFQA61Wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["journalists still have more accurate ways of reporting on crowd sizes than our megalomaniacal president counting o… https://t.co/8tUFG73lrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're lucky, he won't have the attention span to listen or read the info https://t.co/gEXcvmd3CD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamVeiszadeh @deemadigan Two amazing can-do people with big hearts. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon @MikeCarlton01 Trump has the weird look not the eagle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon @MikeCarlton01 Watched over by an eagle on a gold pedestal ... with a weird look on his face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely loving @ellinghausen photos at #AusOpen https://t.co/auHIqCef0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef Voted athletics because don't watch them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So help us god https://t.co/2yk2SCwoEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out! I donated to Put Aus girls back in Aus day ad https://t.co/u8BXy97yLo via @gofundme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama surprises and praises his spokesperson Josh Earnest https://t.co/Oujuc0SBnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot @GrogsGamut @ddale8 And everything he learnt about leadership he learnt from his father. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @cheryl_kernot That often-quoted research was conducted on about a dozen people in early 1960s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sspencer_63 @lenoretaylor And good to read after overdosing on trump madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnottMatthew @POTUS "a big ask" well used by AFL commentators and supporters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @GreenJ @voxdotcom Australia will miss Barack Obama's decency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone just suggested to me that too many golden #goldenshowers are the cause of Trump's weird hair colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 so far: Trump and his #goldenshower, Trump in bed with Russia, polo politics, #leybuy. And it's only 11 Jan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dangers of socialism https://t.co/3urFTJK68t via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it'll be interesting to see whether commercial tv new bulletins run this story tonight. https://t.co/IDdaAxlsWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly @theage I admire people like you who take on the poison some people post. Good on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallows: I view Trump’s election as the most grievous blow that the American idea has suffered in my lifetime https://t.co/3hF4ZSk0pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMurdochTimes I don't know or care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not racist but ... https://t.co/nAsB11HYxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @PostGraphics l'm mourning USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CSIRO invented wifi but we're  an also-ran with internet speed thanks to Turnbull/Abbott https://t.co/EDi4hs6Y39 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does it need to be pointed out that this is wrong? https://t.co/7TS972xJZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraceyLeeHolmes Not yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @RepDuckworth Good interview with extraordinary woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary story https://t.co/wzUcpHgVzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellclaret Good interview. Love your honesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[💩#crookeddonald https://t.co/OM2emwDNRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @smh I'm still waiting for the $550 Abbott promised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan You know things are weird when a 'pro wrestling magnate' gets anywhere near government]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastNews  His hair is a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading this will make you despair https://t.co/eSPsANQ7W2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyLifeAu @MariamVeiszadeh Every day you inspire people with your resilience, grace, determination, intelligence. Congratulations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 As a reader that's all I want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is doing my head in. is it fake or real https://t.co/UeUskKPOx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @abcnews Based on recent events we don't need any more evidence of the intelligence of US voters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the real story here? https://t.co/naZMbplaf9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>