<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetmalone @HistoryLOI No team containing Franco Baresi and I has ever conceded a goal. Fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @FMcMack I was there. Easily the loudest - but not the best - of the three Ramones gigs I attended during the 70s-80s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFinal_Third Great night! Good to meet @acjimbo again after a gap of 24 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FMcMack @bboyd27 @IrishTimesOpEd I'll say one thing for Trump: he's not Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeborahJaneOrr @guardian Is that 'bake' news?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge @AdamSchefter You should read Joe O'Connor's book about various Dublins in the USA. Fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwalshireland @FMcMack And that's why I buy the SBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 All the best Dave. Hope you're not up to early to see what Santa's brought. â›„ï¸ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzoneill Saw them in 1973. Amazing gig!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ttsrfc @historyloi @markmccadden @mclaughlingavin Two ten-team divs is fair if all we have is 20 clubs. What's the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ttsrfc @historyloi @markmccadden @mclaughlingavin Would Rovers' fans prefer more games against Cabinteely or UCD than Pat's or Bohs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorrAlan Spare us the gorey details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @seidodge @luke_oriordan @juliancanny I grew up in the single division years. All it bred was stagnation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner @leyawn Reminds me of coolfizzinpepsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge @luke_oriordan @juliancanny It's basically deckchairs on the Titanic but at least it creates two equal divisions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HistoryLOI @McLaughlinGavin @markmccadden @buzzdotie A 16-team single division would merely recreate the stagnation of the past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McLaughlinGavin @HistoryLOI @markmccadden @buzzdotie So stick with an eight-team First Division? At least with ten there's parity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patmontague Many Hoopy returns Pat, to you and yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 Wouldn't put it past them either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickfarrell9 Indeed. Give us a shout and we'll arrange something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 No Xmas presents in Turin. Santa's gonna skip that town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noriordan In fairness he's a new kid on the block]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethpenrose That's what passes for thorough research these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge @ScotsFootyCards The King! Adored him when I was a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitzmaidan Get someone to take out the batteries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge It's just a posh word for spoofer. Only the clueless or cowardly use consultants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge Really enjoyed that tournament. My eldest son and I adopted Turkey and they went on to win it at the then home of the Hoops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @luke_oriordan We're living in worse than interesting times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @luke_oriordan LoI point-scoring's a very subtle art. We're all in a sociological dustbin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @luke_oriordan Serious pot-kettle situation there. How many homes have Pat's had over the years? Milltown included.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke_oriordan Just refer to it as the U2 loft and you can't go wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That @JohnBishop100 is sound. Here's what happened when that JB met this JB: https://t.co/QnhFtKwafQ https://t.co/Z3uHu3DC1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge People can slag RTE as much as they like but nights such as this show what it's all about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge It's what your new sofa was made for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge I recall when my eldest son was told by school pal there was no Santa I told him to tell pal there was no god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge We're deffo in the twilight zone end of things. Which is much more fun. Plus there's less face painting and fewer silly hats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge What a load of corporate bollocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhuckAllCraic Smith's Irish potato crisps. The noisiest crisps in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phuckallcraic I did indeed. I'd give anything for a number 11 badge now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Napoleon Solo was a hero to me. Robert Vaughn RIP. The greatest ever quiff is gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FMcMack @MaxBoot @ForeignPolicy I've lived through Bertie, Reagan and Thatcher. Bring it on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzoneill @rice_e @ShamrockRovers Dundalk proved Rovers' EL qualification wasn't some fluke #MONGAWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FCUnitedMcr @BPAFCOfficial Looking forward to my first trip to Broadhurst Park. C'mon FC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngosullivan @pajoflynn Ronaldo will sleep easily now that you've hung up your boots!ðŸ‘ All the best Pat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinjforde @seidodge @johngosullivan @HOTSHOTZ2 @cahill_ashley @Denis_Hurley So why don't they play in LoI and prove it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@historyloi @peile50yearsago It's a 19th Century creation: 2 full and 3 half backs, 2 inside forwards, 2 wingers and a centre forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phuckallcraic @emmetmalone Irish people just don't fancy club sport. GAA and rugby clubs also attract relatively tiny crowds. It's endemic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdarabueller @emmetmalone @extratimenews If Dundalk won the Europa League I'd imagine the Irish reaction: 'It's only the Europa League.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinbrannigans He may be a hopeless narcissist, but all else about him is impossible to resist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone out there got a stream link for #NapoliRoma?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How  come Smokey Robinson never got a #NobelPrize for Literature? https://t.co/XIE7WsK2xR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more on #BobDylan's #NobelPrize win and video: https://t.co/fR0WqY5Hqd https://t.co/M8cRJKODN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more on #BobDylan's #NobelPrize win and video: https://t.co/fR0WqY5Hqd https://t.co/NUFBeYyZqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gleesonb The greatest slaw ever is Denis Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngosullivan Easily the most interesting and entertaining new face on the LoI scene. In a world full of clones and cliches he stands out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HistoryLOI @EmmaAWheatley I think you're missing his point there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundaybusiness @TomLyonsBiz Best Irish newspaper by a long stretch. Always insightful and informative. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@17Leagues24cups No chance. Dundalk and Cork are just better than the rest. We're still a top four side. Just way behind top two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 @JerryPijpelink We lost 8-0 on aggregate if that was a European tie. We've come a long way since 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 @JerryPijpelink Decent first half. Showing a bit of hunger. Tough for Dobbs up front alone though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a film today, oh boy! #Beatles #EightDaysAWeek https://t.co/u26iQDvXVY https://t.co/gaZsBcAirh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbyrne72 @FMcMack @ballsdotie Cheers. Yet another great US show that was messed around this side of the Atlantic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaaaaner @noriordan @ShamrockRovers Deffo played for first Rovers' team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaaaaner @noriordan @ShamrockRovers It seemed bizarre at the time. Certainly unique. Had he been GAA you'd never hear the end of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaaaaner @noriordan @ShamrockRovers I recall a Con O'Donoghue playing for Rovers before heading to US to play American football. Tall lad!ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzoneill He's Boo Bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge I'm not bitter. Irish football stood its ground and beat the money men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge I was never as militant about anything in my life as I was about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge @ballsdotie @ConorNeville We won. They lost. Fuck right off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhuckAllCraic Anyone can sue anyone else for any reason - if they want to. It's big stick syndrome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three episodes in and I've completely fallen in love with #Fleabag. Who's got Pheobe Waller-Bridge's phone number?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzoneill Now, that's a man sandwich!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cassette_media @EmmaAWheatley And looks like a character from Vinyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge @RuiDunsta Ich bin ein *what's the Mexican word for 'Mexican?*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhuckAllCraic While his club career was patchwork his international career is peerless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngosullivan A boy amongst Omen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pogmogoal I was watching the game in a suite in London's Dorchester Hotel while waiting to interview Richard Gere. #ThanksRobbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephenrice_6 And madman Dan Murray in short sleeves! Best snow ever though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreadful and expensive draw for Dundalk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electionlit I'd love to see Italy ban Speedos. Why middle-aged  and even elderly Italian males insist on wearing them is beyond me. TMI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamanthaLibreri Any book by Tim Parks. A Season with Verona is a particular favourite. For obvious reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gleesonb Try Dice. It's funnier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't play telly lotto: here's his week's TV Preview https://t.co/leEw2mDXPL https://t.co/n75O4A3OCW https://t.co/pFgUGhrece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTsrfc I think he means Busaras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad to hear about the death of Rovers' legend Liam Tuohy. One of Irish football's greatest as both a player and coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJOEdotie @DarrMurphy Welcome to the Italian football world of 'ritiro']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IFTN @paddybreathnach @markohalloran @ElementPictures Paddy's big break was filming a video for Hallelujah Freedom about 700 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swench Nice article Eamon. Tony was unique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DangerKidsBooks @OfficialASRoma @championat The man's got taste. Next stop: Tallaght Stadium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngosullivan @OCowzer @DangerKidsBooks @Ciaran_O @little_football LoI was dying when there were 14 clubs so having 20 isn't the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeborahJaneOrr What? No Irn-Bru?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulohehir Was it a case of thanks but no tax?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johngosullivan New corner flags for all should bring back the crowds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuiDunsta @FMcMack @AlbertoNardelli Baccala is the cod's bollocks ðŸ˜Ž. Currently enjoying Lucca but still dreaming of Dar Poeta in Trastevere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorrAlan Marni Nixon was what Donald Runsfeld might call a great 'known unknown']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrNightdub @davidbyrne72 Check out Ravello. It's stunning. Yesterday was fantastic btw. I've never seen a happier happy couple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCassidyIRE @philipfnolan Heading to Tallaght on a lovely night for a game. Going back to winter would be insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTsrfc @ShamrockRovers Forelock-tugging Association of Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV Preview includes new @Channel4 reality show #Eden and the @SHO_Billions finale. https://t.co/UXKFwECFaE https://t.co/IdJ3jSGA8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTsrfc @srfcandyc Don't get veneration of Spurs' game. Great moment but we lost. Belgrade was the magical night we won.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>