<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It'd be fun, tho. Skinny runt DeNiro vs 6'3" Trump.  My money's on #POTUS https://t.co/ozIcTbuseN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's with all the bacon? Everything else is perfect. https://t.co/3L1sFYsYfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One small problem. Geneva conventions apply to state of war, POW, soldiers, civilians. Not US or Cdn war, not respo… https://t.co/dpaVjAUcp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a scholarship to Berkeley. https://t.co/OQ53efkqYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They also don't have the tight to prevent him, or any other invited guest, from speaking. https://t.co/0CCFmVTWTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On what dubious basis do you make the claim "ever stronger"? McCain announces senate study doesn't make it any more… https://t.co/ks2h0oruCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't inaccurate. It was a blatant lie to sway NDP voters to Liberal, cos they desperately want PP and thought… https://t.co/QL7cjqJTL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As histrionic demos continue re temporary restrictions on Moslems entering US. Can't make this stuff up. Modern Mar… https://t.co/M4TSGXlNkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot be true. Trudeau said everyone welcome and none are bad. https://t.co/dQp7HftJgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last campaign said he was unfit. Actions since prove it. Oh Canada, what have you done? https://t.co/mpKeJDw6OQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise here. If ID is not checked, there will always be some who abuse the system. https://t.co/tDcpZAUAwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MSM party will do anything and everything to try to prevent Trump administration success. Best to simply ignore… https://t.co/mJlXLXL9SM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otherwise it's exactly what a socialist society needs. Sad they all fail miserably. https://t.co/c5jQOutCab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for media reports that no one attended in person (actually 500K), record TV audience too. Media lies, disto… https://t.co/mx2Xp6PC3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's ok, so long as anti-abortionists are banned from participation. https://t.co/S8PgJnxsv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that a photo from Democratic Party convention parade? https://t.co/6qNOWboQQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ON govt can legally cancel all these contracts, save province billions. Where's the PC or NDP leader pushing this? https://t.co/bgE9r6DRqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent idea. We need far more sceptics and far fewer acolytes. Climate change (former global warming) is a fraud. https://t.co/sxwvtjYHex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very disturbing. Clinton News Network panic level reaching uncontrolled hysteria https://t.co/d5VlIeoRdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depends on police being willing to do their duty w/o fear of future court action against them. https://t.co/TM73q8iIrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envy is a terrible human trait. Warren has envy and bitterness down to a fine art. https://t.co/oFxTBGHb9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can CNN and fellow travellers get any more disgusting? https://t.co/WfFlhfhH3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Leary is no Donald Trump. Not even sure he's O'Leary. Certainly not the successful one he purports to be. https://t.co/6JemNIMDN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this were a right wing or tea party ad, twitter would filter it. https://t.co/yAjW4gNiDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obvious solution for leftist council, hire homeless/jobless at $15/hour to take bikes back up hill. Green jobs and… https://t.co/KBiUFXQGjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less tuneless cacophony with bad lyrics. https://t.co/6zPuELF2lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Heard it once, heard it 1000 times "icon of civil rights movement". ENOUGH. When is 1960 activist recognition… https://t.co/gwlIh2bzXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is the guy I'd choose a@for head of CIA - NOT!!! He needs to go now, not Fri https://t.co/qgM4lbhS0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also not a good actor. But incredibly good at turning on the waterworks. Best movie crier I've ever seen. https://t.co/DqQtn92YEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David, you must be mistaken. Global warming has eliminated freezing weather https://t.co/nmsEJsWTGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty suit, poor intellect. But. nice hair. https://t.co/e0cKBOBfh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ClimateChange fanatics are so far gone in religiosity and need for govt money, evidence and facts no longer matter… https://t.co/ybGBzwC1uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ceases to amaze me how liberals berate conservatives, threaten violence and then accuse cons of intolerance. https://t.co/nz2U788ShF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He needs to embrace Hope and Change. Hope it's ok and expect climate to Change anyway. It always has, always will,… https://t.co/iXjgExlY9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange upside down world we live in now. https://t.co/RjapeVTTLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evil betrayal. And yet most MSM keep repeating the libel that Trump is fascist and anti-Semitic. Bizarre. https://t.co/0FZ01DtIN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He kowtowed to Islamic theocratic regimes, gave Iran nukes, degraded USA globally, insulted allies, denigrated Isra… https://t.co/wcVXsmWy0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if this were true, so what? Who kept climate data historically. Ignore prior eras? If warming, definitive proo… https://t.co/JfZAnJCuW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! How do we secure the snow? Can you get snow net from Canadian Tire? Do we need red flag on the load? What if i… https://t.co/B38OWnvPwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange isn't it. My parents never taught me not to kidnap/torture. They'd never have thought necessary cos they ra… https://t.co/6T3eTeVq7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Eddie. You miss the point. Thousand, ten thousand ... simply regurgitate the same falsehood, doesn't make it tru… https://t.co/ibmlGXPlam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promoting fake news again, huh? https://t.co/xF0hoABDQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of many non-news, national inquirer innuendo fake news stories we can expect to see over the next 4 years. It's… https://t.co/hjdRCHXD0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, who did chant it? And who set the church on fire? https://t.co/CU37xpTxMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice. He's an actor, or comedian, or something, almost (not a particularly good one). Don't expect intelligent t… https://t.co/LMdHIQOj2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grossly unfair characterization. We all know Liberals are entitled to their entitlements. He's PM! Per daddy, do as… https://t.co/d22j8W1wjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC, CNN, NYT, et al, are media wing of Dem party. As party publicists and advisers, of course they have copies. No… https://t.co/UgzWE7JtMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projections on current expected performance. Slight tweaks in interest rates (they're going up), lower GDP growth (… https://t.co/vNrk6ZoEvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she can't make money or a credible case honestly ....... https://t.co/3xoeVhNwmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the victim is beneficiary of white privilege, sic and sick! https://t.co/12zu8VkrVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having invested heavily &amp; sincerely in the early climate change fraud/scam, fanatics now do all to maintain fiction… https://t.co/f2dam2N5JA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPD and left wing logic, can only be hate crime if perpetrated against non-white. https://t.co/pNPq4WURdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unable to read original tweet. It's been blocked, as are many in recent days. Twitter delivering on promises to Dem… https://t.co/nyhNNcGFiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might I suggest divisive hate, promoted over 8 years by Obama, Holder, Lynch and cohorts https://t.co/YKJqL6NiJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigRBrittain @LeoDiCapAHoe Craig, do u say they shouldn't exist or don't exist currently? If latter, points to need for change, ie Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Just not transracial enough (whatever that means). Angels dancing on heads of pins springs to mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigRBrittain @LeoDiCapAHoe No mention in Craig's tweet of democracy, freedom, individual rights, equality. All the things that scare Libs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOIndependence @IndraNooyi Never drank this crap anyway. Maybe start so I can boycott later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@young__conserv i had only one new year resolution - not to make any. Broke it already. Promise to be nice to idiot liberals and safe zones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @greta As we're told repeatedly, Trump isn't president yet so self/aggrandizing "press pool" irrelevant. Any news from Obama golf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different type of "visiting scholar"? He dropped in to try to find some spare brain cells that he's clearly lacking. https://t.co/5Aiy83md67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps consider moving to country of faith with no western devils. How about Saudi Arabia, Kuwait. Syria has lots… https://t.co/PbatRzzpso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sounds so good when leftists talk about coal plant shutdowns - see, touch, dirty, ergo pollutes. Solar, air - no se… https://t.co/lngm88kCjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inevitably Trudeau will side with anti-Israel, Jew hating socialist/fascists like Venezuela. Seat on UNSC impossibl… https://t.co/15E7IBtM32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward with excitement to the day the CBC ceases to pollute the Canadian media landscape. Significant envir… https://t.co/38cqSnQIxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel, Israel, Israel. Not Moslem violence and terrorism from Hamas and PA. https://t.co/fVCJk37ekQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since his policies were rejected via Hillary, Obama's hateful persona has shown thru. Such awful prejudiced comment… https://t.co/BFsUoQRuUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a first easy step - get Wynne to resign. Then get this disastrous Liberal govt to resign. Then have an elect… https://t.co/9oAr5Z8I66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TDS (Trump Derangement Syndrome) continues to afflict liberal minds. When will CDC do something? Is it fatal? Is it… https://t.co/kXyuEFVav6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's smart, well spoken, conservative and female. Every Lib nightmare. https://t.co/Z1myIYjPd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerry's incredibly delusional mind drops another stink bomb. Where's James Taylor to round things off. https://t.co/OOjw2F8Ese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprise from the most anti-Israel, anti-Semitic administration in my lifetime. https://t.co/et3bzP3CWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #Trumpoid tie, of course, to further confirm your and Hannity propaganda bias.  https://t.co/B3qz13sndb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised #Trumpoid rejection so low. He's a disaster in the making. Goldwater redux https://t.co/7blQIf6UKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have real problems. Paranoia being one https://t.co/fHpskG9tqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry. Stupid is harsh. I meant pathetic. World better off. Curious mentality of #Trumpoid supporters. https://t.co/yvavwv6pDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews I've no interest this stupid subject. Leave our faith alone. We owe you ZERO. You got an education. Be glad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. That's stupidity.  https://t.co/A599et4dRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a whole week of #Trumpoid promotion, with Hannity. Quite pathetic. Certainly not fair and balanced.  https://t.co/dtIdNjUH3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's another area of moral indifference. "Pro choice" is a misnomer. You believe in pre-birth killing. I don't.  https://t.co/mI82OAPnRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, you equate auto theft with a tragic, heart rending decision to obtain an abortion? Ignorance??? https://t.co/mkUtIgvsMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, please don't ask #Trumpoid hard questions? No fair. Hence, runs away from debates, fears Megyn Kelly.  https://t.co/nygdx699GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replies from #Trumpoid trolls like you you prove the point.  https://t.co/DEIGzVAopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In and of itself, that is grossly immoral and mysogynist. Perhaps punish vasectomies too? It's sick but no surprise https://t.co/4ZOqCT4fIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your primary approach is to promote #Trumpoid policies, attack others. Cover his silly garbage answers too.  https://t.co/FXGr5gFhIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But you're attributing original thoughts to #Trumpoid. And now #Trumpoid wants to punish women who get abortions.  https://t.co/AuFvYjalPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trumpoid favorite fans show through - ignorant, uneducated.  https://t.co/nEZUPHQt5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just need you and @ericbolling to start behaving with some integrity and not as #Trumpoid publicists https://t.co/jSNvY6BhjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtGranda Romney, Perry, etc said "secure the border". Trump copied it. GOP said no "core education", Trump copied. Get the facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump approach to presidential race. "I'll give you the best of ....". How? "Because I said so, Trust Me!" https://t.co/fWPPreDQv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You truly are ignorant. I'm sorry for you and your ilk.  https://t.co/NIyY5orzKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trumpoid will lose - if not GOP nomination, though likely, but for sure against and Dem dog. He's a coward.  https://t.co/keDY0xcxQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathleen lies! Constantly.  https://t.co/9Y7wh5Hnt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patently false but people like you, "true acolytes" believe him when he spouts this nonsense.  https://t.co/9FVK4uFW1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your words belie your statements. Only ignorance could justify support of a mysogynist blustering bully buffoon https://t.co/AIeWzHBddt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May God rest Rob Ford's soul, comfort his family and inspire others to genuine public spiritedness.  https://t.co/7bZtrA5ZoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trumpoid is a coward. Tries constantly to demean, attack those less able to defend themselves or lose jobs.  https://t.co/iKdJkQVzbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, as #Trumpoid has said, he likes the stupid, uneducated because they believe his bs.  https://t.co/SbU3xlWzRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lies repeatedly. Exaggerates, prevaricates and insults. Pathetic excuse for a "man". No real policies https://t.co/SbU3xlWzRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a gullible fool. Trump has lied constantly. Goebell's personified. Lies, damn lies and then there's #Trumpoid! https://t.co/jed2E6cO6f]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>