<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@msaoife @oconnellhugh she has some nerve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/BIkoO08ChA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skyatlantic It is already?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BiancaJagger The man has a serious mental disorder I can't understand the people around him. He makes House of Cards appear innocent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @POTUS The man has a major personality disorder does nobody see this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willleahy @achrisevans where did that year go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent Oh well that's OK then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@image_magazine @VanityFair and why would that be a surprise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duffygary @AudreyCarville @CNNPolitics You'll end up with very little tourism from abroad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByrneLive The least we do the better you couldn't win with Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PA about time too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByrneLive Shouldn't happen this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomaswright08 @lawlor_aine I'd say the affair will be over if he finds out?💔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfRayKinsella I absolutely hate women only groups shows a total lack of confidence in themselves I've always felt as good as any man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevbarring @MailOnline this is very serious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent no smoke without fire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremycorbyn @Mo_Farah @theresa_may Your country could e going the same route with all the Brexit regulations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @LBC I wish somebody would shut your evil mouth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiddleEastEye Look at all the idiotic yes men!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracemarylaura @NiallHarbison We'll have to agree to disagree? By going we are condoning everything he stands for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fiannafailparty @LimerickFiannaF @SenatorMarkDaly I'm afraid they're close to being returned home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiddleEastEye It announced that they are welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracemarylaura @NiallHarbison We obliterate our principles plus I'm sure we're only a step away from having all the Irish back from US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishSunOnline Dreadful we should a no tolerance attitude to these crimes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neevy101 Trump needs a shrink!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfarrell_ucd Practising ass licking for St Patrick's Day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PA only if it hits Britons?  are others nationalities not worthy of your concern, just Britons. What a  philosophy is that? Speaks volumes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahouraxo @Donal_OKeeffe but he has business there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracemarylaura @NiallHarbison No we can't be seen to be supporting him whatsoever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100 Disgusting! But it's a sign of the dreadful irreverence to mankind that's creeping into society worldwide.  So so sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtetwip @lawlor_aine @RTEOne @RTENewsNow @campaignforleo @loreillysf @RoisinShortall most popular party in the country not represented?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AilbheConneely @Donohuereports is a ridiculous idea! How would woman react if the men were to do the same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenoconnell he'll be ass licking as usual !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully @RTERayDarcyShow I could think if better things to do with honey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoodsMgt Ha ha I got it free for going from pay as go to bill pay!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oconnellhugh @politico He has businesses in them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDRN1 @anbealach some chance he'll a.. licking as usual!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishexaminer Has to be an election!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins I can't believe how you can be so unfeeling &amp; evil it's some feat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GTCost It's looking dodgy for Irish no amount of shamrock will sop him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/BIkoO08ChA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBrandITV @bbclaurak He couldn't remember or didn't understand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donalcronin @guardian wouldn't fancy her chances?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurGriffin @TodaySOR Enda would do anything for power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner the man has a serious personality disorder!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarieTBrady nerve of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitrionaPerry My understanding was Mexican President decided?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitrionaPerry @rtenews holey money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated He must have big business there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent  What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkFM Fianna Fail plan Deputy John Lahart mooted this more than two years ago? No ideas of you own. Glad you're going with ours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling @sineaddesmond @HuffPostUKPol She'll rue the day she did when he makes a fool of her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_clegg I don't want her addressing our Dail as Brexit will cause us grief. Mexico has cancelled their meeting. Let her off silly woman!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly and is anybody surprised he's off to hail his comrades!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FintanCox he's not going on my behalf!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @theresa_may she might not feel the same next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OisinOD How did the great Finian vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidClinchNews @PressSec hope it's not the nuclear one?😆😅😆😅😆😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayoDotIE @Castlebar_IE there must be an election in the offing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnetteLawson @guardian Good luck with that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JOEdotie delighted what an ignoramus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated probably in Mexico?😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @FoxNewsInsider May God help them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thejanitor14 @ger_mccann has Pat had his urgent operation yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurGriffin @rte that's just apalling do they know who did it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @PressSec only US lives matter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillMansell my cousin is in the same state she got solar/oil dual system and is suffering for past 6 mths. Never right &amp; cost a fortune!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/BIkoO08ChA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCJonSopel @POTUS I'm afraid US has elected a total nut job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated more obvious each day that passes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyohconnor you wouldn't in most hospitals even private ones!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrKeithSwanick my husband had a liver transplant 6 years ago. He had Alpha 1. Totally recovered and healthy ever since!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAlPorter @todayfm heartiest congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner Why did he ask her so embarrassing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aravosis He's both! I'm glad I live here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent_ie @orwell4ever Why ever was she asked when she has no problem screwing us an NI?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scientists4EU What happened to free speech and the land of the free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VCurrentAffairs He's a pure loon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tiernanbrady @AlexGreenwich @AMEquality you're doing great over there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated not before he does an awful lot of damage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent_ie embarrassing or what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnMailleach @KarlBrophy because Kenny is an ass licking idiot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinaFitzg @fiannafailparty @TommyBroughanTD @rtenews they should all let them rest in peace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickthehack where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinPoil @EndaCostello Where has Pierce Doherty gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EndaCostello she was elected by army council?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarieTBrady army council?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MONeillOfficial @SarahBardon How come you were selected without a vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terencecosgrave Mary Louis says they voted in on last night's TWIP army council must have made an exception this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hydroponicjuan Money doesn't make anyone happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donalcronin Paddy McGowan Broadsheet Balladeers he wrote parodies during interviews sang them with Val Fitzpatrick at the end of show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donalcronin I remember every bit of that era! So yes I'd say I will. My Dad met JFK at reception in the Arus, Dad was a TV star then RTE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donalcronin @nytimes dying to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianFlanagan1 @CaitrionaPerry @realDonaldTrump she's being playing a blinder recently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TJ_Politics @thejournal_ie of course it is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/BIkoO08ChA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated  don't know if it'll be dementia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Okeating @bingowings14  he really was he did Trumps body language!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins You are a most annoying person !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fiona_Kildare @normamoriarty and the Shinners are there claiming it as their own today?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>