<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@fiskeforbrains Thank you :) How's your work going?? Looks like the BRUVs are picking up lots of observations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkDevocean Thanks Chris! Progress going well on your end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dm_moore_ Thanks! I'll have to get those samples organized for you soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SammSherman27 You should set up those BRUV's to follow the chimaeras around instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VickyV_TeamORF Thank you!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spottedcatshark @IUCNRedList Thank you!! Looking forward to the NZ assessments!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@physiologyfish Thank you!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhySharksMatter How about an IOU for the next conference we both attend?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SammSherman27 Thanks Sam! :) Now I have heaps of time for a proper catch up! Hope you're enjoying time with the parentals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And lastly, #NewZealand has been a great place to study #deepsea #sharks. #PhD thesis submitted! Time to go play wi… https://t.co/5EGYLH50hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2: Most #deepsea #sharks are hard to age. Yesterday, we had an awesome mini-workshop w/S. Campana discussing the c… https://t.co/wDXv2lsyTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DisappointedAnimals: the #deepsea prickly dogfish #shark. https://t.co/rFJCIpzbOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FishListic It's a hard one to find! Look three years of annoying people across NZ to get ~50 of them. Lots from observers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VickyV_TeamOR What on earth happened to the ratty looking one?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#3: Chimaeras (aka #ghostsharks) may enjoy dining via face plant. Find the full #deepsea video here:… https://t.co/8oYgYggg60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an awesome photograph https://t.co/3IDB1iJgls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#4: Favourite #shark species: the #deepsea and always dopey looking prickly dogfish (Oxynotus bruniensis) https://t.co/dYSMse0sYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squatinaivalina @IanFisheries Aw c'mon guys, she was already self conscious about not being able to fit her fat butt on the scale....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#5: #Deepsea #sharks need more #taxonomy! I have a freezer of specimens that local experts have yet to confidently… https://t.co/ctUbyo46it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #SharksNearMe is all about the #shark books today, courtesy of @CSIROPublishing and @Te_Papa https://t.co/S30MYdSNhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bob_calder @JoeyMaier It's from Chatham Rise, off New Zealand. Unsure of exact depth, but most likely 800 m+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Deepsea #sharks from Belize with @squatinaivalina https://t.co/wdr9Aj6Am4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#6: #Deepsea lantern #sharks can have ectoparasitic barnacles (Anelasma). These parasites stunt the reproductive or… https://t.co/8IiFafzMR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#7: Of those species which have been assessed @IUCNRedList , ~30% of NZ #sharks are currently listed as… https://t.co/2Ka7YnkNSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#8: When you need a confidence boost, academic spam always has your back. https://t.co/nnUpTxxXqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#9: R is your best friend and your worst enemy. I'd like to think we've made some progress together since this mast… https://t.co/VkLpS6wcKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#10: #MuayThai has been the best #phdlife stress relief https://t.co/eb0pxGhfxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#11: My most frequently asked question: Do I swim with #deepsea #sharks. No, I don't. My sharks generally arrive to… https://t.co/QQCCRMSF9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fishguy_FHL @lgroskin @jimwharton He definitely had a case of the Mondays. Melancholy Mondayfish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#12: Adding words like novaezealandiae, homonycteris, and Simpfendorfer (@SharkColin) to your spellcheck helps with… https://t.co/eDnbt4ugt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crigby4 and #deepsea #shark fishing. Nice one @SEM_Munroe https://t.co/Ou2sM90ump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#13: Fisheries observers can be a very valuable source for samples. Nearly 1/2 my prickly dogs, incl. the gravid on… https://t.co/rveuWerNU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#deepsea frilled #shark on display! https://t.co/d9MXohlDVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#14: For me,
⇧ writing w/ coffee, immobilizing knee surgery, promises of more samples
⇩ writing w/ food, earthquake… https://t.co/tUdkw80nDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanFisheries We could fry one up and find out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkDevocean @YvoDivoDiNozzo I believe squalene can be produced in the lab sans shark these days too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#15: Chimaeras have fragile, deciduous skin that is often damaged from trawl nets. Black ghost #shark undamaged (to… https://t.co/56sizdbt5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkAdvocates A rhinochimaera one is always on the wish list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#16: When you study #sharks, people give you all the paraphernalia. This was just within arm's reach (some serious… https://t.co/kOCLZanOqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Randchovy Do you have an H. haeckeli??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#17: Chimaeras, like this longnose spookfish (Harriotta raleighana), are some of the deepest recorded #sharks (dept… https://t.co/jzBzglJ8zU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spinnershark7 Citrus fruits are too expensive here to bathe in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EFBauer @mt_ur_mind Mainly reproductive biology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#18: After a long day of #shark dissections, baby wipes (or a bath in bleach) are the best means of getting rid of… https://t.co/K0VodFZjOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevepog Ouch! Definitely not that painful but always something to watch out for: https://t.co/0PBKM0YpKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevepog It's very, very mild. Probably for defense against predators but very little research done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#19: Joys of taxonomy: In my #phd, this #shark has been Proscymnodon plunketi, Centroscymnus plunketi, Scymnodon pl… https://t.co/BaFrULDaIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The non-shark hazards of working with #sharks https://t.co/qZd5dw69BG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SammSherman27 Don't get me started on how many times the males "attached" themselves to me with their tenacula! So much chimaera harassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spottedcatshark The solution to everything: bird-fush https://t.co/WpBHHaReiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#20: Chimaera spines are long, sharp and mildly poisonous. No need to stab yourself for proof. I've done it enough… https://t.co/QkFYfAryyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#21: The most at risk #NewZealand #shark species are #deepsea species: https://t.co/P5sVlp1kAY https://t.co/DBIP3Dft08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I opened a box once to find this #shark that died and was then frozen mid-chew #BestCarcass https://t.co/pBBup5jsgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#22: Baxter's dogfish #sharks (E. granulosus) are the worst. Not enough space here to explain. Pretty sure they hav… https://t.co/VVyMOP6iIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#23: If you shine a light down a #deepsea #shark snout, you can map out its electroreceptors. #sharkscience https://t.co/QGj0KEIORp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#24: #Deepsea chimaeras are capable of storing sperm. This is what #shark sperm can look like under a light (a) and… https://t.co/5XucAuIxf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huttcitylibs @VeronikaMeduna @StephJoycePrice Want to go??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#25: Having a good supervisor will make or break your #phd experience. I could always count on mine for wise words… https://t.co/mikh3DpPF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#26: People eat chimaera, but you're most likely to see it sold as "pearl" or "pearl fish"
#chimaerasneedlovetoo… https://t.co/ZtLI3Loa3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#27: My scooter can carry me + 40 kg of #shark and still manage the hills of Wellington. Enzo has been #phd lifesav… https://t.co/SfqTglWjO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ancient #chimaeras!
#chimaerasneedlovetoo https://t.co/5pMzezRVSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#28: Prickly dogfish #sharks give birth to 8 pups, which can measure ~1/3 of mom's length and are already prickly!… https://t.co/VlY0fGHOA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The life of a #deepsea cookiecutter #shark in cookie form! https://t.co/OaQKcjqGsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#29: Going to sea and being seasick for a month was totally worth it. Most rewarding experience to learn about… https://t.co/RGbSRQxk9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#30: #NewZealand is home to a diverse group of ~120 (and counting) species of #sharks, rays, and chimaeras. https://t.co/FAMYqEWgME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 2017, I thought I'd start the year with a countdown of things I've learned over the past 3+ years as I wrap up this #PhD thesis...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spottedcatshark I see what you're trying to do here.... https://t.co/ZC9lnMFDnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spottedcatshark Where's my bird??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect day for the first meeting of the Trans-Pacific #Shark Cookie Convention. https://t.co/PDvl4MwRQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rfedortsov What depths do you fish at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkDevocean @rfedortsov Who can resist those eyes???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sharks for #Christmas make the best presents. Happy Holidays everyone :) https://t.co/ujWOnxCe6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkAdvocates Awesome! Can I request a chimaera for the next batch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sharks4Kids @SpinyDag @CristinaZenato @GillsClub @MrRussellsClass @epicdiving @DutchSharkSoc @Dr_Yannis Merry Christmas everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PhD thesis meet puppy. RIP thesis. https://t.co/Qk777gbx1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 hours of #Christmas airport chaos = 24 hours of quality #phd thesis referencing https://t.co/zk5HnULjq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyMaier Haha you know me too well! Unfortunately there is a PhD to finish, not much time for Twitter fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for #Christmas, a new species of cat-#shark 
#sharkscience https://t.co/BBANPwSa0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BestSpots: #Deepsea lantern-#sharks are covered in unique spots (photophores), allowing them to glow in the dark… https://t.co/O8p9HY9lAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much #chimaerasneedlovetoo for #BestSpots https://t.co/EEDDkEHlZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connect the fish dot: Body shape, functional diversity of #deepsea fish assemblages across depth ranges… https://t.co/zXDmt02S4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Randchovy @VickyV_TeamORF @PREAUX_FISH @Daily_Express @NatGeo I saw one article describing them as"fish w/penises on their head". Ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep-Sea Ghost Shark Filmed Alive In Ocean For First Time https://t.co/VbEfnokoDk via @NatGeo #Chimaerasneedlovetoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FlatSharkFriday: When your #deepsea skate ate too much and just wants to chill in the tub #sharkscience https://t.co/r8EaPa5b4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickDulvy Does that mean I've converted you from flatsharks to chimaeras?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As juveniles, #deepsea rhinochimaera snouts can measure 50-90% of their body length #sharkscience… https://t.co/dHZtMbszgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mt_ur_mind That calls for a victory dance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paper: Sperm storage &amp; (snout) size matters. More odd facts about #deepsea chimaeras for #sharkscience,… https://t.co/luu4ngYz6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BWueringer I feel a hashtag coming on.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharkMourier @spinnershark7 There's such a thing as citrus pathology?! My latest: Obesity Treatment speaker. I know my sharks are fat but..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I publish a paper on chimaera reproduction, and the internet suggests the following post-doc. Almost, internet. Alm… https://t.co/o2WCDo0lz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spottedcatshark So that's an approximate ratio of 25 bug bites per #shark. When's next season?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of #shark #eggcases, here's some #deepsea catshark eggcase diversity from New Zealand #sharkscience https://t.co/fpCVYtiGZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FlatSharkFriday: #Deepsea skates are so easy and so not messy to work with. Everyone should work on flat-#sharks f… https://t.co/RrH9KkV49g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCraigMc Certainly :) I can get something to you closer to the end of the month. Any requirements?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairDove @DeepSeaConserve @NZGeographic Also, I have a paper coming out shortly on rhinochimaeras. Would DSN be interested??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairDove @DeepSeaConserve @NZGeographic I got all the deep-sea oddities. Chatham Rise survey 2014 https://t.co/8OJIjdLHwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairDove @DeepSeaConserve @NZGeographic Nice one! I feel special knowing I'm one of the 0.001% of people who have seen a loosejaw :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairDove They could take them down in packs. Ever see cookie cutter bites on whale sharks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairDove Hmm looks like Caribbean &amp; Japan are battlegrounds. This is where we would find whale shark neonates.... in pricklys stomachs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>