<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarmelSepuloni maybe fundraise to modify an available state house for Tracey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarmelSepuloni Tracey Penney and Apera Wilson: What is needed to get them into a home, can we fundraise for anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altUSEPA @altNOAA @LiveScience a couple of plane crashes have been linked to microbursts haven't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edgarwright at the moment Peter Cook from Whoops Apocalypse might be an upgrade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cateia97 on this one, I confess, I'm not 100% sure how to abbr. vacation either. Not sold on RoguePOTUS yet but not convinced it's Russians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cateia97 changing the last word for an abbreviation is something I frequently do on twitter in the same situation. Could be that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cateia97 noticed the -esk at the time, thought it odd. I counted the characters, if they use Bannon-esque. they go over 140 chars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_cu_carter Great piece on OL. One thing, Villanueva is an ERFA this offseason, and I think RFA next year. Should be a Steeler til 2019]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altNOAA did Jenny McCarthy ever present the weather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump so not everyone in your cabinet is completely unqualified? Go talk to Mitch McConnell about senate obstruction fucknut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News mmmmm not really democratically elected... but closer to being it than our "leader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottBaio @realDonaldTrump @CNN this Happy Days spinoff is even worse than Joanie loves whatshisface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 how many deplorables do you need to make a basket?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newbalance is it true your CEO fundraised for Trump? If so, I guess I'm wearing my last pair of New Balance shoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong I'd like them to run that Kids vs Mascots game instead of the Probowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathynewman @brianmoore666 @POTUS @lindseyhilsum ah, I see the "in US" bit. That seems a bit contrived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotAltWorld all we need is to fling a giant rock at the earth and we can false flag the shit out of those six legged bastards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mentalben @cathynewman @brianmoore666 @POTUS @lindseyhilsum I'm appalled by the exec order, but some of these facts sound... alternative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathynewman @brianmoore666 @POTUS @lindseyhilsum is that actually correct? Lockerbie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 but but but special relationship??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScienceMarchDC @NotAltWorld just please let it be on March 14th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfitt1 @dlolleyor so if Pats are using it legitimately shouldn't half of their receivers missed the game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKLabour I've been a supporter of Corbyn. I don't want the Labour Party to be Tory-lite. But I cannot vote for a party that supports Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer that new moth with the bad hair and the small penis, we should discuss it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffRisdon @NealCoolong @TheBrownsWire Most talented group of players Hue has coached all year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 Trump has already divorced 2 wives and 1 reality.No surprises his biggest arselickers have done the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 Trump also thinks this is 9 inches https://t.co/z5SHnZGtpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News there must have been about 10 million people on the anti-Trump march today then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 just throw the term peacock back. Loud, preening self publicist with a name that infers a small penis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichSmeth @BBCScrumV that's exactly what NZ teams do every year. Then they laugh at us for overpaying for journeymen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SionDHughes @BBCScrumV The SH is laughing at NH clubs for overpaying journeymen Super Rugby players and impinging development]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCScrumV 1 Springbok cap 4 years ago. Can't qualify for Wales, will keep young Welsh talent out. Crap signing really isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW would make for an interesting comparison to Shazier's legal in 2015, not in 2016 hit on Gio Bernard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong is he trying to blame 2016?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrydulac @AntonioBrown So you're saying Butler beats the average ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW you interested in the hit on him afterwards that wasn't called for helmet to helmet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly asking for Blount is basically trolling! Well done ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 I suppose the odds of a Live TV meteor strike are somewhat limited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW the number of blown PI/Def Holding calls on both teams was staggering. Like they just didn't want to call either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasalerno @Dejan_Kovacevic After his second 6 FG game of the year. We should start including Boz in the 4 B's!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfitt1 he's a good player. Did the Browns cut him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW startlingly similar to the one Shazier laid on Gio Bernard that got the rule emphasis changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW might have been better if anyone was blocking for him though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW falling player. Looked like Davis tried to lead with a shoulder, unfortunate but not a flagrant one IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigSportGB @gallagherbren was at his best with honest hard working players, not primadonnas. Very fitting of a hard working, honest coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigSportGB @gallagherbren such a likeable guy and a great coach. It was a shame the way he was treated as England manager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow if @CNN was fake news, Trump would read it and believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong @btsteelcurtain yep. As I recall we had too many injuries in other positions to promote Mauro to the 53. Our loss, Cards gain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpublik @brianmoore666 @tonygallagher and I thought the Sun only had tits on Page 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NivenJ1 @brianmoore666 reading? That's a stretch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 thought you might have been one of the Hookers. Then I remembered, you wouldn't piss on Trump if he was on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump if it was fake news, you'd believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong that's a great story. Hopefully Deshaun can help Warwick continue that work once he's an NFL millionaire too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette don't get me wrong. You have to love that about Ben. But that's why you absolutely HAVE to take him out when the game is won]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette especially a QB who can't help but to try and extend the play regardless of the game situation. Asking for trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamonFoster if they'd won would the whole league be partying on a boat on a Monday to prep? Nope. Probably not why they lost. GB are good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOnion and he's watching a better performance than half the nominees managed this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette I don't think anyone should EVER return the ball out of the endzone. Even if you make it back to 25, there's usually a flag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW they called roughing the passer though. Right result, but I thought flag should have been for crown of helmet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Realrclark25 AB dropped a couple today too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW basically, the only people who pee in a cup more than Deebo are long haul truckers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NealCoolong I don't wanna be all twittery, but, you need to take Big Ben out of the game in that situation to save him from himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 that always translates as the working poor and the middle class need to pay more so rich Tories can pay less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWalesSport @BBCScrumV would be a shame if this crucial tour couldn't take place on the Islands themselves. Send the WRU ground crew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garydunion @brianmoore666 I think by "mankind", she might mean white people...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW I really want the PSU kid but I think it's a year too early for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly Ayers goes from Practice Squad to starting WR in 2 weeks? Nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyS8 @EdBouchette he didn't have to watch the Eagles? He's the lucky one here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW I'd be very happy if they were in the middle. That was just 2 games ago. If they were in the middle, 4 more wins = SB!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattletiss7 If guys like Giggs/Cantona/Scholes had as many great games as you, they'd be called the greatest ever. And I'm a ManU fan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly and Hargrave would also have been deserving in my estimation. Especially the last couple of weeks without Tuitt &amp; Heyward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly them chanting Heeeeath is a bigger compliment anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCScrumV depends if Toulon fire him for going on the Lions tour or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW Miami. I'll take the backup QB. KC might be the second best team going into the playoffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfitt1 guessing those last 3 guys will not be starting against the Browns regardless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bungdan @brianmoore666 I'd give pretty good odds that Trump has killed more people than Ebola in the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RHahn850 @Dejan_Kovacevic the best bit is on Bradshaw ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfitt1 Dolphins without a doubt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette was thinking maybe they play it like preseason, they get 1 series, maybe 2 so they practice fully all week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SI_PeterKing wasn't he? Played in the era I started watching NFL. Left an impression, and not just for that horrific broken leg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Teresa_Varley @Ike_SwagginU @steelers @nflnetwork @NFL @NFLNow nice to see these guys still hang out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dlolleyor good player. If the Bungles want to cut him after this season, I'd happily sign him for the Steelers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW my brother makes the next generation of Welsh Rugby players watch highlights of Barry's jump sidesteps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dejan_Kovacevic @DustinDopirak it's no coincidence he's wearing his Belichick Costume is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly let's be fair, Bradshaw would probably make the Looking Foolish Hall of Fame as a broadcaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayfitt1 Burfict can look at the final score instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidflatman in the tiny hands of crazy or incompetent leaders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmoore666 I haven't figured out if he's just incompetent or crazy AND incompetent yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFarrior @Realrclark25 especially as these Bowl Games are just about money. Hardly any of their fans will be there either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCScrumV might want to get @BBCSport to look at this: https://t.co/gfJk3ggRk6 Anscombe doesn't qualify on residency. Mum is Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport there isn't really a player in the current Welsh squad who fits the bill either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport Re https://t.co/gfJk3ggRk6 Gareth Anscombe qualifies for Wales by virtue of his mother being Welsh, not through residency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @gerrydulac with the Senate and Congress already slanted in favour of small states/rural areas, I completely agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly Probably a lot to do with a bunch of dumb penalties he gave away in his first year. Taunting, etc. Personally, I love him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimwexell I was imploring them to kick the field goal after the last knee. Because, it's the Bengals and because Boz deserved the record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonColeBR some teams are bad for good reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edgarwright I didn't even eat the Salmon Mousse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtPopejoySW not got the video, Was a helmet to helmet hit, but to be fair, Green lowered his head into the tackler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Realrclark25 used to watch him and his brothers rocking it for the London Monarchs! Can't stand Dallas but can't hate Dak or JG.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>