<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMFeeney I made that Domitian argument in an essay! Negative views are all elite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMFeeney yeah, you're right. The reality TV star stuff fits with Nero. Hope he doesn't kick Melania to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But comparing Trump to Augustus is wrong. He's more of a Domitian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lex Julia de maritandis ordinibus! He'll soon be claiming direct lineage to goddess Venus, building a mausoleum &amp; e… https://t.co/O7SZhlCPjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note UKIP weren't campaigning for 2nd ref on electoral reform. They wanted it enforced on people who had explicitly voted for status quo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farage "defying the will of the people" by pushing for electoral reform after resounding rejection in 2011 ref https://t.co/bYY3ZHO5v2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpechet @KellyannePolls Trump women aren't a diverse crowd. They have to conform to v specific stereotypes https://t.co/DTtSCA3g19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There isn't a more textbook example of a woman hater than Milo. Well, perhaps Trump &amp; Bannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is defending a man who once said women should be especially scared of sexbots as men would have no need for them anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund he truly is. He's incapable of sound judgement or leadership. Labour are becoming irrelevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge deleted last tweets. Pls take my word for it I know this stuff for a fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge I will do. But I promise you, project to move jobs began implementation phase on day May ruled out SM membership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund and Smith has shown himself to be far more in line with Labour voters &amp; possessed of a backbone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge if you want sustainable business model you do need passporting. It's kind of an area of expertise in my household.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund but clearly Labour leadership was always Leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund sure. I think Labour leadership position is v odd. Corbyn won't win Leave voters &amp; so many Labour constituencies were Remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge that's true, it could but at least 1 of biggest banks has given up on passporting &amp; is now planning job moves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge it won't. Govt aren't even attempting to keep passporting. Hence banks are now working plans to move staff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund my guy has purely voted with Labour leadership. Despite being v vocal about hard Brexit being disastrous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronniegeorge I wish there wasn't evidence of it. Unfortunately I know first hand that there is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSaund it's also voting against his own beliefs that gets me. Feels like representative democracy gone badly awry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't feel very democratic for my MP to vote against his own beliefs &amp; the constituency vote. What a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard Brexit will definitely damage job prospects in our constituency as so many depend on financial services for work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My constituency voted Remain. My MP believes hard Brexit will damage Britain but voted to allow govt to proceed with it without hindrance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These people are not well https://t.co/xCagbQjYpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_J_C_Moss even with advantageous US deal leaving CU makes only ltd sense. RoW FTAs will never replace EU trade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_J_C_Moss and there's zero need to acquiesce to demands for a very early state visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_J_C_Moss yes. If he really isn't our 1 &amp; only then UK having other pressing priorities would be fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_J_C_Moss holding the hand of a self avowed sex pest. Yeah, we're really keeping a dignified &amp; prudent distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_J_C_Moss only those deeply emotionally invested in Brexit &amp; the Tories could deny it. Hasty US trip, unprecedented state visit offer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull stood up to a bully. Theresa May held the bully's hand &amp; offered him Britain on a plate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcdonnelljp it becomes difficult if Trump targets those countries specifically. He's already going for Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason why supine UK making Brexit all about the US is imprudent now: it's not just EU states we'll alienate https://t.co/TuOhrVaBLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcdonnelljp I sincerely hope so. Setting ourselves belligerently against our closest neighbours to ally with Trump seems madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcdonnelljp it's unfathomable. Had enough MPs held back govt from triggering article 50 they could've forced a softer Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argument it's anti democratic to vote against triggering article 50 while govt intent on 1 spectacularly onerous type of Brexit is poppycock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiUttley it's speed with which the self styled liberal Leavers have abandoned any pretence at liberalism that shocks. Save the odd 1 or 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Moses_ yep, it's why they wouldn't rule it out &amp; why Remainers said they were lying in keeping it in the mix. They were!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news: I'm on some strong painkillers after someone skied over my face. So apologies for the over feistiness. Pain &amp; painkillers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiUttley nope. Not a shred. They've got phoney excuses growing out of their phoney excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when they told us we could be like good ole neutral Switzerland or Norway. Those were the days. Fucking liars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Brexit is so dependent on hitching your wagon to that evil man there's a big chance it was the mother of all stupid ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, see that, Trump fans? That's where it takes you. Down in the hole with those seeking to minimise the anti semitism of the Holocaust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennywhojenny @shakeys7 it dates from 2015 apparently but it shows exactly the spirit in which Trump rise to power has been conducted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get out of my country" "I'm a US citizen" America is truly fucked &amp; Brits excusing this make me sick https://t.co/BVRSs4Wxhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guy_herbert but pretending to not be. Just rationalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahKate26 window onto Douglas' manly psyche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I imagine Douglas will spend the next 4 yrs engaged in the manly pursuit of equivocating for racist sex pests. Grr. Manly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best bit in this straw man littered piece is the anti woman kicker at the end. Vagina hats, no less https://t.co/mtU4TFQxYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@renieanjeh she's totally at odds with a London constituency that's for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@renieanjeh tricky. Corbyn is an absolute shocker but Hoey is nearly as ideologically nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@renieanjeh Hoey belongs in UKIP. Soubs is a proper centrist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump clearly plans to use deeply privileged access to our monarch to legitimise himself. It's why he wants it so soon. We will rue it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, Brexit didn't have to become inextricably linked to a historically unpopular leader engaged in flouting his own constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexiteers talk of freedom. Anointing an *at best* deeply divisive POTUS with unprecedented haste *at his demand* isn't freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't insult Trump! Brit jobs depend on it!" say people who have made a sport of insulting our most important trading partners for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dhelme570 I'm sure she can. It's case of whether we want her to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Moses_ I imagine he was more discerning!! But yeah, he so could have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GazTheJourno organising perhaps but not signing. They were available at places people went regularly, like church.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petitions forced the ban of UK participation in the slave trade &amp; slavery. Take it you wouldn't have signed https://t.co/CZGlImGBFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright, Oswald. https://t.co/qkUP5im4NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If May does force a state visit on the Royal family Philip should bowl up to Trump &amp; claim he could've had his mum. See how he likes it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forcing our future king to entertain a man who's said disgusting things about his wife &amp; late mother is repellent. True patriots oppose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how what the British people think matters more than anything right up until it means fuck all https://t.co/MOZtZlIw2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSWestminster proud of all involved, inc obvs you guys for good policing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TillyKlein probably. Still smells bad in the circs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EconvaincuU @EmmanuelMacron @lepen oh look. One of Putin's trolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. This isn't "going global". It's clinging to an outdated alliance of "White Dominions". But only the very whites… https://t.co/pejD51ve0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sassycassyL that is a truly excellent squirrel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajjolley @Medium it's not like Bannon hasn't said tearing the establishment down isn't his express intent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveKomarnycky it's awful. West's cowardice or outright support for Putin is shameful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajjolley how America has fallen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PGBBNS if Macron wins in France I'm off to Paris. If not I may join you in Dublin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin took power on back of a terror attack on his own people &amp; you want to "normalise relations" with him. You thick cunt @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inc Putin who has killed more civilians than ISIS in Syria &amp; responsible highest fatality terrorist attack in Europ… https://t.co/Q1HlDy5jWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PGBBNS crikey. That would be truly nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CintaArsenal couldn't disagree more strongly. Nationality should never trump skills &amp; experience. Best person for the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like he didn't make it crystal clear #makeamericashitagain https://t.co/hT8wEqVKKV https://t.co/3vu9UaYaXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here comes Steve Bannon's white nationalism, folks https://t.co/QdmQHVG7ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guy_herbert exactly the same! Same attitudes to women too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guy_herbert same. These are the people who think "Merkel has ruined Germany" &amp; all Muslims are to be suspected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOncoming I think we'd still be going for a deal &amp; leaving CU just without the cosying up to an aspiring despot issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guy_herbert yes. It shows up the extent of the  irrational fear of the EU &amp; all its institutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK being forced to align with countries who lack our commitment to human rights at expense of those who do share it is madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflexibility in face of rapidly changing geopolitics smacks of zealotry. Case for leaving customs union may disappear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much of UK backing for Trump comes from ideological commitment to hard Brexit. Tying ourselves to Trump to justify leaving CU always unwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiUttley I think they actively enjoy it. Small men &amp; women needing to feel powerful over others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiUttley I think it might be worse than sociopathy. Next stop: making lampshades out of human skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the living fuck is wrong with these people? How can terrifying your opponents be the political end game? Psych… https://t.co/UhT4j4UBlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver laughable. Seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver Islamic terrorism isn't even close to the threat Irish republican terrorism was to Britain. Nowhere near.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver this isn't even close to being true. Those killed &amp; displaced by Assad massively dwarfs those killed &amp; displaced by IS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver right, so we're to blame for all evils committed by all Britons? Why are all Muslims all responsible for actions of tiny %?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver without "huffing &amp; puffing" there would never have been most human progress. But sneer all you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver our economic weakness is self inflicted. Hence having to cosy up to a proto fascist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver it isn't about "the left". It's about the leader of the free world victimising the innocent &amp; embracing real evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver it's far from claptrap. What's claptrap is directing people's ire at at ordinary Muslims to distract from the real danger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver but by all means equivocate for perpetrators of genocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver Putin's support for Assad predates Cameron's attempts at action. Miliband is a coward. Putin is a war criminal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftOverForEver it's specifically a vindictive muscle flex. It will help no-one &amp; harm many.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>