<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great story https://t.co/eQ6dr6Y1e7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cancer in the Family: Talking to the fearless Theo Ross https://t.co/CizCk7NJHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the death of the Senate and its long history as the world’s greatest deliberative body https://t.co/TCgHzE7SKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big pharma depends on immigrants. It kept quiet about the travel ban https://t.co/y1m2GpjJ5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump’s travel ban could hurt science - The Washington Post https://t.co/tbG5hPhhJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of lawyers descend on airports to offer free help - The Washington Post https://t.co/8e4XEhx4HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats launch a full-scale opposition push against Trump’s executive order - The Washington Post https://t.co/FeUpIw4PJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge halts deportations as refugee ban causes worldwide furor - The Washington Post https://t.co/C6f8bRmC0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s how to leak government documents to The Post - The Washington Post https://t.co/499RqJEBFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An early test of Trump’s ethics pledge is a glittering new tower in Canada - The Washington Post https://t.co/Tx8ApyBVqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a few hours, Badlands National Parks was bad to the bone in defiance of Trump https://t.co/eih9YDiayF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisconsin state agencies are deleting talk of human-caused climate change from their websites - The Washington Post https://t.co/n6DF40m0U5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think your dog talks like people? Scientists say you might just be right. - The Washington Post https://t.co/7ybT8Vdxya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One problem with shutting down the circus: Where will the animals go? - The Washington Post https://t.co/oUtMJL3y29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Trump echo JFK’s moonshot and vow to send humans to Mars? - The Washington Post https://t.co/mgoeB3X6Kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enormous Antarctic ice shelf rift grows by another 6 miles - The Washington Post https://t.co/iRlejpWanR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is trying to put the bully back into the bully pulpit - The Washington Post https://t.co/x3TfqKWMqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Cabinet nominees meet growing ethical questions - The Washington Post https://t.co/MYCDI4vd1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These presidents all said they were going to change America. How’d that work out? https://t.co/q9cDspxudG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s health: What we could expect with the oldest incoming president https://t.co/wwlYQISRF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Trump draws low marks for transition, response to Russian hacking - The Washington Post https://t.co/4FnCNWwky9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We were soldiers’: The flesh and blood behind the new civil rights monument - The Washington Post https://t.co/us5kFzGKQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Smithsonian loses one of its top scientists after a bitter conflict with administrators https://t.co/klfgN1oUiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States already has a vaccine safety commission. And it works really well, experts say. https://t.co/6vLxhf2o39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 70 percent of Japan's largest coral reef has died https://t.co/1PVirC1nP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists don't have a decade to find a Zika vaccine. They need volunteers now. https://t.co/DV5Y2d0R3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardinal Health fined $44 million for opioid reporting violations https://t.co/IKS0Cwz7UL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who uncovered the secret lives of snowflakes https://t.co/E0dSKmXHnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's Interior Dept. calls for major changes to 'modernize' federal coal program https://t.co/U6mXems9EY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chickens 'changed the world.' So why do we ignore them? https://t.co/VVBHLO036A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, agreement between @JoeBiden and @realDonaldTrump: high drug prices are a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on high drug prices: companies getting away with "murder."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drug trials take too long. Will this help?  https://t.co/3ZJdKTaAbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a doctor, I see how a lack of health insurance worsens illness and suffering https://t.co/6i1L0C0FGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HHS Sec warns about health care "going over a cliff" with ACA repeal. by @goldsteinamy https://t.co/dauqaJGpug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions that need answers: What's the point of mucus? by@sarahkaplan48 byhttp://wpo.st/2xaQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The trend toward clean energy is irreversible' -- Obama by@brady_dennis https://t.co/W4WzNznlLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polar bears are on exceedingly thin ice. @bydarrylfears  byhttp://wpo.st/JvaQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump still hasn’t named a leader for the Department of Veterans Affairs - The Washington Post https://t.co/tXhXRvBSxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump got wrong on Twitter this week - The Washington Post https://t.co/0aFKNUpcOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To save an elusive porpoise from extinction, the U.S. government turns to military dolphins https://t.co/hj9O5Lwxss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancer death rate has dropped again. But it's still higher for men than women. https://t.co/dL5gddeVL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebola virus found hiding in lungs of health-care worker https://t.co/JJvabeq5nS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden to tackle cancer drug prices as part of post-White House 'moonshot' work https://t.co/co79BJ4blM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysterious radio burst came from a galaxy 2.5 billion light years away, astronomers discover https://t.co/WxAKkJ40JI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA's newest missions will explore the solar system's asteroids https://t.co/5gYR4FoFz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOAA challenged the global warming 'pause.' Now new research says the agency was right https://t.co/lmaGkm8CCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is dedication. https://t.co/FmHdhfzUyx by@karinbrulliard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black parents take their kids to school on how to deal with police - The Washington Post https://t.co/wBgsID23MH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump takes aim at House Republicans, and they run for cover - The Washington Post https://t.co/0eOS8yWMr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The head of the FDA defends the importance of drug effectiveness https://t.co/OhWlKLVTB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new urgency to protect survivors of childhood cancer https://t.co/up330jxH4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump could quickly doom ACA cost-sharing subsidies for millions of Americans https://t.co/L61xOb25cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medical detectives raced to save a man from a rare, 'universally lethal' disease https://t.co/6Bx6F63dyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution quarantined at NIH after particles are found in it https://t.co/3hrCHO9V96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four more officials charged with felonies in Flint water crisis https://t.co/IMJNeqAtC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In breakthrough experiment, scientists shine a light on antimatter https://t.co/TXe2DcOdgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These two sentences could hint at the next threat to climate science under Trump https://t.co/4UaZsAQVBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another chapter in how to mess up the ACA. https://t.co/rqHsmDIseQ by@Goldsteinamy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In California, water is personal, and thicker than blood. @bydarrylfears https://t.co/ye3JT5QHl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real time eruptions of the non-political kind. by@sarahkaplan48 https://t.co/W7Zwbk8yA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New FDA warning on potential impact of anesthesia on infants and toddlers: https://t.co/jbCwyvU4GU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should have a special Mother's Day for this bird. It just won't quit.  https://t.co/m4e1IrQyZ5 @bydarrylfears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important story on fracking and drinking water: Do the two go together?  https://t.co/8Cgj1siJc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bad luck for the dinosaurs...good luck for us." by@sarahkaplan48  https://t.co/YVSGrCwxdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This explains why some Dobermans chew up the blankets.  And other fun doggie facts. https://t.co/3CiEWygaQU by@karinbruilliard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood fears it may be first casualty of rekindled abortion war - The Washington Post https://t.co/z92EBEk8SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defeating cancer was once a ‘war’; now it’s a ‘moonshot’ - The Washington Post https://t.co/qEKtOpoN0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Gilman, retired Army major general, to head troubled NIH clinical center - The Washington Post https://t.co/DwHQcOo5Cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the flames, ‘mountain tough’ Gatlinburg looks to the future - The Washington Post https://t.co/UdE0ccOxF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Glenn and the courage of the Mercury Seven - The Washington Post https://t.co/65FU7FfJTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt, Trump’s EPA pick, has both sides of climate divide girding for a major fight - The Washington Post https://t.co/rCehElkpyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump transition team for Energy Department seeks names of employees involved in climate meetings - Washington Post https://t.co/vr3fu6AbEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden, on valedictory tour, mixes emotional farewell with lingering ambition - The Washington Post https://t.co/afbRtpkIBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danfagin and to think that I thought the Obamas were doing Xmas shopping at politics and prose bookstore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The termites destroying science https://t.co/5z3JB4Za2Q via @statnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrichtel @nytimes fascinating story about emerging side effects of immunotherapy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanrockoff total shock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pannill but what's a wing flat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pannill he's incredible, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner I'm coming over to see him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterSullivan4 @BuzzFeedNews what are we really supposed to think? Just saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner what kind of pup is it? I just spent a day at penn vet hospital and it was great, they were all playing and howling in the lobby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond @KellyannePolls that's very smart observation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond so voting against your economic interest isn't new, a la Kentucky Medicaid. So this Is a much bigger phenom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner totally get that! Would love to meet the special one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner have fun as the world goes up in smoke. Seriously, I'm a fan of time off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaiserFamFound @larry_levitt smart take by Drew; he says wrecking the insurance market could affect attitudes toward the entire GOP agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoyneoftheRealm would love to hear more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBlau @CNN @statnews good luck! Great organization]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chadterhune sorry to be late responding but what is reality, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoyneoftheRealm what's wrong with the design of the hopkins and NYU studies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are at war"  -- Voices from Standing Rock. https://t.co/Z5szfTHPou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three cancer patients explain how a psychedelic drug eased their fears https://t.co/slErcfyF2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key ingredient in ‘magic mushrooms’ eased cancer patients’ fear of death https://t.co/WhPEMKV4OZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of scientists speak out for science out of concern about Trump @SarahKaplan48 https://t.co/NjlQ9zk4ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers popped the DNA out of one egg and into another to make (mostly) disease-free embryos. @JoelAchenbach https://t.co/k8V5W24DKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy had her arms in the past and her feet in the future. By @SarahKaplan48 @PostHealthSci https://t.co/uKIH1ee3i0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rancher has a permit to kill mountain lion P-45 for killing livestock—which is what cougars DO. @KarinBrulliard https://t.co/JzkvMRJkwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to ignore genetic warnings about cancer, and that could have been fatal - The Washington Post https://t.co/NvPWVI7aKg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>