<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part of all this... When finally TSHTF.. We are the ones with all the guns 290,000,000 strong gun owners o… https://t.co/hdE2znA0AW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_bodley @greeneyes0084 you call them protestors.. I call them "SpeedBumps"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WAKE UP PEOPLE!!! THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO TAKE AMERICA BACK AND DISPOSE OF islam FOREVER https://t.co/lqfwhHJkZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrittPettibone good thing they built all those fema camps.We just need to round up all these obama domestic terrorists for their own safety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet if the US Army lined up artillery &amp; Abrams A-1's on the Mex border the Mexicans would get damned busy buildin… https://t.co/0AiUxyK5qj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexAldridge20 @Rockprincess818 why dont we just call it Kent@State and send in the Guard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattMcGorry @funnyordie @shailenewoodley @DuleHill @Caradelevingne they're gonna love u in tehran when we deport you as a gay refuge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time!!! BOMB THE LIVING HELL OUT OF iran BLOW THEM AND EVERY TRACE OF pislam OFF THE EARTH FOREVER!!! THEN FI… https://t.co/iIPioEqwO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Vietnam VC sent small children in to groups of American soldiers wired with explosives.. This is a 5 year ol… https://t.co/bE4x2M91DP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themindcircle @historyepics i dare you to walk down the street like that at dusk, or not have ur hib jab at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the DNC is trying to nominate one as their chairman https://t.co/5qZa9GZPF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U ms. brasile are an ignorant cunt.. And as we DRAIN THE SWAMP WE WILL REMOVE ALL OF islam FROM OUR SOIL AND BULLDO… https://t.co/FSDbDVKh6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @ChristiChat the Democraps have been selling out the American people for over 30 years.. DRAIN THE SWAMP!! GO NUCLEAR!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElectricLit I had no Idea SImon &amp; Schuster was going into the toilet paper business..Tho She has been talking out of her ass for decades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had no Idea SImon and Schuster were going into the toilet paper business? https://t.co/8lrIzMe5p4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My President is not only putting the White back in the Whitehouse... Looks like he is putting the White back in Ame… https://t.co/bZTjgHBJ6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apblake @TVsAndyDaly you dont like it? Maybe you should get the fuck out of America ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Mr. President..I would love to hear you tell her.. Senator Scumbag..."Your Fired!" https://t.co/L9O3t4tqUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndieWire @funnyordie @shailenewoodley @SusanSarandon keep in mind u FUCKTARDS.WE MADE U!!  And WE CAN UNMAKE U!!! U ARE FARTS IN THE WIND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont think for a single second that just because u wer in some movies that We the American ppl giv a flying fuck ab… https://t.co/kO7gGrzUwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well it is obvious what they used obaminations $$$ hundreds of millions in aid money for.. He was aiding terrorists… https://t.co/Ce8lQFRo5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marisacordero3 @Rockprincess818 @SenSchumer Sad thing is we have the "Cuban Adjustment Act of 1966." AKA-Wet Foot, Dry Foot Policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlissTabitha @nypost my faithisrestoredin religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter the swamp is crying already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek didnt take them long to take that video down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek the swamp is crying already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im being censored by twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter and they're off.... https://t.co/1L2mYvK64z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @FoxNews i predict huge dem losses in next senate election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBurtonXP @AnnCoulter they should start writing their petitions that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek you know that is going to be all over the leftist media tomorrow morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter the more the left cries the more we know President Trumps choice is a solid one.The more they cry the Stronger he becomes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peddoc63 @ThislsNotAJoke Poor cupcake.Americans taking back Our Country got u down?Poor baby u should go climb back into ur fathers vagina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CollegeFix its ok cupcake.. The whiteys are coming to remove your islam from OUR AMERICA!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kiss108 Taylor your like twenty something and your boobs are already sagging like an olelady girl... Get some help yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The term "Politically Correct" is an oxymoron!! And people who believe in being politically correct ARE ACTUALLY JUST MORONS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Todays word is "Flora".. Use it in a sentence: "All three 'Flora' my house is so messy I think I need a maid!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @realmadrid this is the shit they will try to pull here if we dont REMOVE islam FROM ALL OF AMERICA AND DEMOLISH THEIR mosques!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mashable please include your voter id cards with your signatures cuz you undocumented fuckers have no right to petition my government]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican prez calls for illegals in USA to walk off jobs in solidarity..Newsflash!! Briebert: Dishes piling up at restaurants everywhere!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @realDonaldTrump I think it is time to reinstate the draft!! 18-32 male/female send them to the front lines. With "stress cards"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@midmoj @AnnCoulter you should go crawl back in your dads vagina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter it should have never been passed.. It was a lie perpetrated by a traitor to line the pockets of his friends w/ taxpayer dollars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter the so called affordable care act was neither affordable, nor did anybody really care, it was forced upon us never truly vetted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fok1m @cnnbrk @AmyMek you bafuck should get off the mother talk me and the football team just got off in yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kausmickey @AnnCoulter i opt for a digital solution.. Such as a virtual "Town Hall" forum with callin lines like american idol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump please bring up mr. Obama &amp; hillary on charges of treason, high crimes &amp; misdemeanors, against Ame… https://t.co/3xktjsqytj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[islams message of acceptance and inclusion of other races and religions https://t.co/npGLLpVDdz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptDavidRyan @BiasedGirl i showed someone at work a you tube video of schoolhouse rock just the other day.. They had never seen it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M0L0NL4BE @SenFeinstein feinstein needs to be rounded up with obama, hillary, and their horde of traitors tried, and executed for treason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@h3h3productions @Brenden_kelley regarding the Constitutionality of the muslim ban, you are incorrect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek yes but I want to see the traitor obamination and that cunt hillary swinging by their broken necks from the gallows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America.. It is time we start culling the herd of muslim cows on our soil... DEATH TO ALL OF islam IN OUR AMERICA!! https://t.co/ekl97OMRSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neesflash!!! NIGGER LOVES REALLY DONT MATTER https://t.co/rfwHTdaLkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @Cosmopolitan u go gurl i would be happy to help in a blind taste test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fok1m @cnnbrk dont u have sum goats u should b fucking.??? Little boys u like to fondle? I c u need update ur sexual predator registration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OurRightsCount @Mohammad_Ho @cnnbrk @AmyMek go fuck yourself u goatfucking child molester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndieWire the muslims u support are laughing at ur ignorance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ternz @OmarHedeya WRONG!! Point in case...The US Cole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mohammad_Ho @cnnbrk @AmyMek no muslim life is an innocent life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To islam:Tho the weak&amp;the kind may have let u in r house, We r the eyes wer they cant see, the ears wer they cant hear! We defend r homeland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chezjauregui @cnnbrk  you lil cupcake are a shit stain on the underwear of life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mohammad_Ho @cnnbrk @AmyMek mohammad was a goat fucking child molester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fok1m @cnnbrk @AmyMek We will come for u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mohammad_Ho @cnnbrk @AmyMek innocent lives my ass!! We WILL REMOVE EVERY HINT OF islam FROM OUR SOIL!! THAT IS A PROMISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk @AmyMek  We need to hear more good news like this! Only it should b 320,000 muslims die in mysterious gun cleaning accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never use uber again https://t.co/UmES8r1SD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time we remove ALL OF islam AND ALL WHO SUPPORT IT FROM AMERICAN SOIL ONCE AND FOR ALL..EVERY mosque EVERY REFERENCE TO IT DESTROY IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @thedailybeast We need to hear more good news like this! Only it should b 320,000 muslims die in mysterious gun cleaning accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrewGOPWe need to hear more good news like the 5 goat fkrs killd Only it should b 320,000 muslims die in mysterious gun cleaning accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScrewGOP This is very sad!!! Sad that the shooter wasn't a better shot!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to extend thanks to U stupid reg heads.. DFW Airport is loaded w/ latest FBI face recognition hardware… https://t.co/AEeTCsDHxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look it is that fucking hollywood moron sharia la douche https://t.co/tIJJJAfiMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissLizzyNJ "Yes we Can" prosecute a traitor ex president &amp; Sec of State for TREASON  &amp; then watch em swing from the gallows like pinatas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @NYCMayor This is very sad!!! Sad that the shooter wasn't a better shot!!!... Now someone go kill that fuckn commie De blow me o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauren_Southern @cristinalaila1 This is very sad!!! Sad that the shooter wasn't a better shot!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very sad!!! Sad that the shooter wasn't a better shot!!! https://t.co/Uv3q7PXGRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Superbowl would b way more interesting if instead of just the final score ppl called in &amp; voted for their favorite team like on Am Idol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever scores more points will probably win the superbowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iReIateLife @FascinatingVids i have totally picked my nose in front of uour boyfriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI Awesome!!We need to hear more good news like this! Only it should b 320,000 muslims die in mysterious gun cleaning accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlissTabitha maybe Ellis island Cuba? And they can swim over and get their green cards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JKaralun @3GoMigos @BlissTabitha i like this idea.. Ellis island iran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isnt this interesting?? https://t.co/jahpnETOY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Drew_McCoy_ @AnnCoulter  say the protesters win , cpl yrs from now no go zones in their town &amp; sharia they supported bans protesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery and i guess my muslim mail order sister wives are on mothballs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[islamic terrorists posing as the media incite rioting and civil unrest at airports! Time to start filing the FEMA c… https://t.co/xNDjTrh30t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The corruption &amp; moral turpitude perpetrated over the past 8 years through all levels  of r government is deplorabl… https://t.co/yLHsIrDN5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cristinalaila1 why is this no surprise? https://t.co/6f12BXlg7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will defend God and my country, its sovereignty, and borders from all aggressors both foreign and domestic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gelockt @POTUS I question your allegiance to the United States of America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time to reveal the treason &amp; treachery of the obama administration  to the people &amp; prosecute all involved fo… https://t.co/RruPBLMIGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[islamic terrorists posing as the media incite rioting and civil unrest at airports! Time to open the FEMA camps https://t.co/2er3WEN8SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GelocktPeters @POTUS no next will be You!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[islams message of peace https://t.co/KHZLXSO3um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I support the @POTUS in the blocking of terrorists form muslim lands being allowed into the USA!! NOW REMOVE islam FROM OUR SOIL FOREVER!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I believe in religious freedom, islam caliphate doesnt support freedom of religion.  Nor can sharia exist und… https://t.co/4mHJRLzQSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyRoss01 While I believe in religious freedm, islam caliphate doesn't support freedm of religion.Nor can sharia exist under r Constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk while I believe in religious freedom, islam caliphate doesn't support freedom of religion. Nor can sharia exist under r Constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin While I believe in religious freedom, islam caliphate doesn't!! Nor can sharia exist under r Constitution Ban islam from USA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>