<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs @CNNPolitics he's playing to his supporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bullshit.  Illegal aliens lay low.  The last thing they want to do is compromise their ability to remain in the US. https://t.co/IRuSeUEPHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs Not much difference between a Spicer/WH press conference and an Alex Jones radio show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's about time. https://t.co/eyem6s7wMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucktodd They're lies.  Stop inviting habitual liars to your newscasts!  Why is the habitual liar Kellyann still… https://t.co/PWrd99k2Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 In order for Trump to win, he needed an ignorant/misinformed electorate.  He has that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he can  provide $7M/household in tax cuts to 400 rich Americans https://t.co/KUDJXRMv3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunWebbAuthor a lot of them are supposedly Christian...including Ryan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Kurt, good tweet...you're my favorite reporter/person I follow on twitter...hope you hang in there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karoli Fake news/blame the media is his standard play for these things. We need the press to be persistent/relentless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid The same thing with the President-elect...still hasn't released his taxes...so not really vetted either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunWebbAuthor @HuffPostMedia 14 mm = the size of her Adam's apple...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaioccoCSN, @JedYork Jed York must be dismissed or the 49ers are going no where. He lacks every skill required for his position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul @thedailybeast Sure, just like he promised to release his taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul I think it's closer to 200 million that didn't vote for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His many enemies include about 75% of this country. https://t.co/B7yXyF48v4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump The reason(s) can't be good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politicususa As with all of his lies, the truth doesn't matter.  Only thing that matters is what his supporters believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@speechboy71 I don't think it's mental illness. These tweets are to maintain his base.  And it's working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRather The truth-their climate change denial is not about reality or science-it's about making money in oil now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey That someone is Newt Gingrich a prominent landmark in that swamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @maggieNYT Gingrich is the swamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey Not only that, the last place an undocumented voter wants to be...is any place that asks for citizenship ID.  They lay low.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These tweets are for his base. They'll believe this and not realize the hypocrisy. Then be even more anti "left" an… https://t.co/T07KLjGuUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle They dispute climate change not because of science.Their objective is 2 expand oil drilling, prolong it's use and make $$$ now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattbarrows that's terrible news.  The only way the Niners become competitive again is if Jed York is removed.   He's incompetent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outright lie and diversion directed at his base to keep them drinking the kool-aid. https://t.co/1MO9QROPAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders It's all about oil and making a lot of money now. Has nothing to do with a debate about the science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as Trump's base of supporters maintains/increases, he will continue to lie and do whatever is necessary to… https://t.co/5NOaccP9LZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's tweets are for his supporters.  He's doesn't care about the response of anyone else. His aim is to maintain… https://t.co/SfM2PNxTN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieHosken @tina_nguyen @VFHIVE Agreed. Just thinking about eating there makes me ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now twitter needs to do the same. https://t.co/l4MNSu3mXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeepAmerGr8 @Salon Twitter should respond by taking away his account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @VanityFair Neutralizing anyone who criticizes him and diverting the public attention from a real issue is always his priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planned distraction.   Media fell for it again. Hook, line, and sinker. https://t.co/1vwpGFvFq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC He doesn't need to.  The press is already doing everything he wants them to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MittRomney Sorry, but you were used by Trump.  To quote the great Mongo - "Romney only pawn in game of life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markberman Questioning the CIA is not his primary reason for the tweet. Diversion by creating doubt about their report to his supporters is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC So far, he hasn't had to handle the truth. His lies don't matter. Until he's made accountable to facts/truth, he won't change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz He's a flagrant toxic narcicist...of course he doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His usual response. Divert/blame opponent-secure his base. So far, he's been Teflon. Nothing sticks to him.  How do… https://t.co/pR2fjCPFsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laynier @marcylauren that will be a problem, none of his own people are intelligent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs Of course, blame his opponent same as Trump does. Hitler playbook.  Now let's prove who really did it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump Of course he is.  But that's irrelevant. His denial is intended for his supporters. Oil expansion is his goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mediaite He's been trying to intimidate the media for 18+ months.  Why still report it? MSM needs to step up and report the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood He's playing you/the press as always.  Tillerson = diversion from CIA report. When is the press going to step-up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos @Reince @ThisWeekABC I'm sure they will be very honest and open with you.  When is the press going to step up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein This is an issue for later. For now, we need you/the rest of the senate to stop Trump/Russians from taking over our country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @JohnJHarwood treason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @JohnJHarwood especially Russians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticusSarah Obama is still president, don't you think he should lead this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cherry Garcia used to be my favorite... https://t.co/HXwhOEI6ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Not surprising. He's following the Nazi playbook.CIA is now his enemy.The attack is to neutralize them so nobody believes them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum Not just shameful, criminal...he should resign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPM Good luck on Celebrity Apprentice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good observation https://t.co/QmP7zle5dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mediaite Trump has a lot of special cases - any criticism directed at him by media/twitter,any fact... Not really a believer in free speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blakehounshell @CNNMoney no surprise,  this was all a publicity stunt.  No doubt, many more to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/MEcT2HDtP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald the Koch brothers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @RonBrownstein Mein Kampf "big lie" play book.  He's been following this for over a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann He's following the Mein Kempf "Big Lie" playbook exactly.  Lie, neutralize critics of the lie.  Effective with Twitter/MSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood He's following the Main Kempf "Big Lie" playbook exactly.  Immediately neutralize your critics, maintain the lie (Carrier)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smoothkobra @durisdeer Trump cares about neutralizing anyone who criticizes him...and maintain the Carrier lie he told.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4) and if you repeat it frequently enough people will sooner or later believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) concentrate on one enemy at a time and blame him for everything that goes wrong; people will believe a big lie sooner than a little one;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) never concede that there may be some good in your enemy; never leave room for alternatives; never accept blame;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump follows Joseph Goebbels methods almost exactly 1) never allow the public to cool off; never admit a fault or wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieHosken He's not delusional. He follows Goebbels "never accept blame; concentrate on one enemy at a time and blame him for everything"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrnEyedMandy @HuffPostPol Of course,  that's what he does....lies and diverts....blame the opponent.   Goebbels play book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a MAJOR problem! https://t.co/TrJLbHIeDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @marcylauren Lies are what they are...so let's refer to them as what they really are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtenlow Hitler, Stalin, and Putin were all Times Person of the Year.   Trump fits in that group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald we can't let that happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @politico torture might work on Trump though.  Try them on him first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricWolfson @RonHall46 he wants to use his own Trump plane and market his brand...advertise his namefor 2020 election, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @TammaraMaiden1 It's normal for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Truth don't matter.  Tweet the lie, media --&gt;headline, supporters believe he's taking on govt waste. He flies Trump, we pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer his ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 No he's not. He tweeted this so it expands through the media to the masses to give a perception that he's fighting for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid The media needs to step-up.  We need honest accurate reporting....consistently.   Lies need to be replaced by the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @farhip Nothing to digest. it's a lie. Why is the media chasing all of the crap these guys throw at you? He lies EVERYTIME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@durisdeer I can't...they drive me crazy.  Likewise, just sports and HGTV :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@durisdeer why is she still getting airtime on any network?  Should be lies=no airtime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoAngelo @mmfa There is no "fake news".  There's the truth and there's a lie.  Hannity knows nothing about the truth, he only lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartyChargin @politicususa I like your idea though, skip the election, no electoral college, whoever returns from behind the gym wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartyChargin @politicususa lol...Trump needs his ass kicked in the worst way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's bad, McConnell is right there with him. https://t.co/WE1Yhu0Moa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marinafang Good graph, but it's missing his biggest news source of all - his rear-end where most of his news/facts come from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should be arrested and held accountable for consequences of the lie he tweeted. https://t.co/YeGCCBDjJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great! Should have run against him this year. https://t.co/dXqMrmolHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey when will the recount in Michigan be completed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro we need to stop referring to these things as fake news.  Flynn's tweet was a lie , he needs to be held responsible for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey the irony is Obama has always behaved in a manner consistent with Christian values. The Republican "Christian" leaders haven't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood he means when the press will lie and spread his lies like he does.  For Trump, if he tweets or his lips move, he's lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeddyDavisCNN token African American appointment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mediaite Illegal immigrants avoid any situation where their lack of US citizenship maybe exposed.  No way 1 voted let alone millions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Only one option if Trumps lips move or he tweets --&gt; it's a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath Where are the GOP leaders?  They own this too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @marcylauren that's not what his bible says]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>