<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even feel like jacking off anymore. Who am I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants surlys, chur burger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't posted a Butt pic in a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants what do you feel like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops I took too much codeine, hopefully the pain stops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always forget to take prep with food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainly cause I took my underwear off earlier and can't seem to find it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm currently wandering around the house covered by blanket. Little does everyone that I'm naked underneath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having leave Britney alone moments. But I'm Britney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stinastefanie literally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been up since 3am and I can't seem to get some sleep causebpeople in this house keep on talking so loud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgiaoqueef_ should start cancelling that Jenny Craig subscription you got for Xmas huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless the twitter gays for making a troll account tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most exciting part of today was to finally strip down after work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good internet troll is one who doesn't overuse dragqueen jokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love how some people come to twitter and start acting up like stuck up pricks. Like that's gonna help your situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgiaoqueef_ it's always fun to play with amateurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgiaoqueef_ so you're a Sydney queen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't trust accounts with less than 10 followers and 5 tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kay_Daver yes man I'm watching the Ep now and it reminds me of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kay_Daver  can you perform gods and monsters but like the AHS version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A true blessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made pizza for lunch cause there was some dough in the fridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna die rn I'm so bored and tired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANDY_P_S then why you poor? https://t.co/z4rN0SSNDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stinastefanie haha like kms tho cause bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stinastefanie you should tbh I'll give u bread ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I laughed too hard https://t.co/gLjF4Gfoh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@that_cub @mtwhel he said he'll look into it when he wakes to. He's just going to sleep it off for now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MossyKraken when I come home from the club at like 3am the station is always scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtwhel @that_cub all done boys thanks for the help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtwhel @that_cub Fairfield and he spoke with the cops but seems like they brushed it off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants he's at home with a few ice packs and pain killers. He won't say how many guys hit him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants he called the police and they said "we'll look into it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone just stood and watched as he was punched. No police was called.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mate just got bashed at the train station for being gay. When will this stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjp123abc queen of trends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone ever compared Casper the ghost to a sperm cell? https://t.co/FhItOiCJcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So am I like worth 10$ is that what it's come down to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should make a Grindr with my profile saying "sucking dick for 24 nuggets"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JyeKurz what's on the menu?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish KFC delivered but 
A it's 8am 
B they don't deliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so bored y'all please ask me things 
https://t.co/o6v9xq4srn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 12 hour day ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could kms with a bread roll I would https://t.co/XbmNVtVKxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitchy Asshole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so tired wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urbanpitch MY life in one tweet tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urbanpitch snapchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@channelclem they should have a gay version and I'd probably fuck all the guys in the house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't worn a jockstrap in over a month. New year new me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I certainly didn't give him permission to post a photo of my ass on his page. I'd like it to be taken down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eyelovegaga I thought you'd laugh at this https://t.co/grNKIFirbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is la la land worth the hype?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants you truly are as wicked as they come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got chili in my eyes, it's definitely worse than cum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fml I can't get up now cause random boner ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mick7AU new phone who dis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forever remembering those guys who liked you before they before they because popular on twitter and stopped liking your shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up even more tired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally in bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOddBallGay he's calling himself daddy. Saying he's coming for me. A twink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MossyKraken sounds like a murder case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MossyKraken it's a different story if he called me daddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twink just snapchatted me with "daddy is coming for youðŸ˜ˆ"

I'm actually confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why u do this @ twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LachlanRiddle it's only a month away. Some of us have to wait like a year for some shows. Cry me a river and drown me in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hasa81 some things are meant to be â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stinastefanie judging baby gays that sing along to the shows https://t.co/ra8h8KJP7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This heat kills me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hasa81 thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Secret Crush] Your Secret Crush is @Hasa81! Who's yours?
via https://t.co/kJpeXukze6 https://t.co/EjYDQaaOsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Hidden Twin] Your Hidden Twin is @Stinastefanie! Who is yours?
via https://t.co/kJpeXukze6 https://t.co/3UuTtFn4CC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hasa81 next time you're down . Nuggets and sesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burley_chassis do you have any eggs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Handsprings1 calm down with the likes dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Handsprings1 thanks for the support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jawshuare buy me fried chicken and bring over the little mermaid DVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screwing things up is what I do best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@l_ips it's not Christmas time and we're in 40Â°C weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you drop off 7 boxes of panettone when it's not even season for it? https://t.co/H6geA5pKMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4 stages of ejaculation https://t.co/5Lf831oY5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't try to power trip me cause I'll walk out the door]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyways sorry for ranting and not tweeting better things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really bad feelings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and I honestly feel worse about myself eveday due to this. Even some of the things they've said, brings up emotions even thinking about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idk I just feel like trapped in this cloud of constant negativity due to these people in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight is a complete fuck up. I am so pissed off. I'm ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Fanta_Pants the gap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also too poor so stuck in this mess I just wanna goooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stress is too much. I just wanna leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Tells guys has a boyfriend so that they won't bother me 

*also me is single af ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never met these guys ðŸ’€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random guys who have seen me at the bar are asking me if I'm out tonight? how did you get my facebook first of all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urbanpitch what's the bathes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like 7pm but whatever https://t.co/z6z8I7ZiQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigBootyBromo thanks mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANDY_P_S dropping hints about your watersports obsession?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bpacey77 @aetheriun we both know I'm not the smartest guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bpacey77 @aetheriun I think I have his tumblr ðŸ¤”]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>