<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes a "friendly" is a casual exhibition match, usually soccer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow I don't think he's going to be confirmed in the next 10 days. https://t.co/kQBFH4OyBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was promised a rose ceremony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IN HISTORY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 econ paper title. https://t.co/9lOTYewOWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandablount2 this firing was 100% legal, Nixon's was not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHWeissmann @stanveuger @Evan_McMullin from Chaffetz's hometown paper last week https://t.co/lwqH4fZeBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHWeissmann @stanveuger @Evan_McMullin Chaffetz is who he should go after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBlickstein poster board, markers, pink yarn, tin foil, red yarn...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lymanstoneky quick skim of "What Hath God Wrought" suggests that the Nullification Crisis loomed larger in people's minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very special "live" episode! https://t.co/qk5gfYN5cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting some clarification from our own government would be nice. https://t.co/ncpozt76Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've really upgraded representatives since living in @jasoninthehouse 's district. https://t.co/nC7uyxNGeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelight I don't think I got a confirmation reply, so someone else could have done it easily, only record would be letter at election board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelight Possibly. I called the election board, they told me what info was needed: full name, DOB, and address I was registered at 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelight Me too. Until my mom called. "Got your absentee ballot. Should I send it to you or just fill it out?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelight Anybody could have filled it out and submitted and I'd have been on record voting in two different states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelight I did exactly that a few years ago when I was registered in AZ and MA because AZ was still sending an absentee ballot to old addr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencasselman Also: shameless plug for Python in general and my (alpha) econometrics package in particular https://t.co/nFdFwQoidz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencasselman sorry, can't help you there, other than to call rstudio from the command line and try `ps aux --sort -rss` after you've closed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencasselman @rstudio SQL child process that's not getting killed on R close?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lymanstoneky Where are these cheap DC rents you speak of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes The past two presidents (at least) have done "names", though the flavor was definitely different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @lymanstoneky also does nothing for the "in person" count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I didn't realize he's been sucker punched every day since Nov 8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trains coming through Virginia Square have been completely full for hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @MattBruenig mother's demogs at time of birth, esp. age. Hispanic does drop a lot too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pshurst I might create a dummy account so I can like this again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpdatedPriors @graykimbrough If [width=\linewidth] doesn't work, could try the "wrapfig" package. If they allow it. https://t.co/zpI5gcJRsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@p_ganong I think you just solved the puzzle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a fan of promoted tweets, but this is momentous. https://t.co/9dmxaaBJft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @UpdatedPriors I went through this dance recently as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @UpdatedPriors @UpdatedPriors Mathtime is a proprietary font. Use \usepackage{mathptmx} for times roman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prichaaarrrddd @TheRickWilson "In [the] banya there are no generals."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @jm0rt @ernietedeschi Air access and sufficient hotel space. That's basically it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was the first time I skimmed a paper by someone I'd never heard of and they happened to cite me. So that's nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dynarski 19-year-old men who might be interested in doing cool things with helicopters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought this was NBD now? https://t.co/oi36GzLg0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro @Nate_Cohn Yes, from Gordon Wood, "Empire of Liberty": https://t.co/WKiSSxE9LE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModeledBehavior @graykimbrough but will distort consumption of amenities, esp. b/c mostly choosing from existing stock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModeledBehavior @graykimbrough Albouy has an actual optimal taxation paper on targeted housing taxation. Cross-elast's play a big role]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ModeledBehavior @graykimbrough tax sq ft, you'll still have restrictive zoning to keep out "others". Tax value differ'ly, tax oth. things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @ModeledBehavior and housing is a complement to other things (school choice, clean air, child care). Albuoy has working p. 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @ModeledBehavior gaming/enforce. of the def. of "mansion"; durable housing stock; 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jaketapper I would hope that reporters of all people would also remember Anna Politkovskaya in such lists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pro-Trump bots chatting with each other in the replies is the best part of this https://t.co/7NNbnFUfUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpdatedPriors @mckaycoppins I guess I need to spend more time with my family back in "Dixie".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep asking the tough questions! Don't take your eye off the ball! https://t.co/IXGVAGqTK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/Is7myiBnVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who's writing the "Trump's Tweets" behavioral finance paper? https://t.co/ecaHN4QxYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research meets the real world. https://t.co/ocBw888ps0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Papa Putin is gonna be pissed too https://t.co/vwiuzYHLEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The outrage surrounding this is really something. https://t.co/R5WOEoTvTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpdatedPriors Only if your line is the right color. Everyone knows you red-liners are just taking us orange-liners' jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpdatedPriors can't decide if the lack of Mussolini references in this thread is good or bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin This is the quickest way to kill the Clean Air Act and most other environmental regulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunterschwarz Given most people just vote for their team, the dissent was pretty stark: https://t.co/3AFpsJtotg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to all those voting machines Clinton had rigged during the primaries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is "Drain the swamp" https://t.co/94bdbp3UYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@captainhurst I don't see him as a "quitter" though. I was actually saying I think he'll just turn himself into a figurehead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@captainhurst I'll take that bet. Way easier to hand everything off to Pence. As he said "most powerful VP ever."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nate_Cohn Let's not forget the segregationist third-party flare-ups, e.g., 1968.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stanveuger it's been how many *hours* since the waves of "I can't believe we let him lead us around like that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedKolko how much of this is driven by increased residential segregation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A *bit* hypocritical, yes. But let's not shame improvements. https://t.co/1Qq5n6ORno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White supremacy doesn't exist." I'm done with Facebook for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really didn't have time in my schedule this week for the apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddpaolella @Roberton3Will @RobertStavins If only there was evidence that pollution's FX are significantly worse than currently thought...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough This is straight bias. No robust, clustering, or even IV (probably) is going to save you from this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickconfessore @jbarro just b/c county *shares* flipped doesn't mean voters flipped. Simul. movement in/out of voting at least as likely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ddpaolella @RobertStavins Increase focus on co-benefits? As long as coal doesn't get burned, "why" doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyleransom @JeffDenning @DataIsBeautiful that explains the "missing" '12 guys but it's still not record turnout. Had to be blank ballots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffDenning I've been noisy about finding out who these missing Obama voters were. Eager to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffDenning comparing a few Ohio counties, there definitely wasn't record turnout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffDenning been wondering this, too. The "record turnout" I saw was record local turnout or "wow long lines".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianCAlbrecht @iarroyo48 @ashnavabi In campaign, signing on is legitimizing him. That incentive gone. CEA spot an opportunity to do good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiveThirtyEight But what about the *levels*? Where did she lose in *levels* relative to 2012? Was the Midwest more R, fewer D, or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have not seen anything about the demographics behind the Obama '12 to Clinton '16 voter drop. Anyone??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is conflating levels and percentages, though. Where were the missing *Democrats* this year? https://t.co/boiqh6t4zS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's been a lot about the low Democrat turnout, but I haven't seen anything about the demographics/geog of those who stayed home. Anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough not going to dominate but that marginal group should be enough to keep James O'Keefe out of the cabinet. will still suck tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough McCain's gotta be done after this term, right? He always comes back to the center after elections. There's Flake + others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graykimbrough @jbarro That's the point of this thread: republicans only have narrow majority and enough even-keeled among them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins Once upon a time, slaveholders wanted to get extra representation for their non-voting slaves...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@stanveuger I feel like half my re-tweets are from you. Could you stop with the awesome content so I can stop tweet-stalking you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littledeadbird The *vast* majority just vote for their team, regardless, which was true this year---except in UT: https://t.co/3AFpsJtotg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littledeadbird It's bittersweet for me. On the one hand, it's an obvious affront to everything good. On the other hand...1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So do the *majority* of Americans. In the insanity of the man himself, this rare historical fact is being lost in t… https://t.co/4cwzCvMB86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to friends back home about what they thought, what they had heard, has been very enlightening. In the worst… https://t.co/WDLyGZeoqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with "real" people sticking it to the "elites" like this is that doesn't dissuade elites from thinking… https://t.co/IHg2006Eaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins torn between "they best resisted a simple party-line vote" and "omg 2/3 of Mormons voted for Lilburn Boggs"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGreatCorbini his people, who took away his Twitter access, are definitely aware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting back to our roots as Americans. 3/5ths, NE-KS, Lincoln/Douglas, Reconstruction, 19th amendment, segregation. https://t.co/7dREIwjduo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbjardine A default/renegotiation will fix that right up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stanveuger Right after we abolish the EPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbjardine I'm somewhat familiar. Though as Keynes said, "In the long run we're all dead. Unless you're Estonia or Ukraine, then medium-run"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter just woke up. Bad dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow this is Thomas Jefferson's fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jbjardine Only consolation: tomorrow, when over-60 vote that broke for Trump 3-to-1 look at their 401(k). Will prob blame Obama anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where his being a pathological liar might actually become a benefit. https://t.co/lf3seipCUE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>