<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@NekittaM thank you my sister thank you you are beautiful soul I appreciate the follow up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pastor Leonard Smith I hope all is well @your church and you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themzbc Wow, too much of that going on,  its so so sad. In some cases these churches not following God's plan an autopsy is needed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEREALDEALBLUE are you all suppose to be here at Constitution Hall Valentine's Day with a group doo wop entertainment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ginabowser1313 hi Robin welcome to Twitter I hope you're doing well I saw you earlier today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gladbell Gladys this lady has so much guts and I'm loving her response! She is an example to anyone else who understands the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Catherine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbynLovegood love the support thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmonds_turner hey my gurl, how are you! Welcome to twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring Fever - 2017 1st All White Upscale Studded Soiree * Adults 40+ Grown &amp; Sexy! Dress 2 Impress  The Biggest Al… https://t.co/XCMzwWyQCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am attending the Small Business Administration seminar on loans from 5-35000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A First White Soiree Party 2017, Best &amp; Only Sanctioned Frankie Beverly &amp; Maze Tribute Band Dress 2 Impress ♢ Sultr… https://t.co/pGjRLvzwJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnieSimpson @mymajic1023 @Chillerspeak @COMICCOP Please share with all your Frankie Beverly lovers in da house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mobetta77 @IAMANITABAKER Anita never give up, take care of your self, dont let anyone get in your head. You still have so much to give!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spoonthedrummer Please share with all your Frankie Beverly lovers in da house https://t.co/lZyWsz9qoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanBowser Your right living wages not poverty wages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely you can not come at God just any kind of way. We must remember who He is &amp; who we are! https://t.co/2e3pJ9x3aJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanBowser Upscale Event the Mature Grown Sexy 40+ Get your Tickets  Now best seating! This is the only band sanctioned by Frankie Beverly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnieSimpson Upscale Event 4 Mature Grown &amp; Sexy 40+ Get Tickets Now 4 best seating! This is the only band sancti… https://t.co/cSeLafw4Y8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upscale Event for the Mature Grown and Sexy 40+ Get your Ticket Now for best seating! This is the only band sanctio… https://t.co/MOXI0b9B2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FBCNB4000 @PastorDuaneKay sharing with,all mt friends and social media marketing outlets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IdaCampbell please share this event thank you warmly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Break the cold winter with Spring Groove and Funk Save the date with one of the Prolific Sanctioned Tribute bands p… https://t.co/nJDkWIFGIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCHFA @MayorBowser I am Ida Campbell with TriState AEC,  I would love to become a part of this effort. 30 yrs of Real Est Exp&amp;Construction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next Saturday celebrate Martin Luther King Jr Weekend LadyMary&amp;IndaHouseBand with Wpfw89.3fm IdaCampbell, Tom Newma… https://t.co/YWKByxLU2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Sis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing with Jazz phenomenal saxophonist Ronnie Laws I feel like making love. It was an awesome experience https://t.co/5PK7mVngmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been added as a special guest vocalist for this show. I am so happy and humbled! https://t.co/IF5gkol5jE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone https://t.co/BXg9ylrEJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanosbo1 @MsMichelWright @justsunee @ladyMickeyH @jazzy10_pamela Merry Christmas @RickiDOVE @COMICCOP @DonnieSimpson @AlwaysAskAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaylaaBlackwell @nytimes I admire this man I think he was a good soul and 1/4 that everyone recognized]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best Jazz is@ Bethesda Blues Jazz Saxophonist Ronnie Laws December 14th showtime  8pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LethalWeapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenplusportia @TheRock @Eagles @JonDorenbos I love the rock he is just so confident all men should be that way as well as women!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenplusportia @TheEllenShow @portiaderossi love that strong statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be interviewing Jeanette Harris Jazz Saxophonist coming to the Bethesda Blues and Jazz club November 17, 2016 7pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IdaCampbell on air interviewing music blues and pure fun on the air right now 89.3 FM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJDIRTYRICO thankyou, you are a wonderful personality and true to your community, thanks for all you do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamalhbryant Yes Yes thank you this is my mantra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themzbc @RevYayaB MtZionBaptistChurchis the one in Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themzbc @RevYayaB Strong Afro-American Churches build strong communities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong Afro-American Churches build and uplift strong communities! First Baptist Church of North Brentwood MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My gurl Petra Martin and I #Fbc110yrcelebrationof community service https://t.co/GTYMOR6wWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing 8 yrs ago@Old Towne Bowie Inn in Bowie, Maryland https://t.co/ahfJmxDAYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCist I like New Columbia however whatever makes it happen it happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBKingMuseum @acltv Yezzzzzzz So so proud of the King of Blues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayorBowser  cont'd&lt; they need the $$$ that is nonsense not to have these events exempt! They're not working on tracks @midnite mk no sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayorBowser Since the public is the third party assisting in footing the rates hikes public hearing should be held and this voted on they &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtfolsom @leonardnsmith @popemuzick @WWJimmieDo @tlenayebi So tru esp if your not yge 1 causing the issue/hell! Hello]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamalhbryant @DrChrystal1 Pastor McKissick spoke of your mutual friendship! I love it when truth is spoken fr the pulpit.  Oh how blessed !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamalhbryant @DrChrystal1 yes this is so true...Pastor Jamal Pastor McKissick spoke @FBC of NBRENTWOOD Md...Such a spiritual message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevYayaB @leonardnsmith @themzbc cont'd...Not listening 2 his wd....his guidance&amp;direction &amp;applyn his wd daily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevYayaB @leonardnsmith @themzbc true and not so true...some of the mess is what we have created x being human, not listening 2 his wd 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FFBehavior @PJNorwood thats a beautiful statement...My son is a Firemen and Pharamedic in Prince George County Md! I love that young man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mymajic1023 @Vaneese wow is this really true I hope so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnieSimpson @mymajic1023 @Chillerspeak @COMICCOP hey Donnie, that's my gurl too Carmen is such a star!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow happy baby happy life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGuys I'm a Blues band in Washington DC who do I talk to about playing at Buddy Guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow At least you know who you are and happy! See the thing is to not let pep's judge you 4 being the extraordinary,do ubaby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VUL1886 @leonardnsmith @1PreachingQ @Jacques_Boyd @NapoleonAbram ok what are the pins for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@930Club cool looking forward to vis6for the first time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mymajic1023 @Vaneese yes go with it. That show is juvenile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leonardnsmith Many Happy Birthday blessings to you sir, Servant and keeper of the flock! May our savior keep u wra… https://t.co/EIGKXLc4LB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yr Invited 2 First Baptist Church of North Brentwood MD 110yr old Epic celebration Revival 3 days 10-3/5-2016, Bishop McKissick fr Florida]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZemiraJones Spread the word on how you did! Its an awesome achievement!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnieSimpson Hey Soul Man, thank you 4 the follow my friend. Listen someX's 89.3fm Dont 4get the Blues 12-1pm Friday's...We keep u laughn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraButlerTru yes come out and support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Legendary Musicians&amp;Friends with Ms.IdaCampbell performs, Blues,Jazz&amp;R&amp;B support Live Music my friends https://t.co/4ekwZDRaBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND Spoon is a phenomenal drummer organizer of three outstanding bands....I'm glad yr in his life Gladys....great support sis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gladbell Thanks my sista that means I alot to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND Yes WeAreOne is the absolute band for making music No 1 Oh my goodness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Absolutely I just became Election Official in the Satae of Virginia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAMJHUD @DavidOtunga yes develop his organizational &amp; management &amp; thinking skills...so proud of baby boy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gladbell Hey sis so good to see Gladys the band was on top tonight wonderful event!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND @IdaCampbell @silkysoulmusic @COMICCOP @DonnieSimpson Awesome Phenomenal Tribute Band don't miss it ....its on Live now  !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND See you all tomorrow for a wonderful concert !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND love&amp; 
respect this brotha for sure, he has accomplished  much, married &amp; a true family man.Brothas be righteous represents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WAOTRIBUTEBAND @IdaCampbell Yeesssss such an honor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AronoffOFFICIAL @VenetianVegas Amazing so happy for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spoonthedrummer @IdaCampbell Yes listen in to the show we are wild and crazy in a good way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spoonthedrummer @WAOTRIBUTEBAND you are to kind! But it gonna to be fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MHSdodgers1976 Welcome to Tweeter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow that baby is really enjoying his-her dreams!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBKingMuseum what the location on the planet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows Tulsa man had hands up before police shooting | WTOP https://t.co/2pdhtIaS3Q via @WTOP as a former federal agent its ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow oh yeah he does not want this job just yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Hey My sista fr another Ellen, young lady is so talented her major Graphdes I would love 4her 2 met u https://t.co/UY4H4DEjIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Oh yes, Courtney Lovette 2nd yr student @UMBC Graphic designer needs your help She drew this just4U https://t.co/hBUWa5fMOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSGenove @leonardnsmith @APSDrew Also we as an extended church must find a way to nuture their young minds and experiences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJAphotogRaphy @themzbc @leonardnsmith Amen, amen so it is so much easier when you believe, know 4 yoself that you have a comforter 24/7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSGenove @leonardnsmith @APSDrew future visionaries and architects, builders of the future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BluesMagazine this piv looks like Slam Allen an amazing Blues Artist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ssimmons276 wow I hope he is better, he is too cute to be sick! I could not help it the Holy Spirit was so in that plave OMGoodness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ssimmons276 hey sis how are you great service today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACrochan hello Al, Good to see you on Twitter how is Carolyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Address for first Baptist Church of North Brentwood MD 4000 Wallace Rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Baptist Church of North Brentwood MD live now Job Fair, learn job skills, resume building and everything you need to secure a career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBKingMuseum Hi Ida Campbell from Dont4GettheBlues on Fri 12-1pm played BBKing 4-1full hr.my listners were elated!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WindyCityBlues Is this a paying gig or everything on the band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leonardnsmith Miscommunication &amp; understanding often happens cause folks aren't hear'n enti  message, take personal etc restore is on them]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>