<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: How to watch Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Time, TV, live stream, matchups, line, pick https://t.co/u7kaotq1Lw https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Roger Goodell: NFL 'is moving on' from Deflategate https://t.co/vJ4pEWYsDZ https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Why Doug Gottlieb says Tom Brady isn't the greatest, even with Super Bowl win https://t.co/8y1AfaJ470 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Atletico Madrid-Barcelona: Suarez takes on the world and scores goal for the ages https://t.co/u5q3WyPc2J https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We promote #football players to all pro leagues. Get noticed by the #NFL #CFL #AFL. Signup today.  https://t.co/Huxk0hH7Fg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Steelers running back Le'Veon Bell might need surgery to repair injured groin https://t.co/i0aBGD3vz6 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Phoenix Open picks: Jordan Spieth looks to upend Justin Thomas and end his run https://t.co/nM0xQdJoD2 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Michelle Wie joins Callaway after Nike leaves hard golf goods industry https://t.co/EYjJ5b2Ofj https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Tiger Woods discusses Roger Federer, says plan is always to win tournaments https://t.co/PQ4uAT4xR0 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Matt Barnes reportedly turns himself in to NYPD for nightclub altercation https://t.co/GoC4eFsmE6 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Raiders to officially host Patriots in Mexico City in 2017 NFL season https://t.co/C3n1fOd8zk https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: WATCH: Young golf fan freaks out over Jon Rahm's tournament-winning eagle https://t.co/r1h8m14mg0 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Roger Goodell's answers at 2017 Super Bowl will only make Patriots fans angrier https://t.co/c7Ct5ks1zS https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: A quiet Final Four contender, Maryland has everyone fooled -- including Vegas https://t.co/XJtmVCcsqc https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Copa del Rey 2017 first leg: Atletico Madrid vs. Barcelona live score,… https://t.co/vvJOZ4TBBe https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Lions have a new color scheme, will unveil a new uniform set in April https://t.co/bfOnP99ndV https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Head of NFL Referees Association complains about players' referee complaints https://t.co/kqrPf1bdIK https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: National Signing Day: Jarez Parks finally commits to Alabama after strange day https://t.co/jTZVgG7YrH https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way to reach passionate sports fans is to let us tweet your message to our 85K followers. #NFL #MLB #NBA #NCAA  https://t.co/s2IOy7ZZd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Former refugee Loul Deng speaks out on Trump's travel and immigration ban https://t.co/vTL6kz6Woc https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Raiders to host Patriots in Mexico City next season https://t.co/0kD4lAS2TH https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: MLS Expansion: Here's what to know about the 12 cities to submit franchise bids https://t.co/dA4FYD3k0g https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: National Signing Day: Alabama keeps reloading with five-star DE LaBryan Ray https://t.co/07rps3DUuo https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Low risk, high reward? Champion Cubs trade for a former top prospect arm https://t.co/PBL87WPArI https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: LSU makes a splash with addition of four-star DE K'Lavon Chaisson https://t.co/zzvFOMHq3c https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: San Diego interested in pursuing the Raiders if 'Vegas falls through' https://t.co/Y9ey4hDEbL https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Top 10 NCAA Tournament resumes: UNC makes debut, has brutal schedule ahead https://t.co/nzShQJGpiJ https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl: Dwight Freeney perfectly sums up why Tom Brady is 'aggravating' https://t.co/MibObLH4Yh https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: WATCH: Tiger Woods hits shots into ocean at Seven-Star hotel in Dubai https://t.co/Nd7FKZDIfi https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: College Basketball Player of the Year rankings: Malik Monk jumps into top 10 https://t.co/z4tNA2XqM0 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: USC's huge National Signing Day push anchored by blue-chip OT Austin Jackson https://t.co/3OBoCGTWHw https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Brady or Belichick? NFL stars on the key to Patriots' Super Bowl dynasty https://t.co/QzzCburylg https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Michigan State recruit cannot sign on National Signing Day because he's in jail https://t.co/RkzbOMGatG https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Heat's Dion Waiters channels his inner Kobe Bryant to defend his shot selection https://t.co/GBeWaXzk4E https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Browns still interested in Garoppolo, but at what price? https://t.co/fozgEKltVA https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We did something crazy! We uploaded our entire How to Become a #Sports Agent #Video Course for #free on #youtube.  https://t.co/guTa9Zf75H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Tim Brown: Tom Brady not starter without Tuck Rule https://t.co/9rw9cirDno https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Le'Veon Bell still determining need for groin surgery https://t.co/ymVxgDy3Dn https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: MLB Hot Stove: Five free-agent signings that should happen, but probably won't https://t.co/TNPfMY158H https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Northwestern, NCAA seek to dismiss basketball player's lawsuit over transfer… https://t.co/XfOpHjpX9s https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: WATCH: 4-star Henry Ruggs commits to Alabama with heartfelt tribute to late… https://t.co/vYqZIAkNbm https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: LOOK: Super Bowl 2017 ticket prices are plunging for Patriots vs. Falcons https://t.co/j7ha4L70xq https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: College basketball rankings: Creighton reenters Top 25 (and 1) with statement https://t.co/gzJFxUyRrN https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Falcons' Jalen Collins: 2017 Super Bowl will be won on field, not with experience https://t.co/ikHce50WTc https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: New 49ers GM John Lynch once heaped praise on Kirk Cousins https://t.co/5bTz7KwE8H https://t.co/RIpFK6EvHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Why Lonzo Ball isn't the surefire NBA superstar people seem to think he is https://t.co/DEmTvESsUd https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Who is Kobe Buffalomeat: Illinois State lands 6-foot-7 OL on National Signing Day https://t.co/s7ONyJjqg9 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: National Signing Day: Ex-Michigan commit Aubrey Solomon still signs with… https://t.co/j1cfo7YhKa https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Larry Fitzgerald has made his decision about 2017 but isn't ready to talk https://t.co/OVv2beTojc https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Here's the top offseason priority for the 30 NFL teams not in Super Bowl https://t.co/veXGP7qgc0 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: LOOK: Alabama recruit has a touching moment with announcement from cemetery https://t.co/WS3eXYuDQr https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product demo #videos help increase sales. We shoot awesome videos that go viral on #socialmedia.  https://t.co/LiLWbktHuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Brandon Marshall done lobbying for New York Jets QBs https://t.co/fVipjRJuq8 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: J.J. Watt cleared for football activities, has 'new fire' https://t.co/rZLsxB12Dt https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: J.J. Watt: 'There's a brand new fire' in me https://t.co/3aC8Y2mj4u https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Tom Brady's mother has reportedly been ill for the past 18 months https://t.co/nPsmykV5jV https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: LB Levi Jones trolls Florida, Florida State with T-shirt commitment to USC https://t.co/jSjstEB1h6 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Super Bowl halftime show rankings: From terrible to transcendent, 50-1 https://t.co/5e42gulC0J https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: UCLA's Lonzo Ball isn't the surefire NBA superstar people seem to think he is https://t.co/DEmTvESsUd https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: When is 2017 Super Bowl: Schedule, time, date, TV channel for Patriots vs.… https://t.co/7O1LjNYNKp https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: List of previous Super Bowl halftime performers: Lady Gaga set to join U2, Prince https://t.co/VvOSacyCvi https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Brandon Marshall done lobbying for Jets QBs https://t.co/45qf3nFEVx https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 NFL playoff schedule: Times, dates, TV for every single postseason round https://t.co/e2LoIxfJ0m https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: List of previous Super Bowl MVP winners: Brady seeks his fourth trophy vs.… https://t.co/uQEZRjNOD0 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Van Noy on trade to Patriots: 'I'm in a better spot now' https://t.co/ZYTg8q77to https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: List of previous Super Bowl champions: Patriots seek fifth title, Falcons eye… https://t.co/2Xtz8d77iP https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: NFL playoffs bracket: Patriots vs. Falcons in great 2017 Super Bowl matchup https://t.co/DLaBtna6h6 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: No cable? How to watch 2017 Super Bowl online with Apple TV, Roku, Xbox One, more https://t.co/wCoVUnfJZI https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl: Ranking all 50 Super Bowls, from worst to first https://t.co/fFkk1mnV71 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl: Country star Luke Bryan set to sing national anthem https://t.co/3Un8dDi45x https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl tickets: From the cheapest tickets to the outrageous https://t.co/HHTLt9nP48 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl halftime show: Here's a sneak peek what of Lady Gaga is planning https://t.co/lh62GMP6Wg https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of your boring #job? Go after your dream and start working in #sports. Learn more about this opportunity.  https://t.co/exg16fFIXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Latest 2017 Super Bowl commercials: Watch leaked ads, best and worst of all time https://t.co/Bi9tApAqto https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: What's the weather forecast for 2017 Super Bowl: Updates for Patriots vs. Falcons https://t.co/R3iQHvgK8A https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl bet: How long will Luke Bryan take to sing national anthem? https://t.co/RoPcukQ7aM https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl prop bets: Here's 51 of the weirdest things you can bet on https://t.co/gGst06Ymdh https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Jerry on Romo situation: If I can make everybody happy, I should be president https://t.co/AxDuwjtsfZ https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Where is 2017 Super Bowl: Location, time, date for Patriots vs. Falcons showdown https://t.co/OAC3bfo8DF https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Who is playing in Super Bowl 2017: Team rosters for Patriots, Falcons, how to… https://t.co/7NNLCJ1SCK https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 National Signing Day live blog, recruiting rankings, commitments https://t.co/1BEOPz5JeI https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Steve Addazio kicks off his 2017 National Signing Day as Salt Bae https://t.co/kFnrV3dttY https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Dante Scarnecchia's return, approach keys Pats' O-line revival https://t.co/O4DBYjDFwx https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Patriots' Chris Long was pursued heavily by Lions https://t.co/tNAUe1UUdx https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 National Signing Day announcement times, schedule, TV channel, live stream https://t.co/oCv8aNz5oa https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Five things to know about the Baylor-Kansas game that might decide the Big 12 https://t.co/qQEW5UA8Qw https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Iowa State drifting toward NCAA Tournament bubble after West Virginia loss https://t.co/UdfKVFdPMg https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Malik Monk's heroic performance pulls Kentucky out of its losing streak https://t.co/3RVajZd5No https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Redskins Wire: Kory Lichtensteiger Will Almost Certainly Be A Cap Casualty This… https://t.co/H6MJ3VdDw4 #NFL https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Brent Musburger's last game: Broadcasting legend signs off from Rupp Arena https://t.co/6Ecx2By8pS https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Maryland wins at Ohio State; now why aren't the 20-2 Terps getting any love? https://t.co/CNiW6nFTe8 https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: NBA Trade Rumors: Cavs reportedly interested in Mavs' Deron Williams https://t.co/41w1VLQI2O https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a professional female spokesperson #video for your #business? Use #videomarketing to grow your #sales.  https://t.co/C5OzGHpbi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl: No one can replicate Patriots' way of building a franchise https://t.co/luii9izQDA https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Rashad Jennings: Giants 'left our defense hanging' https://t.co/3p6yyoLjON https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are professional #socialmedia managers. Custom #marketing campaigns. Engaging Daily Content. Audience… https://t.co/DbM2BEZMkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: 2017 Super Bowl: Falcons hit big on draft picks to construct a winner quickly https://t.co/4UFqrhMUxz https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: Carmelo Anthony speaks in third person to address recent trade rumors https://t.co/V4TVNXv3aa https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: WATCH: Ohio State's Thad Matta spits out gum yelling, doesn't break character https://t.co/c1KEIojJVb https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFL Wire: When is 2017 Super Bowl: Schedule, date, time TV channel for Patriots vs. Falcons https://t.co/7O1LjNYNKp https://t.co/RIpFK6W6z5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>