<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains Was so busy all day I didn't see this until now. Delighted - the week just got a lot better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Exactly...what I fear is that this is just laying the groundwork for things to get much, much worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Now that really is asking for trouble...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galway looking extremely fancy today https://t.co/whyAQ6Vm1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus we have a new area focusing on the events of 1917...weekend plans, anyone? https://t.co/xP2zUAx4hT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @nerve_centre @Creative_100_  resources looking v impressive in our @NLIreland WWIreland exhibition https://t.co/9G73JeABCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 135th Birthday Mr Joyce! And Happy 95th Anniversary of Publication Day to your big blue book. https://t.co/ijGFwGll6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry After I first ran 10k someone in work said - "well, if you can do it, anyone can." Truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry Oh, you are so capable of it! The feeling of being able to run when previously you couldn't is pure joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMagennis A year later, this remains one of the funniest things I have ever read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First outing of the year coming up this Saturday...looking forward to being back on the road #mayogaa https://t.co/lEKMtuyqXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys Increasingly unsure how many more days any of us are going to last, to be honest...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pohara And values -hard work, decency, recognition of the worth of others - that seem in starker relief than ever this weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane I think he would hate the absolute desertion more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maria_Brid Maybe you just look very chic and French? Try joining the gym in Trinity! The oldest people there are literally half my age...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maria_Brid Were you time traveling again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane He's saving something up for Week 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woop woop - nail biting following this on Twitter...â¤ï¸ðŸ’šâ¤ï¸ðŸ’š https://t.co/BHovHiPMK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oliverburkeman That is the perfect encapsulation of what I have been trying to articulate to myself all weekend. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mamster Which may not be a ringing endorsement, but on the plus side our President is a left-wing poet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mamster Much better than it used to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mamster Come live with us here in Ireland! We love a fiery rant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have just added gin and Campari to my shopping list #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packed house here @NLIreland for Helen Shenton of @tcdlibrary speaking as part of our "Library Matters" series. https://t.co/xlMeobLtD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to be @DubrayBooks for the launch of our lovely friend @aocdotme 's book #thehappymedium https://t.co/r5sbY9ql0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieSadlier Your secret's safe with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieSadlier Although, thinking about it, it might dramatically reduce the interviewee pool if people keep leaving as weeping wrecks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieSadlier Fantastic, illuminating interview with @lukefitz11 . Make sure to make the next guy cry though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robinsonmj07 Congratulations! Hope you and the crisps had a very happy day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinmcdon @NiamhNiB @CMoonDL @caitlinnicg Wow, that's quite the coincidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrenchfoodieinD There is the lovely @HanselGretel_ie on Clare Street...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussion for @firstfortnight on migration at @david_monahan's Beyond Leaving" exhib at the Photographic Archive https://t.co/k25WiIOctm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Perhaps some kind of mutually beneficial swapping arrangement? More than happy to help you out ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gusclaw You're on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes Hilarious, and touching, plus musical numbers! What's not to love? xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes I watched the whole series on flights to and from Australia, and it was the only thing they kept me from going MITH altogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gusclaw I am aiming for the Dublin Marathon - perhaps we can knife each other? ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnauldwebster Can't beat the west of Ireland! Happy New Year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OlwenCD The 4 stages of returning from the cattery: Ignoring - Furious Staring - Needy Meowing - Return to Standard Indifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieharrower ðŸ˜¢ Lots of fluids, and staying in bed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janholmquist Happy New Year Jan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's to fizz and friends and kindness - and standing together to fight any battles we need to in 2017. https://t.co/y5NYBygRae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner Such fond memories of reading your book in France last summer. Thanks, and here's wishing for a 2017 that's kinder to all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gusclaw Go for it, and enjoy every mile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrNiallMcGarry @DavidsonJenn Our year, Niall! These M&amp;Ms predicted the future https://t.co/H5eCTtV7gB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thawing out from @leinsterrugby match and settling in for cosy NYE at home https://t.co/B78LPxrsqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you see Someone, say Someone's safe"...listening to @BoxOfDelights84 and making mince pies...proper Christmas Eve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughtweet @MaddockCarol Finally something to talk about...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A night of Buffy @SydOperaHouse ...not sure it gets better than this https://t.co/xUzCvbnOrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be here @SydOperaHouse listening to @borrelli tell us how tv got good - and arguing against cultural tiers #BingeFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinmcdon Good shout!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day working in @Library_Vic  It's been lovely! https://t.co/1oTshODw0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineMcGee Yes, til Monday, then on to Sydney. Certainly enjoying so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viktor&amp;Rolf: Fashion Artists @NGVMelbourne utterly beautiful, captivating, witty...loved it. https://t.co/mwRuckd2gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part of my ongoing quest to sample every baked egg in Australia https://t.co/Eyx7CWJKxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MauriceLinnane Too late to be up in Ireland, Mr Linnane!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Alternatively, you could try being in Australia for three weeks - I'm finding that pretty helpful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Take some sweets from a child today - it will help you rebalance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Ah now, you cannot blame Christmas for all the terrible things done in its name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieharrower Sorry/not sorry ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieharrower Hope it all goes really well - sorry I can't be there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@finndelaney Correct use of apostrophes being one of the small pleasures, I take it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't help who we love (seen at the gorgeous Little Lefroy in Fremantle) https://t.co/gZmpiyVjGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what first gave you the idea you were no longer in Ireland? https://t.co/xG5TAU9Z9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorshell Well spotted! Day 1 working out pretty well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinmcdon @RTEOne @jamieheaslip I wish I could â¤ï¸ this multiple times!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieharrower It's extremely bearable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Perth - you're doing a great job so far. https://t.co/Q227l3PKDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 22 hours traveling, total bliss to be clean, lying down, and listening to the sound of the ocean...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia bound! https://t.co/NOjdKj8Kiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous run in Regent's Park this afternoon - London looking wonderful on a perfect, still winter's day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DowClaire What can I say? Bit keen by nature!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mincemeat made, bags packed for Australia, and a magnificent Ireland win. Decent Saturday. https://t.co/ZaktnAiGVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that was something! #IREvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabethcraft Happy Thanksgiving Elizabeth! You and @gretchenrubin bring a lot of joy to people worldwide and we're grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes If he's a God she probably is too. So it's the family business and she probably always expected him to go into it in the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Eoin's always has really good vegetarian dishes in the restaurant @FallonandByrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see so many colleagues at the @conulireland Strategy launch https://t.co/MiXTabQ9s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro God help them, poor creatures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro Plus side, rather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro It is (but on the place side that's a great expression I don't hear often enough in Dublin ðŸ˜œ)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro A rhetorical question, I know...but no, it's just subjecting everyone to the same miserable nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenstrong That's the spin out on it by Trump - cunningly done to divert the news cycle from the University settlement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenstrong It was completely the audience, and only briefly. The cast statement was measured and thoughtful - a long way from harassment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenstrong Yes, there was some mixed applause and booing at the beginning when he came in. The cast statement was at the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now listening to match on the radio...always so tense #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the ref says "we have to accept it", it's not exactly a huge endorsement of the TMO. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady In the small cunning mind of Donald Trump, this diverts attention from the Trump University settlement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the most chilling things I've read. https://t.co/C7YYV1vutG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sabriste Assume it's a deliberate distraction by Trump to divert the news cycle away from the Trump University settlement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sabriste @HamiltonMusical @BrandonVDixon And they were not remotely rude - read a very open and measured statement. More lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner Glad to know you're in a better place. I loved your book, and thanks for sharing your journey, which can be painful and scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane But in truly excellent news, Bannon believes he is channeling Thomas Cromwell. Please, nobody tell him how that ended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'll be watching #IREvNZL in town tomorrow on my own. Suggestions for where gratefully received!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnauldwebster Post-truth, alt-right...these sound like intriguing postmodern ideas, rather than what they really are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughtweet Wouldn't that be nice! More an attack of infuriating clumsiness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life advice: consider not breaking a glass into 8 million tiny bits just before leaving for work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane Good gig at the moment. Plenty of work on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a tough day/week/year? Try these 42 beautiful seconds to help offset it. https://t.co/xYHAzLiuUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnauldwebster My only aspiration left for 2016 is that I make it to the end of year without my head exploding...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>