<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are getting pretty bleak when the game on your phone feels the need to tell you it supports human rights https://t.co/z5sM6zko1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've basically given up on washing my hair so now when I do I get tons of compliments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so impressed that Levin has its own snapchat filter https://t.co/5PRk8Se1zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my flatmate's mirror fell over and broke but I'm the one who found it, is that seven years of bad luck for me or for her? The household?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I am so excited for the future https://t.co/ctWywHT0nv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coworker just told me, in a tone of genuine confusion, that he thought Russia had been disestablished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorkSubway thanks Nurul! I did, it was real nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling that ideal post-blood donation feeling of smug but lightheaded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately this means I have finally had to say goodbye to old brace face https://t.co/AsLU97E7VW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can DRIVE on my OWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I passed my restricted driving test which tbh is slightly terrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purplish_tea I think you'll really enjoy it. It's just v nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guys I saw Moana and it's just very uplifting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi sounds worse than the bus tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi I'm on the bus and it's great. They sent the airport bus for some reason and the seats are v comfy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi great excuse to glare at men who don't give you their seat on the bus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a kitkat, an easter egg, a restaurant mint and 20c in a purse I hadn't used in a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official okay well otaki also has mains sewage and they are half that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official how does the internet know the population of stars hollow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official good to know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand how Stars Hollow doesn't have mains sewage??? Levin has mains sewage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi @purplish_tea too easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I always so much more flushed after one beer than five?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi not an acceptable use of my gherkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really has the syntax of a trump tweet whoops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst part is that she uses chips to do it. What a waste!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Em's trying to lure seagulls to attack me again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swam in the sea today instead of work and it was great but now it's six hours later and I'm sunburnt and sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a man wearing a fluro vest carrying a trumpet just walked my house and I am concerned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official it's supposed to start clearing in the afternoon? maybe not maybe this is just the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official do you want to hang out later when the rain stops? I'm bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femmeandfierce I'm off work again tomorrow if you wanna get coffee or something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erst_while don't wash it. Dry shampoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purplish_tea my office is closed until further notice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erst_while that does sound unpleasant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[office is closed 'until further notice' lol sounds ominous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erst_while would that be much worse than a quake when you are anywhere else in your house?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this turned out to be v good forward planning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst damage we had here was a single tiny toy penguin falling off a shelf so all those pictures of the CBD are surreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I went back to sleep they were saying there would be no tsunami so I'm glad I live on a hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whole flat just sitting in the hall wrapped in blankets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuuuuck geonet says that was in christchurch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've considered blocking Tony Veitch on facebook but I like to know which of my facebook friends are interacting with that scumbag's content]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have an excess of cookies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made so many cookies that they don't fit in the biscuit tin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning to drive seems to involve a lot of losing my dad in pak n save]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't feel great about Trump but I'd be pretty alarmed if a https://t.co/mO3VhmKktH petition was enough to overturn a democratic election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought ginger coke because I was intrigued but it just tastes like bad ginger beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel I should cut this bad US customer service rep I'm dealing with some slack but on the other hand capitalism is all they have left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't they make giant family bags of jaffas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official did you just run into her or were you loitering with intent? Did you give her those flowers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are teenagers so much on guy fawkes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like the first attempt at removing your halloween eye makeup is far scarier than whatever you did on purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out dive gear is weird in a car]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi @purplish_tea I also just ordered my first uber! Currently sitting on dark steps on Owen st in cold cos it's ages away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi @purplish_tea I talked to so many strangers I'm EXHAUSTED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I have to get DRESSED and WALK TO THE DAIRY to get twisties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flatmates have returned from holiday and now I have to stop talking to myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official what better way to teach children defence against the dark arts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official lucius malfoy, whose attempts to depose dumbledore show he was clearly a man with only children's best interests at heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purplish_tea @emilu_reidi does she think we're bad influences? I've always wanted to be a bad influence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi I can't remember who I voted for but this is clearly v wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there's a grog called Jean-Bob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix added the swan princess. Today's the day Willie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even bigger call from Lily: '@romana_official should plan your funeral'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emily reckons she's gonna outlive Michael Flatley which seems like a big call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femmeandfierce but also I don't lift things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femmeandfierce my parents are considering buying a ute and I'm sitting my restricted in December]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really sorry everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have cursed what promised to be a glorious day by making it my first no tights work day of the season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official in fact https://t.co/osYwHcdd4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@romana_official this is a thought I have often had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves lots of out of print NZ history/pols books come up cheap on trademe quite regularly, just set an alert for the title]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's this weird continuation of post-imperial panic and it's exhausting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about this is that it's not actually young people who are stressing out about it. Because it's not really about the 'kiwi OE']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't worry! they're only shutting out people who will actually contribute to society!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain makes a terrifying descent into fascism and kiwis are worried about their OE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbasaurusrex @verslibre oh my god I am filled with rage everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god I just saw a penguin as well what a charming walk to work!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The baby seal is back and it's real fucking cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey good advice, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you choose between a bunch of white guys who all say they stand for balanced transport strategies and transparent spending?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femmeandfierce my flatmate is vacuuming :( :( :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@femmeandfierce the youth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I gave up an hour of my weekend for an extra hour of this overcast gloom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Em thinks dirty dancing is better than grease and I think she's wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised ten minutes after leaving the library that the answer to all my problems was obviously agatha christie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a babysitters club style series dedicated to New England quilters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to the chick lit section at the library? That's what I need right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm talking about my mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman with tangerine orange hair just questioned the suitability of my outfit for work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean I would have done it anyway, obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me tell you it is hard to not sign a petition when the school librarian and the woman who taught you to read ask you to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked past my old primary school on the way to work and was accosted by protesting teachers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbasaurusrex excuse you my grandad orders a larger and lime everywhere he goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huazk_zag your tongue is too long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my head hurts and there's no milk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purplish_tea oh my god I still can't believe they were fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know why ivy is full of police???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilu_reidi @romana_official I'm working on it]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>