<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strutty74 @spfl @JamTarts amazing and yes I do... I watched this the other night #justmagic #believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AEW Electrical -  https://t.co/FeLNeCd40z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinburghsport well done Gary! @gilnay  pass on my congratulations... I was hope it was at Tynie tho! Lol xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelsShareEdin Party Lunching tomorrow! Looking forward to it! Mid afternoon boogie... what's not to love?!! ðŸŽ…ðŸ»ðŸŽ„ðŸ¾ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbbmuirhead Amazing night for you lad! Well done and keep it up!! âš½ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸Gâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was fabby last night! Love Scarlett! xx https://t.co/9JNk4kQQvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw sleep sitting up to save you a job in the morning then Babe ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw now are you just off to bed?!  xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems ages since I made a @JamTarts game and was looking forward to it... c'mon lads make it worth sitting out in this weather! â˜”ï¸ðŸŒ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely amazing news!!! #fromthesefoundations #proudandexcited https://t.co/niwJcikved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishchicp great first day then?! Up at sunrise to make the most of it chick xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dannyg31986 wish you many more successes and milestones! #Topbloke #jambosfamily #legend #bunsofsteel ðŸ˜œ xx https://t.co/6e5IIoKTQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MM99Chair where can I find the u13 fuxtures, my niece plays and I've been looking to take in a game but find it hard to find them online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw @lucywalkingshaw NO WAY... So not true!! xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callump7 https://t.co/qYi3GC7R8k another accolade #FIFA17 #HeartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brad_mckay it certainly was well done and to #BillyKing on a great strike good to see you both doing well xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edintravel it's not a bank holiday Lloyds and BoS defo open. It's a public holiday x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw I'm not the into the creepiness either lol Strange Things was addictive even though I was shitting it!! ðŸ™ˆ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw what you watching, we have just finished strange things and the returns both creepy but good, not chosen what to watch next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@on_lothianbuses @LetsJoinEdi  is there issues with wi-fi on the 18 the journey is boring enough but not getting online is ðŸ’© please help! ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw thank-you for visiting Harris and I today! Lovely catch up. Hope you enjoy your bubbles n balls ðŸ˜œ ðŸ¾ðŸ¸ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We do have some idiots in the stands ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/wtRqNJHxXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamTarts a hard game to follow on Twitter ðŸ˜‚ Happy with the result but need to be taking more of the early chances! #welldone #2-1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandSky @brad_mckay Congrats @brad_mckay All the best Inverness Cally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want some #NOW ðŸ¾ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/5gsqUspU9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab chance taken well @Callump7 ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/USSFYcRL1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callump7 congrats on the goal added to your tally! ðŸ‘ðŸ»âš½ï¸ #HMFC4life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@32watto âš½ï¸ Well done and Congrats on your goal! Welcome to the #Jambos #family ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw know you have big plans but hopefully see you over the weekend if not will drop a wee ðŸŽ into Granny or the Strutts x #enjoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw Happy 21st Birthday Girl... Some kisses for youðŸ’‹ðŸ’‹ Have a fab day Soph luv ya ðŸŽ‚ðŸ¸ðŸ’– https://t.co/U1NRSZofeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@32watto @JamTarts thought you were too man! Keep it up âš½ï¸#HMFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmmm #thanks @sophwalkingshaw Home made Taco's!!! ðŸŒ®ðŸŒ®ðŸŒ®... N vodka of course! ðŸ¸ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudiSkacel51 all the best at Raith and welcome back to Scotland! â¤ï¸âš½ï¸ https://t.co/ZLP650UGHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavyWilson #blah #blah #blah play another tune! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavyWilson fuck off part timer!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw so I need my smartcards with me tonight!? ðŸ˜‚ðŸŽŸâ›”ï¸ðŸš·ðŸ™ˆ https://t.co/IKc1X0eOIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw can I have a sub when you do? I'm happy for you to win it if you see me alright ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜œðŸ˜˜ ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a snap shot in time that tells a story if ever I saw it! ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #dempstergivingaroasing #smugmupetrie ðŸ˜œ https://t.co/fo2R7FM3pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Luck @NadeChristian at Stair Park âš½ï¸ https://t.co/JekszfVf62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jordanm72 @Boro brilliant! Congrats and good luck âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw lovely to see DannythePinapple at FBS Glastonbury! He ALIVE @Strutty74 @sophwalkingshaw @LynseyGreenhorn ðŸ˜€ðŸðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry Harris #EUref ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw can I come?! Gavin hate the cinema!! ðŸ™ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilAlexander_1 @AberdeenFC Best of luck (apart from when coming back to Tynie or when we visit the granite city!)  x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSickKids Make sure the guys in the training team dig deep... Tell them I sent you! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw loving them too chick! Glad you had another great day. ðŸ’‹ You all looked lovely ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw where is this heaven you speak of? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw have a fabulous day, lots of photos please! Weather is looking good for it! â˜€ï¸ðŸŽðŸ¾ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw you look fab without Abs... Love what you have hotty ðŸ’ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuckoosBakery Thanks... It's going down well!! ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‚60!! https://t.co/PBPaFVMA8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw mmmm or some of this bad boy... https://t.co/FeIz9EMZnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent #Fraud detection by @RBSGroup efficient text &amp; call service to confirm the declined transactions from my assumed cloned card ðŸ”’ðŸ’³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandSky embarrassed of the state of Hampden. They #hibsed celebrating in the classy style we all know! Minority I know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strutty74 @paulr1tchie totally agree it's a tuff choice! Loveharry xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cutest and most luv for a boy in a hearts jersey since @paulr1tchie don't you think @Strutty74 ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Q8VzxhKa81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸŽ‰Happy Anniversary @JamTarts and my fellow #Jambos! ðŸŽ‰ Amazing memories of that #greatestday ðŸŽ‰ âš½ï¸ â¤ï¸â¤ï¸Gâ¤ï¸ now #thejourneycontinues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ™ a little sad! Wish @NeilAlexander_1 all the very best for the future. Thanks for all your efforts #topkeeper â¤ï¸âš½ï¸ https://t.co/lmQXtjmjpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strutty74 @The_FOH it's really good you love that place so much! ðŸ˜‚ Hope it's a good meeting. #TheJourneyContinues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackveron best of luck for the future! #HMFC â¤ï¸âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSportsound commiserations to @StranraerFC ðŸ˜Ÿ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnSouttar @JamTarts Thanks for all your efforts, have enjoyed seeming you play for the JT's! #HappyHolidays! â¤ï¸âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilAlexander_1 thanks for all your efforts throughout the season Neil. Your girls look rightly proud! Have a lovely break #HMFCâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone explain this yet, thinking I just didn't see what actually happened?! ðŸ¤” https://t.co/YmGovi3oI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SFA ðŸ™ðŸ» work with refereeing staff close season! Many performances have been diabolical! "Doing their best" is clearly not good enoughðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of Luck for the future! âš½ï¸ https://t.co/iSB3jDK25s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hairsandstyles's video https://t.co/vKoc0iaAlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless you have #hibsedit more times than most! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/r2nZcGOE1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely feel sorry for a number of them! ðŸ™ˆ https://t.co/nRPrv738CG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw hey me too! Might shops for a Dress to match ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #heartbreakingly sad ðŸ˜¢ Thoughts are with F&amp;F and colleagues.  https://t.co/18jr07nBb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callump7 congrats on the call up! Thoroughly deserved and about time!! xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw serve a pic so I can be excited too?! ðŸ˜‚ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllasKitchenUK hi, it's from this tesco baby club link. https://t.co/fyAnvOmWIQ TY xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TescoBabyClub @EllasKitchenUK can you make the chicken sausage recipe in advance and freeze them? TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishchicp @Strutty74 @Callump7 we have the RT girls top lad! Hope Harry isn't in bed yet &amp; missed itðŸ˜‚ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strutty74 @Callump7 gutted his fav player hasn't given us a RT yet!! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a wee Jambo's 6th #Birthday today! Harry (@Strutty74 ) would be cheesing if @Callump7 wished him a happy day! ðŸ˜‰ https://t.co/WWRCCaZKN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callump7 @JohnSouttar See your mood hasn't improved Paterson... It's not Souttars fault you missed! ðŸ˜‚âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving watching @LCFC Trophy presentation! Dream of dreams can't wait to see the @JamTarts win the league next season!! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚âš½ï¸âš½ï¸ #believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophwalkingshaw could be worse you could have @GavyWilson for company! #adultlife ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishchicp BELIEVE... It could be us next season (not the EPL ThoughðŸ˜‚) Can't even imagine the scenes! â¤ï¸ðŸ™ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nic_200 aw go Dixie... Shame that you will be demented by both sounds! ðŸ™‰ #chin-up ðŸ’ž xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WELL DONE #LeicesterCity #CHAMPIONS ðŸ¾âš½ï¸ðŸ†ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/A2ZsRlzjvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #honeymoon in 2013 we has a corner room, stunning panoramic view #takemebackâ¤ï¸ https://t.co/Z9aB4ndPqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishchicp @Strutty74 @sophwalkingshaw I fancy it just need to check with he who thinks he is boss ðŸ˜˜ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liamsmith_29 Congrats in securing your place in the 1st team squad! Deserved and shows again how hard work and determination pays off! âš½ï¸ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[âš½ï¸ðŸŽ‰ðŸ†CONGRATS Gary and all @EastFifeFC Worthy champions!! ðŸ¾ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/z11WReE2dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear oh dear... Same again Cummings!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜³ðŸ™ˆ Who will Hibes it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw Well Done @DylanMcGowan91 âš½ï¸ðŸ† @Dannyg31986 lead them on Captain you can do it! ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/NgqYnn4SIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go with the flow, don't try to follow all the advice given so kindly by others #aceit https://t.co/IzE9Od8W6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And what about the Jambos?!! #Europebound https://t.co/97jj0Mfzxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @JamTarts way!!!  https://t.co/Faq2YoZWpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passports at the ready! The @JamTarts are going to #Europe â¤ï¸âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck #Jambos Kick on from Friday!! â¤ï¸âš½ï¸ https://t.co/TuBbVGqEFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon too right. An absolute shambles!! @Edinburgh_CC need to step up as well as whoever signed off the work in the first place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strutty74 @pieandbov I've picked it too! ðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnSouttar you played brilliant! Well done!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @MudpieFridays and @Trunki Harris loves his new ðŸ’™Made for Me Trunki... #winner https://t.co/7yovFAzR7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jade__Richards @MallowValley or @A_Cheesecakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotchWhiskyExp we have memberships from a previous visit can you confirm what privileges they entitle us to? I can't remember? Thx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>