<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[having nobody to send your pics to is the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwatchTheThrone lol I got the memo. I'm going today ðŸ˜¬ thank you ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CierraTaviaa @Amun_Kotokoli thank you ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amun_Kotokoli lmao I haven't been to either mall in yearsðŸ˜‚ which one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is better? Tysons, or arundel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people only contact you when they want something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause ain't nobody else bout to build it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump keep talking about building this wall. Not to sound racist but who he gonna get to build it for the low? ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKRoseMARIE of course i did but you have to call me. i be forgetting to reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKRoseMARIE phone on DND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinceVanGo94 I meant to say some. And I have so many reasons ðŸ˜© I've personally seen it ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[starting to think black men hate black women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my sis cooking for me before I leave ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that looks like me but it's dominique ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[family goals ðŸ’• https://t.co/TVmteGxzYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 days off ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cut so much out of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's something so exciting about crushing on someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i always was a cut line type of bitch at the gogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really think ur heaven sent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offset need to hurry up and come get me ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stand Hilary Clinton ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being 21 has been the absolute worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can say I'm truly tired of niggas treating me like shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickey escaped jail ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I get back to school I'm binge watching masters of sex ðŸ˜¬ love that show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate not driving to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that I work downtown today is blowing me ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trying to figure out how I'm bout to get to work for these next two days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I really want these name earrings but i don't know where to get them from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna be alias together ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would've memorized that number if I was the waitress ðŸ˜‚. Offset is baeðŸ˜Œâ¤ï¸ https://t.co/GWytTmmzL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my wings are made of plastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he gives me diamonds for my time and now i own baguettes ðŸ’Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i got a nigga out of oakland,he be ridin for me. gives me head til I'm dead then i ride him to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this year i will have a candy pink jeep. mark my words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just leave them guessin, then move on to the next one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bitch im taking calls, no small talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But in the mean time, I'll just run this bag upðŸ¤‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can wait til I meet my ride or dieâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ChocolateeMelt send me your number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I be pressed when starboy comes on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to be pressed to scan pics from the gogo ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want a boyfriend so I can get his name in some big gold hoops.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My next car will be a jeep, then that g-wagonðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKRoseMARIE if I seen your text I would reply. I don't check my text cause my boost be dryðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If  Neil birthday wasn't coming I would be right back at school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to go back to my apartment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frm93til @PATisDOPE exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my shit together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low key missing my old hoeðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody is human. Stop judging people. You never know their stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to go get these braids done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PATisDOPE if someone is not disrespecting you, don't disrespect them period. Who cares if they not respecting themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FatherTone moe you really killing me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’€ðŸ’€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My problem has never been with you bitches, it's with you niggas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boss my life up by Kodak is my everyday morning song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ate butter cake. It's good but it be way too sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My birthday bout to be so litâ˜ºï¸âœ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the scars on your â¤ï¸are still mine https://t.co/KyeXw4ZlEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All about my money ðŸ¤‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marijane_Swings what's up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TooWavy_Rodg that's your shit?ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜©âœ‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draco bad and boujee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dudes like to treat women like hoes, then wonder why they act like hoesðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ retards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing my bitch ðŸ˜© https://t.co/kOJJsKWeSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a lingerie party/ sleepover on Valentine's Day â˜ºï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A car with no booty call. 2017 has been unsuccessful thus far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggas always think you want them. No, I want to sit on your face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so close to stripping it's sad ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggas are good for NOTHING I tell you! Not even a booty call ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a night owl. But all my crazy fun friends live in Baltimore ðŸ˜© all my boring friends live here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo gotta pride to the side be making me have flashbacks to when shit was all good ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a baby to that song ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fr though ðŸ˜â¤ï¸ https://t.co/H1EBCgEts9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jono_manic it's a Jamaican thing. They do it on your birthday ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dee__Mich @LT8900 @Nickksun get hit. The chicken made it to the other side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gaining weightâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKRoseMARIE you could never do such a thing â¤ï¸ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alfa_Male that's what's said ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’€âœ‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend just told me that there is no such thing as a pure African? ðŸ˜‚ bruh wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black kids I encourage you to attend a HBCU! Stick with your people. PWI's are NOT the move!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinceVanGo94 I don't break hearts ðŸ˜‚ I barely knew him. That's the crazy part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally told this boy I wasn't interested. I became a bitch so quick. Ctfu then he threatened to kill me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ wtf young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Wes taught me one thing, he taught me EVERYTHING is possible. This man is the ultimate workaholic. I swear I admire that. â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing all your money into something when you don't know if it will sink or swim be the hardest. ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching my business this year. I really hope I succeed but I won't know if I don't try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegallyBeautifu @VinePhilly lol you know I'm goofy. I was dying when I first seen this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People love to talk so much bad stuff about me, just trying to contribute negativity. Sha BYEâœ‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday I think I should drop out of school. Then I think about how much money I put into it already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No SoundCloud link ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜© I'm dead ðŸ’€ðŸ’€ https://t.co/05UmteeGXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always at Fridays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My manager gave me the realist talk today. I needed that ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 in 3 months ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinceVanGo94 thank you ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜Š I will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need to stop trying to change people and accept them for who they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just hope i have a good year. that's all I can ask for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if im a bitch your lil sisters are some lil bitches. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't fuck with no dude that refer to you as a bitch. so disrespectful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can listen to sleigh bells all day]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>