<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how #trump’s ego will deal with the #stoppresidentbannon? I think this will rattle his cage more than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you getting enough vitamin B1 to help fend off Alzheimer's? https://t.co/udgBb3S6QF via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealCFrampton you do us Nordies proud! Hold the head high, it's just a minor blip! We're all behind you, once a champion always a champion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#intellectualdisability &amp; #assistivetechnology: opening the GATE wider: https://t.co/pCO8Lw58aH #disability @WHO @WHOdisability @doctrid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#questiontime #Trump lies maybe 86% of the time, the same % of questions #TheresaMay avoids = a #specialrelationship going nowhere #Reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #trump now aiming to prove time travel is possible? The US at this rate of regression should be in the mid 1800's by next week. #potus45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthew_tipton many congrats last night, super win for the club and great boost for the town moving forward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant tonight lads, big congrats to all at the club! @thepointfc @warrenpointtown https://t.co/KepxhtwC7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to @thepointfc @warrenpointtown tonight, would love to be there but due to work couldn't make it up. Will keep track online!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. take back control via courts but #leave now want control only via an unelected leader who doesn't like questions. #brexit #Article50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Viewfromstormont the fella with the domain expertise must have been off this evening when the panel questions were set? #highlevelbanter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the @ProACT2020 team @PhilipsResearch UK as we move to the next stage of system development &amp; trials:… https://t.co/pVV4MTmCas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May’s “Global Britain” is a branding effort to mask an expensive mistake, opposed by the 48%". #brexit https://t.co/DqpRRQucaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible speech. Negative in tone, aggressive &amp; artificial under the pretence he is aHoly Man. Symbolic it rained as he spoke #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duponline @sinnfeinireland @M_McGuinness_SF wonderful to hear the words of @ianpaisleymp on @bbctheview. A ray of light in a dark tunnel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebsShoes72 one man representing all that's wrong with NI politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah you got to love the parallel universe of #Trump and #Gove. Need to realise the UK is still in the EU. Pain comes… https://t.co/PI0CUuHKIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news - are #digitalhealth/ #lifescience jobs coming to Dublin? exciting times https://t.co/mUpxPlXKeq @IDAIRELAND @Entirl #ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply brilliant-Scottish Herald TV Guide for the week ahead. @realDonaldTrump #trump @billmaher #Inauguration… https://t.co/sxaLW1bERP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic to see this level of hunger and development in the sciences at such a young age @BTYSTE esp. in my own ar… https://t.co/0rV7oaUeYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're seeking paper submissions in #ehealth solutions as part of #AAATE2017 @AAATE_net @ProACT2020 @eHealthIreland… https://t.co/353tlpS7so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heliaebrahimi @jonsnowc4 In a nutshell; populism, aggressively split societies &amp; poor political leadership to deal with it e.g. US &amp; Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenNolan @paulgivan @duponline stooping to the lowest level by deflecting to the most vulnerable in society #bedroomtax #RHIscandal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulgivan confirmed the bubble the @duponline are in with interview on @bbcnewsline expected more humility not deflection #RHIscandal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New report reveals scale of #Trump debt and it's breathtaking https://t.co/eUvR4QphBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great effort from the boys at home! Well done to everyone at the club! Super result. https://t.co/kQUr9aI5lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DUPleader @duponline presently handling the #RHIscandal @StephenNolan #stormount we need to move from deflecting a… https://t.co/Bz6lvfotSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ProACT - Digital Integrated Care - 2016 Newsletter" https://t.co/Wd2rkWV55u by @johndinsmore on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never switched the station so quickly  as when I heard Katie Hopkins come on @LBC wouldn't waste a moment of my time listening to that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderful Christmas spent at @PortmarnockLink, thanks to all the staff for looking after us was a great few days!… https://t.co/bHpX7BmXBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big merry Christmas from the whole #family #christmasday https://t.co/QKgVUW6Qn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artists sketch of #donaldtrump  and #putin secret meeting on having more #nukes…it really is this farcical… https://t.co/IGE21hNAMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJaneWalsh @EU_H2020 @nuigalway @Whitaker_Inst @michaelhogannui All going well albeit a lot of hard work, we must link in moving forward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this a template for future #EU research post #brexit @UKSINet @Scientists4EU @innovateuk @QueensUBelfast? Import… https://t.co/lbVrgXJEDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply unbelievable that in 2016 we are reduced to this when you see the money pumped into the docklands and grand… https://t.co/HD9EJXBiv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drjanewalsh @eu_h2020 @nuigalway @whitaker_inst @michaelhogannui @researchatnuig Many congrats to the team at NUIG, a super achievement!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinNewton4MLA #robinnewton Is this cronyism at the highest level to satisfy political ego? Why was the farce today allowed to proceed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live view of the @DUPleader ego being satisfied, ironically her words will ring hollow after today. Should not have… https://t.co/xCGk0z0FYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenNolan Farce at Stormount. #arlenefoster should not have been allowed to speak. Ego satisfied at detriment of NI. #nolanrhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Marvel based Netflix series 'House of Edjits' to be released staring #jonathanbell as the 'Incredible Bulk'  #NolanRHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrjamesob UK has more citizens living overseas than any other in EU- 4.9 million live in other countries around th… https://t.co/JEvYVAghJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many congrats to @ALONE_IRELAND @CASALATWEET on winning the @SInnovationIRL award last week. Well deserved-an excellent team! @SeanMoynihan_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZDF Article on @IBMWatson @ibm_in_ireland @IBMHealthcare linking in with @ProACT2020 to advance #populationhealth https://t.co/nyM0kLwQYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @SilverCloudH on their award tonight at the #irishmedtech excellence awards tonight @TrinityResearch #mentalhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful setting-meeting great innovators and visionary leaders at #IrishMedtech awards @TCD_SNM  @TrinityResearch… https://t.co/phnpMhksy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#irishmedtech understanding change management for the adoption of #digitaltech key to #behaviouralchange ecosystems… https://t.co/7zbGtppAFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to speak on @ProACT2020 at the #irishmedtech CEO Forum hosted by @cooper_m from @todayfm @TrinityResearch… https://t.co/0nt6yqF1oP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived for the EU Digital summit on Active and Health @ProACT2020 #digitalhealth #ageing @EU_H2020 @EITHealth… https://t.co/UfSraE3zJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic moment suffering a head injury going through security @DublinAirport if one person runs late doesn't mean everyone has to rush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great talk yesterday from the midas #H2020 team on combining data sources in health @ECHAlliance @eHealthIreland… https://t.co/yeqA20rsaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy beside me instantly regretting opening that bag of #Tatyo cheese n Onion on public transport. Nostrils ain't ready #irishrulebroken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcquestiontime hit a whole new level of irony tonight with the leave camp. Quite depressing really #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing site for individuals with #disability #disabilities just watch the promo video says it all: https://t.co/V7BJuqQYgp @yooocanconnect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MittRomney appears to have been bought off by #Trump? One should be true to their core belief. He only comes across now as untrustworthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clydehut outlining the exciting new QIC Progamme from the @eHealthIreland at the @MolMedIrl  #digitalhealth… https://t.co/leCt6k0vR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent paper - #assistiveproducts and Sustainable Development Goals https://t.co/OIWPsbVw0T @ChapalKhasnabis #SDGs @WHO @StellenboschUni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stat:@tcddublin is the Top EU Uni for entrepreneurial grads raising venture capital. In the last 10 yrs 192 grads have raised $2.166b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply amazing by the @okgo team - constantly breaking new ground: https://t.co/EuXHGk7WCX #outstanding #visonary #paint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@proact2020 @hselive Excellent - with significant overlaps in both strategy and the H2020 programme @clydehut @eHealthIreland @R1chardatron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe this is worth signing - Petition: Repeal the new Surveillance laws (Investigatory Powers Act) https://t.co/yEFGL46ph8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent work by the team @TCPHI_TCD @TCD_SNM @abrady4 @ComiskeyCath great to see the Centre grow and support new… https://t.co/CPtlyqmn0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved seeing the @mircosoft @HoloLens have some great ideas for its use in #digitalhealth would be keen to R&amp;D its application in the field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nigelfarage winner of immigrant of the year award. Salary paid by Brussels for 20 yrs. Now wants to live in America https://t.co/Rg5nMIJeIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking 2:50pm 2moro on @ProACT2020 #digitalhealth #integratedcare #AgeingBetter @eHealthIreland @DeloitteIreland… https://t.co/QZnhk0Yjsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With no Mandate to be PM #Theresa May and her cabinet are simply eroding civil liberties. Welcome to 1984… https://t.co/Jwx3cKWPLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eHealthIreland #hisi16 Role of #digitaldoctor - CCIO's in the UK #NHS and US key to linking clinical and eHealth a… https://t.co/rK3Zb71IMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBMWatson, Cognitive Computing and the Future of Healthcare with @ProACT2020  IBM Lead: https://t.co/nyM0kLwQYG @eHealthIreland @clydehut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feature article in Senior Times @ProACT2020 EU research to empower #chronicillness self management #digitalhealth:… https://t.co/w1GYxysugV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent workshop w/@assistidcofund #MarieCurie #FP7 team @ucddublin great talent across the Irish Universities… https://t.co/Mfeadb2A5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great work and wonderful outcomes! #assistivetechnology #disability Community Design Challenge @EnableIreland https://t.co/2df7dW4hEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving from #wearables to #implantables the next logical step. https://t.co/5utRPCYbNW #digithealth #connectedhealth @ProACT2020 @TCPHI_TCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump promised Unicorns &amp; when those that voted for him don't get Unicorns they will be very angry. It's a poisoned chalice now #USElection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonsnowC4 it's like the 23rd of June all over. Will cement the rise of anti intellectualism and disregard for any truth in politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LBC are interviewing #nigelfarage on the US election and read my comment saying I just tuned in and thought it was a Halloween special lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to limit sugar intake in the diet is hard! And only 24 hours into this self diet experiment - sums it up: https://t.co/8pQY8ynwfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedy gold :).... yet sadly true :( https://t.co/Tb5Ar2DEsO #brexit #trump #modernpolitics #politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part 3 Feature #H2020 article #digitalhealth #integratedcare @clydehut @jdoyle_cas @CASALATWEET @lc_walsh… https://t.co/ahzqBEvSJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part 2 of Feature Article #digitalhealth #integratedcare #multimorbidity @TCD_SNM @ProACT2020 @ibm_in_ireland… https://t.co/v79puAXz54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part 1 of a feature Article from @EU_H2020  project magazine on @ProACT2020 #Digitalhealth #connectedhealth… https://t.co/n80p1WRq6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great review of #ageingandthedigitallifecourse @DavePrendergast @LifeDeathTech https://t.co/5W2L5SwUbM #ageing #digitalhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a press article from 2014 when tidying the files: #userexperience  #assistivetechnology @frontlinepbs… https://t.co/hawqxYDlG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travelling now for over 2 years on Enterprise weekly and the wifi has never work? Has it ever worked? @Translink_NI @IrishRail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The underestimation of the role of Privilege in #entrepreneurship ? https://t.co/Wcb2O7NXau @JohnNosta @innovationzone @NDRC_hq debate topic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to @TrinityResearch @audrey_crosbie for hosting a group of Spanish tech CEO's to @tcddublin the… https://t.co/ZvtlGK9OES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full house at the @AdaptCentre event @CrokePark great session on the many ways to link in with their research teams… https://t.co/mtxBnHADfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my @ProACT2020 colleague @PhilipsHealth is at an @IEEEorg  event in London and spots this on the screen going in… https://t.co/ozydTOaOeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronanmcdonnell cheers Ronan you should come visit! Spare room awaits anytime!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mountain running to clear the mind, current audiobook listening 'The Obstacle is the Way' highly recommend… https://t.co/zpMCSycVBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glowing review of book I contributed a chapter in https://t.co/vZPcdUq8hy well done @DavePrendergast  @LifeDeathTech #ageing #digitalhealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkFM not a bad thing, why does society seek to give justification platforms to conn artists? #trump #tonyblair in recent esquire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The book I always dreamed of, a real find for anyone who has lost their heads. A great bedtime read for any kids lol https://t.co/rfVIf0JNXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainjwatson have to say I agree with @yanisvaroufakis only one who talked sense on #bbcbrexittime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yanisvaroufakis absolutely legendary on @bbcquestiontime you spoke complete sense in what has been a weekly non-sensical argument on Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebsShoes72 watched the first episode, was at least 3 weeks long....or at least I aged that much in the hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic documentary on the @BBCiPlayer called #HyperNormalisation well worth a watch! https://t.co/9ociVRGHs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adrianmarkey race for the presidency :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draconian powers creeping into UK around #internetsurveillance. Creating a bigger data haystack doesn't mean its easier to find needles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 3 #Presidential debates it's clear the outright loser is #America. The race has detrimentally  defined a new form of #politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see some Italian Press on @ProACT2020 word is spreading across the #Europe @EU_H2020 @TCD_SNM @CPHI_TCD… https://t.co/PcUBZhNQqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Brussels to look at closing the digital divide for persons with #disabilities #digitalhealth @ProACT2020 @TCD_SNM https://t.co/rrVKuXAgm3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>