<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, GOP Lawmakers Back Off From Immediate Obamacare Repeal https://t.co/qaR9wMdrl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump has lowest approval rating of any President in US history https://t.co/mMftUV5EuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journey 84 | 84 Lumber Super Bowl Commercial https://t.co/u0TmjdlVZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Administration’s Dark View of Immigrants https://t.co/RMvci21J41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copied from Larry... I'm sorry, but unless you are anti American Republic/Democracy, Steve Bannon is seriously... https://t.co/eAcv8uwUkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Administration’s Dark View of Immigrants https://t.co/X23Z51kqt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga sings medley of hit songs at Super Bowl LI, steers clear of politics https://t.co/RJXYEmf5Tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Mexicans Swarming Across Border, Enrolling in Law School, and Becoming Biased Judges https://t.co/RPRjnl8Vwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga DID take a dig at Trump - but it was so subtle most viewers missed it https://t.co/Nn4pgPWzLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump moves to undo financial regulations, Sanders calls him ‘a fraud’ https://t.co/Ak5NptIyeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opposition Mounts for Education Nominee Betsy DeVos https://t.co/ulfGQMqBd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art of the Scam https://t.co/1b4mj58NA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram photo by Mikey Kay • Feb 5, 2017 at 10:47am UTC https://t.co/L67YvgFMnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times targets Lamar Alexander on DeVos vote https://t.co/Cwt65Xt93b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser Super Bowl Ad Triggers Boycott Threat https://t.co/91tm6fG0ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Neil Gorsuch did not start a ‘Fascism Forever’ club at his Jesuit high school https://t.co/lCrAfbzBwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust Records Show Trump Is Still Closely Tied to His Empire https://t.co/KfgPricjjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copying from another post. I fully support Melania's decision to not uproot their young son, but taxpayers should... https://t.co/kXvSz6h5xK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Copy and pasting this from another post.) 

California friends!
ACTION: EMAIL DIANE FEINSTEIN IF YOU ARE FROM... https://t.co/FLAl1AG1mJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump bid to reinstate travel ban fails - BBC News https://t.co/JsFIwVlqzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The psychology of why 94 deaths from terrorism are scarier than 301,797 deaths from guns https://t.co/b6jQEOyj0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s travel ban is unlikely to make America safer https://t.co/B4F4sFz8yZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working Women Respond To White House Dress Code Report With #DressLikeAWoman Campaign https://t.co/38wcK0KfiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this... Have a feeling I'll need to reference this.

'If I said I knew a finance guy who promised me that he... https://t.co/CTUdduv2Rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Anti-Trump Resistance Movement Is Growing Within the U.S. Government https://t.co/RDzDkF12XI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documents confirm Trump still benefiting from his business https://t.co/n9QEnICnUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Inside the White House-Cabinet battle over Trump’s immigration order https://t.co/5MggYoeDux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Statue of Liberty Was Originally a Muslim Woman https://t.co/223ugsRLDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Work from Home https://t.co/4JcZV5mkTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks Offers All Veteran Employees Free College For Their Spouse Or Child https://t.co/ecV0eXVnP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Journalism Brands Where You Find Real Facts Rather Than Alternative Facts https://t.co/wrNZz9iGAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard Stern Claims Donald Trump Wants Hillary Clinton to Be President https://t.co/JkckX5ewPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bogus 'Bowling Green Massacre' Claim Snarls Trump Adviser Conway https://t.co/wNQNZ8G5WY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howard Stern: Trump wants to be loved, presidency will be 'detrimental' to his mental health https://t.co/XyIIAtVA88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway cites ‘Bowling Green massacre’ that never happened to defend travel ban https://t.co/HA2Kvb6brU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway made up a fake terrorist attack to justify Trump’s "Muslim ban" https://t.co/jhzMsb6zSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Trump's Remarks at the National Prayer Breakfast https://t.co/ozRRIGwDWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frederick Douglass Opens Twitter Account from Beyond the Grave to Troll President Trump https://t.co/wbKmBd3yWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Left-lane bandits’ may face $250 fine https://t.co/k2eCPaBNpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ban is boon for ISIS recruitment, experts say https://t.co/aEsiWSNShy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to keep sharing these stories. Bans and similar actions by POTUS create more stories like this. More... https://t.co/DnIOaasgbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit family caught in Iraq travel ban, mom dies waiting for approval to come home https://t.co/64gNA0U348]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From a very smart left-leaning former-attorney friend...

"Liberal friends: this is the wrong fight to pick.... https://t.co/JbltfLJVoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point by Corey. 

"Everyone, keep your eyes peeled during the Super Bowl. If ever there was a time when... https://t.co/l1GSnb1rep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has fired the acting attorney general who ordered Justice Dept. not to defend president’s travel ban https://t.co/txfCAOeoda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not know Heather Richardson, professor of History at Boston College, but I did a search and she is real.... https://t.co/KEO9m7gwfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Senator: Please Protect My Child With a Disability https://t.co/9r6GHUvUkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ‘rogue’ group of staffers is tweeting secrets from the White House https://t.co/0XWGCP2aEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Respond to Donald Trump's Betrayal of American Values https://t.co/MEy64BoIxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Things More Likely To Kill You Than A "Refugee Terrorist" https://t.co/GSbdrfAceZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The very long list of Republicans in Congress who have taken no position on Trump's refugee ban https://t.co/73AWTtxqgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump gives National Security Council seat to ex-Breitbart chief Steve Bannon https://t.co/WlknW4ABIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STATEMENT BY SENATORS McCAIN &amp; GRAHAM ON EXECUTIVE ORDER ON IMMIGRATION - Press Releases - United States Senator... https://t.co/3bl2GeoNyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Judge stays deportations; Trump order barring refugees, migrants from Muslim countries triggers chaos,... https://t.co/CBOnalI5pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Trump’s erratic first week was among the most alarming in history https://t.co/nk3puHDyBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The First Week in Donald Trump’s Kleptocracy Was Very, Very Kleptocratic https://t.co/3uVAxJsAlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dick Cheney Condemns Trump Plan to Ban Muslims From Entering U.S. https://t.co/mSs1rkct0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Federal Judge Just Issued A Stay Against Donald Trump's "Muslim Ban" https://t.co/GEb8gcLSyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Visa Ban Also Applies to Citizens With Dual Nationality, State Department Says https://t.co/JDkiqLqTsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran to ban US citizens in response to Trump's immigration order https://t.co/6LLGtPgIqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau says Canada will take refugees banned by U.S. https://t.co/6CE0FYtSSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Bars Syrian Refugees Indefinitely to Keep Terrorists Out https://t.co/ax7wUD4TQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Thing the Standing Rock Protesters Were Afraid of Just Happened https://t.co/A194pDRfXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead Of Trump's Wall, Let's Build A Border Of Solar Panels https://t.co/dZ2KuBwCYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dick Cheney Thinks Trump's Muslim Ban Is 'Against Everything We Stand For' https://t.co/CV0rSfYuRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Refugee Plan Will Prioritize Christians Suffering Religious Persecution https://t.co/FruZkGQMvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human rights groups appalled by Trump's plans for weekly list of crimes committed by immigrants https://t.co/y8eDvPZ5fT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is getting payments from foreign governments. We have no idea what they are. https://t.co/qcDCot4pBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Simplest and Most Perfect Explanation of Privilege I’ve Ever Seen https://t.co/ZND02z9V4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims about inauguration crowd https://t.co/APWXSopRKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Twitter account appears to be linked to a personal Gmail account https://t.co/gHWoazkYCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of George Orwell's 1984 surge after Kellyanne Conway's 'alternative facts' https://t.co/yqHNmdylMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We the People’ Demand Mr. Trump Release His Tax Returns https://t.co/ZYzDO7l7NI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House website is no longer available in Spanish https://t.co/uWMewKI3Sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National park Twitter account goes rogue, starts tweeting scientific facts https://t.co/7a6FMKCZCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's March Protesters Dumped Their Signs? https://t.co/EKZZCJH9Bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA science researchers ordered to stop publishing news releases, other documents https://t.co/v9ZOT6UoLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke the Panama Papers story. Our next mission: Donald Trump https://t.co/tin8Wmo72y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Reportedly Brought His Own Staff to Cheer During C.I.A. Speech https://t.co/mVuIW16rSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What To Tell People Who Say You Have To Accept Donald Trump's Presidency Now https://t.co/jSAO2RkKGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump CIA Speech may have made worsened intel community relations https://t.co/GD89dhBiXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French people are finding it really hard to translate Donald Trump because of his 'limited vocabulary' https://t.co/R3h6cJNgzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an Idea: Stop Putting Kellyanne Conway on T.V. https://t.co/jFXt8I7E5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Million Muslims March Against ISIS and The Mainstream Media Completely Ignores It https://t.co/ygS44mrHWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without evidence, Trump tells lawmakers 3 million to 5 million illegal ballots cost him the popular vote https://t.co/Fc0hjAYN8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Declines to Air White House Press Conference Live https://t.co/fWT75xLbmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration just told a whopper about the size of the federal workforce https://t.co/0rwcwSZ1VN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you can fact-check Trump’s tweets — in the tweets themselves https://t.co/07noSwkpWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC’s metro system keeps trolling Trump for his poor inauguration attendance https://t.co/gKmsALklZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Doesn't Want You To See These Humiliating Photos Of His Parade https://t.co/XlW4HleLyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Pushes ‘Alternative Facts.’ Here Are the Real Ones. https://t.co/QKE5MkhViD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Christy on Facebook, who doesn’t need the Women’s March https://t.co/1OR4UsBYJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump won’t release his tax returns because people don’t care, top adviser says https://t.co/Fgft9pUFPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Alternative Facts': The Needless Lies of the Trump Administration https://t.co/goAhzCezHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Is Yet To Sever Ties With His Business, Despite Promises To Do So, Report Says https://t.co/6p99xjWc8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Women's Marches may have been the largest demonstration in US history https://t.co/fDv9NyfxSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The perfect meme for the ‘alternative facts’ era: #seanspicersays https://t.co/RelryjMutp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing 25- to 34-year-olds now with 25- to 34-year-olds in 1989 is super depressing https://t.co/i11dl51NAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 2.5 million strong, Women's Marches crush expectations https://t.co/wi9gjQXDn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's March Is The Biggest Protest In US History As An Estimated 2.9 Million March https://t.co/G92ck7XyQM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>