<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@roddrury @garethmorgannz @TheSpinoffTV Gareth, apart from "investing" in land, where are the other benefits that TOP seems to require?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roddrury @garethmorgannz @TheSpinoffTV New Zealand has clear citizenship rules that should apply equally to everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HalfOnionInABag better half an onion than a whole orange!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlickElectricCo @FastCompany imagine if you could just 3D print an entire outfit at home. Then reuse the materials to print another one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladyleet don't eat them all at once! #johnnyCash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan he should turn the other cheek and offer himself for some torture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vicki_Scarlett @sarahmei were they an effective sales team? I'd expect them to be crap if they are that blind to other perspectives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen @consumernz I have a 2.8L inline 6. But I'm Wellington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HalfOnionInABag makes me cry. But so does @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StackPodcast Data is a robot on Star Trek. #StackOverflowPodcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch @PressSec likely a collection of Grimm's fairy tales.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan what if there are no virgins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains unless the book is "little miss happy". That is an absolute precondition for me ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haruki_zaemon @martinfowler that tells me the decisions are being made too early.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StackPodcast is it the bug or the submitter who is not reproducible? Con. #StackOverflowPodcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurmarcusallen @grmpyprogrammer trickle up economics, on the other hand, does seem to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer @jurmarcusallen I believe trickle down economics was proven not to work a few decades ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan @SteveKingIA while trump will be a nightmare, at least our comedians will have material for several decades :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains @ImaginaryTime I still use zip lock bags - Anova is my 3rd sous vide cooker (built my first one!).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImaginaryTime @jbrains nice. Creme Brûlée is also great in a water bath. I bought modernist cooking at home. Lots of ideas in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains no I mean 68 for 48 hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImaginaryTime @jbrains do you put them in one water bath at different temperatures for fun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains I have one of those. It is awesome. Brisket at 56 Celsius for 48 hours yum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlickElectricCo power back on. Candles are now out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch @IBM @cdixon does this mean that a bee beat us at chess and go? Bugger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlickElectricCo oddly we did have fish and chips for dinner. Home made. While still had power. Young kids so eat early.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlickElectricCo already rang your help desk. Should be back on at 9:30. Pinehaven Upper Hutt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlickElectricCo @futurism I'd rather that my power doesn't go out in a storm. Like right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daryllgray @adidasNZ report them to the DIA for spam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buildmaster we got a Honda CR-V. Works very well. But only 5 seats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrKrisViking @_youhadonejob1 there was another one on the other side of the uni that says "this university is shit" but it got removed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrKrisViking @_youhadonejob1 NZ is a young country. Not many old trees. I find the plaque nice that someone cared that much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrKrisViking @_youhadonejob1  this plaque is at Victoria university in Wellington New Zealand. I remember the tree. It was nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmei @jessethanley coding is complex and hard. I think it is ok to blame your tools once in a while :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmei @jessethanley and yes - I saw it as a jab at people who value tools as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmei @jessethanley some things need the right tool. Cutting ripe tomatoes with a blunt knife. Refactoring legacy code with notepad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahmei @jessethanley all the pros I know use great tools. Programmers, carpenters, chefs... a pro knows the value of tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funkatron @grmpyprogrammer sex robots will be cheaper so will prob be widespread first. But likely will converge on widespread sex cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanlong @joemccann if all good devs are hacking in holidays, I am happy to be a bad developer and have a life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfuchs @grmpyprogrammer if amazon built self driving cars they would say: "people who went to your house also visited the pub"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to be the 14,966th backer on @BackerKit for Font Awesome 5 | Thx @fontawesome! https://t.co/demkzbxSzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjh remember to return the driver too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePracticalDev I once had to build a fake progress bar because the product owner thought the system was too fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan @nzherald good points. Also, darth Vader doesn't exist :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnovaCulinary @greytownnz here is another photo. https://t.co/urBmm3VhCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnovaCulinary spare ribs from the @greytownnz butcher. 3 days at 56...will be a great Christmas lunch... https://t.co/9gKzO3QypF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonJeffries had this once. Think I deleted the account in messages and added it back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch @transition2017 @techmilind or a word document.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skepticalhumor could make a good talk at the next java users group John...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer we always praise effort and try to avoid praising talent or cuteness :) swimming lessons in New Zealand aren't so intense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimbuktuMag so proud of the colour scheme my 6 year old chose for herself for the queen! https://t.co/bW6iMY2ert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buildmaster @8iReality @nikz I am virtually there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan @hcirePT @nzherald that column is worth at least $2300.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePracticalDev a good pillow and mattress. #devdiscuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePracticalDev the tooling will always lag the new hot languages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer I know this feeling only too well. It sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buildmaster they are awesome. Kickstarter it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinfowler @Grady_Booch count me in on this as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachelmaleady @StackPodcast peanut butter? In NZ Jif is a kitchen cleaning product.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HiranThabrew @ICBM2016 awesome! Lots of computer science research about making sticky websites. Outcomes harder. https://t.co/e5p69eNCcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains @Englishbobster eating an elephant: one bite at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains @juanmirod I have: test after; end to end; dep injection of mocks; testing implemention v behaviour; that's all that fits in a twee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juanmirod @jbrains has anyone looked at the stages people go through when learning TDD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama I agree with Elouise here. Because awesome dreaming magnadoodle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This verdict leaves me speechless. Dumbfounded. Shoot someone in the back and get off? How? https://t.co/xFqrbsSfgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mogest @buildmaster it is probably more Owen's bulging muscles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@troubleisbrewng easy. Don't go outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@troubleisbrewng I am having #weedstock at my place this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FireflyCinema I hear there is a movie too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer one of my friends watched Fox News for a year before realising It was not a satire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer strange how "talk to other people" is not on the list. Glad the phishing one is - the rest don't seem interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelialaundy Depending on required features, an F5 might work. (sry about lots of tweets - you asked an interesting question!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelialaundy AWS API Gateway does have a redirect to arbitrary URL feature - configurable per method on each endpo… https://t.co/32qpSBoD7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelialaundy they can redirect I think. My point was more - this is a problem others have solved. Building these is hard :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelialaundy why not use an existing service - AWS has an awesome one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer @CBCNews protect identity of main suspect so they get a fair trial? But usually so family can be notified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaelle76 @rogerpfaff I thought for a second "this has to be satire". Apparently not. WTF. #dcmuc16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama Yeah, that should be much more restrictive than business filtering. And not just porn - also self harm websites, etc, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YitzOfTheBits @grmpyprogrammer No. Unit tests for validation, bus logic, DB, factories, etc. Then 1 local end2end test (incl local DB)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pageofwords new books! https://t.co/k7Qvfld2Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama unsavoury is difficult because one person's unsavoury is not another persons. So ISPs might avoid that. But who knows!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farnamstreet @Grady_Booch or, having just googled, I might be wrong about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farnamstreet @Grady_Booch @amazon pity homework doesn't increase educational outcomes. But alexia prob doesn't know that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer and component based react front end makes test driving components also nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer testing a small bit of code that responds to a well defined interface in a well defined way is nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grmpyprogrammer I have just finished a big serverless app TDD. Worked beautifully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama that is very sensible. What content blocking facilities are you after? Malware or unsavoury?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama use any of the major ones. Most of the time they don't work so are blocking everything by default ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxwellstrachan @RaybonKan reminds me how trivial first world problems are. Growing up we had to sell lemonade to our sheep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjammingh Wellington try datacom or catalyst - they do lots of infra and are usually hiring.  (I am from welly and it is awesome)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASAWebb gravity is what keeps me escaping from a hole. So it seems aptly named. Is it black?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbrains I am completely dumbfounded. This is odd. Am interested to know the root cause!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual @RaybonKan is awesome.  https://t.co/XqNh0bHAqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch @NateSilver538 this sequence of tweets made me laugh. https://t.co/sgWR4Oj4Ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch a small one. I was in a 7.8 last week ;) but really, hope everything is ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buildmaster consider yourself hit :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmckibben @Grady_Booch this graph gives me the shivers. What have we given our grandkids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadlyllama they all should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_youhadonejob1 great for watching paint dry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newtron hey - what remote options do you have. I am in New Zealand!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>