<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Long hours, dangerous conditions - truck driving's one of Australia's deadliest jobs https://t.co/MZZwvDyGrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw a NZ Union leader on TVOne News tonight talking about how immigration should be curtailed so wages can... https://t.co/BTlQmtkWO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has signed an order banning the sale of sliced cheese in the US - now you can only buy it by the block - he... https://t.co/s3EQrast4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rugby players offered jobs, beds https://t.co/I7De1arJRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've Got a Friend In Me - LIVE Performance by 4-year-old Claire Ryann and Dad https://t.co/QWMgPoV7Mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lower Hutt's municipal gardens from the Roblawmax office. I wonder how the road cone got up that enormous tree?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling all Kapiti Coast Hammerhands and Carpenters, We have a project which requires additional labour onsite... https://t.co/1RNm5eTvHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year - We hope you are all ready to get back to work!
We are currently looking for skilled labourers to... https://t.co/lOSGFzmZsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Observations on Zombie towns – Whale Oil Beef Hooked | Whaleoil Media https://t.co/3soeuflpqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luckily The Man from Snowy River was at the Roblawmax Christmas party at Boom Rock. Along with Jeremy and Scott... https://t.co/BVGB0kX44Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger has a new child to go with his recent great-grandchild. Thats great they'll be able to play together.... https://t.co/DUPAizXqqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all those who have suggested that I run for Prime Minister of NZ I'm afraid that my current life of indolence,... https://t.co/cAHXy3IAhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELECTRICIANS NEEDED - Wellington!

We have a positions available for a highly motivated and enthusiastic... https://t.co/VqbwH6OGno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the headline telling us that Fidel Castro died prematurely because of all those cigars. maybe if... https://t.co/vmsku1AXHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent shake here in Plimmerton. Genet says 4.5 27km deep off Paraparaumu. I'm a bit over it really. I am from... https://t.co/A36gIkoLiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Everyone, 
Our Kapiti Office is looking for a Qualified Carpenter for a short term position. 
This role will... https://t.co/HGphkyLLGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WANTED! Reach Truck Operators! Start Monday 28/11/2016

- Long term placement
- Top pay rate
- Must have own... https://t.co/bStcwrbIeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WANNTED!! Qualified Carpenters &amp; Skilled Hammerhands for various commercial construction projects in Wellington... https://t.co/Od4pfLwntx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honey Badger Houdini - Honey Badgers: Masters of Mayhem - Natural World - BBC Two https://t.co/PIkesQSOvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raced home from work (took 2.5 hours) to make sure I didn't miss the tsunami. One of the advantages of living at... https://t.co/go9xuvLno0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had another in fact not sure it has finished yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and it went on for at least two minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MSM - Main Stream Media (television newspapers and radio ) and Social Media (Twitter Facebook etc) were all... https://t.co/1x2RhVDQOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ideological Disease known as 'Cultural Marxism' Exposed https://t.co/ULukcdRUjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ideological Disease known as 'Cultural Marxism' Exposed https://t.co/uITHCiyIis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for a Civil Labourer with a Confined Space ticket to start an assignment in Kapiti ASAP - Call... https://t.co/iFEPlnJrQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great effort by the Irish team Will Mallard  #/NZLvIRE - have you been coaching them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Ireland #NZLvIRE 40-29 up. Best team all day a very impressive effort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have just watched the first half replay of the #NZLvIRE game from Chicago. Only one team in it at 25-8 to... https://t.co/BA3mT8ttAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Foods to Cook in Your Sandwich Press https://t.co/lWgY0lhE4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 8pm and the sun is streaming into the house just before sundown. A beautiful time of the evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$100 reward offered!!!!!

Qualified Carpenters needed urgently!!! 

We have major projects all over Wellington,... https://t.co/jbFgvskNP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for Lower Hutt Based construction Labourer with a current EWP ticket to operate an EWP. Immediate... https://t.co/TUkDjhistw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had well over a 100 more like 130 kids knock on our door for Halloween tonight plus 30 or 40 parents. Luckily... https://t.co/4RvYD1lDDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another triumph Elin Tomos #NZLvAUS so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. How great is this? https://t.co/6peY8UpNUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WELvWAI 24-28 I'm feeling very neat re the coaching and the game plan so best I keep my own counsel at this... https://t.co/IPsVrTn4rZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memoirs of a Maori https://t.co/zr7c9ZEWAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Kapiti branch are looking for 4x Labourers for the Kapiti Coast.
You must have a Restricted Manual Licence as... https://t.co/adYCJCSNRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smith outrage unfair - Reason https://t.co/lgpBQeBsQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rugby Union’s clerical duties https://t.co/toO4bTJ8hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Class 1 licences Labourers Required for Monday Start in Kapiti.

We are looking for a couple of FULL... https://t.co/4ZIbf85sPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE MUSIC VIDEO PREMIERE: Ben Hazlewood - “Love Strong” / Ones To Watch https://t.co/HaLxPJDoOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know about incredible but I like it. https://t.co/ak4GNlG2Ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Registered Electricians for temporary to permanent position. 

Our clients company is a highly... https://t.co/W8gZRs9PNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to be apart of Wellingtons Newest Motorway Projects??

Our clients have a demand for Experienced Dump... https://t.co/ONMQX6mUnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want to be apart of Wellingtons Newest Motorway Projects??

With the growth in the Civil works in... https://t.co/acw4fKFtbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for experienced Construction labourers for various heavy &amp; light commercial work - A current Site... https://t.co/VKa4jQOuIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are currently looking for an Auckland based Trades Labour Hire Consultant to join our busy Central Auckland... https://t.co/aMgAluckui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Earlier today, the Wellington Lions rugby club apologised to......etc etc" (Radio NZ website). Since when are... https://t.co/RUKDtMqswi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for an experienced Logistics/Warehousing worker, picking and packing orders for dispatch.  Lower Hutt... https://t.co/JOJ2gmhF37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Herald interview with Key https://t.co/9yNzTmPk92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey All,
Looking for 3-4 Labourers for on going work in Civil Construction on the Kapiti Coast.
You will need... https://t.co/eUm5cZ1SeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously. Who cares if George Clooney is divorcing Brangelina. He should never have married them in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Huffington Post. https://t.co/JUKz4LNpCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six good ideas from Trump https://t.co/P1N0Nyr87m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world seems to be rebelling against the Intellectual Idiot class (not sure we need the 'yet' in the title). I... https://t.co/sqlUx7uvYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNationTV3 What's with @RusselNorman he seems to be bouncing when he talks is his beard unbalancing him? and so bored!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WEL vBOP WRFU have a great policy for concussion - Hey Leni what is your name? I dunno bro. Neither do I get back on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WELvBOP I thought Peter Umaga Jensen was away with the Wellington U19's but not so .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jockey New Zealand Rugby Commerical https://t.co/yCmCOe4ffG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any site safe labourers looking for work? 
We are super busy and have work in Wellington, Lower Hutt and Kapiti... https://t.co/PauQDVmgOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for Carpenters for various Residential and Commercial Construction work, from Formworkers to... https://t.co/mYfJH5d7lt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NZLvARG Argentina up 7-0 over the All Blacks after 3 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably a waste of time if you are not fishing or boating or some such but how much dearer is polarisation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#COUvWEL last minute long range penalty by Jackson Garden Bachop put Wel in for a win 28-27.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you see Vaea Fifita hurdle that tackler? Never seen that before. Terrific. Outstanding. It will be worldwide before the game is finished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep that's what I want. https://t.co/SP1Iq3SNNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this is fun 6.17pm and it is nearly fully dark - and the electricity is out! Apparently it should be on... https://t.co/ePlsCAjQwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just read David Pocock #ausrugby #NZLvAUS started an answer with " As a human, as a citizen.......'  what a dick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #ALLBLACKS  in #AUSvNZL  on Sat night played a different game to anything we have seen before. Completely... https://t.co/BMprfSbW5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT! Storeman with a Class 2 license required for a company in Petone.  7:30am to 4pm, full-time hours. This... https://t.co/xlSUk4reWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this doesn't make you hungry nothing will. https://t.co/36x6KiksOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NZLvAUS #allblacks well done up 32-3 at halftime. Beauden Barrett is outstanding. Shag says Bewdy Beaudy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't Elin Tomos  singing the National Anthem I'm not used to this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CoachShag... Righto boys lets get into them...Who we playin Shag...Dunno... Richie who we playing? Must be takin... https://t.co/8ur94ESEKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transcript of #allblacks bug #NZLvAUS... 'Jeez Shag that Cheks a dick...Yea I'm gonna get Richie to kick the shit... https://t.co/LqfEGYbPi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #AllBlacks team room bugged in Aus. "Hey Shag whats the game plan? Buggered if I know where's Richie?...... https://t.co/oa6V8rSoTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always thought so. https://t.co/cVpDtwYtQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving to Sydney?
 
An established logistics company in Sydney are interested in hiring talent from our shores!... https://t.co/zKTikt8r4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coaching and RDO roles at Johnsonville https://t.co/WNgJgwpFra via @clubrugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you working as a Labourer through an agency and paid as LABOUR ONLY (Self Employed)?

If you are for example... https://t.co/YJfvI4dHJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great example of harness safety. https://t.co/nHVUbfL5qK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done John Happy Birthday! You are doing a great job though you do seem to have aged a bit - probably having... https://t.co/gfz8QlntFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got back from watching Tawa24 beat MSP 20 in the #Jubilee Cup at Jerry Collins Stadium Porirua.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HOBMvPETONE Hardham Cup Final HOBM 17 Petone 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump's ratings have suddenly changed from positive to negative - this is why. https://t.co/XMHSRRdUwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real hate crime scandal | Coffee House https://t.co/WDre2OgwiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lily Allen- "Fuck You" (Live in HQ) https://t.co/KMJC40H3ND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casey Abrams - Georgia on My Mind, American Idol 2011 Hollywood Week https://t.co/soy0JR55eJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely this is not true. Reported in the Guardian UK. https://t.co/SR3cm0FwNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Southwest Airline Safety Presentation (Open Captions) https://t.co/KJso2Z3XIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Southwest Airline Safety Presentation (Open Captions) https://t.co/L9PxJIHWXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Southwest Flight Attendant https://t.co/JyhU7DU3t8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible growth in Auckland and we are glad to be a part of it @roblawmax https://t.co/23ZSqv6LjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An update on tools seized from a Wellington property today. Please get in touch with the police if you have had... https://t.co/EHS27n2sNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notification received today 26/7 @ 11.50am. https://t.co/coCH3RIcx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrevorMallard is no longer standing for Hutt South. 
I have known Trevor Mallard for a long time and he is the... https://t.co/1TlFasC1EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sevensharp Why on earth are you interviewing Rolf Harris about rugby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HURvSHA Hurricanes 41 Sharks 0 and they were lucky to get 0!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>