<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@neva9257 Yup! Like all virtues (though it's not one), if it's not directed to the good, it's merely a 'glittering vice'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nuanced take: what is virtuous about patience is not particular to patient actions. It's a product of a larger virt… https://t.co/qSiQXySChe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot take: patience is not a virtue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW Mr Trumble would be an excellent bad guy in a Roald Dahl novel. https://t.co/BPj9gniaYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rotating door of the Australian Prime Ministership continues. Who is Prime Minister Trumble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tread carefully through this selfie-ridden age, friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday I got new glasses and send a picture of them to my family. I didn't explain the reason for the selfie. All they saw was my vanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MADforpeace It's pretty dangerous if the subtle message beneath it is read as 'you can't be a terrorist unless you're religious (Muslim)']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Att: counter-terrorism experts... https://t.co/lL8TyaPmkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duane_dmt That makes sense - I suspected there was a security reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that strikes me most from the photos from Trump's Turnbull call is that the Oval Office still uses a phone with a cord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been thinking a bit about whether we need a concept of 'political time' to address some of the culture war issues. Will report back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SimonLongstaff on surviving the Trump era of politics https://t.co/LuIalntv8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As funny as Turnbull being burned might seem, there's a bunch of vulnerable people who could have been settled somewhere who now may not be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will study this dumb deal" is now my preferred way of voicing objections to things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time @patstokes writes something... https://t.co/NpAc4EPs94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've read over four tweets today and this is the worst tweet by far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBarryLam Hmmm. I'll give it some thought. Our podcast has a broadcast partner which is a big help, but there are other avenues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBarryLam You've done an incredibly good job with this podcast. Can't wait to listen to more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this, if you get around to it. https://t.co/vO1J92sT9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damonayoung @TheNewPhil @philosophybites @patstokes @RuthQuibell I'll retweet this... 

Later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had the pleasure of meeting with Mike Robillard a few times. He's a really nice guy and an excellent thinker t… https://t.co/vsOXtMNpzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HiPhiNation is a brilliant new philosophy podcast. This episode on moral exploitation is so good. https://t.co/8fB0mrWl0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BubbaMacLeod @SusanCarland That's a different point and one I don't agree with. It's also not supported by (or related to) the article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BubbaMacLeod @SusanCarland But each of those is presumably an instance of targetted, malicious killing and basically morally equivalent. 4/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BubbaMacLeod @SusanCarland Nor does it explain fear or terrorism vs fear of gun death. It would explain car accidents, disease etc... 3/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BubbaMacLeod @SusanCarland But seeing them as more significant doesn't explain why we exaggerate the likelihood of their occurrence. 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BubbaMacLeod @SusanCarland I think this is part of it. Certain kinds of death and horror are morally worse. We avoid them more strongly. 1/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How biases control us - The psychology of why 94 deaths from terrorism are scarier than 301,797 deaths from guns https://t.co/OGQanJ2X9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenofthinair Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenofthinair who would you recommend reading on the ethics of whistleblowing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur And so conflates innocent bystander responsibility with the responsibility to restore an injustice one is responsible for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur I think I follow: Singer's TE paints all passers-by as bystanders rather than as (potentially) having prior responsibility?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur And I'm genuinely asking to learn. I studied ethics but its intersection with political philosophy is somewhat new to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur But maybe I'm missing something. What do you see as the apolitical problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur I think for a general audience, it's a useful demonstration of why inaction is no more ethically neutral than positive action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zaranosaur Yeah I'm not a fan on a number of fronts but the thought experiment is useful for Aus politics atm. https://t.co/jXWgcqvGK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singer's drowning child thought experiment teaches us the ethics of inaction. "No comment" is a choice not to critique the status quo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer For me the organ donation question is a big one too - although chimeras might provide new organs, there are other options.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we need to literally inject humanity into a creature to start worrying about its moral status? Chimeras pose big… https://t.co/pw1pXqhFsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After almost 7 years of living the the United States, I got deported." https://t.co/IT3UZLhrAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reddishraven 

- Obscure theorist totally predicted Trump X years ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Spins the hot take wheel*

TRUMP IS

- Machiavellian genius
- Russian stooge
- Man of the people
- Existential threat
- Problematic
- 1984]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It turns out the Doctor was right. Time IS wibbly-wobbly. https://t.co/eVANYyDXSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread 👇 https://t.co/zYNBxfTRl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about the ethics of human/pig chimeras (coincidentally, my nickname in high school) on @abcsydney at 10am with @wendy_harmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter @marrowing @BishopUmbers I would have directed you to Mike as well. Maybe check the feminist philosophy blog too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patstokes @ConversationEDU so THAT'S the sound that plays every time I tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ring the good take gong, @patstokes is back at it. https://t.co/xzRKZYdUv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My abbreviated take on the pig chimera: more humans should probably be organ donors if we're making new species... https://t.co/mBDgJWx9Rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm chatting Modern Dilemmas on @RNLifeMatters right now. Talking ethics, poverty, charity and social biases!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also how good are ball kids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🎶 Young pope, the subject
Of cardinal conspiracy
He's vaping, and angry
Dresses so handsomely 🎶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randomiotas Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarielaLib @elephantjournal Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK at the risk of sounding stupid, what the heck is gaslighting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good take from @ellenbroad on Australia's silence over data ethics. https://t.co/7MscXfbXLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please. Move Australia Day to May 8 so my birthday is always a public holiday https://t.co/zQ5u3lORKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter Unless you gave the right of objection to everyone, but that may amount to a denial of substantive rights in some cases...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter I see. I wonder if there's grey area on that basis though - musicians, professional MC's, etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter But I'm wondering why you see bakers and florists differently then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter Yeah, exactly. I can see how it might be seen as trying to facilitate cultural change somehow, but it'll be ineffective imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter In which case you'd eventually weed out the reluctant ones. That has it's own set of ethical issues though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_salter Maybe the idea is more that if anti-discrimination law applies to celebrants, objectors won't practice anymore...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Flannery on why your grandkids might never see a tree kangaroo https://t.co/0872R2IZEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really good piece on the task ahead for Defence leadership in the US  https://t.co/myekrBE0KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My take on the political entitlements scandal in @smh today: why "following the rules" won't always save you. https://t.co/Dxa7SCx1t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenofthinair Right intention seems significant too - though as always the hardest to ascertain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenofthinair I wonder if the jus ad bellum criteria might be useful in this context? Not perfect but they might help with framing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Forget the title, just write.
Also me: https://t.co/8Cl6dSJoEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong moral leadership is needed to combat populist tide https://t.co/IuhfPXb6WK via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigidWD if you liked this you should check out this RadioLab podcast. It's harrowing. https://t.co/gGZ1MGzFIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Metamagician @philosophybites 'Et al' is a noble title and puts you in esteemed company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@portusprince Sure, but 'it's been done before' isn't an argument for doing it now. Though it highlights more issues of economic disparity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something for everyone here... https://t.co/BYfyXdIerh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad dilemma - would a robot crib affect my parenting?  What value sleepless nights? https://t.co/aMvIBdZ1px @wef… https://t.co/dYkmOvhXvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military robots: is the act of killing one humanity should be outsourcing? 
https://t.co/JxQVG9wC0M
@wef… https://t.co/PJdulw9HOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we automate work, would life be worth living? Where would we turn for meaning?  https://t.co/xPKVtFBcox @wef… https://t.co/Vk1YXm2au2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because @wef are meeting for #davos2017, I'm tweeting some stuff I've written on the 4th Industrial Revolution lately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damonayoung I know - we've got friends with an 8 month old who still wakes every hour. I'm not sure how they're still functioning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damonayoung Teething at the moment. It's wild stuff, though he's still a comparably good sleeper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cool to not like Kyrgios - I've written about his failings before, but this reeks of 'I'm smarter than you'. https://t.co/3sS5he9KsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @Radiolab episode is harrowing and ethically heavy, though there's a minor simplification of double-effect.… https://t.co/JC1fxW8gXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone leave academia and still manage to get their thesis published as an academic volume? Cannot. find. the. time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davidramli However, perhaps we would need to understand what property rights are *for* and how AI could/would benefit from them first...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davidramli Even more relevant given things like this: https://t.co/WLCp3wC6DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've got your Roomba working overtime, you might soon be in trouble for violating its rights. https://t.co/J8rtdCWlhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhennessy I'll give you $20 of good advice: get off this bad website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rgcooke I've been featured in truther blacklists/email chains for having written on Bryant last year. I'm part of the cover up. Wild stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To my shame, it was actually @BecDeUnamuno 😳 https://t.co/qL37wfNTj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatting to Christine Anu on @702Sydney for perhaps the last time now 😭 

We're talking new year's resolutions. What's yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke to @SBSNews for their story on the Trump files and media ethics along with Julian Disney and @PeterGreste https://t.co/2sb2JC7XIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This got me well and truly misty. Beautiful reflection on a doctor watching her colleagues treat her daughter after… https://t.co/PgARFCgffk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful debate on whether UBI is a good idea or not. Good intro for those (like me) not super familiar with it. https://t.co/mtl9xlixjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year's resolutions remind us of "who we take ourselves to be and what we aspire to become". Lovely meditation. https://t.co/HuM8ZYPg98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great. Philosophers and writers help inmates tell their stories in The New Yorker https://t.co/NctLk8aqrI HT @DailyNousEditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this one is a good outline of the reasons why the publication was justified https://t.co/2coq3GZ1qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece outlining why Buzzfeed shouldn't have published the Trump allegations https://t.co/dBlilWLrBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sympathetic to the idea regulation and law can't create integrity, but not sure about the ICAC claims here. https://t.co/IIA8tMJ7Ll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll admit, I can be a bit dismissive of the norms of politeness but this got me thinking. https://t.co/Yrfkq4fRjG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>