<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Vincent Fort replaces him. We need a genuine progressive. @atl4fort ðŸ‘ŠðŸ½ https://t.co/AttfDhTH2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please continue that dialogue here. https://t.co/AEkslShGC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owned. @MikePenceVP https://t.co/tWoRwQRtnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You continue to argue on the assumption there is one truly good side free of bloodshed. As if. https://t.co/sqiHmlLgDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except that we're already dead, alongside tens of thousands. And, the question is how many more must die? https://t.co/sqiHmlLgDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheYoungTurks @ShaunKing @francis_maxwell This actually helped me. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @RaniaKhalek Zionism Zionism. Murder only one side. This guy @BritishLebanese still doesn't get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BritishLebanese @Seb_Castro @RaniaKhalek Didn't know today was "Let's celebrate the dead bodies on one side but not the other" day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamanjperez This picture is so awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @BritishLebanese @RaniaKhalek The reason Rania has our respect in the 1st place is bec of her adversarial criticism on all sides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Canova I'm a fan btw. We will make you win next election. ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Canova I'm just giving you a tip so that all your followers can see your tweets. This is a common mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Canova Hello Tim, if you start your tweets with an @, then only people who follow those people can see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @joelfw75 To exist is to resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're proud of your campaign as Stein supporters! https://t.co/ylSdnAu1yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro That's insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro She is going to lose to an Orangutan #JillNotHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules I watched your video and I completely understand how losing a friend in Iraq would make you for Trump and #NeverHillary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules Aw, thank you. On policy, Stein is basically Bernie's girl twin. We miss you. You're always welcome back to the fold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenJauregui @Seb_Castro Thank you thank you #JillNotHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @eimajery We'll never know unless we try. ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimTryce I won't tell you who to vote for but please kindly consider Hillary's record on war, TPP, and healthcare. @frey_keith @GeorgeTakei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimTryce It took Greek progressive party Syriza 10yrs of fighting on both nat'l and local stage. Not either or. @frey_keith @GeorgeTakei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimTryce It took Greek progressive party 10yrs of fighting on both nat'l and local stage. Not just either or. @frey_keith @GeorgeTakei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimTryce Between nationall &amp; local, there's no reason to think progressivism requires one strategy. @frey_keith @GeorgeTakei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimTryce At the end pf the day, lesser evil voting has only made us a more right-wing country. @frey_keith @GeorgeTakei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stein's up in this poll. #SteinBaraka https://t.co/M3wN193gWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein #JillNotHill Corporations of the billionaire class can shove it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein We deserve better than establish't Dem or Repubs. #JillNotHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing the duopoly continues. https://t.co/cobFqKXhXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was obvious in terms of coverage that you denied her the amount of screen time she deserved. #JillNotHill https://t.co/jUVfKBVsjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillFilipovic 30+ yrs of Lesser evil voting is the reason Trump exists in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillFilipovic How does the fact that a majority are voting against S.O. look healthy and democratic to you? https://t.co/MKJ5N2j6vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @Tim_Canova @GreenPartyUS Join the fold Tim!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbnychef I dont discuss politics w/cursing children incapable of didtinguishing communism from socialism. Blocked. @wizegie @FisherBurton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbnychef Sad that ppl like you never complain about trillions on war/corp welfare. That's free stuff on all our dime @wizegie @FisherBurton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorsynth Instead of criticizing activists try criticizing the larger vabdalism of the DAPL @DrJillStein @RobynnTysver #NoDAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this new @DankJillMemes https://t.co/SIPpGg9Y0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kgosztola Don't mind @JHWeissmann. He knows he's a corporate puppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein Jill Stein is the only candidate for the 99%. You hillary funded trolls should find a new day job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein Jill Stein is the only candidate for the 99%. You hillary funded trolls should find a new day job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldCurmudgeonII Actually our DrJillStein has already clarified this a thousand times. Corp media needs to come up w/a new narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein @NPR Jill not Hill. Because the country deserves more than another corporate shill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein @NoahRemnick I hope Noah relates Jill's platform fairly and doesn't reduce @nytimes to anti-vax smear campaign. #JillNotHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenPartyUS @DrJillStein #JillNotHill The age of TPP-Democrat sellouts is over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@YoungLiberalDem @StuckJake @DrJillStein After Hillary's super corporate VP pick, what makes u think she'll pick a progressive SC justice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @teddycasino Congratulations to Bayan Muna for Zarate's appointment. ðŸ‘ðŸ»ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein Cornel West !!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this Haha #RunNinaRun https://t.co/bHowxJ8fPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's progress https://t.co/4rFDs0aFxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly regal https://t.co/Do25EuVWeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My facial expressions haven't changed since last ep : ðŸ˜³ https://t.co/mfctUWdIul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atomaraullo @ABSCBNNews
 E. Experiencing subtle flirtation from Atom Araullo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe to say Duterte has already won. https://t.co/Zc9PF5k0YW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha This is cute â¤ï¸ https://t.co/Z4tG5IoWpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie is on fire. I didn't think he had a chance of making a comeback, but the Bern is alive and well. https://t.co/BreY1wq9kS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seb responded to me pala. ðŸ˜¬â¤ï¸ https://t.co/FXj7wvCOmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro What can you say about how your state of GA will not pass that Anti-Gay law? ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck is happening in Arizona? Voter fraud? #AZPrimary is trending and it looks like Hillary has major explaining to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#EBGodGaveMeYou This picture could be better though :) Hehe https://t.co/tI68fhiuLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FifthSolomon Poe was better at debating, but I still don't like her because of Danding Cojuangco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 million tweets, but how many brain cells?  https://t.co/qo7aTcui84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro Either will do as long as I can call you daddy. ðŸ˜»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhichHillaryCensored @Seb_Castro  https://t.co/oSRLFzLMnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree yes!  :) ðŸ˜»â¤ï¸ https://t.co/82xdRncPVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro Haha This is one of my favorite parts of your music video ðŸ”¥â¤ï¸ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just a bit serious and heavy for me, but I love Seb as always

#FeelTheBern music video: https://t.co/Vid2rxTpea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter party peoples #Karelasyon  https://t.co/ZnESf5eeoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real starting time 2.50pm â˜ðŸŽ‰ https://t.co/bVAjOpQVVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too funny https://t.co/OIoGztACKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @gmanetwork @mart_drosario I am totally watching this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more reason to hate Bongbong Marcos. As if pillaging our country wasn't enough.  https://t.co/UPSxQcmWp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not enough. It's time we demand equality and stop settling for being "worse than animals" ðŸ˜¤ Gay marriage now. https://t.co/KajF2TFjGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro No. First longer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro You will be fine. Promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @ANCALERTS @iamkarendavila Walang hiya. These trapos need to just stop running.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Fans, Take note!  https://t.co/M9lL7tGjsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GmaLovers Steamy!!ðŸ”¥ðŸ˜ðŸ”¥ðŸ˜ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for this :) https://t.co/eiSfvw20fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @KarelasyonGMA Crush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro He's falling for you ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I prefer Makabayan over Akbayan, I will definitely vote for @WaldenBello #PhVote #waldenbello https://t.co/SI6rQZNmmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I believe in @BayanMuna! Dont forget to vote for 1 who has always had the poor at heart Neri Colmenares! http://t.co/UzVMZjDJc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bongbongmarcos How much did you pay for your army of apologist idiots? 10 million? P50  Million? Fuck you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually liked his acting here. GanDah!  https://t.co/8B3tR7YJQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro @TIME  That's awesome. Sparks conversation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea I can so imagine this. ðŸ‘¬ +ðŸ‘¶ðŸ¼ https://t.co/76xAV1rGoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro I can't wait to watch, but I can't wait to watch the real thing even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone seen #HeneralLuna? How was it??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Poe is straight?! ðŸ˜µ  https://t.co/0P2siaR9ZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate it when people spread unnecessary hate on twitter, but I don't like seeing good people I love being attacked. Haist!  @aeLmo_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back off from Ryan. Ryan reports facts. Just bc your idol said something dumb or unlikeable doesn't give u da right. https://t.co/PQmekejmc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah someone is attacking our SebRy love love Ryan Chua because of a story?! @Fifth_SoIomon @Ryan_Castro @SebRy4Ever https://t.co/PQmekejmc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and I'm the most beautiful princess alive!  (according to my own survey) https://t.co/moSy9g3yX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Fuck ! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜µðŸ˜µ https://t.co/e0EHm9nFey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yass This is something that still doesn't exist here sadly. https://t.co/Mw5h7dT7XV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Castro Very very true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now why can't more Philippine politicians do this Haisst !!  https://t.co/n8wSxFlhRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me when I found out Enrile was being let out of jail.  https://t.co/Sd3QWqjiup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute twinsies :) https://t.co/t3CZEuhkar]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>