<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBanksy @neiltyson @tom_marzipan #weaponx #nextyearinthehalloffame https://t.co/7lmAefdFed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired pls stop recycling your trump rants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasteful government overreach. Clearly time to eliminate the agency. https://t.co/gH2EBoDZ5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired there's also a heavy post-apocalypse element]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired don't forget unlimited wireless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel I hear she will be wearing an imitation vegan meat dress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza "ok mr trump, playing Macarena on Spotify"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just waiting for a similar tweet about people dying from poisoned water https://t.co/nbjSVedzOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT like many sentient mammals they follow the shiny coins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired I never said that. Just saying no rules can stop civic corruption. Govt is made of people. Go read federalist papers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired the people in office have something to do with how the govt works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired all politicians spin, bend , exaggerate, assert. This is different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superwuster Jobs would have made the leap to WiGig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired our local park is a national park. There is a lot of canine disobedience going on there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ylanmui @SenSchumer why does this democratic firewall idea not inspire confidence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost was that the day Putin stole his Super Bowl ring?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crampell @WSJ Translation: diversified index funds are low-margin products.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired Correct. Probably an intern writes most of them at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom yeah but everyone knows there are 3.64 TRILLION refugees in the US because of our weak borders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePlumLineGS won't be long before the phrase is "repeal, replace, and repair"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NormEisen what's going on with his audit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePlumLineGS "opening up investor options". Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait Professional anarchists = jobs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio any plans for a mass audit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamsFlaFan @Fahrenthold @washingtonpost and Mnuchin made Storks. Nuff said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired i have the evidence should you ever be nominated to scotus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crampell @washingtonpost Gorsuch nomination in stark contrast to Sessions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewRepublic Andrew Jackson is quite the gossip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, reality tv isn't real?
@ https://t.co/9Lamp56Pyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired I'm sure it's very complicated....but not really so complicated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired in all seriousness public contracts should not be secret unless for natl security reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired I suppose, yes, you could be at a disadvantage if you disclose bribes and your competitors don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can the rationale possibly be? How hard is it to make a simple disclosure? https://t.co/szTriG97Ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias that's what Jared says!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennethBaer @attackerman @guardian my experience was that agencies take the process VERY seriously and for good reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired so now we call agencies that have worked fine for 80 years the "deep state"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @TheAtlantic my grandfather was illegal for 15 yrs bc of this law. Delayed his marriage to my grandmother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rschooley @benschwartzy @HeerJeet and made his money in Hollywood. Genuinely bicoastal elite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro @WSJ we're gonna end up with that sheriff from Wisconsin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennethBaer @taylorgourmet makes hoagies named for the street I grew up on and my dad's too. This is hard for me. But I will boycott.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP @jaketapper AP tweet headlines have gotten much better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect a lot more run-on sentences in the code of federal regulations https://t.co/6uPDFrLJlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza @JoeNBC @thedailybeast Do we want ANY know-it-all 30 year old making policy in a vacuum? Bypassing interagency coordination?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First women, then scientists. How long before Chairmen of Joint Chiefs march on Washington? https://t.co/a9BK38um9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg @andrewglazer @realDonaldTrump @nytimes "aptitude" and "conviction" doesn't sound like DJT's voice (if that even matters)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlcalderone @EricLiptonNYT @nytimes does he have a seat on NSC too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 I look forward to the President saying Happy Holidays to make us all feel included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennethBaer @ZekeJMiller how common for political advisor to be on this committee. Were @davidaxelrod, Valerie Jarrett, or Karl Rove?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @sppeoples look who are the serfs now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottwallsten surely there is division of labor in the White House - different people doing all of those things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveRattner can we start a cable news network that shows odds along with the news. Could be based in Vegas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A parable for our times: Multiplying Evil Rens beat up their clone, Indifferent Ren. https://t.co/H4gMsxlQ4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicahGrimes @maggieNYT so Bannon does interior decorating too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could a nice Camden County girl become so diabolical? Would things be different if eagles had won a super bowl? https://t.co/A87sZKWx4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottwallsten @WIRED Chinese have bought KEF and other storied brands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired @BillKristol and with the added feature of possibly banning all green card holders from reentering the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jirosenstein @joshtpm @TPM one gets the feeling that while Reince is filling out HR paperwork the two Steve's are writing executive orders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT @nytimes there have been several headlines like this: suggests a process issue not a one-time correction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @WSJ did he just approve a massive military aid package to Mexico like Obama did for Israel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day has finally come when I agree with Charles Krauthammer https://t.co/HZuaiBY1Hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias might need to hire some immigrant laborers to do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachbarnhart and basic numeracy if not statistics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 next thing you know he'll do something truly disqualifying like order a cheesesteak with Swiss cheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired @anneapplebaum @Twitter @BBCNews @jack Correct, much as MySpace didn't adapt to real identify and Facebook ate their lunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired @anneapplebaum @Twitter @BBCNews @jack avg users shld be able to get verified accounts and filter non-verified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired @willsommer we need a national crash course in statistics. Or maybe just counting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @SpeakerRyan how does cozying up to the Russian-Iranian-Assad axis make Israel more secure? https://t.co/axwwaE3G2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes now we can stop paying attention to the Dow: it's an obsolete index]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @voxdotcom maybe someone should take him to visit a golf course with a Syrian refugee golf pro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza @nytimes the proximity effect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thesis: people who own houses in multiple states are more likely to be registered to vote in multiple states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait @RyanLizza who's taking bets on how long it takes for them to reverse course on $20 bill?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costareports @AnnieLowrey @maggieNYT @nytimes an alternative choice https://t.co/VmWimhPhUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsWolf a winning (if not fair) strategy: winner take all in your team's states, proportional allocation in other team's states]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennethBaer @kennwhite get Rudy on the unsecured line, stat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @JoeBiden with all the infrastructure talk, what are the prospects for super high speed rail in the Northeast Corridor? cc @AmtrakNEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanweisman @KennethBaer because they couldn't climb the great blue wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FCCTech @NABShow @davidhlayer Please tell me this reception is nicknamed "Amateur Hour"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear new textbook editions are on the way... https://t.co/v0T6hK9XBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thesis: had election occurred prior to revival of Star Wars franchise we wouldn't be talking about "the resistance"

https://t.co/l5NsKGahDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired e.g., a source can have ideological bias without being partisan. Some biases are intentional, some not. Or click bait bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired Your distinction is underdeterminitive. There are more distinctions at play and most people intuitively grasp them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired Why is The Atlantic considered "the media" but Fox News, National Review, etc. are not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it obvious Kellyanne's remarks were a refutation of logical positivism? Clearly a commentary on Tarskian language vs metalanguage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCist DC is a burning hellscape of small plates restaurants and pilates studios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper except that millions of people experienced it firsthand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired because voters obviously delivered a mandate to upend the world order in favor of ethno-nationalism or whatever 🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLizza the audit is now permanently ongoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianstelter also, population growth, e.g., over 40% higher in 2016 than 1980. So viewership rate for Reagan was even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence think he's watching in the situation room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelaidylou @jbouie maybe they are looking at trump hotel not airbnb?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunKing "In our nation’s capital, killings have risen by 50 percent." Misleading. https://t.co/7AB4fPxuWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired I'm not being fecitious. My 2 kids are in a D.C. Charter school. I am on the board of the school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired look at how it's done in DC...50% of kids in charter schools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madebygoogle yes. The problem isn't playing it, it's that it recently started playing a foreign version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madebygoogle  "Ok Google play Moana soundtrack" "Ok Google play Winnie the Pooh soundtrack" We're using Spotify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Twitter offering to translate some of my tweets from Romanian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madebygoogle kids like to play moana and Winnie the Pooh soundtracks. Worked great. Then a few days ago started playing Hungarian version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soveryverytired And he wears stylish glasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieLowrey @nytimes the author probably lives in the neighborhood called Brooklyn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>