<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ER72JcLAqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Saturday on a Monday! Great session with @UnaHealy today! https://t.co/oxwRzx6LDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ER72JcLAqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt was an incredible actor who brought so much to every role he played. One of the greatest actors of his generation. A big loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays I can only sleep on stacks of magazines. I've got back issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAFCofficial @Alookman_ @premierleague @Everton What a player!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radiojagger As am Everton fan that was the highlight of our season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F**k off Pep! #evertonvsmancity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I used to go abroad as a kid I would dress inconspicuously so I could blend in with the locals. https://t.co/fF77PxdHvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To quote Morrissey, I would go out tonight but I haven't got a stitch to wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Graham Taylor. Brilliant club manager with Watford and Villa but who struggled at international level with England. Do I not like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morrisons Couldn't possibly eat it. Going to keep it in the freezer and only get it out to impress people who come round! #BiggestChipEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @Morrisons this is without a shadow of doubt the biggest frozen chip I've ever seen in my life! Is this a… https://t.co/6yyC7dC2VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1987 I was granted a scholarship to play in the NBA for the LA Lakers. https://t.co/oxsVYHaGZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a kid I once auditioned to be Harry Potter. https://t.co/enMdxrR7qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teabag stays in the Cup longer than we do! @Everton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you forget to switch Twitter accounts when you're on air! https://t.co/eaclICSLKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've made it to 2017. The year Schwarzenegger's film The Running Man was set in. It's time to start running!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Health, Harmony and Happiness! All the best for 2017. God bless you and all who sail in you! #HappyNewYearEveryone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant! 2016 The Movie.
https://t.co/no9neclbWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #georgemichael concert on BBC1 is so good. Incredible voice and lyrics. #prayingfortime one of the greatest songs ever recorded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More sad news today. RIP Carrie Fisher. #MaytheForcebeWithHer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do you stop saying Happy Xmas and begin wishing people Happy New Year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael was one of the most talented singer songwriters Britain has ever produced. His music was the soundtrack of my childhood. RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stick a fork in me I'm done. #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's The Lion King for me! F*** you Frozen. #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Pigs in Blankets this year instead we're having Goats in a Duvet! #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bucks Fizz for Breakfast @Cherylbaker ! Have a great Xmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite Carol of all time is @carolvorders #happychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has he been? Should I get up now? #xmasday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just done the Chris Rea #letchristmasbegin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abi Titmuss Everybody!!! https://t.co/27uB3g1kVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football Nation with @FranDonovanTV at 7pm. All the latest from @SwansOfficial @CardiffCityFC @NewportCounty &amp; @Wrexham_AFC on @NationRadio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that special time of the year again. The time we have to learn to accept the word 'sleeps' being temporarily used as a noun! #Xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank The Tank! #oldschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichFenton Hey mate. How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 16th December everybody!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShedSimove You too! Have to catch up soon mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ShedSimove good to see you on the tv tonight! Hope you're well. https://t.co/n2vcJJw9qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlhughesradio Think it's on one of my computers. I did a Xmas special with bands and singers telling the story behind their festive songs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interviewed Greg Lake once. Fascinating guy with so many incredible stories. Really hope his festive classic is Xmas number one this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireEliz86 Oh brilliant! Will have to watch that as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceWithNoLemon I don't know tbh. I would make sure I knew my cover story inside out if I did though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manuel looking for his pet Rat Basil in Fawlty Towers is still one of the best comedy moments ever. Still incredibly funny. #RIPAndrewSachs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60 Days In Jail is an incredible social experiment. Best show on TV at the moment. Tension and drama throughout. Groundbreaking reality TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SendACelebToJail Felony Griffith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my flatmate Craig for the early Xmas pressies! He must have seen my list. These were all in the top10! https://t.co/Ptd1cq9e3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't seen the Danny Dyer episode of 'Who Do You Think You Are?' yet make sure you do. Best TV show since 'Shaun Ryder On Aliens.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please can we all stop with the Mannequin videos now thank you. #gettingboringnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who they are but they're persistent! https://t.co/tTwVn2pSa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Radio First. A listener wants me to stop mentioning the weather as what I'm saying is stopping customers going to her shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mate @29Nolan has had a busy week keeping me updated with the breaking news! https://t.co/vaeVdFJJMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Sugar needs a new catchphrase. 'You're fired!'should be replaced by 'You're a C**k!' followed by him throwing a brick at the candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at 7 @NationRadio I'll be looking with @philblanche at the @FAWales World Cup clash with Serbia as well as all the weekends games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kat_barnes83 Good to have you listening again X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @tonyblackburn any idea who number 22 is in the picture round of my local pub quiz? @mydragonradio @ThamesRadio https://t.co/iI94SUwAIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanjenkins I would but I have a busy day at work tmw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump wins tonight please can the last person left remember to switch off the lights. #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am genuinely worried about what news I'm going to wake up to when my alarm goes off at 5 am tomorrow #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't listened to @mydragonradio yet, give it a listen! On DAB Across the whole of Wales and Online!https://t.co/Lz6UkFppjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quinnundo Should know by 4am UK time tmw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blame Brexit for this!
https://t.co/NNw0imLU9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody didn't this through properly! https://t.co/8205e07tST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VHC3 @mydragonradio Hey Vicky! Thanks for listening. The music we play gets me going in the morning..As well as the coffee X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Sir Jimmy Young. He's off to the radio station in the sky to do another award wining handover with Sir Terry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Chicken Scissor Salad for lunch! https://t.co/5WiqI0aEoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Emperor's New Wheels. https://t.co/NZ7lnAbVq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who's going to set fire to a scarecrow on a bonfire tonight to commemorate a bloke failing to blow up Parliament in 1605? #november5th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football Nation on @NationRadio at 7pm! All the news from @SwansOfficial @CardiffCityFC @NewportCounty &amp; @Wrexham_AFC !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 16.07, or 17.07 if you forgot to put your clock back last night, or 18.07 if you put your clock forward rather than back. #madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played Steve! https://t.co/Q7pBf8PDTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I regret this FB status from 5yrs ago! https://t.co/jZWnXJUp94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please Cher.... https://t.co/Y50C6OhDHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another beautiful day in Italy! https://t.co/rHaVUPcQbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a Cave Dweller! #Italia https://t.co/cgqsLRXMOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Italian views! https://t.co/nkF5rEUv7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't have time to Mount Vesuvius! #Italia https://t.co/3MtnDw44Z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always been fascinated by Pompeii. Today I finally get to explore it! #Italia #UpPompeii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted in the toilet of the bar we're in tonight! #NapoliGraffitti https://t.co/I0Pv75G84r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyblackburn Brilliant news Tony! Really pleased for you. #RadioRoyalty #GodfatherofBritishRadio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been saying this for years. https://t.co/8rkySY1Ptr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican City, The Trevi Fountain &amp; Shelley and Keats House on the Spanish Steps. I've stood in front of them all! https://t.co/JcAu614aiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic City! https://t.co/SbMhRYmzLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roaming in Rome. https://t.co/QVlFld52Xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in Rome....#Italia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought we were flying from Luton. We're not. #weareflyingfromgatwick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the pubs are starting to look younger! https://t.co/sEDqrOleXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time I've visited. Impossible to comprehend what everybody went through 50 years ago. So sad. #aberfantragedy https://t.co/IoQfRRhsiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always good to start a holiday by splashing out £140 on a new tyre and steel rim for the car!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Popprince Catch up over a beer soon mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @RoxannePallett hope you're ok! Would love to do an interview with you in Cardiff next year when the show comes to town! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant night @theCentre for Mamma Mia tnght. Brilliant cast with amazing songs that the audience loved! #abbadabbadoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Estella035 Really good. Did you watch it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Robbie Coltrane is innocent or guilty? #NationalTreasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This.... https://t.co/IUgWOXVTyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 days until my Italian adventure! Rome to Napoli driving along the coast. Can't wait to get away! #Italia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Chris called Rhondda. https://t.co/gKMnyPR90V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hare we go! C'mon Everybody! C C C C'mon Everybody @jive_bunny is on @ThamesRadio  @mydragonradio NOW! #RabbitRoyalty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a kid these were the equivalent of the iPhone 7. #gamer https://t.co/PFJQFAkXyj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>