<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Next month is Women's History Month. 
I'm betting @OrvilleIV offers better insight to women's history than @POTUS  
https://t.co/43lCcMw8ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatResources citation needed on the claim that job losses were due to the stream protection rule.  Please provide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoshuaJoss @ddale8 But even elementary students would offer at least a fact about figures in history! 
"Born in..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a student that didn't do any of the readings for #BlackHistoryMonth .  Ever.  ....EVER.      
Failing grade… https://t.co/ANUlq19LBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamMikaze I'm glad you're here &amp; I will be persistent in fighting for and advocating for refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our last #SCOTUS nominee was held up bc GOP questioned whether the acting POTUS reflected popular opinion. 
#resist https://t.co/Z1qdMU2Wpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["-his writings I've studied closely"  
999999999999999 Pinnochios!!!!
#SCOTUS #SCOTUSnominee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KofieYeboah Although people like anime, there are really only 12 good anime movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KofieYeboah Robotech was better than Macross, Mospeada, and Southern Cross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debsting That tweet could have been about anyone, right?    ...Yes, it's that bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will SCOTUS coverage take the bait?  Can media help itself from doing some anticipatory tale-of-the-tape comparisons?  ...Not confident. 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck this guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsLeahCatherine Are you listening @SpeakerRyan ?  Are you listening @GOP ?  Are you listening @DNC ? This is cruel &amp; a bad policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stay did not stop detention &amp; separation from families.Listen here for #LAX actions continuing in spite of the… https://t.co/0srN3UAz9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cj_reno6 @lowkell @AriBerman @DavidCornDC (ya see,  clean replenishing energy has a lot of benefits aside from climate)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cj_reno6 @lowkell @AriBerman @DavidCornDC or maybe @lowkell would be forwarding a technological edge in energy for export?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cj_reno6 @lowkell @AriBerman @DavidCornDC I'm guessing @lowkell would be improving air quality to reduce negative health effects?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No senator courtesy should be extended to someone with that response.  #NoSessions https://t.co/GYh1TuTbxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twoheadednerd The Wizard Wayback Machine!!!  Give me a heads up on needed issues.  I bought some in bulk last year.  Happy to donate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The line to get into City Council right now. 
#NoBanNoWall #Resist 
@District15Ohio https://t.co/jvcmpC2zrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth reading these tweets about flat out lies from Mnuchin.  #ForeclosureKing https://t.co/a7iPHTQQwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoshMandelOhio I take it you won't be representing the 2,000 refugees that became Ohioans last year?
#NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoshMandelOhio Your tweetstorm suggests approval of a #MuslimBan 
Will you go on record calling it that &amp; approving it?
#NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMandelOhio That's not a false dichotomy or anything, is it Josh?
Try this:
You want the most vulnerable people in the world dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop talking, Spicer.  And dammit, Robby have some self respect!
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/U5aeASPedw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoshMandelOhio is a candidate INSPIRED by Trump?!  What credible candidate says that?! 
(Keep retweeting Malkin, bro)
#NoBanNoWall #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 100 people condemning this heartless goon, but he gets 34 likes.  
Listen to constituents @JoshMandelOhio &amp; ma… https://t.co/Rrk7eNpIkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This hate monger @JoshMandelOhio wants your vote based on fear.  
(His head seems to be in the sand re:slaughter of… https://t.co/wAKydGz41q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep Stivers created this poll when he advocated for a Syrian refugee ban last year.  It's still open.
#NoBanNoWall 
https://t.co/oox4hB4B8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philnoto Just noticing your Twitter posts elsewhere. Sorry to make you repeat these conversations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philnoto Thank you for your work. Moving.  Needed. 
Would you be offended if that image found its way to telephone poles across Columbus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Marvel Will you make @philnoto prints available for purchase?  Proceeds to benefit @Refugees and @ACLU ? https://t.co/MctENUjQ7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so embarrassingly dumb.
...Refugees would suddenly get in faster? https://t.co/h6hK4iVQYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nation of immigrants &gt; Nation of fascists
#NoBanNoWall #PresidentSteveBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow this #RoyalRumble decision for #30 is TONE DEAF!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@alexisgoldstein is at the 4th tweet in this thread so far.  I'm certain she can produce 10x that amount. Read.  C… https://t.co/QOLu74vK0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously fucked up.  Look through the thread on this. https://t.co/IMg953Kwso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepSteveStivers @POTUS Locking us into a fossil fuel economy burgeoning green tech boom.  BAD investment with harmful consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepSteveStivers @RepBeatty I've taught financial literacy to refugees in Central Ohio for 7 years. They're part of your state. Support them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepSteveStivers Right now the biggest issue involves the thousands of refugees that will die due to the President's executive order.Speakup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepSteveStivers Your survey seemed to offer broad topics, but missed the point as to what the actual ISSUE was. Don't misuse my results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before anyone applauds the Koch brothers for opposing #PresidentSteveBannon , their full statement should assure yo… https://t.co/5oDDGsOchY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kroenig Anything to say about the refugee ban?  Your remarks at Ohio State last week suggest you may have something to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twoheadednerd You guys are the best-  thanks for doing this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattyMurray I wish I could vote for you.  This is what a leader looks like.  Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all those sticking up for Ivanka, do reconsider.  #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/o3af1sp5x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe I may have to give @Starbucks another chance.  Thank you for giving voice and opportunity https://t.co/OVpMGqQdp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenSherrodBrown for having compassion for those most in need and for responding to your public- you've g… https://t.co/6XHtK2tjX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twoheadednerd Could you fellas post the artist info or link?  I want to support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read their joint statement in full.  Bipartisan claims here- compassion, national security, proper policy-making pr… https://t.co/8EVRw7kebT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup.  Also, it shuts the door on the most vulnerable people in the world.  Tell your friends, Lindsey.  Not that th… https://t.co/w552O0fUUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexisgoldstein Also bizarre stance from a governor since governors actually apply to receive refugees. We'd be glad to take Alabama's!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon If you recall, the correction I was asking for was about terrorism rates reflated to refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Wouldn't it be good to provide the data that says that it's 1) unprecedented and 2) the result of an immigration crisis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon I distinguish terrorism trends from sexual assault.  I don't downplay it. I also try to look for data to see if trend matches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Show me where I ever try to deny a New Years rape event!  Not what I'm doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Look, you need DATA on these things! We don't do thought experiments on rape statistics.  I'm looking first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon looking at DATA now.  that's what you are supposed do.  You provide none, so i have to hunt.  Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Now you're conflating Muslim immigration with refugees. Data on refugee TERROR says you're wrong. Looking for rape stats now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon is is why you need to clean up your claim- conflating sexual assault with terrorist attacks (both without data) is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Go through your list of terrorism incidents.  Show me the refugees. I'll compare with Global Terrorism Database.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Your continued "point" across tweets was that "stats" say refugees increase terror. You don't provide a cite, but cite these.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Your use of "terorrism AND sexual assault" might need cleaned up here.
Let's combat sexual assault- I'm for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare this guy say "Never Forget"
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/gurD4ifrFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debsting i have a "you should feel bad" post that i talk myself out of writing several times an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tweet from Twitter worth reposting?   
YES.  Thanks for posting this @Twitter https://t.co/CL4fQi7AmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debsting and STILLit gets worse!
Waiting for all of those "change of heart" or apologetic FBposts from friends and family...STILLnone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jesus fucking christ https://t.co/0spmXdab41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thread- watch #jfk terminal resistance build from the beginning.  #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/IKuRNvciXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@senrobportman Your week in review didn't mention the ban on refugees- don't be silent! You tweeted "NEVER AGAIN"… https://t.co/YqDKj27aC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This video holds up well.  https://t.co/J9Q7ZO92x8. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon Not refugee terror perpetrators in Nice or Paris. What terror attacks are you citing here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinkyEmoticon @ChanelleL_ @navgirl63 @Tristanshouts what database are you using for your stats?  Because the #s say white men even with 911]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread.  Read. https://t.co/FyToPFrw7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a_house_plant @Apkamps Wondering what church @FranMFarber claims to belong to.   Churches here have been doing precisely that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWaid This is all I can think about this evening.   All the people condemned to death by our refugee policy.  N… https://t.co/vxCyNsKa19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wpjenna States already have a role.  Governors APPLY to the State Dept to receive refugees, localities apply to the Governor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many Christians grew up with an image of a white Jesus &amp; Mary that they consider anyone else in the middle east a threat.  #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But second,  they're liars.  No way they're playing "Stars" by Hear 'n Aid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First,  aren't they supposed to curate a collection FOR me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would a radio station advertise that they "play anything"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebiglead uh, these are @davemeltzerWON to a T.  The other people are personalities that are widely viewed.  Dave… https://t.co/qsQqgIAxMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenCox83 "About a week" was far too optimistic. And none of his voters care: https://t.co/sYVTrmAq5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly the public has to call in to Info Wars if they want the @POTUS to hear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGinther Any reason why your website still displays a still of @ZachScottOhio with "CRIMINAL" on the front pa… https://t.co/IdTjS03AJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck. This. Guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Mary.  I'm sorry you had to see all this in your final days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattbaumstein @twoheadednerd I listened to you guys recap a  Slayer story 2 minutes later, so...yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to know the limits to how @SenSherrodBrown extends "benefit of the doubt" to nominees. Here's his justificat… https://t.co/GJwR1vgrJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know why the POTUS fans object to the #NotMyPOTUS sentiment.  Don't they want to take sole credit for how FUCKING AMAZING THINGS ARE?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you start a flaming dumpster fire, do I have to acknowledge it as mine?
Even if we share a lease, do I have to?
#HesAllYours #NotMyPOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a list of refugee countries of origin. Show me which countries have had no terror incidents.@POTUS criteria… https://t.co/7ma0iNsrGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch for our Prez to botch the difference between refugees and asylees. Banning entry from instability/conflict origins bans all refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refusing refugee admission from "terror" afflicted nations would preclude admissions from every donor country. That's why they flee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know how this federal hiring freeze is going to deal with my daily phone calls to reps.  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_L I'm a fool!   I follow now- thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_L I'm seeing Annual Report forms signed by Trump yesterday. Are these documents demonstrating current involvemen… https://t.co/UhtVF3WStd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_L @ProPublica This is incredible- great work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_L @ProPublica What file are we looking for? https://t.co/Zh4FoodXfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomKludt The full show is..something. An awful song parody from Joe Scarborough. Norm Ornstein at the 43:18 mark: https://t.co/9hTSfU0O1G]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>