<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit. The Donald is awake. https://t.co/NL37cGIWVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mviser: This is huge: The DOJ -- under orders from acting AG...won’t defend Trump’s executive order. https://t.co/ZpVixyU6hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And more than two years ago I named my dog in honour of @Richard_Schiff's character. He's a great, great dog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oonagheats No offence taken! Your tweet was funny! Even at this late hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weekend I took refuge in The West Wing. Again. Despite the passage of time it seems more potent than ever. Thanks @Richard_Schiff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Colmogorman That was some pretty awesome cookin on #celebritymasterchefIRL tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claire Clark is on #celebritymasterchefIRL next week! She is one of the best pastry chefs in the world. She taught me how to make trifle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thing is, having been there, I can say with absolute certainty, that the stress on #celebritymasterchefIRL right now is completely genuine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niamh Kavanagh is on fire on #celebritymasterchefIRL..... not literally like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@robingillchef and @Midsummerchef are great judges on @MasterChef_IRL. So positive and upbeat. And so little ... https://t.co/RQMZNFWHIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, I do know Mundy is deep frying a pigeon on @MasterChef_IRL. Oh my my my oh my my my oh my my. deep fry.  #celebritymasterchefIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @MasterChef_IRL tonight. Although I missed the very start of the mystery box so have no idea what's going on  #celebritymasterchefIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a 2013 quote from Steve Bannon, the most powerful man in America today. #stoppresidentbannon https://t.co/BxeDs81f81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is Trump signing the executive orders targeting lightening? And lawn mowers? Oh, and armed Americans? https://t.co/MVAAtifJJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's #MuslimBan is just insane,  racist and incredibly counter-productive. It can not be allowed to stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They came through a storm. And those that didn't die want a better life. And they want it here. Talk about impressive." President Bartlett.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Midsummerchef For sure..... it'll have to be Coppinger Row!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Midsummerchef @IrishTimesLife I'm not sure where it can be bought but I'll stick a copy in the post.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day with the real Master Chef, @Midsummerchef https://t.co/uEz5y62fAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in tomorrow's @irishtimes there's...... ME! https://t.co/hBsXAXYm27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Shane_RossTD takes dress down Friday really seriously. https://t.co/pCiT9j7CaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The apocalypse is going to be tremendous. So special. Period. 
https://t.co/AWeWPwMuOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the Trump administration and @presssec's attention to detail that is so impressive. https://t.co/dvfY1avL21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@re_keogh I was really looking forward to writing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for nothing #euromillions.... And you know where you can stick your cheery "better look next times". https://t.co/1hu84cYVAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it you? Here's what you might do with your millions.https://t.co/yOHBxT9ICV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Irish person won €88 million on the euromillions tonight. If Pricewatch doesn't appear on Monday you can take it as read it was me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can almost feel the rage coming from the Express, Mail and Sun as UK Supreme Court rules May cannot trigger #Article50 without parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skint? Looking for tips to make it to the end of the week? https://t.co/0UoPwSprpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viagra, suicra, Barry's Tea, Donegal Catch.... Are they Irish or are they not? https://t.co/gQqBmT1lw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sheer brazenness of all the #TrumpLies would be hilarious were the situation not so grave. https://t.co/DuMHSOF49J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One big problem the Trump presidency has is an obsession with ratings. You're not a reality TV star anymore Donald.… https://t.co/cTuZmDJMEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alternative facts"? Just how stupid does the Trump administration think the American people are? https://t.co/EXR5a2Auqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up with this sort of thing. https://t.co/n3ancOCyV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cantonaisking77 If she paid by card she can use a "chargeback" with her bank to get money back. If she paid by cash it is more difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crowds. So let me tell you about the amazing crowds. So amazing. So big. The beautiful people stretched all the… https://t.co/H78ksyFu7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a cold and grey day for a march. https://t.co/jgOBFFqKNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PopulistwatchIr From what I saw, maybe 200 tops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #womensmarch is not the only protest taking place in Dublin today. https://t.co/IZIYouNOHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey Hey. Ho Ho Donald Trump has got to go" #womensmarch https://t.co/Lz3fzCLw3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garda tells me more than 5k marching against #Trump #womensmarch https://t.co/qytwusQdCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["anti women anti-gay Donald Trump go away" #womensmarch https://t.co/WM3kkNZZNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #womensmarch in #Dublin is well underway. Too early to guess at a turnout but there are a lot of people on the… https://t.co/dvm1rXsFY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus, @piersmorgan spends so much time trolling the world, it's a wonder he has time to do anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all the terrible things about it, this may be the worst thing about Trump's presidency. Poor woman. Poor country. https://t.co/fOJ51AF0VF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can you say? https://t.co/lmcr2xOqr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As of right now Donald #Trump is US president. No turning back now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My plea to President Trump. https://t.co/wpyYFukWV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazthebat Not many. The Ts&amp;Cs will outline it. If you want to mail me details - cpope@irishtimes.com - I can look into it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes good news happens. 

https://t.co/rPcN7UiERh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no words. https://t.co/5aeOzQuS0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmokane @philipnolan1 @manairport Sorry, there was one detail I did NOT recall. I flew Shannon to JFK.... and then connected to Boston.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmokane @philipnolan1 @manairport I was 20! I flew Aer Lingus from Shannon to Boston. I still recall almost every detail of the flight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the person who thieves the  bike I  locked outside the @IrishTimes last night drop it to any @dublinbikes station? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We just got sight of the email chain that brought Flatley to Washington. It's SO AMAZING.  #MickyLeaks #FakeNews via @irishtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeirdreOKane1 And I am left with nothing but beans. Thanks @SixOClockShow https://t.co/jkefD7xYok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DonnellyStephen and @NoelRock to take on the touts https://t.co/l4ajVbiDC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you could write Donald Trump a letter as he becomes US president, what you like him to hear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed. https://t.co/MEppdIsOfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Dan Brown had devised a plot along the lines of what is unfolding in the US  even his most trusting editor would have sent him packing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American press should stand in solidarity with @cnn and @acosta and robustly fight Trump's attempts to silence journalists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's treatment of @cnn's @Acosta as he tries to ask a question is absurd. Dangerously so. https://t.co/CMQYrQZHuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if this day - and this word - was the best moment for Donald to show a lack of understanding of  how quota… https://t.co/QGP99FjSBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The learning should never stop! https://t.co/QPP2vN87qM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see @BryanJOBrien shortlisted for Videographer of the Year in the UK @ukpicedsguild Awards! He better bring home the prize!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 Ah would you ever just jump in and stop complaining. It'll be grand once you get used to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edel_Schultz I surely am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin allies have made $29 billion on the back of Trump's triumph. #moneymoneymoney  https://t.co/eivsgGLQWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard an Irish act was on the Trainspotting 2 soundtrack and was sure it'd be Nathan Carter's Wagon Wheel. Turns out it's @Rubberbandits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A powerful and timely evisceration of the #AltRight in today's @irishtimes https://t.co/Q4PyKAUw0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year on https://t.co/owy0izF0tZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why yes! Yes I do! https://t.co/VnxrKvoaDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from his buffoonery, what's most striking here is the time frame. Just how slow does Trump type? https://t.co/rOxbw0DDiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have Meryl Streep. And then you have this. https://t.co/g22ut6lI7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've not seen this yet, watch it. It is awe-inspiringly great. https://t.co/B90HUB6mUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daffodils? Now? That can't be right, can it? https://t.co/nbgYR2ubsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Star Man. https://t.co/TTz5oW0rnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_jenner It's my children's favourite programme and the only kids show I don't sleep through. I wish it had been on when I were a lad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished another Horrible Histories marathon. It has to be the smartest kids' programme ever made. I love it. Thanks @greg_jenner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KOSullivanIT: David Remnick's considered verdict...Trump, Putin, and the Big Hack https://t.co/BU8laqKz9l via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenoconnell They are all women in their 40s and 50s who make for admirable role models. There are a whole lot more too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenoconnell Julia Louis-Dreyfus, Tina Fey
Amy Poehler, Halle Berry, Julianne moore, Rachel Weisz, Amy Adams, Cate Blanchett, Michelle Obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManMadeMoon To be fair, there's also the mindlessly irresponsible and utterly moronic tweeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece, this. https://t.co/XjtPPqsZMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any time Donald tweets something absurd like this I wonder what he's trying to hide in the smokescreen. https://t.co/JXqlfYYOSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Donald, I think your grandkids are on your @twitter account..... cos not even you could tweet this puerile non… https://t.co/0Njc3vfYcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a mail from Revenue promising you tax back? It's a scam. It's always a scam. https://t.co/NEUo9Rdwyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The famous blue latte is here. https://t.co/8xPaDS254j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Trump's real rime updates on the status and content of intelligence briefings. I feel so much safer kn… https://t.co/z5SZbGI1bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanofiachra I think most of the issues were due to a pre-christmas rush so they have probably all been resolved by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire not ice? That wouldn't make for quite such a dramatic film sequence. https://t.co/XYySEopZwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wipeable onesie from @Dominos_ROI in Rathmines? That IS a thing. With €50 to @Barretstown for each sale #DomiNewYear https://t.co/V1AZ8AF4aM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzienugent Finnegans Wake in 2017 so? That's a pacy little read with a great twist at the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzienugent What? Even the showboating Latiny bits???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CassandraRules Sorry, I keep forgetting what a peacemonger Putin is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many Americans are regretting their Trump vote tonight? https://t.co/sLLBgDEpsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016: The Movie. The best Internetty thing I've seen in ages.   https://t.co/LwUUEAWIUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to transform a room? The secret's in the paint. https://t.co/nkgwWJbQnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it only me or does anyone else go on Twitter these days filled with dread over who's next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dollymount today https://t.co/QrC5eZaJbV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>