<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Leafs always lose the lead in the 3rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taymacd0nald when are you headed there? I might be going too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Latin_sh13 well my mom said otherwise so ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a feckin eejit if you think groundhogs control weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samanthajhoover hahaha yeah looks like I'll need to pay him a visit thanks for the message!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samanthajhoover tell him I say a Snooty Fox lecture is needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleMedeiros_ feck that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casino outside how bout dah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaburnison one day I'm going to give a TED Talk on how to chirp efficiently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're expected to pay like $50,000 in school fees by the age of 25, #BellLetsTalk about how debt impacts the mental state of students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BellLetsTalk about how social media creates an illusion of company and comfort, when in reality it creates isolation and anxiousness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depression is a war, you may win a few battles but the aftermath is present. Smiles are sanctioned, happiness is rationed. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world of 9 to 5's, you need support from the 5 to 9's. Help your loved ones get through the stressful times #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure to follow @KyleDatz and favourite his message (not this tweet) to make a difference! #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/9MMYPdg8bW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold the fries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey can I get a McTequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally just spent 5 mins looking for my phone using my phone too https://t.co/mTdr8556dW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["hey how's university going" 

Me: https://t.co/RIomTL53nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prior priorities of a proletariat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrydee What type of nutbar would go eat at @NutbarCo? They must have some serious cashews to spend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how many more puns I can create if I study linguistics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tell you what, 51% for a guaranteed quarter million job increase https://t.co/PJTIoJNVS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jc is the boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough choices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHSTVNEWS half milk and a sugar I gotchu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHSTVNEWS can you tell Trabuccs I can't make first period, gunna be about 4 years late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changed myself trying to change the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik I apologise for my false words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleDatz I retract my statement too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, @JordanLan19 don't expose your trophy to try and get the fantasy league trophy https://t.co/df1NiVurgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik every NFL playoff game is a blowout, how's that fun as a sports fan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least the CFL playoff games are exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I deserve this hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a heated blanket time to KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hridgewell on a scale of 1 to turnt I was tfourns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ora is lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen a random husky run by on highway 8 near fruitland, tried to grab it but it's way too fast hope he finds home its too cold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked by this cool looking building that I thought was a coffee shop, turns out it's a cremation urn store. Don't ash me how that happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaburnison maybe his girlfriend bought it for him to keep puck bunnies like you away 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get so excited for double decker GO buses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaburnison the Leafs Jersey is the second best looking in the league, next to this one https://t.co/bzxnaIf1qd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pissed that my team is losing by 5 goals so just gunna tell Jess to feck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobbpope sounds like a hard person to read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik yeah, maybe you should start doing some scouting for your fantasy team while abroad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a strong feeling that it will a Minnesota vs Montreal cup final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lysszoccoli she doesn't talk to thaaaat many guys at once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_agot sippin on the finessey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eebgx0 grind until life becomes a vacation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik don't tell me how to live my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik yeah, 0 luck when it comes to your fantasy team too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a comeback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did every OHL super star get traded today or what @KyleMedeiros_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cheese! Put your hands up where I can see them" https://t.co/TN6UDGRPkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuhadSoLegit that is a surreal thought my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odell Feck-him Jr was salty after the loss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liam_barry_99 don't tell me how to live my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not content with how life is going, how can you contend with other people's content]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta struggle to succeed but damn this is something else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to do a mini workout and ended up ordering pizza and wings from Domino's instead oopsies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lonely nights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lysszoccoli que the tiny violin orca-stra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lysszoccoli sucks that he passed a whale tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Crow Attorney rules this man a free bird! https://t.co/BgxjmJGh6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to a Flyers prospect to lose it in OT of a championship game though just saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least it wasn't Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is Toews when you need him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shootouts shouldn't be in championship games no matter what level of play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes a knee on knee, comes back and snipes a beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik @TheGreatTait ohhhh good trade but they wouldn't give up Barrie tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There we go boys that's what happens when you shoooooot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIT THE PING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deenpawlik just connecting dots, Colorado is shopping Duchene, JVR being shopped too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope the Leafs trade JVR for Duchene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is nuts! We must dig to the bottom of this https://t.co/y2gcjooctw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Toronto has the 3rd best library in the entire world, and I'm here looking up memes and watching cat videos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me how to live my life https://t.co/8ciqo2Tku7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @justinepowerr hope to randomly see you on campus today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOYSSSSSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hridgewell honestly have no idea how I knew that 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hridgewell I think that means "not easy" or it's a swedish beer either way LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning against Sweden is inte latt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caton_lynn pizza pizza extra large with BBQ base and chicken with green pepper onions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caton_lynn following my heart rather than my expectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anumm09 preach gurl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TylerBoucher7 welcome to the show kid https://t.co/BsI1vfeN1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changing a major is a major pain in the ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anumm09 happiness is free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snaiils why did you screenie that hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TristanGeorge95 stay safe, hope you're doing okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snaiils my life is not a documentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lysszoccoli @Jc_Cordeiro_ my rhymes are like a Scottish granny's haggis served in Las Vegas, but I don't gamble on it cause I'm too sheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did U of T start the day after New Year's I'm still feeling the hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackhawks are never good in outdoor games just stop giving us one every year @NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellll Tarasenko decided to show up outta nowhere https://t.co/ynyvojvILi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ambition has gotten me this far, passion will carry me further]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make a difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanksgiving was lit last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MATTHEWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaantalST JENNY WITH THE SEASONING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanLan19 yeah, this time last year you were in first in the fantasy league and look what happened]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>