<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If Iran keeps it up, it's going to be finished at Faber College. @deanwormer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to those who hit the Australia-Iran-Mexico-Ukraine crisis superfecta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know. https://t.co/fB6rSna9RI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved that movie in which Frederick Douglass starred with his brother Kirk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's in line to join the Principals Committee. https://t.co/xQza1NJCIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Era Invites a Bolder Hollywood Red Carpet https://t.co/cuJJUPd74e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Washington Correspondent’s Own Refugee Experience https://t.co/GpAuUEn5EJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia-backed extremists are shelling Ukraine while president threatens to send troops to Mexico. Why should NATO worry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're going to have to insist on better readouts from the president's calls with foreign leaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They followed @tvandenbrook's exclusive. https://t.co/MxGD48pTmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did we miss the part of the 2016 campaign when Trump said his platform included getting in a feud with Australia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Longtime Doctor Says President Takes Hair-Growth Drug https://t.co/94RFprIR9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump critical of Iraq invasion during campaign, called McCain and Graham warmongers, now wants to invade Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combative White House tone started before today's threat to Iran. Australia, Mexico calls threatening to longtime allies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump threatens to send U.S. troops to Mexico to take care of 'bad hombres' https://t.co/G6VZ6cRgJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions in campaign funds went to Trump firms https://t.co/88uSyKKDX2 via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jared and Ivanka turned down a free dinner on date night. Could they have taken it? https://t.co/FVslnasK4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatened to break agreement with Australia in call with PM. https://t.co/QoZagVOasi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Trump giving CNN the cold shoulder? https://t.co/wwQa30eBfL via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Force busts retired four-star general down two ranks for coerced sex. Another @tvandenbrook exclusive.  https://t.co/tzI89VfKKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats, pushed by grass-root protests, unifying Trump opposition. @HeidiPrzybyla is on the case. https://t.co/xE9SmKDOIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump memorializes Navy SEAL killed in raid in Yemen at Dover base https://t.co/vGjWoWnhCM via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only one FAQ about 'Fifty Shades Darker:' Why? https://t.co/OfOSRz43U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA nominee David Shulkin vows faster improvement, more choices for veterans https://t.co/VaaZLP0Jrj via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House puts Iran 'on notice' after ballistic missile test https://t.co/pyXh8kZGlx via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Division III school John Carroll became a Patriots pipeline https://t.co/QDG9crr5XG via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep up the good work, Fred. Dead since 1895. https://t.co/3f6XwkFPO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would Dems confirm Sessions as AG just to get him out of the way so they can vote down DeVos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adviser Flynn puts Iran "on notice." Meanwhile, Russian-backed forces shelling Ukraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jenna Bush Hager quotes father on Islam, urges acceptance after Trump order https://t.co/S81oCjfAkw via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four copies of #NixonsGamble are checked out from @NLB in Singapore. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump opens Black History Month by calling black America a dystopian hellhole to be fixed by Ben Carson. https://t.co/v35x4Emwpy via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really a scoop. We posted this at the same time: https://t.co/pWltUuah1a @gregorykorte @singernews https://t.co/q9gjhtjCh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Is Jared Kushner? https://t.co/lSc9JSFn6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Gorsuch, the Nominee for a Stolen Seat https://t.co/CMrbkCac5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine clashes leave several dead and test Trump's Russia stance https://t.co/ZryK7wqNrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Go nuclear and abolish filibuster on Gorsuch vote if needed.  https://t.co/DMTAzSRxsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump tells McConnell to "go nuclear" on filibuster to get Gorsuch through Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump transition email shows initial effort to oust all inspectors general https://t.co/1WeAuHVoDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to Frederick Douglass: Keep up the good work. Douglass to Trump: Dude, I died 122 years ago, but thx anyway. https://t.co/b447cF3CPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump blasts 'fake news,' CNN at African-American history event.  https://t.co/b447cF3CPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "Frederick Douglass," who died in 1895, "is an example of somebody who’s done an amazing job and is being recognized more and more."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British leader Theresa May: Trump's travel ban 'divisive and wrong' https://t.co/45Qk98aqYw via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's next in legal battle over Trump's immigration ban https://t.co/dTHgIfUP4s via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton signs two book deals https://t.co/jtspKA2B7f via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary's new book is NOT called "It Takes a Village to Lose to Donald Trump" but maybe it should. https://t.co/jtspKA2B7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House Has Cut Off CNN. Network should use this as a badge of honor but instead will probably beg. https://t.co/J2rxTthkVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President conducts African American listening session but devotes his time criticizing CNN, but not for not giving Don Lemon more air time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The racist history of the group Trump trusts to investigate his voter fraud claims: https://t.co/CNXOX1pwM6 via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Supreme Court pick is not as bad on criminal justice as you might expect: https://t.co/KUYKijX2AD via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's big announcement: Donald Trump has picked a Supreme Court justice https://t.co/ywsYv38wzd via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Gorsuch is principled, dexterous, eloquent. Basically, nothing like Donald Trump: https://t.co/slnpyDZ5Ae via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Supreme Court reality show—the capstone of a long campaign to degrade the law: https://t.co/yohiNV4V2C via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Call it a Muslim ban if you want https://t.co/1XMQiXvK4X via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strife Over Immigrants: Can California Foretell Nation’s Future? https://t.co/6tEHkjcbYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Steve Bannon is Trump’s conscience. Yikes. https://t.co/XOPf9eiwsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | For Bannon, the game has only just begun https://t.co/rBWp8pBlm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The GOP senators who spoke up against Trump’s ban are all talk https://t.co/rOrGFIEu5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Why let ’em in?’ Understanding Bannon’s worldview and the policies that follow. https://t.co/MUmy9fVFg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In deadly Yemen raid, a lesson for Trump's national security team https://t.co/wXMCP0bCwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See how Richard Nixon burned LBJ in the Paris Peace Talks in #NixonsGamble at @collincollege]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scaramucci fights to stay in the White House https://t.co/EbuVHNlYVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worlds collide! https://t.co/wI28OidnT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have thought that Gorsuch, a Protestant, would somehow be a diversity pick for the court?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems like a pretty thin reed to hang onto, as much as I like the Netherlands and Oregon. https://t.co/nQtDzK3BTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wyden issues release criticizing Gorsuch's opposition to Oregon's death with dignity law. Important, maybe. A disqualifier? Hard to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merrick Garland knew when he was picked that his confirmation was a long shot. Still, a tough moment for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of your politics, the nomination of someone to the Supreme Court is a grand and humbling moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Unanimous. Can you believe that, with what's going on? ... I think it's going to happen."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court pick is Judge Neil Gorsuch. Was it a surprise? Not really, but they did a great job keeping the secret until the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump calls this the most transparent Supreme Court nomination in history. "I will do as I say."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4politics2 @philwillon Enough for two days on TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Muslim ban poll finds Americans support Trump order by 8-point margin: https://t.co/zotCrV9eDw via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon's comments show how he sees U.S. in a clash of civilizations with Islamic world. https://t.co/3JOEgR1utp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof that Nixon "monkey-wrenched" Vietnam peace talks @HuffPostBlog https://t.co/9MNQuzVZEa via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon words on Islam, China at odds with decades of U.S. foreign policy doctrine https://t.co/SfGimh8XZ6 via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite talk, Trump postpones cybersecurity order https://t.co/YDwMazYZH0 via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jermain Defoe is so old that he must have been in my high school class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish color commentator in Spurs-Sunderland game sounds like Groundskeeper Willie after a bender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey joins '60 Minutes' this fall https://t.co/EbVQFXSOxp via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brunhilde Pomsel, Goebbels’s Secretary and Witness to Nazis’ Fall, Dies at 106 https://t.co/FCWA5svHqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Robert De Niro Learned to Become ‘The Comedian’ https://t.co/Cko20Tsbg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inmate on bashing cellmate's head: 'He wouldn't die' Oh, OK. https://t.co/219gDp94Hi via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is Stephen Miller’s Job, Anyway? https://t.co/rfAcHSi2iZ via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenkinsSkeeter Ban seems punitive and dogmatic. They prefer a different term, but they undercut their arguments when prez. calls it a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican Fausts https://t.co/VTUjo9W0vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President calls the media despicable, but @PressSec implies he's so impressionable that he uses media's wording on… https://t.co/jaJ5q8c6SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the president's tweet calling the immigration order a ban. https://t.co/lzyBlHyz0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obstructionist Senate just confirmed president's choice to be transportation secretary by a 93-6 vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's one-sided to look at @realDonaldTrump as divisive, @PressSec says. This morning, the president called his opponents names on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is really questioning the president's right to remove Yates. She served at his pleasure, and he was no longer pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec calls travel ban a vetting system, but it's one in which certain people are banned from traveling, even if vetted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it seems @realDonaldTrump waits for @PressSec to say something and then tweets the opposite just to see what happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The immigration order is not a ban, until the president and Homeland Security secretary call it  one, which they did today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec says the default position is qualified nominees should be confirmed. Tell that to Merrick Garland, whom Orrin Hatch praised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec says the immigration order isn't a ban, but his boss tweeted a couple of days ago that it was a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet secretaries who are kept out of the loop tell someone about it, but they don't do it on the record to confirm it to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't mess with @AprilDRyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kelly, the one Trump Cabinet nominee Democrats seemed to like the most, may be the first one to quit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The immigration order didn't have to mention Muslims, just as EO 9066 didn't mention Japanese Americans. https://t.co/xeei26iMiO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>