<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna miss "Andy Polley" https://t.co/mXadtTX7K3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #dctech, we’re looking for an  IT Operations associate to help @fundrise continue scaling in 2017  https://t.co/UbxyXTEtt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Mets’ general manager does not want Tim Tebow to be viewed as “a circus animal.”
https://t.co/a7hrQ293DK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I feel really really old. https://t.co/AWuSBpXSzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Brooks is completely lost out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is outrageous by the new @Dropbox desktop client:
https://t.co/1np6MQuAbC. Absolutely the wrong thing to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimFullerton he's home schooled. It's not his fault?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brady and Belichek endorsing Trump?!? Say it ain't so @TimFullerton!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can they buy @shophouse too? https://t.co/noWQpiHrQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should do this, bigly. https://t.co/PgWxg28Lzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be it for Papi @TimFullerton. Don't worry, @TimTebow will be up with the Mets soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #dctech, if you’re ready to move beyond MEAN and LAMP:
https://t.co/SE1YwSmFMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing how it is fall, is @TimFullerton a fan of apples? https://t.co/d80h4NkNrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that it would ever happen but how good would a Jerry Springer debate cameo be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @sendgrid_ops, we have multiple campaigns that are not being delivered. Is there an update or ETA on a resolution?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[September call up? https://t.co/EgMSQN8gLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing the Wisconsin players held it together after that dirty hit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimFullerton it's worth it to have him on the roster for the pregame speeches. #ironsharpensiron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curt Schilling and @TimFullerton, peas in an anti-Tebow pod https://t.co/w2S1HQ21wJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re looking for a great accountant to join @fundrise. We’re growing quickly and have unique problems to solve! https://t.co/DsHpT761G4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #dctech, we’re looking for multiple Software Engineers to join @fundrise: https://t.co/VDaK8s7KRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of @fundrise Engineer Nathan for achieving "Hot" #Chiptopia status for July. Only 22 burritos to go! https://t.co/OEo0i4qsUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited that @fundrise is on @mint, @PersonalCapital and @Betterment! https://t.co/BVfdLL3aQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fundrise passed 100,000 Users tonight! Should we put the car in reverse so we can get a photo at an even 100,000? https://t.co/oVevpNJtAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 1,000 before @fundrise hits 100,000! https://t.co/AZ1fcZ85Fy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMillerise, you gotta have a cars with the doors that open like *this*, not like “this” https://t.co/Fs6OWkJk1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a crucial set up by Wondo https://t.co/nWPeX2iaKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tactics schmactics. https://t.co/LdOywhuuol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fundrise is less than 3,000 away from the 100,000 milestone. Those are Pied Piper launch numbers! @SiliconHBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump coming out to "We are the Champions" is amazing. Can he debate Hillary on WWE Raw?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In '02 we had Reyna, Donovan, McBride, O'Brien, Cherundolo, Beasley, Pope, Friedel. Who in todays 11 would you take over them? #USAvCRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fundrise Review: Diversify with Online Real Estate Investing https://t.co/K8aGUuKY9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else ever wonder why English speakers call Costa Rica, Costa Rica, but call Ivory Coast, Ivory Coast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious about @fundrise deals? Check out our deal track record:
https://t.co/Hrw9lJuW5M https://t.co/VO8WrVsLOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just released our new @fundrise Track Record page with a fancy new @Mapbox map: https://t.co/Hrw9lJuW5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fundrise supports Pied Piper also preferring tabs over spaces!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your money outperforming the S&amp;P 500?
https://t.co/UQF7DTjdVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @sendgrid_ops, we just uploaded a list and received the notification that the upload was complete but we’re not seeing the contacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$280MM to UCLA and the players get $0. @JayBilas https://t.co/LV30PJJz41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1.8% of all LinkedIn passwords in the breach were “123456”. https://t.co/UbeLabQPFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4 questions to ask when purchasing an investment property: https://t.co/IRE6Kt4kYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Eater_DC, any idea who's smoking bbq next to Kramerbooks? https://t.co/Q7zvvjRD5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you use ImageMagick: https://t.co/81W3OH1i8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @penne311!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch for @fundrise by @maketto1351 x @shakeshack! https://t.co/EHTllxe55z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafferty: "How about those onions!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omarish @MintCares Omar, we heard from the @mint team that they’re working on it. Hopefully we’ll have an update in the next few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @StubHub think’s I’m a loser. They just sent me an email titled “You could use a night out” Ouch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited that @fundrise is now in beta with @mint!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimFullerton As @TimTebow would quote Luke 6:22: Blessed are you when people hate you and when they exclude you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Tebow 3/16 @TimFullerton. Between the Ides and St Patrick is another Saintly figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did “Please Advise” become the closing salutation for every customer support email?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LukeWhosTalking, any idea what @KendallDavisDC is talking about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marcus Rashford is Harry Kane-ing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtpoet Not necessarily. Our web application security does block certain bots so it’s possible your VPN was misidentified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtpoet Could you send me the URL you are trying to access?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to have our new Accountant to our @fundrise team, Brooks Horn! https://t.co/WOk5bhdTU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to our new @fundrise team member, Sarah Nania!

https://t.co/SeikNvYNoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 yo boy at MSG: "Daddy, why don't the Rangers try to win?" #CapitalsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Case Keenum can beat the Seahawks what chance do they have against Captain Kirk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investors Blow Top Off Fundrise's eREIT, Sells Out In Four Hours - Capital Markets https://t.co/dbHlo50mRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. $2 million in 20 minutes on @fundrise. https://t.co/3dD7oVgazD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a terrible half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up the echoes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible clock management. Use a timeout!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to DC's 2015 Restaurant of the Year @maketto1351! https://t.co/XG86Z9Ufxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our latest @fundrise deal just closed out in 23 minutes! Man things have changed since last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be a way to shame the people who post on @elance to copy your website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #dctech we’re looking to hire a great Content &amp; Marketing Manager to help grow @fundrise:
https://t.co/MtEOuCnXzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We just sold out our latest $1.6MM @fundrise deal in 3 hours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a tour of the new @fundrise investor experience: https://t.co/jBA47C9w4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We just released a new version of the @fundrise logged-in investor website. Let us know what you think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HubSpot It's over now but GA was reporting it was coming from your network in Ashburn. User agent was Chrome but it behaved like a spider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @HubSpot, seeing a lot of traffic from your network, whatcha guys doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for @maketto1351 for Eater’s Restaurant of the Year:
https://t.co/fWA96turET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our latest @fundrise deal https://t.co/EenOsIWM8F closed in 44 minutes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TimFullerton I hardly think that's how I would characterize two national championships and a Heisman trophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TimFullerton I think @timtebow would endorse Python. It's versatile like a run-pass QB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miles_matthias Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only available in Dupont!  @LukeWhosTalking http://t.co/kOv3Y2Ts6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That hurts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimFullerton Filming the practices?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, @timfullerton, seems like the Pats had good film on the Steelers goal line D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Mitch Williams was given three shots to blow a season for the Phillies he'd be up in Storen territory. #Nationals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimFullerton This is a dark day. But as Tebow says, it's always darkest before the dawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tebow time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to our newest @fundrise engineer https://t.co/CLiz0FehB3!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fly Tebow Fly!
https://t.co/uEg3jWUCVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited that @FLOTUS was at @fundrise’s first deal, Maketto last night:
http://t.co/agw7Ny27sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would sign @TimTebow in a heartbeat. Heard you could use him for the first 4 games this year! #OhSnap! https://t.co/OpgWqWvpZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @maketto1351 for being named one of the 21 Best New Restaurants in America http://t.co/FrRlsueySP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a tiebreaker. Come on Fed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @dominos, since @pizzahut can’t make us a hot dog pizza for us any chance we could get one from you? Our office is full of hungry people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PizzaHutCares We tried that last night. Can we get another branch to delivery to us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @pizzahut, how come we can’t order the “Total-Game Changer”? All @fundrise wants for lunch is a hot dog pizza! http://t.co/pXmo4beDBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PizzaHutCares we filed the report and hope the hot dog crust is in our future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We tried to order a hot dog crust pizza for the @fundrise office from @pizzahut but they didnt have the ingredients. #disappointment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That has to be red]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for the truth to come out. https://t.co/mVokv3bkpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re looking to hire a customer service associate @fundrise.

http://t.co/vHypRkrz82]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>