<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff still have to be mindful of available funds. Diabolical is harsh word. I think simply intionally favoring owners/RE industry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff agreed. I wish I knew why they did it: economic illiteracy or wilfully bad/corrupt policy making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff still a disastrous idea. How is a "conservative" party handing out taxpayer money to inflate property prices even further]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember being a kid and thinking there was such a thing as an adult?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamirHot haha - I'm adopting Trump's speaking style. Seems to work for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good talk re psychedelics by @markhadenblog at @Vancouver_CM this morning https://t.co/5dIUWKJX0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamirHot what's frustrating is that many voting for him for this issue alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little known fact: Swiss Chalet was originally called Meat Spin House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS JUST-IN (get it???): Politician lies. https://t.co/SX1u5ZVWhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun thing to ask at a doughnut shop: "excuse me, how long are you johns?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally an app made for me. https://t.co/2r28ZXpCpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CoV seems to (1) care more about brand than reality (2) not get urgency/need for substantially new housing stock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we want to reduce carbon, we should focus on easier/less-costly solutions first. See attached McKinsey GHG abate… https://t.co/WXK25rryla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obsession with "green" over affordability is out of touch with reality. Buildings represent a small fraction of car… https://t.co/too3YBF4X5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Vancouver struggles with a supply and affordability problem, CoV adds additional building reqs to be "green"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to social media echo chambers some ppl may not realize that majority of Americans (sadly) support muslim ban https://t.co/NmGXHvwAzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staydecent completely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more complex the world gets, the easier it is for a demagogue to rise to power with simple/scapegoat arguments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SyrupTrap oh don't worry. As Dawkins has said, Islamophobia isn't really a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff @HousingBC keep up the good work, brother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff @HousingBC that's good. Have they been receptive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDavidoff @HousingBC thanks for advocating common sense solutions. Curious: have you found any willing ears in the BCLibs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes art explains reality better than words https://t.co/TO80KRKiMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tunayo thanks. Appreciate the kind words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My argument for more housing supply in Vancouver https://t.co/Pvqvar6JCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do top cities for artists have in common? All hubs of commerce. Business and Art are complementary not hostile https://t.co/w4TJo7c8LJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a Trump fan but why are people so against the wall? A country has a right to sovereignty. And $14B isn't much and will create jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5/ Not to mention you cannot attract tech cos when you have a rep of being hostile to disruption (aka Uber)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4/ solutions must attract/retain good people to city, and nurture cross-polination of knowledge/talent. Grants and tax breaks are not enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ Politicians/bureaucrats think in linear input-output. Startups don’t have that luxury - must think of non-linear / dynamic systems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ Startups + tech companies are attracted to cities with existing tech talent, infrastructure. Creating one from scratch is tough af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building a local tech ecosystem is itself a chicken+egg network-effect problem. Aka a startup. Which is why politicians are so bad at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc I agree. Lack of good local news (and public support for it) are themselves a shame on BC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's embarrassing that the public only cares about local issues once Americans (NYT) report on them. We need more self respect. #BCPoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianbremmer You wore a parka to an interview? How cold was that room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[traffic is looking good today :| https://t.co/yHj63n80IR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[we] make peaceful revolutions impossible by refusing to give up the privileges that come from immense profits of overseas investments -MLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use the word inspiring sparingly, but MLK's courage and conviction truly is. This speech will give you chills. https://t.co/ATXMUIkEgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I thought of this. https://t.co/fu6lHJWp5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertriecken completely agree. I figure the "fairness" of tax burden issue goes more unnoticed. Sold as $ argument not justice argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karamcnair GBI requires collecting more taxes. If not everyone is paying in fairly, people will revolt against the idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtnbvan too many gov decisions based solely on economic cost/benefit. "Soft" costs are not understood or appreciated. It's a shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtnbvan their mandate has been flawed. Audits should not be based on ROI or ease. Social costs are greater than financial nickel and diming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The left and promoters of guaranteed basic income, in particular, need to advocate this. cc @scottsantens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gov's role should not just be collecting $ but promoting confidence in system/shared responsibility by punishing shirking even at a loss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is why tax cheats/loopholes cost more to system than revenue loss. They create permanent fissures and resentments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What politicians don't understand is that people's appetite for taxes is proportional to perceived fairness of tax burden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhwfung @JustinTrudeau in Canada they'd get a $1000 fine that they could spend years appealing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At bottom of listing: *house comes with human. Email for more than arm pics. https://t.co/GTxvEJyhnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SThomps @lzimm showed me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About 1-2% of designers are genuinely capable of anything besides me-too designs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protip: stock market gains tend to happen gradually, while losses are quick and dramatic. Returns are nowhere near normal distribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pretty much my life https://t.co/NCZ8vjxzHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question: does anyone actually still use Dreamweaver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports are about as fair as things get... so not that fair -@billburr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astropadapp I bought standard and was disappointed with its speed. I see there is Studio now. Can I pay the difference for the upgrade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodgeheave that and a stutter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many girls have had erotic fantasies about Porky Pig? There's got to be at least 12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stop looking at this. https://t.co/C8RezNW8Uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain is like David Attenborough. You know it'll seduce you after a few too many drinks, but you're really looking forward to Planet Earth 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved Meryl Streep's speech, but why did she need to put down football? It perpetuates the whole two Americas thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man didn't write a book about persuasion for nothing. https://t.co/TInPPm6Mbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc yeah, debating opinion is rewarding. Debating facts is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc to be fair, differences of (informed) opinion are also abound. I debate with smart/knowledgable ppl all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc local news is just awful on this stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elharaty just read your bio. Bloodsport 4lyfe, brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder. Billy Bush was fired and Donald Trump became president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self awareness https://t.co/ptG9qCTrfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Relationship Between Cognitive Ability and Experiences of Vaginal, Oral, and Anal Sex
https://t.co/ULfYFNg7xQ https://t.co/SWjxfNDrlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fiscal argument for single-payer healthcare in a nutshell. TLDR: competition doesn't reduce prices when it come… https://t.co/kNxNQ88qfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rudolfwinestock yeah, I'm not even talking of right and wrong, just the sheer irony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wisemonkeysblog straight up. Gotta call propaganda what it is though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a country interferes with US elections, it's act of war. If US interferes with a country's election, it's advancing freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I aspire to live by opposites. Like being assertive and open minded. Confident and humble. Loving and rational. Self assured and vulnerable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm curious. Do you think we need more housing supply in Vancouver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loyalty is promises we keep to others. Principles are promises we keep to ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goklemp happy new year, George. Best to you and your family :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should think about Alex Trebek. A lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rich people pay less in local/state taxes. Taxation is part of inequality problem. US data but presumably true of C… https://t.co/eRRY67lHoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BillGates on energy, Trump, and markets. Good interview. https://t.co/as9G9BNyAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael's Older was one of the first albums I listened to in its entirety. I just started listening to it again. Damn it's amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can ppl stop editorializing videos w/ words like "OWNED" and "SCHOOLED"? Politics aside, Kellyanne answered well https://t.co/nXqFYvoYZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wynlim this put a smile on my face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is lit. Merry christmas https://t.co/6SZ9q80YSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueNose1989 sadly you're right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I feel about the new @KidCudi album https://t.co/j4dESV38Qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(1) brain drain (2) overregulation (3) monopolies (4) overly-financial business culture (5) over-reliance on US... to name just a few]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think Canada's economic woes are temporary/cyclical. We have fundamental/structural problems that will persist if unattended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bando416 I love your stuff. Will you be performing in Toronto over the holidays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article's explanations are weak. Better explanation: rates rise in inflationary env. People invest in safe assets like RE during inflation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't assume home prices are (strongly) affected by interest rates. https://t.co/Gaw3OXj77q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@maxkellerman on Steve Balmer "he managed to do a v bad job running a big org and got rich bc he happened to be the 11th guy in the garage"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ednever I agree. That's where encouraging density comes in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ednever I think you and I agree on solutions. (1) less gov (2) more supply (3) incentivize productive use of land (e.g., LVT)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to mention how fiscally irresponsible this is. BC/taxpayers are now forever in bed with RE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't make housing more affordable by artificially creating demand from people who can't/shouldn't afford a home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is reckless, misguided and counterproductive. Headline should be "Tax dollars funnelled to fuel housing prices" https://t.co/zCWxGQ7L2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to work on my ping pong serve https://t.co/HEkTDeAbKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiveThirtyEight Elon Musk cloned himself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westworld in a nutshell via @PBFcomics https://t.co/fNu40xJThz https://t.co/4hyVpjDAFD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>