<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[He wants a star on his school work. https://t.co/vBLhF9NXqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for stepping up. I'll have a Bud. https://t.co/INtojzlvlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats and liberals: While you were protesting and feeling good about resisting, you were being duped and it's... https://t.co/SOx2zBmnr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brave and brilliant. https://t.co/Wy38E9LZY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Justin Trudeau did what a man does, he takes responsibility.  He was the first person refugees met at the... https://t.co/6isdk81XE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a shout out to the governors who kept a steady hand and ignored the fucktoids in the W.H. and got court... https://t.co/AJuROfbBz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada &amp; Mexico are the top two trading partners for USA and are getting better terms with more stable partners than Trump &amp; his pal Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DisBERA Justin Trudeau was warmly received by Canadians over the past year.  It still takes in Muslims and others from Syria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American leaders gave our country to a sick man, who grabbed power and became a patsy to a Russian dictator. What could go wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American leaders gave away our country to a sick man, who grabbed power, a man who is a patsy to a Russian... https://t.co/Ra66ux26TL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John, I am indeed pleased to see the NDP take the lead and heartened to see my MLA David Eby's dogged pursuit of... https://t.co/P1BJz11ksf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer humanity search for intelligence than money. https://t.co/jOYkTjhLhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is the simpleton Ryan and his attack dogs when the GOP uses private email? https://t.co/Ue0U3pzvVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha ha ha... the park workers in the Badlands national park ignored Trump's gag order not to talk about climate... https://t.co/3XZDTaxGPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry Brown has thrown down the gauntlet to Trump on civil liberties. Back off! https://t.co/xkeY6y5fTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bafflegab!!!  A word to describe horse SHIT. https://t.co/sR3Oy2ipEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harsh, dude. That's no way to treat a lady. #FreeMelania. https://t.co/nuK14BwmOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeShandrick By all means...it was a rigged election after all... https://t.co/7ttm7dzoxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government workers in the Badlands refuse to sign gag orders not to mention climate change re the piplines. This... https://t.co/YkIQRYYL8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dutch make a deal with Trump. It's the best deal ever invented. https://t.co/RJa6PSgDCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destroying sacred land for dead energy is not an American value. Just ask Custer. https://t.co/FT3ryddlcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our revolution 1963-1973. Learn from ours but make your own. https://t.co/mQjjkSJEpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was my revolution. 1963- 1971 https://t.co/arTZVUE833]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the march of the possible. Do I hear an Amen. https://t.co/hK7ExwvmmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The largest protest in the entire history of the United States. And women organized it. https://t.co/zodU2ovEd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! A liberating song from a new generation of liberated women. https://t.co/B32yBUqlnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why America got job  creation all wrong. https://t.co/aJSkWQ2fSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this film. https://t.co/8IwTfDi8UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Fake News: Disturbed Man Gets Past White House Security, Gives Press Conference https://t.co/HsF3rSgVhE via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fairer sex has spoken. Fasten your seat belt. We ain't in Kansas anymore. https://t.co/rMUlt7otMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gift from Moby to drown out the buillshit coming from the puppet masters. https://t.co/nFwXRVcRud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump voters lead nation in drug abuse. Look it up. They were fucked up when they voted. https://t.co/nzvLIs5kzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Participants at the Sundance Film Festival in Park City, Utah march for women. https://t.co/vLjHvkQhkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds to me like Trump bargained to use the White House for free. https://t.co/gw7Kg8ykMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if this will be framed for Trump's Oval Office. https://t.co/tgdgIS7NbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until this is verified by Canadian authorities it falls under "fake news". https://t.co/kof9f0iA5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There Are More People At National Mall For Women's March Than Attended Trump Inauguration https://t.co/evuvpFs4b3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister is marching in Denver along with her daughters and grandchildren on this historic event. Never... https://t.co/1wIJgA9mz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three times in  the past three years there have been oil spills from tankers, two of those in the Burrard inlet.... https://t.co/ctNxKRf2nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC leaders: we say NO to Kinder Morgan https://t.co/vQF5YYpbgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trump idiot doesn't know a gun from a bear. https://t.co/wEje054gfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ignorant man has deliverer us sheep disguised as wolves. https://t.co/RF0KrxpGPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No point in healing. Don't sit down with the traitors. https://t.co/fXQ9D3v1LG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count me in....for the impeachment proceedings. https://t.co/sNBfmgYfqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took a nation wide search to find a showman jerk who has an enormous ego and who wants to be the next PM. https://t.co/1zqOvmIs2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the flat earth bankers. https://t.co/WO4qq5h7UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomofsnj On radio I heard how the French were defeated. Gave Vietnam a miss. As I will the US for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LifeTrumppoliti @tomofsnj Trump, a whore mongering liar,and racist traitor, is not my president. Thank you Mr. Lewis for calling him out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W.'s popularity will soar in coming days. https://t.co/igI0tBeAe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a white kid who organized a sit-in at school to suppot Dr. King in my small town. It was the smartest thing I… https://t.co/qR4W29FtWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynetteBenton I would like to send you links about my days as a young writer sent to compete with HST. Hs was not afraid of Nixon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shwood oil,gas,coal is dead energy that poisons. On the wind and sun expand life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyZuker @HumanityCritic FAKE TRUMP Who is starting to look like a guy who needs an ambulance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ass hole at the bar who needs attention. https://t.co/i8X6UBb6KZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't about the money, there was a higher calling as machines worldwide protested the Inaugural. https://t.co/loUV8OJHUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karaoke Machine Backs Out of Performing at Inauguration https://t.co/KeVCC6CyCf via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Deletes Donald Trump’s Twitter Account: “We Will Not Tolerate Racism &amp; Hate” https://t.co/QHjjHDi5eU via @CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Youxia88 @AcuffBrose I grew up around five uncles &amp; my father, whom fought in the war. I knew early about Hitler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a Twitter user who applauds Twitter Corps resolve to delete the account of Donald J Trump for his racist &amp;... https://t.co/LTsR78QtAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynetteBenton have your students read Hunter S. Thompson's Fear and Loathing books. Then they'll be serious. We need his voicell today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A troll who tweets with his tiny hands. https://t.co/ygvFFQlyHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynetteBenton Every serious writer knows this. Or should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott white Dave's brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure kids are going to learn much worse. Parents will just have to be inventive. The worst is all the half-baked lies Trump tells adu...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[believe him. BTW I got a weird FB from Scott...really odd ...is he deranged?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe this is the scale of the "Golden Shower" Trump received from the Moscow prostitutes he was visiting. https://t.co/CSGZTZMwlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lovely lady is a rocker who gave Bruce Springsteen a song and inspired Bob Dylan. What a talent. https://t.co/i0QhscGjlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This mountain has its own weather patterns. I climbed it bone dry, as well as in winds but never in a snow pack.... https://t.co/nwBezbCdYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was just beginning to get over my grief of having Trump to deal with for the next four years.  I saw some hope... https://t.co/0UwkWaWy1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That'll take care of those but cracks too. https://t.co/tc23VVYdHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump never spent a day in jail for the sexual harassment crimes he openly committed. He should be locked up. And... https://t.co/1oGCONJVk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women of America may not go along with the old white male GOP. https://t.co/9xqekNQXav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam" a booklet to prep you prep for protest led by Bernie Sanders Jan. 15. in nat'l protest against Trump actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam preps protesters for Jan. 15 when Bernie Sanders leads  national protest over Trump's lies&amp;GOP ethics scandal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam

The document you need to hold your representative's feet to the fire. 

Once you read... https://t.co/C3K4uFJD49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is using Hitler's (and Putin's) tactics to bully social media. The mainstream media has already succumbed... https://t.co/GeczYgcaGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chief executives of the Wall Street Journal refuse to call Trump's statements "lies". Bernie showed up with a... https://t.co/ekzkcUKlum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans march. This is just the beginning. https://t.co/a9L2LbVHVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no adults in the room any longer. You are all now expected to take this fight into the trenches. This... https://t.co/vsAQGUTmYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You bastards have no scruples.  What do you know about morals. You are bigots claiming virtue when you have no... https://t.co/IaPKdV9w8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count me out. Not my president. Not watching all the horse shit coming out of the pundits. I've moved on. A Hard... https://t.co/avYi0ja1eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who do deals with Putin are murdered. Now, Trump must show his tax returns to his new boss. And we thought El Chapo was a threat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillMcPhail @NewYorker Trump the pilot flying a plane with Twitter for guidance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smoothkobra Wasn't that the plan for the DNC on Nov. 8 for the hapless HRC ? Goodriddence to whatever strategy they were working on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borralvarez I would like to guide you on a warm day to show you where the Spanish captain turned around. You like history?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borralvarez thnx, Bri. Always found Vancouver's Spanish connection full of lore. maybe you will too. I'll buy the coffeefelice anno nuovo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The show me no black people hate state where bigotry is an amusement park. https://t.co/UvHJVfacjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Brazilian men are not known for their cooking. https://t.co/RymNe3x2gP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singer quits Mormon Tabernacle Choir rather than sing for Trump: ‘I could never throw roses to Hitler’ https://t.co/6CYWmwpvmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even as American intelligence agencies tear down the Russian spy network in Washington D.C., Trump defends the... https://t.co/jGQBszefUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum w/o inquiry this whole affair could slip into wing nut turf and end up buried in New Jersey swamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borralvarez the Spanish first came to Isle de Langara (Spanish Banks) to look for a short way back to Spain? Never found it @MikeShandrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiest people are also the healthiest . https://t.co/m0krGNrNbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryleeMacD Thanks for following, MMD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you. Berne supporter. https://t.co/H63kyryzca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dumb ass can't read. Show this to his cabinet. https://t.co/0xzBjlZeqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenduca I can see the resemblance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Terminator is back. https://t.co/v4adIYvm2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this train bringing cheer across Canada. https://t.co/gSSZBfrryD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear American FB friends, 
What is going on politically will not endure. I've survived Nixon and W. and now we've... https://t.co/3EaDfLb2rM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>