<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[HOGR vowed not to &amp; did not investigate 44's past. It did investigate &amp; target his conduct as potus. Should repeat… https://t.co/BRBIRqaQZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenJDuffield Steve, I know. We overlapped on Sen. Judiciary. You're a good lawyer. DM/email me. I'll buy you a beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenJDuffield look they will; app. ct. decisions build a more decipherable record; anyway, 06 was way pre-Garland...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different position. #SCOTUS stakes and reach are much bigger. More of a record to examine.  Requires a closer look. https://t.co/e34Jxn16o8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election 16 is empirical proof of that.  #savewinston https://t.co/Tt3e65oKf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 'give the president a chance' plea rings hollow. Recall the party of no? Disagreement's ok. Join the debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only pt left to debate is resign/not.  Neither Goldsmith, Wittes nor Lederman challenge her judgment on the EO itse… https://t.co/U9Ajntvjal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep.  Especially in a dangerous world.  #newtonsthirdlaw https://t.co/G3Boz0qp0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, @ClevelandClinic raises $ for Trump. https://t.co/Lm8MLJU7XW https://t.co/3esXmeiZjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nodding head..... https://t.co/6foSYoMrk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeamusHughes tells us how #MuslimBan will make it harder to gain CT cooperation from Muslim cmmty. Follow him. https://t.co/Tx9R8l9SMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny, you didn't mention this, @ClevelandClinic: https://t.co/Lm8MLJU7XW cc: @SenSherrodBrown @robportman https://t.co/0L4nkDlu60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and add him to the NSC principals committee!  #jareddoesnotspeakforme https://t.co/kUb8QpHnjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love. Not hate. That's what makes America great. https://t.co/4CHMTnULcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newton's third law.... https://t.co/44ueXt0Ri3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said it before: Must read @michaeldweiss &amp; @hxhassan book on ISIS. Also #ff them. Best book yet on ISIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of the WH pointing to Jared's sign-off on all things related to the Jewish community. #jareddoesntspeakforme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. It should give all pause as to what's driving WH policy in Israel. https://t.co/o050CZuNGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shunning good people from joining the American experience makes us weaker. It will anger others. Self-defeating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This blanket ban on Muslim entry to the US is rotten to the core. Millions of Americans oppose it. All should know that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, Secretary Mattis. https://t.co/f2uqYwse3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reporter and writer.  I'll be ordering this one, now. https://t.co/totZa3AUBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the cross at Auschwitz discussed in the early pages of James Carroll's Constantine's Sword.  #NeverForget https://t.co/h0lg0I70KU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what must be re-read today by @DavidColeACLU re torture:  https://t.co/h465RpUzEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to re-read @DavidColeACLU. Whether torture works isn't the point. It's immoral, illegal &amp; threatens our securi… https://t.co/EMhr3WaNEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...after Republican lawmakers criticized Obama for not punishing Russia earlier and more harshly than he did. https://t.co/CdV4ylbEch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should US move its embassy to Jerusalem without M or DS @ State, a dangerous situation will only become more dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Losing Pat Kennedy is losing decades of institutional knowledge, leadership and cohesion at State. https://t.co/Cd52NaIb72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And not what I'd want a Jewish state to be doing either.  #proudJew #proudZionist #enoughwiththesettlements https://t.co/pJ5vi7jTMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  Was there in 1981 with my dad.  Would complete a circle to attend it with my son in 2019.  #gotribe https://t.co/mLuFEbRnWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, Tom Price also traded Aetna, too. #cantmakethisstuffup
https://t.co/8MCApFBaDi https://t.co/opp9NZ5KmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIG STORY. Speaker Ryan relied on AETNA's lie as a big reason for repeal of Obamacare. Scrap the repeal. Rethink it. https://t.co/opp9NZ5KmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some protected speech worth following at @BadlandsNPS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, the Under Armor CEO was at the WH, this morning... https://t.co/D1hJqdZecW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajcdeane Thanks much. Likewise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajcdeane Glad you frequented the used bookstore on the Hill. That bookmark was funnier immediately after publication!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bait, meet switch on draining the swamp.  https://t.co/pCatK3Z98a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silent on high job #s, natch. Home ownership was false index when there was nothing else to cheer. It also led to 2… https://t.co/F6eaD81lAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA proves we do peaceful transitions of power well and massive peaceful protests well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Area president invokes "enemies" in failed effort to distance himself from Nixon, on Day One. https://t.co/syWJQ4zCHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Tom Price's lawyers play it fast and loose when it comes to conflicts of interest....  #swampingtheswamp https://t.co/eK3uuaiKzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three if by air. https://t.co/Z8Ruudr6lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news, @Schultz44!  Terrific choice, Mr. President. https://t.co/GcigK0uShw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's today's everyone will keep their doctor....  In a related story, bridges all over New York are for sale. https://t.co/fu7YAWzTGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaub to House GOP: Interview me in public. https://t.co/7kX9bsnevg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-MI6 agent's frustration as FBI sat on Trump file for months https://t.co/rVkfMrMW0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never the crime; it's the cover up. https://t.co/CtkU1aVhMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On his ATF Form 4473, did he state he was buying those guns for himself? https://t.co/voKH9s4JeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bo knows now. Big domino. &amp; another big talking pt for convo with my son on why he's not playing tackle football. E… https://t.co/f1UnlN9rmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrumph! https://t.co/mVPKCXCeUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call us when there's a reference to Hedley Lamarr.  cc: @jetjocko https://t.co/jClchoOixh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jetjocko Hits away....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preach, brother. https://t.co/AQKNqhUbKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, @GeraldoRivera!  Talk soon.  Welcome back to the States! https://t.co/fQ7pUJKjDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your eye on Kentucky Senators/Congressmen re Obamacare.  A whole lotta beneficiaries there.... https://t.co/cJ0jgnNVHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When WJC demanded removal of all US Attys, AG Reno had them stay until replaced. Will/can Tillerson will do the sam… https://t.co/lzkRLKbFrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the twin forces of Trump's paranoia, insecurity and ego combine with Flynn's suicidal war against the IC... https://t.co/JZYi9aGc83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Founding Fathers created a House of Representatives, not the Queen of Hearts. https://t.co/9ArQJMkASb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistent with Trump's message. https://t.co/XTTclwxVZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be interesting to see how Kentucky members of Congress discuss Obamacare....  https://t.co/W8X70B7Mj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0-16, then? Sigh....  Go Tribe and Cavs! https://t.co/OuHH6AF9Vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans Back Down on Bid to Gut Ethics Office, via @nytimes https://t.co/bbMkS1VKlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope cooler heads prevail. We need an independent check on unethical behavior of Congress &amp; its staff. https://t.co/XnrvP0fDA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gen. Mattis, Mr. Tillerson and U.S. Senate, please help us. Sincerely, America https://t.co/9OwxDMzvHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Tullio Del Sette, Commander of the Carabinieri, wins best name and job title of the year.  cc: @OKnox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another photo of same anti-ISIS march by Muslims, in DC. https://t.co/YzH1Fw2kLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside my office earlier today.  #courage https://t.co/lT3O1hPEty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside my window right now in DC.  #courage #americaatitsbest https://t.co/4ssQbFkEc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish our dads could C this!  #gotribe #Indians https://t.co/IKgAFx81S4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox Hope your PPO covers bandaids and lollipops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox If this had happened 20yrs ago to you at a press office, America might have lost a reporter and gained a lawyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unethical to compel a witness to invoke his 5th Amendment right in public. https://t.co/vvD8sMYrpy https://t.co/LV9obDlRbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved pub' for good friend @johnpmulligan &amp; co! https://t.co/eunw8qWSD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Fifth Round Picks Ever!  Must read.  Go Browns! https://t.co/yzqp9Mfjxo https://t.co/FPgBqDOqkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dropping a close one to the Red Sox today, Cleveland's magic number is 42! cc:  @deepthought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must read, here. https://t.co/VWvk3ywMeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disagree. Trump crossed very important lines first. More than ok to denounce him. It's America. https://t.co/UXbaaUZXAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RNC reportedly does not want anyone in NE Ohio to vote Republican ever again. #GoCavs https://t.co/T8anTnJfPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This was LeBron as Godzilla, and the Warriors were the buildings." #LetsGoCavs https://t.co/5eK122nWYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wearebetterthanthis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, the WH is making Zo miss his Miami Heat in a pivotal Game 6, at home?    https://t.co/7jkgBj8Vmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensible SEC position on obtaining emails. First ask you, then compel ISP (with notice to you). https://t.co/LePJXUwuDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reportedly, no exclusion in deal.  #healthcare  https://t.co/gXkyGJxZDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJGomez127 @APDiploWriter No. Not the norm. Leaks like that damage reputations and violate privacy rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....in presidential primary race against controversial Obama birther. https://t.co/WQAmh41E12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox @joshlevyesq .... another chapter in the travels of "need coffee to make coffee" @austinratner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's funny because it's true....   https://t.co/B4MAIdmh3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, metabolism, I get it. If I don't crush a bag of pita chips and hummus after dinner, I will lose weight. Noted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And....scene. https://t.co/y4wH6b8wBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need 18 to play baseball, 10 to play hoops, 22 to play football and 9 Supreme Court justices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this photo.  Can't wait to watch the interview!  Go, @OKnox! https://t.co/enSnN8u6yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News on Bob Muse's move!  https://t.co/wi5jGikgKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, @JoeyViturbo!! https://t.co/2Miu7KGrOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic and great day for our law firm:  http://t.co/v9ehG0DVtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You people clearly have never seen Superhost!  https://t.co/zAhJgbhMHm  https://t.co/r2wepGO3eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Intel chair: Charleston shooting could 'easily' be called domestic terrorism http://t.co/RUAyj43LUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ambush" sounds rather strong. Don't we pay those members to vote on resolutions?   https://t.co/teKKptdlwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope tech savvy CMS nominee leverages #bigdata to narrow gap between pay and chase.   https://t.co/mLAPnySB8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @UncleMonkBoards for unique, hand-crafted furniture. Perfect for a man cave. https://t.co/aMZrSBw9W2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THE_REALSHAQ is writing headlines! https://t.co/BgByzl1wtm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>