<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@theladyvictoria HELLA aesthetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theladyvictoria  planning to !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally wanna do some writeups about body image &amp; definitely pink at some point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one of these days.. pastel coloured hair...one. day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theladyvictoria forgive me, i've let down the environment artist club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also hopefully will figure out time to work on personal projects, so look out for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@demanrisu thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who might be wondering why i'm lacking in twitter updates, its because I now work full time as a game dev!! âœ¨âœŒï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im back &amp; somehow still alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching voltron S2 bye social media âœŒï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pheonix game w the bae tonight âš½ðŸ˜ https://t.co/nTmTpu1IQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Bakjb0aRJo Chill sunday song for the soul âœ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres a new element of danger added to this household @c_barilla @Suddenly_Tom https://t.co/IwQCKsjb3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catty_art had this problem since high school, tried so many different things and nothing helped. Suddenly it's fixed ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Messes me up how much you realise after you finish school. Used to have huge sleeping problems, slept way too much and still feel tired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voltron season 2 is coming up and yes I'm going to be a nerd do so much fanart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gonna be a long bus ride... https://t.co/CnnyuY9fYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohyoufox thanks bae!! ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theme of 2016: a tired pug sleeping in my lap https://t.co/NhJ1izYGBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved these dresses so much I have to show off ðŸ˜‚ (bought the one on the left) https://t.co/dh0SAQUx9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 is gonna be my I don't care what your standards are I'm gonna wear this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a xmas evening of my sister reading boxing day advice that compares 5pm to the circle of hell ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas &amp; happy holidays everyone!! ðŸ˜ðŸ£ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ https://t.co/aBUftT675j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found my old racket ðŸ¸ welly best be prepared https://t.co/prmxmUg9pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bonerman_inc woman thing works every time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tell my mum I'm gonna get sunburnt outside, she reassures me I wont. 2 hrs later: sunburnt. trust: gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found instructions my mum leaves about our cats ðŸ˜‚ savage https://t.co/KwcnPtCuhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I end up being the favourite when I come over to my sister's place ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ it's like lonely children https://t.co/7UYbzWcTe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnalieseBevan thank you !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catty_art ðŸ’• I wanna draw all of these https://t.co/jx4VaSdTl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna live in the winter gardens ðŸ˜ https://t.co/lPGx6ltuOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shiprib @lucyamorris @IMAKELSEY @playbyplayfest textureclippingkeepsmeupatnight123]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAKELSEY now that I think about it @playbyplayfest doesn't speak to me anymore either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't speak to that friend anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the middle of the dancefloor...alone.. infront of many family &amp; friends we didn't know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember back for my friends 18th me &amp; 5 other friends got up during bohemian rhapsody and sung the entire song with a co-ordinated dance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like recently, 50% of my time is phone calls, 30% is me messing up the phone call and having to ring again &amp; 20% dreading phone calls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[turned them into tiles bc its me https://t.co/TAlPzUPSVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What better thing to do on a sunday than re-watch five people play uni for three hours https://t.co/Am5bV3OdqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[favorite pastime: sending @c_barilla 3hr long videos from YT with no explanation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reason being I dont even have to pick up the waterbottle when im working anymore I can maximize my lazyness to its full potential]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[getting a water bottle with a straw in it is the best damn thing I've done this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was inspired by the last of us 2 trailer's song https://t.co/BQ7FhC8SNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its really cool when you buy tall stockings that are too tall for you but plus size stockings are too big...so...hand..y.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer I live on the edge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer Honestly for maya it has the "close and open it" solution for everything.... everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer omfg..... Innovation at its finest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer my favorite is when maya just forgets whats going on and either ignores any clicks or just keeps everything highlight, so handy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer ahhhh, such beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love ya Starbucks but how hard do i have to pronounce the b in my name for it to stop being written as Rihana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catty_art we don't own a cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at this cute cat https://t.co/ffIvJBum8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_barilla 12 postists currently... you think you can beat?? me ?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my life now: don't know if earthquake or drawing on tablet too hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you click to enlarge an image but its still the same damn size https://t.co/zCW3YEmQ44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have a solution for photoshop forgetting about pen pressure when you tab out and then tab in again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FleshyTech this is vital information I should have known ages ago.... oops...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but it IS a very handy way to visualize sizes of objects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also I'd like to add I should actually get a ruler rather than measure inches by postit notes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to do: stop googling A4 paper and actually write it down somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From yesterday !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farahkhlf i wanna try this too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowy lowpol Robin and Gnome â˜º https://t.co/UQGvoaKomU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My current state https://t.co/rmvccu4qir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonycoculuzzi glad u keep me up to trends tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rudeism true! If it's Auckland city its more like does this bus take me up this hill or not ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catty_art the bus drivers?? Call out ?? The streets???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rudeism ouch, I just moved from auck so honestly relatable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok but how do welly busses always arrive in order what kind of future tech is this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our bathroom has a little Listerine family ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜„ https://t.co/bCwfYOreDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc_nz ðŸ˜‚ from the wrong people I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris just getting settled in after moving &amp; freelance &amp; the personal stuff too ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omg I just realized now I modeled a mustache above the nose ðŸ˜‚ someone help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farahkhlf me too!!! Its ok I will find time to visit ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so busy I forget how to write properly.. oops...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and they say it gets less busy with you finish grad ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer oooh omg so many places to try!! ðŸ˜† Will have to check them out during this week !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shiprib oh sure ! Will head over ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daffyflyer haha maybe I didnt choose the best spot to hang, will look at those though !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welly peeps where's a nice little place to get coffee near civic square ? ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@c_barilla wouldnt let us get the dinosaur lamp shade ðŸ˜¢ https://t.co/1Bsycv6GL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a walk around and the botanical gardens are so nice in welly ðŸ˜„ can't wait to take some reference photos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Suddenly_Tom  @c_barilla when will I be accepted into this household ??? When !!! https://t.co/rM9RcU0tIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X LOL alright, might rest for a while and catch up in the afternoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AquiL4X come hang at my empty house im lonely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catty_art got to welly safe! Now it's just me, brave and an air mattress that i brought as carry on ðŸ˜´ so tired https://t.co/ElHjf44G2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbdoesart I feel ya bud, hang in there ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbdoesart thank you ðŸ’• good luck to you too !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbdoesart moving with claire and tom, not decided yet on a job but I've got some things possibly !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbdoesart thank you !!! Should be good ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin thank you!! You'll prob see us around ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farahkhlf miss you already ðŸ˜­ promise I'll visit ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naviverse @c_barilla ðŸ˜« omg so jealous right now!!! Lucky !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[âœŒ flight in 6hrs that finalises the new stage of my life !! Wish me luck, pls be nice to me Wellington ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_barilla is this a challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one minute I've got one uber taking 10minutes to drive down the road to me, next minute I've  got 4 ubers sitting outside mds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IMAKELSEY: Brianna this is so in-tense (putting on eyeliner)
Me: not past-tense?
@IMAKELSEY: (whispering with a hint of anger) Brianna pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to sit on my side table cuz it's the last seat in the house I can get to right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peachsharks omg srry!! it kinda happened real fast so I haven't been able to tell everyone but im moving next to the botanical gardens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just letting everyone know I'm moving to wellington in a couple days, so might not be quick to respond with packing/moving going on]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>