<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer @dimpayet17 a hero ruined by not comings out and telling fans the truth. If he said family haven't settled and want to go.👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLadBible surely you only need if if the 25 or under comes into play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlzeeS @WestHam_Central don't rate him. Not many players come from Italian league and do well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer it is there business, they can run it to how they want. And it needs to make a profit otherwise it is a bad business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joeisntfunny @MartynHobbs12 @WestHam_Central need a RB more than anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsullivanwhu any signings close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestHam_Info @WHUFC_News @MailSport yeah totally. But if you step back from everything and think what a fantastic player he has been for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brad_WHU yeah totally true. No teams are gonna sell there best players now unless they are happy to go down. Like Defoe, snodgrass,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brad_WHU yeah. I can't see why the board are after him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @WestHam_Info @MailSport such a shame that it had to end like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brad_WHU yeah true. Can't see hull selling him and snodgrass to us though. Maybe when they go down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brad_WHU Adam smith is a good right back. Maguire us quality but is a centre back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brad_WHU @WestHam_Info whole reason Swansea went downhill because he left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jam1ema5on @dmyeo66 @ExWHUemployee yeah I said that all along too. Buy himself out of his contract if he wants to go so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeepsMan @SkySportsNewsHQ wouldn't say disloyal. He came up with Southampton from league one. He is 33.2.5 year deal is better than 18month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer think mark noble should of had a word with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spz1899 @WestHam_Central he should show WH more respect and the fans. If he wants to go back for family reasons. Come out and say it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spz1899 @WestHam_Central you only want him back now we made him a star]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlavanOut @GriMaHcs @robstanley_ he is proven with a big budget. Like pep is proven with the best teams.Our quality players now may not fit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlavanOut @GriMaHcs @robstanley_ who is out there that is realistically a better manager that is proven?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlavanOut @GriMaHcs @robstanley_ we need to back the man who is in charge and get behind him and the team. Otherwise what's the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlavanOut @GriMaHcs @robstanley_  I don't think anyone knows who's fault it is. Because we don't no who is in charge of transfers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GriMaHcs @SlavanOut @robstanley_ is struggling to get Man City to compete. Well a lot of players are underperforming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GriMaHcs @SlavanOut @robstanley_ and has proven he is a good manager here and previous jobs. Premier league is the hardest league. Even pep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GriMaHcs @SlavanOut @robstanley_ yeah we could be but to say that the manager is a problem is false. Not you said it.He is a well respected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GriMaHcs @SlavanOut @robstanley_ West Ham over performed last season. Top teams underperformed. We are a mid table team on spending ability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @ExWHUemployee if he came out saying the reason why he wants to go. And actually spoke to the team it would be different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber half watching it and doing the utility room. Yeah but dad is big Sam lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Damo_84 wouldn't let him train with anyone there is a bit of grass you work out the rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Damo_84 I think you and I would be sacked if we didn't do our https://t.co/MHTx5HzXAe want to leave buy your contract out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmedleyTony @RobbieSavage8 great answer. I know we all would be sacked for doing what he is doing with our jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Damo_84 if he wants to leave fine him for not doing his job, until he buys his contract out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimpayet17 @whufc_official you get paid £120k a week. It would take me 7 years to earn that. Yet fans like me pay your wages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimpayet17 @whufc_official what has happened to you. All about the love affair continues. Grow some balls and do what your paid to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReadWestHam tombides would be better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News that's only two weeks wages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimpayet17 @WHUFC_News @westhamtransfer @DaveSulley a potential West Ham great, turns into a West Ham ungrateful in a blink of an eye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber @dimpayet17 well I bet most players want to leave and go to better clubs but the is a way of doing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewesthamzone @WHUFC_News nah get big money from abroad or if he wants to leave get him to pay off his contract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber from being hero one season to being a cunt in a few months. @dimpayet17 your attitude is poor. Earn yourself a move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber don't pay him or get him to pay off his contract if he wants to go so bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News don't pay him. If he is refusing to do his job. I would get sacked if I refused to do mine.  Or get him to pay out his contracts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimpayet17 one simple answer do you want to leave West Ham?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @Moncz97 he needs to demand the ball like he did last season.taking the game by the scruff, like Sanchez would for Arsenal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer we are in danger there are a few teams worse than us. But some have more spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGeeMan007 @WHUFC_News nah sell up players who don't want to try like payet. Lower teams players put in a shift. This lot are not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExWHUemployee he will do brilliant for us in championship next season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGeeMan007 @WHUFC_News it could be our only chance to stay in premier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News we were playing well. Then penalty kicks us down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News what else is on tv?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News should sign fonte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News well how much would you lose if we went down. Lose than just more money,players like payet and lanzini. Goals win games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6_AaronLee trippier isn't option now his at Spurs.Adam smith at Bournemouth is a good player. Would love Patrick v arnholt at Sunderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6_AaronLee @ExWHUemployee 1 striker hendandez when he was at Utd. And yedlin when he hadn't even signed for Spurs.He was still playing USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6_AaronLee @ExWHUemployee I think you made so good points. Striker and right back is the same as the summer.I mentioned 2 yrs ago to jack s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6_AaronLee @ExWHUemployee oh to be honest I didn't no that's how it worked. Apologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExWHUemployee @6_AaronLee what makes him so special? There's a lot of people who support West Ham that have opinions that don't get a say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExWHUemployee @6_AaronLee pointless tweet. Says everything that everybody already knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News Defoe, dembele, hogan, gray, don't entertain batshuayi. Didn't want to come to us in summer rather sit on Chelsea bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westhamtransfer £10m maximum just cause of age. But for goals in premier to save a shocking season. Defoe guarantees them. Long is goal shy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlyWayIsPayet @DaveSulley it is irrelevant. The 3 points have gone.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @TheSunFootball  dembele is better for sell on value. Gray isn't a natural finisher. Defoe for 2 seasons pay 10 mil is gd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveSulley @WestHamUtd @sffeghouli pretty irrelevant as we lost the game because of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_Willey @SkySportsNewsHQ @SwansOfficial @premierleague some really good on form players don't even get a look in to even making squads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_Willey @SkySportsNewsHQ @SwansOfficial @premierleague yeah all bout premier league anything below is nothing. Like English players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_Willey @SkySportsNewsHQ @SwansOfficial @premierleague rowett ten times better than giggs. Other than Coleman probably the best one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @RMCsport who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball he was a nobody before he came to westham. He needs to help the team that made him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimpayet17 if you want a move to a so called big club start putting a shift in for the players and club that made you great last season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GNev2 thought you done well on Sunday supplement. Bit like lamb to slaughter for you and trying to get your valid point across.#talksense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlippiOfficial would love a special video message for them if that was something you could do some how?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlippiOfficial our house loves you songs and videos. Keeps my boys entertained and quiet for hours and they learn a lot from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber @C_Stanborough tj don't go to nursery, he ain't even two yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball @westhamtransfer westham sign him up. Proper captain material]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlippiOfficial everyday your videos are on in our house.The songs are very catchy too. You would do well in the U.K. Kids love the videos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News @TheSunFootball  nah randy is the best keeper we have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News it is worrying Last season over achieved same as the likes of Leicester and Spurs.lot of teams underachieved too. Even it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News really like him. Works hard for the team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveSulley @Gary_Clarke_ ever thought about fans behaving and getting behind the team.Bigger stadium just means more scum can get in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellingford_paul @S_D_C_C @WHUFC_News no one talking about the fans disgusting behaviour. Pay to watch football, not to go fighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT none of them just want to play football for a normal wage. Under worked over paid and don't no what hard work is. #getarealjob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestHam_Central @JayRichardsxx is it fully deserved. Been playing right back and looked shit. What about noble. Henderson is shit #England]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaretandH you have to spend to improve and compete with the bigger boys and aim to be one of the bigger boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsullivanwhu why was it tough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestHamSocial he was the best player on pitch for us and only come on with 20 odd minutes left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@princekyl @djleon1983 @WestHam_Central imagine taking your kids to a West Ham game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCWilliams_ totally agree. @talkSPORT was bigging wilshere b4 euros. After it why would you take a player who ain't played 90mins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_carey yeah they all good. Living in the country now lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_carey good mate. Very happy with life. Yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_carey that's a bit personal to put on Twitter bout that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_carey nordveit looks ok. Nothing to make me go wow. Whole team looks average when payet ain't playing. When he is he makes them better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_carey he ain't been great but now getting bit more confident on the ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loldeantimber crap team though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball yes two games in a row he should have been sent off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News yeah but strikers are hard to come by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHUFC_News amazing atmosphere today love every minute of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare TV. This is every night now for week. Now all I'm watching is the humax screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare that just keep cutting out. Now not getting past humax screen.I am not happy.I work all day and just want to come home and watch the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare have factory reset it twice still the box keeps cutting out. Want something done asap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTCare website is a bit long winded]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>