<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Normani Kordei queen of everything have us shook and post a group cover that will snatch our weaves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are you??? @NormaniKordei @LaurenJauregui https://t.co/k36XLzKR5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she don't know where mani and lauren are ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is a mystery tbh what is her purpose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why can't DJ's cousin go home????????? omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i feel like W*ll is the type of white person to say the n word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[um is DJ's cousin gonna tour with them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone ask why her cousin aint in school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at least 2 of her answers have to be wrong i was reading straight from the book UGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i spent so long on my bio quiz just to get a 14/23 i want to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is a 100 level class and a gened and it's legit my hardest class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow my bio professor wants us to read so much who the fuck does she think i am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she's so small https://t.co/dXo0zDxFtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victoria_kordei horrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard b*d t*ings as a whole at my workout class for the first time and it's...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks queen ! https://t.co/LrOqGsS9We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also I keep tryna ignore the girl but y'all keep bringing her on to my TL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[full of fence how can *** ****** be doing so well???? like it's just not a good song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need my printer to get here so i can be lazy and just highlight my readings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jauredramatic those were the days...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[y'alls president really wants to destroy america]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DopeXMani I was just thinking about him for some reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait my birthday is coming up and my dad needs to get my a present lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe my parents will get me an ipad for surviving 2 years of college...probably not but i'll ask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iaurmanisdope @laurmanibebless yeah my parents have the older version of the mini and i really like the size]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[since when are there so many?? https://t.co/vSNoX6kPEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i really want an ipad for some reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Normomi_Kordei that's good then lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whereisnormani]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why are they taking her blood?? omg that seems so serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5h...queens of acting https://t.co/5eMlGxsWsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[y'all had to make them say one thing they liked about each other each damn soundcheck but you couldn't ask that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we never found out what L left in the hotel room that was embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandcastlesmani this interview was great laurmani were so funny during it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandcastlesmani which interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sledgehammer is playing in the dining hall my meal was interrupted by candoolde screaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've eaten so much and I'm still hungry skhshs help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my roommate is in class and i don't wanna ask any of my other friends to get food da;j ill starve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im so hungry but im too lazy to walk to the dining hall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ExsandOhs #BestCover #iHeartAwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what is this omg https://t.co/Q1NOHU0Ewo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'd love for all of them to act tbh they acted like they liked candle for years so they must be pretty good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good for ally! queen of acting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If *** ****** out peaks *** I'm gonna delete my account and off myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love mani...I want her to do well chill out https://t.co/ABijcQkkRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg!! I forgot all about this I loved it https://t.co/iQv1ObgqTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wig? Obliterated https://t.co/SqNLSNDC5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a modern day icon https://t.co/ngBAtzBwqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is ending https://t.co/V2e5gopJuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[his dumb ass is gonna get us nuked sjkdh i HATE america]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[um when dc is nuked i best not be here !!! i have NO interest in dying because of y'alls president doing some dumb shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_wobblewobble was it all in my head?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_wobblewobble I love work from home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish it was just Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot about ***]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my 9:45 class was cancelled tomorrow it's LIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BestFanArmy #Harmonizers #iHeartAwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WorkFromHome #BestMusicVideo #iHeartAwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love mani's sweatshirt/outfit in general queen of comfortable fashion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why are L's shoes never tied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queens of writing songs but not statements https://t.co/6UPFRpIWwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised https://t.co/4CkFScrSe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and i don't wanna go to whole foods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want to make grilled cheese tonight but the dining hall is cheap and gives you one damn slice of cheese in a sandwich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LaurenJauregui keep using your voice â˜ºâ˜ºâ˜ºâ¤â¤â¤I love you so much and I'm so proud of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got this alert from my school sldhsh I hope it attacks T*ump https://t.co/O0EJqugHXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lauren's letter was good I'm proud of her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and is ally wearing just socks? lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dklsfj why is lauren barefoot https://t.co/X2RVDYXvc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deenah June did sound really ill I'm glad they called it off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are any of them gonna tell us if Dinah is okay or...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DopeAdults which ex bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my roommate ate a huge dinner and a few hours later we went to mcdonalds I'm going to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He trash but this is really cute https://t.co/irz9KnUvMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my cousin wrote such a nice piece on our grandparents being refugees aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will Normani Kordei have us shook and change her layout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow one of them was actually ill I hope DJ gets better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dog isn't doing well at all ðŸ˜ªðŸ˜ªðŸ˜ªI wish I could go home and see him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth It is playing in the dining hall I can't escape those hoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jauredramatic I would deactivate and never talk about them again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If one of them is really sick I'll feel soooo bad lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kordeign ally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth Harmony couldn't make it to the all star game because C sabotaged them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it wasn't really a major performance so i'm not mad i'm just curious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they've performed sick before like....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they def refused wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they have to be protesting it like djf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it you? Did you refuse to sing it @LaurenJauregui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who fell ill??? How sick can they be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened??? What is going on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carly don't have the range but she makes bops so it's okay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Carly I love her hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd DIE if the girls come out skating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't JB gonna be playing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They really hate these men kahshs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are they booing this man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're STILL introducing people???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin is the only player I know cause my friend was obsessed with him and his last name means lamb in Russian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My stream crashed lahsdjjdhdhd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>