<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuralDoc_Emma thanks Em! Still flying for a while, just moving states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pushing for a National Rural Generalist Pathway. Moving to rural Qld soon partly bc they recognise/reward my GP + E… https://t.co/j0XBFAqfgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because sometimes you need to see a baby fox with big ears: 
Fennec fox kit born at Taronga Zoo https://t.co/kKwNIBehFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird here's mine - too hot for full flight suit #DressLikeAWoman https://t.co/BRWJBp0WF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMtraveller @mmbangor she's also an ED consultant... so knows they toe line more when talking to a "hospital boss". GPs also consultants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird @SwearyPaed @Apathetic_Cynic @ketaminh @EMcardiac @RoyalFlyingDoc I might have the brumby shirt in more than one colour...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iGas2 @ketaminh don't worry, once he realises it's there, he'll come up with a way to make Idon livid too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwearyPaed @ketaminh @evanster @ketaminh that's perfect placement. Makes more time for nervous wee before patient arrives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh hey that could work..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is unbelievable. I doubt very much the denial came from Nauruan govt given their own women are flown outhttps://t.co/NjY3Ma2hyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guessing he hasn't heard of Pine Gap either. It's kind of a secret anyway right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, I'm actually kind of glad #DonaldTrump doesn't seem to realise how close Australia is to South China Sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ralanshirley and as a combined GP/EM trainee, GP skills very useful in hospital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ralanshirley I think this would stop a lot of "GP to chase", and stone walling of GP referrals by hosp registrars. Increases safety for pts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ralanshirley every pt sees GP at some stage. Imp for hosp docs to know how world outside hosp works &amp; what GPs can practically do for pts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The landline is a lifeline in the bush. Rare to get an emergency call on a mobile out here. 

https://t.co/BAK4VRLy9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird @nomadicgp @EMS_Junkie @mina_el_naguib no she was really happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird are you going? Want to go but don't think can swing the time off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomadicgp @EMS_Junkie @mina_el_naguib I'm never keen, always worried about getting an elbow to the eye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomadicgp @EMS_Junkie @mina_el_naguib have seen ripper brawl over bouquet, also one girl left alone in middle cos all knew meant for her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG tells POTUS #MuslimBan is unlawful. Rather than take this on board he fires her. Crazy. #mondaynightmassacre

https://t.co/c6aI9AxE0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not get too smug about how much better Australia is than US #MuslimBan right now. We should be ashamed of our… https://t.co/gPcFrxy0jK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw man, I'll go fishing with you Ray! 
https://t.co/yFf6nGp1ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news, great for rural medicine! https://t.co/gI9ZJhHWsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TacmedAus @gppocus thanks guys he has and is now sorted. Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm disappointed to read this, and hoping for a more detailed response from the College than that quoted in article https://t.co/VGEDum44XP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perkleberry THIS! An awesome job, but still a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mate Stu sharing his story for the Australian of the Year awards https://t.co/iHknBpRwAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatchTheBaby @WineDoctors ha thanks! Followed. There are quite a few of us in Aus, tho not many on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcsassymd one of the pluses of living in the outback on a big island - the zombies will hopefully decide it's too far and too hot to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tale of Two Colleges: A recap on the birth of @ACRRM in our 20th birthday year https://t.co/8H0uW36cOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh yep. Was fruitful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh @nwqran ha thanks Minh. Had a good couple of days visiting Qld too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh @nwqran thanks Minh knew you'd have the contacts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildernessEMC @ketaminh @NOLSedu thank you! Suspect his wife would like the NZ option too so extra bonus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gppocus @TacmedAus he is in Newcastle so that might be a good option!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-army friend needs to do HLTAID005 remote area first aid cert but having trouble finding a course in Aust. Anyone know of options?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coffeeheadaches fixed wing is  definitely nicer to your hair and they never ask you to jump out either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh @choo_ek @MDaware @Eleytherius @emedtox @kyliebaker888 @annecreaton thanks Minh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the #NHS refugees thinking about moving here but worried about Australian creepy crawlies...https://t.co/IxwazGDje5ping @mmbangor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanCon11 @RoyalFlyingDoc I remembered to ask him the other day - you are right - his family is Irish from Kerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @mina_el_naguib @sbattrawden @julesnorton @coffeeheadaches @GBeecham not fun to fly in granted... 🤢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @mina_el_naguib @sbattrawden @julesnorton @coffeeheadaches @GBeecham + toxinology makes for fun ED.. espec if pt brings in culprit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @mina_el_naguib @sbattrawden @julesnorton @coffeeheadaches @GBeecham it's nice &amp; warm too.. but srsly we… https://t.co/X85SG5PEck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dralangrayson @davehartin @mina_el_naguib @coffeeheadaches @_NMay @EMManchester @docib vague memories of Flavia and Marcus here.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @mina_el_naguib @sbattrawden @julesnorton @coffeeheadaches @GBeecham yes you should all move to Australia......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anhilden @Dr_Polarbird might have to give it a go! At least w cold you can put a fire on/drink wine. Not much you can do about that heat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anhilden  Brrrr. No thanks! Mind you @Dr_Polarbird would be right at home in that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanAckermann nearly there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird ugh the worst! Similar yesterday with tar and AvGas smell following us back on plane. RDO in aircon today and storming now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah bit warm here today #outback https://t.co/7ojdtMGngQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EDEnchanted do it! But yes advise finish training first. Vintage plus exams at same time (always at same time!) = very bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EDEnchanted yes!! This feeling led me to move to Tasmania, buy a farm, start a vineyard and start making wine. Best decision ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDamphetaminh @ketaminh ha ha. Note did not tweet this whilst actually in back of said ambulance, it was a few days ago and am still livid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you are doing on the road, it is NEVER more important than an ambulance running lights and sirens. PULL OVER &amp; get out of the way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenZabar but was successful. Got v nervous when gastro arrived, announced too unstable to go to theatre, so would scope &amp; pull tube in ICU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenZabar we call it a Sengstaken, have only seen it used once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poped01 @docfromthebush @KangarooBeach v frustrating to get "GP to chase" but hosp won't release results bc GP didn't order/not copied in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docfromthebush @KangarooBeach @poped01 @thedrwrites not really - plenty of us who do / have done both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reflection on Carrie Fisher / Leia 
https://t.co/8FZhoPEiUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite possibly best Christmas present ever: book titled "why my Aunty Shell is absolutely brilliant" by my 6yo niece https://t.co/d9aWqKCMy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coffeeheadaches possibly the best road trip snack planning ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DocOnSkis @FLTDOC1 @FoxNews if that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need more rural doctors.....
@RuralDoctorsAus 
https://t.co/ga4ePyGAWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Tassie....https://t.co/mr8AWyl4Br]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor just got home from last retrieval, just getting into bed here. Sending you caffeine vibes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @YGEDBangor but great idea. Merry Christmas Bangor ED people!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmbangor @YGEDBangor that tower of china fills me the anxiety. What if one of the people on the bottom layer comes in first?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas from somewhere over the outback https://t.co/SvpFtLvHRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just going to leave this here.... https://t.co/yIazaEHNnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitGP @Dr_Polarbird @Fly_texan @ACRRM @RACGP and for those concerned re getting onto spec training, it helps bc referees know you well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitGP @Dr_Polarbird @Fly_texan @ACRRM @RACGP yes! Better training, more experience, and bosses know who you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird i totally would!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird oh awesome! I thought of you when I saw it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird have you guys seen the ad for the Maatsuyker lighthouse job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coffeeheadaches yes, nice patient, nice family, both poor prognostic indicators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why you should call an ambulance if someone FALLS FROM A SECOND FLOOR BALCONY. 

https://t.co/blpC5qQDhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanCon11 @jducanto @airwaycam @FLTDOC1 no worries. Also never heard it called anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanCon11 @RoyalFlyingDoc don't think so but will ask him. I'm squeezed in behind the car door there with the pt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoghanCon11 @jducanto @airwaycam @FLTDOC1 from a non-lad: coude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so confused by this guy being the opening act for crowded house. Goose with mullet comically bad. #painful https://t.co/fxKjU0623F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of Calgary/Outback at the Opera House waiting for Crowded House https://t.co/TFERzpvwWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pilot: can't take off prob with *pilot speak*
Me: what now?
P: thing tells if we're up/down in air
M: oh like a proprioceptor 
P: ..sure..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NocteNurse @ketaminh @feminemtweets yes indeed! This must have been sitting in drafts I wrote it ages ago. Ah well better late than never.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunset between two cloud bands in the way home @ https://t.co/SOMFe8lwep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thatsbias Many places I've worked had no sterile gloves my size, only large (man hand) sizes. Lady doctors do procedures too @feminemtweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ludicrous. What happens when all the rural doctors go? Hire expensive locums of course! What a way to save money https://t.co/jseMF5VV0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another #justaGP doing fabulous work. Interesting screening for takotsubo with echo post #eqnz quake as had cases l… https://t.co/R5VXSKI6UI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird yep. I looked a bit like that. Explanation was have to wait for update from UK due to licence. UK updated &gt;18 months ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was an intern I was scared of intubation bc I worried I wouldn't get the tube in. Had no idea of RSI drugs/risks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably more concerning focus on intubation even for juniors w/o discussing dangers of RSI. "Fixing" "A" before looking at "C" = disaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting these things went out in UK APLS course &gt; 12 months ago https://t.co/1YP3R37b71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At APLS learning such pearls as hard collars in all inc head injured pts, and 2 x 20ml/kg crystalloid bolus in hypotensive trauma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to have a pre night shift snooze and hope when I wake up I'll find this was all a bad dream, and it's only Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh @jeffayton Goondiwindi &amp; St George last 2 EDP in Qld both closed last few years due to local availability blood products/retrieval]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Polarbird @xaqu1n @KangarooBeach @RogerRdharris chasing the sun home on a Friday afternoon! https://t.co/efg1ceJiFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EBMgoneWILD @ketaminh @aLittleMedic @Cannulator rural Aus towns have known large panel, screened reg. Multiple donors called in for trauma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh fantastic local resource. My hometown stopped last year now have stored blood avail &amp; chopper in vicinity: https://t.co/ns5R9tpzjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh ah will see how turns out then. Problem is if I give blood I tend to faint 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketaminh my family all O neg, Mum &amp; Dad both EDP. Remember being bundled into car for trip to town at night a couple of times when little.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>