<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[John Cleese: Letter to the United States of America https://t.co/8qZGRulENU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadboucher @waikatotimes  scratching my head that anyone in Comms in the 21st century would ever expect this story to be "pulled"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @vaughndavis funnily enough I know a bloke who bought a plane WITHOUT telling his wife and kept it secretly at a rural airfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact of the matter is, the car sat for almost a week https://t.co/W8kyWErMcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Lamers @traskjd yup this is like the printing press destroying the Middle Ages mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom ! Nice historical snapshot of the power of under estimating disruptive threats thanks @traskjd https://t.co/SWQaAd3q4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Rules to Being a VP of Sales in a Startup https://t.co/eEk3rTvVnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That difficult second album - how founders struggle to transition from "doer in chief" to "company builder in chief" https://t.co/qMTs8C2wL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roddrury @paulbrislen @claude_savagely Wairau vineyard with only a modicum of body flexing on the way ... https://t.co/PK5Eqo7zIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @roddrury I did have two of them but swapped one for a dirty old 911 - some sweet irony there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claude_savagely yep the latter mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roddrury chur bro 2.8 injection special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wairau Valley Vineyard 2.8 Injection Special 1986 @ Wairau River Wines https://t.co/mQ9W5glFht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nelson to Blenheim in the mighty Cologne Capri https://t.co/bolNKKapaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire Trump supporter Peter Thiel "is sending more wealthy mates our way", an associate says. https://t.co/9WHEC2H8fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toxaq awesome man - you should come out to Ohariu Valley and we can save the world or at least liberate some hydrocarbons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toxaq cheers man - Lyn Rogers Blueprinted engine- are you local?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Redefining organizations for an exponential world  https://t.co/s8HqaoWIWb on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/feTcaY0zqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisCJ love how it blips the throttle on the down shifts ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisCJ a lot more stink!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisCJ busted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bank Products Are Dead. "Long Live Experiences!"​ " https://t.co/m9r0fj7Mlj by @brettking on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christopher Liddell will advise Trump, tapping years of business experience to "effect substantial change"  https://t.co/Pd8ISbTj82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are in Aucks and appreciate the motorcycle ecosystem check out ##@CarbonGarage in Newmarket https://t.co/7n9h66kzGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still there in 30 mins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tippy_top I think about 80%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start up or creative company looking for fantastic character space on Cuba ?  Boy have I got something for you  .... https://t.co/4eGPDdELl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought for the day from the Raygun guys https://t.co/ue8geep40X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marekkuziel brilliant shot man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to only see one of the big four tech companies in here https://t.co/YR3tabzRHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woo - hoo ! New Twin Peaks season to provide 18 hours of weird David Lynch television https://t.co/BDRykBXhxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammeikle oh no ! does this mean good bye because I'm married to a yank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Glendower @TimFraser5 https://t.co/8np2HatyNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DazzzAndLeanne @TradeMeMotors @Volkswagen_NZ true that - looks pretty cool - but without the famous "bubbling" exhaust note]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porsche kept this 911 a secret for 10 years https://t.co/UjCYlI0Npx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jupiter's Christmas stash https://t.co/5Jr3IfLR71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arowin perhaps instead of the kitchen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pavlova by 11 year old Sierra - woo hoo! https://t.co/Y7VeySxPdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homegrown lamb charcoal cooked on homemade firepit inspired by @winsboroughdave and @Danjite happy silly season guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email too short – here's why you time vampire .... https://t.co/MZtyqlnmvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielrbridges and it misses you ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Channeling Wuzza @cateprestidge with help from #ruthpretty https://t.co/XKm4KDD7O5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikCarmichael thanks mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John O'Donnell - a fighter to the end - thanks for the lessons - rest in peace brother https://t.co/STRcDVfdhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toxaq bit of both - well predicted sir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Boom Rock https://t.co/CaGcemcGSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Christmas! So here's Gareth Morgan! https://t.co/mvGTL4dYVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massey University's Chris Kelly steps down after backlash to his female vet comments. https://t.co/5vMtISC4hI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike O'Donnell: The Commerce Commission doesn't get it or just doesn't care https://t.co/DHKTDJcQgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't get it or they just doesn't care https://t.co/gGPXOhAMkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arowin true that bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkepes @JennyMorel he revels in being unmedia trained - its his natural place ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gsmithnz hopefully not the only thing though....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timely ranks #71 on the deloitte technology fast 500™ via @Timely https://t.co/P88tIZfrM3  woo hoo!  @timelylife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Marlborough https://t.co/EkGtS0XyOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin van Beynen: John Key inspired confidence https://t.co/5byUaIcmkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implications of Monoclouds for as-a-Service Startups - Why Differentiation Matters More than Ever https://t.co/dVQOf1rH6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great digital role on the go at Tourism NZ https://t.co/KVa5wwNYoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arowin dude give me a call instead - out of town for the next week or so ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGordon thanks dude - poor subbing - fuxed now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tepunamike @HaikeManning True that !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davebruce cheers bud - hope all good with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanbakernz  so much for the need for governance/executive distance ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanbakernz at least there was a custard square in it for you mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc  magnificent 'What do you want us to do, be a bunch of boring shits?’ On the Lash with Patrick Gower  https://t.co/Rcrhbkx6xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the time Naz said Sutherland, a digital marketing consultant and stripper, was "all she could ask for https://t.co/0xGjKblYjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Llamas, tourism and PPPs https://t.co/8EDrc2FKTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanbakernz @timelylife @hakatours @Timely coolio - have left you a voice mail in lieu of pillow talk ...  seems I must owe the team beers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute legends - take a bow guys - a stellar way to end the year. @timelylife https://t.co/lZOQ30beJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arowin these always remind me of the Jman https://t.co/KaxwKtpDaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronPinkham oh to be that hip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronPinkham truly you are blessed my red haired driving friend !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kris_bNZ @themorgan @juhasaarinen not that you would need it given the snug size of the MX5 cabin.  Specially for muscled Scandihooligans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natural disasters prove the importance of public interest journalism https://t.co/Bvjain1hho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukaszfromwelly @modsta execution and monetisation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinMcMullan ghosts in the (smart) machine? https://t.co/iiIGv7mTSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much better beer choice at Andy's Burgers tonight https://t.co/kW4tme9jRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryaninnz dead right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TradeMe two - one who wanted me to pay them to build it and an agency who are a bit .... twitchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynyard's Telstra sale confirmed - shareholders pretty much buggered  https://t.co/EL9tYC3PzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winner of the worst beer menu today - White + Wongs - nice food tragic beers https://t.co/TMvidFTPdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normnz @stevenljoyce Me too Don - great spot.  We could start a business together - you the brains, me the beauty - uh oh, praps not ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely moush https://t.co/0KpxiNfHJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tragic - one of the best pubs I know. All strength.  North Canterbury's Historic Hurunui Hotel red-stickered https://t.co/1bQT939PaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ @radionz in the North Island they would have stolen the train mate ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porsche tractor, Springston, Canterbury https://t.co/umBsrgBo6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pie in the Main Street of Leeston https://t.co/fdiwoIOy8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't even think of trying to get on SH2 out of Wellington or joining it at Ngauranga - gridlocked- yay for motorcycles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartpublicsvcs cool cool  - plenty of room here if the fam fancy some Llama patting or some scotch drinking 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Tweep Friends.  If you are an apartment dweller in  Wellington and you'd like a safe warm room out in the country then hit me up. MOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strikerpaul @SusieFergusonNZ @radionz agree that - starting midnight #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro good to hear bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicktmro hope the wee one slept thru it mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester cheers Justin - power is out in Ohariu - aftershock now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZcivildefence 2 minute roll in Ohariu Valley 6037 - now power is out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnat @rowansimpson good call Taffy ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowansimpson  thanks for quote! Stability in product and market fit – a crafty idea https://t.co/WZvzqKpCJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product market stability – a crafty idea https://t.co/t7sVDkjZsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the long face? https://t.co/Wny1Gr20rN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>