<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchellReardon @5kids1condo @CTVVancouver same network that had Ann Coulter on the same day as the mosque shooting victims funeral]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@musser_english @NewYorker @jelani9 yes! incredible work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Hutch he's had some fun moments at P-R but never anything that made one think he took it seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodirmurphy @lailayuile lifelong skier, I can drive in the snow, but I avoid the roads on days like today.  Agree hills are the issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodirmurphy @lailayuile I have snow tires as I spend a lot of time on the sea to sky.  But it's an expense that not everyone can justify]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile combine this with inexperience driving in snow and you end up with problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile it's tough for people to justify the considerable expense of real snow tires when a real snowy year is so rare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonsmorecowbell @beardedPDX @thebotanophile it took you literally an hour to come up with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamPhreedah @tonsmorecowbell @thebotanophile i'm actually a bot tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonsmorecowbell don't be salty about other peoples' likes, it's not a great look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonsmorecowbell yes that is the exact problem we are dealing with now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonsmorecowbell @thebotanophile they're slanted against him because he's an obvious clueless buffoon who knows nothing about anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samknight1 "we gonna punch the shit out of you then go home and order a pizza"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBeinart free speech doesn't mean giving odious ppl a platform, or keeping silent while they spread hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric cars and cheap solar 'could halt fossil fuel growth by 2020' https://t.co/bzX25L6ODj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhorowitz this guy is, unfortunately, too dumb and doesn't give a fuck.  He can't make the connection between the ban and himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed up for my 4th time.  Best ride of the year, every year! https://t.co/LkmNTjxDH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsheppard18 @TweetBrettMac @SpawnofGluten oh man I love both of those things so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsheppard18 @TweetBrettMac @SpawnofGluten I don't really see how it could possibly be any more good than it already is good, its that good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FieldGulls I'm stoked.  Russbot might actually be partially human?  Russborg?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentToderian terrorist, and nazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LionoftheSenate well now he's the same as them, and his supporters are the same as their supporters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basedbryank @IntiAmaterasu @alplicable @chrislhayes it's dark humor or horrified screaming at this point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tastemeeeee @LMoniqueMarrie @ShaunKing @realDonaldTrump there was only 1 shooter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travisharder @BlueBoxDave @cjane87 metaphor actually works because any informed person knows arsenic is poisonous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericdemamp @JordanPeele noted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PistolPeterr @DragonflyJonez where does this unlimited stuff come from? Who ever suggested that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@impishchimp so, how tough is it to get a work permit?  Can you grease the wheels if you have the funds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DragonflyJonez this can't end well for his ego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For any Canadians who think this doesn't affect them. https://t.co/1iC1MkV0ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaximeBernier this is reprehensible.  Canada is about inclusiveness and helping those in need.  We need to accept more refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AhmedDHussen Canada needs to step up and admit more refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AhmedDHussen we must revise the Levels Plan in light of this new stance by the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKwanBC @MPJulian thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur "one of the brightest individuals" not to sound elitist but it seems like there's a different standard for brilliance there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvalis @EmmMacfarlane i feel like you shouldn't be hanging with nazis given how not white you look, seems risky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skiingrogge my theory is he's actually 400lbs which makes the tricks even more impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UweBollocks optimistically, it looks like he's about to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christiana1987 no, it's about which countries they think they can get away with banning.  Saudi Arabia isn't on the list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanAlias lots of people who wear suits all the time would also prefer not to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nolanlawson just followed! I'm a sql guy and mostly follow db specific tech accounts but i'll give you a try ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJeffDuncan more confident random tweeps have read it than i am trump has #trumpcantread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mary3Cs nobody associated with that administration deserves any respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSRudin I've emailed my MP to demand a review of any existing caps or limits.  Everyone needs to do the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mary3Cs @jsatz23 @thedailybeast @AlexBrookLynn @FLOTUS her bibliography?  Really?  That seems weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau @JonathanWNV Bravo.  Now let's back these powerful words up with action.  The world needs Canada, now more than ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garossino I'm OK with that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time for Canada to help those in need.  I've emailed my MP and demanded that we open our doors wider.  This is what we do.  Let's go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@island_cynic @ddale8 any election's a long way off.  And all parties should be united on this anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theshrillest its good to remember that trump is an actual crazy person so assuming any machiavellian plan is probably overcomplicating it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elizabeth_fels @buckweiser13 @bourgeoisalien he should also delete the beasties reference given that they're proud and vocal feminists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougSaunders a better example would be someone not complicit in the deaths of 100k muslims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olram307 @DaWriter This GOP congressman lives near the border https://t.co/kL4guKdapN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommySnark try to bring more dogs if you can, I mean 3's a good start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any Americans want to come stay at my house, that's cool, I feel pretty bad for you right now. https://t.co/3mCwLS3EAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garossino "guy denies talking to me but i'll tell the story anyway"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieFlack @Kev1365 @DannyZuker @JaimieAlexander YES. When a nazi troll annoys you, donate $$ to immigrant support groups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden agree its more about the medical system in many ways than it is about stigma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden its about consistency of care.  Funding the system so that a doctor can properly follow and serve a patient long-term]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden really sorry to hear all this.  My MIL is a retired psychiatrist and I can guess what her answer would be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bourgeoisalien trump is also proving to be a massive baby, what a strange coincidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garossino I haven't seen any hard numbers that support the idea that Stein influenced Trump's election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bourgeoisalien it's hopefully less years of extremely painful, horrible decline.  That's how I think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tramp_stamp @Home_Halfway @nuclearcarly if punching nazis is fascism then fascism is a lot better than I've been led to believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steejo @MartinBelam @Shikaboom yes, there were actually 8 men, Pence is out of the frame to Trump's right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDeaux @Chop_Gunna @NFL not even finessed, straight up jacked for his shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MasthoMpfier @scott_tobias @mamisano @PressSec just deep breaths. make some tea. turn off your phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Illlll_Willlll @EdgeofSports with Trump it transcends politics and just becomes an issue of who's not obviously shitty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrwalsh8 she can definitely do it in Canada, most of Europe, most of South America, large parts of Africa and Asia... what you smoking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brettdrc @lailayuile not really a parody account when he can't stay on message.  Just a dumb racist who thinks he's funny.  Report and mute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deeeebers17 @cjane87 that's good. Punching the ones that are marching around should keep it that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelani9 @jpaceDC @AP isn't it more likely that his obsessions will prevent him from executing his duties as pres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremiahLumbee can you spellcheck your memes at least, is that too much to ask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielnasaw nazi punching is a great American tradition and i support it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could there be a more appropriate album of the day?  Good luck, folks. https://t.co/pwCxdZS9y9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dufus you should probably pay @leslieleeiii his 20 bucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball as it should be.  Taxpayer money going to pro sports is a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 that was immediately obvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@go_nino @melhartsell @SierraClub that's not fraud, that's the media calling the election based on early returns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southldntabby I don't think you're using the term strawman properly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southldntabby that seems irrelevant if they're all dead in a nuclear winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southldntabby sorry Sean but being illiterate absolutely should disqualify one for high office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMcTruck @JeremyMauss @nytimes I just don't get why you posted that unless you're trying to make fun of climate deniers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMcTruck @JeremyMauss @nytimes is this a fucking joke?  It ends at the START of the industrial revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @adblockplus - I've used your product for a while but the fact that whitelisting doesn't work properly is a dealbreaker.  Uninstalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy a @wahoofitness KICKR and ride it so hard your eyes cross and you feel like puking https://t.co/JKp26RoZNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyButler10x @SeahawkScout easy Cody.  Worry about the Packers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johno615 well let's not go too crazy.  Coffee and booze are staples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johno615 honestly some of that stuff sounds pretty tasty.  I like veggies and salmon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johno615 the kind where you can play elite sports at 40 against 20something steroid freaks?  Minus the Trump stuff of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a lot of sports hate for this guy but as a fellow 39-year-old with a 9pm bedtime, he's also pretty inspiring in… https://t.co/nlrjgUxRfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hawkblogger cable is involved in draft/fa discussions tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile agree but plz thread! https://t.co/zK7GlZaDSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omar_aok and actually a better song, and great album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Swole_Hawk @JacsonBevens even dumb guys can beat NFL testing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zjwhitman @Eradicator_NYC plus ADB plays like a big WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bccycle @dongho_chang given the choice i ride in traffic vs use a MUP.  More predictable and safer in most cases]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dongho_chang @bccycle not great.  MUPs are not cycling infra and are a cop-out that endangers both peds and cyclists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanWNV @Thuncher @NorthShoreNews @jordansturdy every single detail, no matter how mundane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanWNV @Thuncher @NorthShoreNews @jordansturdy btwn climate commitments and selling resources for pennies on $... i want it reported.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>