<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RicFinlay Not to mention 146no for Marcus Stoinis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoshanaMN @BJSM_BMJ @RepDonBeyer @keithellison You can sign this declaration if you want to publicly join boycott https://t.co/sLxI4HWxO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseline concussion testing? https://t.co/PmEkdZezNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davymark1 @darren_lehmann photographer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why wouldn't they attempt to take all of the coastal Blue states with them and leave Trump/GOP with only rustbelt a… https://t.co/bSSqSypyNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is very nice. Plenty of movement both in the air and off the deck #greentop https://t.co/T4D4xKwfMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davymark1 it was @darren_lehmann. My only achievement of note for the round was walking the course after a 5k run today. 25000 steps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birdie 2 13th Cape Kidnappers @darren_lehmann https://t.co/U4zQtVIM9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Marcus Stoinis' 146 was a freak innings https://t.co/y0dYnCIlTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump banned refugees on Holocaust Remembrance Day. That says everything |  Cecillia Wang https://t.co/11xVtUL0p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To complement the #flashback Aus Open tennis finals, BBL final currently features Haddin, Johnson, Lumb, Bresnan &amp; Bell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How science helped to swing the Canadian election https://t.co/phm1XHuMpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists can’t fight 'alternative facts' alone | Jenny Rohn https://t.co/9YHxNpPmOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative facts, fake news and Trump's war on mainstream media  https://t.co/NvboeRyESl via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take nobody's word for it – evidence and authority in a world of propaganda https://t.co/7mJBwRqDvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump in the White House is the end of the 'American Century' https://t.co/TI0nmiLLCr via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillyJonesJrNZ very good idea. Effectively ACC has a NZ nationwide registry of ACL injuries so it should publish data each decade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia joining US in openly trashing global climate efforts https://t.co/wNCs4SHzro via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do feel the need to read Fake News, please choose from a menu of @BetootaAdvocate @TheOnion @TheShovel… https://t.co/UI4S1AOVDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a slacker Muslim. But Donald Trump has us atheists nervous | Sohaila Abdulali https://t.co/Hf1fmtVa3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spirit of cricket alive and well in WBBL https://t.co/WAYv1o6clf @AlexBlackwell2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiebCricket Also should be mentioned:

Mitchells are bowlers
Marshes are batsmen
Mitchell Marshes therefore must bowl and bat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is a meta-analysis that a treatment works a debate? What is the other side of the debate? Post-fact logic? https://t.co/SoswRtkGKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obamas changed how the world sees black families. That’s their legacy | Lola Okolosie | Opinion | The Guardian
https://t.co/PBzPI0wOtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the ‘alt’ is polarizing, and harming, medicine https://t.co/l723kMq2r8 via @statnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acxjones @eddiecowan After recent Twitter merging of BBL/Test team, waiting for someone to ask why Black Caviar never won a Melbourne Cup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump may indeed do this. Little known fact but he has more idea on "what is a planet" than the folks at @NASA https://t.co/V2YyE7mV7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is proper science @CSHeartResearch @jessicajorchard   https://t.co/rjeFdJLaIR
https://t.co/8UloUmZlIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t call it post-truth. There’s a simpler word: lies | Jonathan Freedland https://t.co/lh05RDenzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandy Hook tragedy has attracted another kind of ugliness: conspiracy theories https://t.co/Br0NNwWDyG via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why certain Liberals can't believe in climate change https://t.co/71VgOPeDVf via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration is the backbone of Australia's economy https://t.co/4dfuWLZGW8 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Conroy is just the latest addition to the loathed Canberra swamp https://t.co/q8NTTLug46 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is out there Mr Bogut, you just have to look   https://t.co/TGulyUkNrm via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academics aren't lobbyists – so our research changes nothing https://t.co/ivPMq51fdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real Malcolm Turnbull exists – in Auckland https://t.co/aoMWh7d5lD via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyrone Unsworth was just a little boy whose death was preventable https://t.co/Czh5tVao7B via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shouldn't care if they give up sport as long as they don't give up exercise. Win/loss is gr8 for some people and… https://t.co/oxa9lBkEQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar tax isn't a sign of the nanny state: it's a step in the right direction https://t.co/2yB6zK9ROF via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RodWhiteley @DrSportSante @craigarxl Could a proximal hamstring tendon rupture occur in swing phase? Interesting to hear if/how it could?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSportSante @craigarxl If you measure tendon loads directly https://t.co/ciBDGlwR0a high loads #stance &amp; minimal loads in swing phases]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bleak-looking sea ice graph has Twitter in a frenzy https://t.co/v5prSZzZsf via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market failure: private health insurance only worth it for 'the pregnant, the rich and the sick' https://t.co/YWD4F8bQRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This statement out of date, surely. Gardasil much better protection against cervical cancer than early detection https://t.co/7ot4yt0Tji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Donald Trump watched an AFL game in 2015: 1) he boos Adam Goodes 2) he'd have worked out all there is to know about AFL in 10 minutes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defamation, not 18C, the real threat to free speech https://t.co/P84LF2uohK via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Coalition of All Democratic Forces, Part I: A Political Focus on What's Truly Important https://t.co/OdkoQFylZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English trio in Australia immigration nightmare https://t.co/0zy8u3Reqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our mission is to give the doctor the most independent role... they should be paid by the league or the federation https://t.co/c82h4nWWsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Howard says gun laws should be strengthened, not weakened https://t.co/XwF0nbNOba via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW bat forced off by concussion https://t.co/mkIjl6DKjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New convention centre set to impress on Saturday's public open day https://t.co/BttwFjIZu7 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think when patella tendon ruptures it's in mid air as well? If this has to be a ground contact phase, why is… https://t.co/Rnz8jYh1RR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step b4 kick is a deceleration stride. This braking step is the common denominator bw kicking and running quad/RF s… https://t.co/JmQ5f9GekO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muscletechnetwo no hard data published but anecdotally high no of kicks at training sessions prob a risk factor for quadriceps strain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlespedret sadly have a cricket tournament this week can't leave. I will get to Europe when it finishes for Berlin concussion conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NRL grand final 2016: Andrew Fifita scores a try and all is forgiven? It doesn't work like that https://t.co/1tGwywqb7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shout out to @jakelands, Gary Zimmerman and David Young. Top shelf medicos who have  played a massive role in WSB Premiership win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMJ Careers - Bullying of surgeons remains big problem in Australia, study finds @bmjcareers https://t.co/7uiN7Jag78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA, keep your Olympic medals. Australia's latest world ranking is far more impressive https://t.co/tlpHdhQbW9 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be too harsh if GWS Giants are the team that wreck the Western Bulldogs' dream  https://t.co/JzaUiSUE31 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian surgeons accused of cartel behaviour to control the market and fees https://t.co/6GzjiK275f via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike helmet review throws cold water on sceptics: they'll likely save your life https://t.co/W9Di0eLGtE via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Australia's MBS review deliver on its goals? https://t.co/gCb3yxNXfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We see unilateral lateral comp syndrome in front leg of fast bowlers - asymmetric action &amp; loading though https://t.co/58sHJWvXgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't a systematic review (vs expert opinion) the best way to answer the question you have just posed? https://t.co/aTlGhopihz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The oceans are heating up. That's a big problem on a blue planet | Bill McKibben https://t.co/9w8N0RJqUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bledisloe Cup failure shows outdated private school system letting Wallabies down https://t.co/Fmohhm1YES via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but by taking the weekend off, AFL gives everyone a better view of Andrew Fifita driving the NRL over a cliff https://t.co/057ovTpBAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editorial: Rugby league finds a brand new low | Daily Telegraph
https://t.co/G3w7o4WmUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Fitz ALP and Greens shld return serve by saying they'll agree to a plebiscite but only if only LGBT people are allowed to vote in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKouk @smh seriously? 80% clearance rates, low supply high demand and reserve prices getting smashed. If that's cooling what's warming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Like 1968, Sports and Politics Are Colliding Again” by @bryancurtis https://t.co/lWXDYFOMWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brain Surgeon’s Legacy Through a Grandson’s Eyes https://t.co/3zMjI7LuU8 #lobotomy #medicalreversal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull to Shorten: Meet me in the sensible centre https://t.co/4QFXFaNBtP Does sensible centre include a conscience vote on gay marriage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to sleep: the doctor who helped stem cot death epidemic https://t.co/jCSiVrY1I4 Hard to find a better story supporting medical research]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyjacko @wutube Agree though with thoughts that in 1996 the tallest ruckman (Alessio) would have stood the mark https://t.co/iO5W5rlK76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyjacko @wutube Lloyd was (1) off the field with a ruptured spleen (2) in 1996 wouldn't be seen dead chasing his man into defence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wutube Swans players Heuskes, Dyson, Plugger and O'Loughlin. Bombers maybe Olarenshaw &amp; Wellman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smith’s critics condemned by players union https://t.co/gDzLuBSLjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stanford earns a PhD in cluelessness for its woeful Brock Turner response https://t.co/ey7AqYgEgU via @LifestyleAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is hard to take ScoMo's latest Budget Emergency plea seriously when his party is determined to blow $200m on a non-binding plebiscite etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EpiPen outrage: The US senator's daughter who raised price of anti-allergy medication by 400 per cent https://t.co/4Uf7fozHwL via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If anyone has actually planted it there...?" BP. What is his other theory - that the bug planted itself? https://t.co/ugdEBcZZc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let the blame games begin – Australia's favourite Olympic event | Kristina Keneally https://t.co/vqcp0YCRPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sussanley Health &amp; Sports Minister a class act as well for keeping the big picture in mind &amp; not being obsessed with medal count]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillyJonesJrNZ I think because females increasing more than males they are assuming that WBBL impact &gt; (men's) Cricket World Cup impact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being Unfit May Be Almost as Bad for You as Smoking https://t.co/P7j8nFCOLg via @nytimeswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Rio Olympic medal tally for Pac-12 https://t.co/RBmbA0mWeS - other story is how valuable Title IX has been for US female athletes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieLeask @rebeccaivers @smh wonder whether increased law enforcement here will actually beat driverless cars, which solve the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenSeiler plenty of angst in Australia about our recent drop but we are smallest nation on this graph still punching above weight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emphatic response to Betts issue was missing when Goodes was booed https://t.co/m20rFPa1Ru via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SydneyThunderGM @HockeyAustralia @DolphinsAUS @AthsAust This is a summary of the (lack of) argument https://t.co/8mBynetvLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's well-planned, well-funded Olympic over-achievement is finished | Paul Connolly https://t.co/CMPVONrMTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['My taxi driver openly wept', Kim Brennan, Olympic gold medallist on sport's role in nation building https://t.co/9ttTSNaj3K via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful early night sky this evening with Venus Jupiter and Mercury in an inverted L to the West. Saturn and Mars in Scorpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outcry grows after banana allegedly thrown at Betts https://t.co/46U0f7Xujf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Uber's Fleet of Self-Driving Cars Save Lives? https://t.co/IqszT41yUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Ken Crichton NRL Fellowship - https://t.co/iDfuWReKsY https://t.co/fq89cXEMUX Great initiative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners in the Olympic art of losing gracefully https://t.co/EN4ROgxYMv via @smh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>