<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[China's secret Trump card: Could Beijing deprive our military of critical defense components? |  https://t.co/YQageo9eqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["China’s military is not going to be rolled back and abandon the islands. It can’t." https://t.co/eyw0NXV8V5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy Advances Future "Ghost Fleet" - Swarming Aerial, Surface and Undersea Drones https://t.co/jooJJiQCfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions Of US Jobs Lost To Trade With #China, Study Shows https://t.co/9kYzOdlFBr via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Chinese Aircraft Carrier Program Progressing Substantially Into the New Year https://t.co/QPKEXyg5Ve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it 'too late' to stop China from taking the South China Sea? https://t.co/smfSiSERuS via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China Sees the U.S. Navy's Sea Hunter Drone https://t.co/m85P15a5cZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis won't ask Japan and South Korea to shoulder more U.S. deployment costs | The Japan Times https://t.co/nPPfOuREOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Tests New Multiple-Warhead Missile Amidst Tensions With Trump https://t.co/a3zKbdAPD9 via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duterte Suspends Drug War To Purge Rogue Cops https://t.co/nHJy7zIiFW via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the US prevent North Korea from testing an ICBM? https://t.co/cuOzX3oxbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big thing everyone always ignores about China’s internet market https://t.co/rUWZ8LzCMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey: Pinoys want sea claim vs China pressed https://t.co/SLZFt28fh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nuclear arsenals of China and the U.S.: Plans for a future armageddon | Popular Science https://t.co/s9wVYgAsRv via @PopSci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is the New US-Philippines Military Pact Under Duterte? @Diplomat_APAC https://t.co/7C2sjRPgQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Economy Becoming More Strict, 'Less Open' via @forbes https://t.co/J7fxSMgHof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Government Engaged in ‘Holistic’ Cyber Effort to Infiltrate U.S. Industries https://t.co/hVR2B0JSJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are China and the US Set for a Showdown in Space? @Diplomat_APAC https://t.co/CrYs6ZUxgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A diet of corn is turning wild hamsters in northeastern France into deranged cannibals that devour their offspring" https://t.co/XSb7EW9N0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dating Guide for Communist Party Members https://t.co/9w3k9wLWRN via @chinarealtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China displays new version of bomber ahead of national holiday https://t.co/RkrjwZh6Fv via @upi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China ‘steps up preparedness for possible military conflict with US’ | South China Morning Post https://t.co/VoKrAd0OYc via @SCMP_news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US to upgrade Philippine military bases as Duterte reverses stance https://t.co/Io2ILOxHQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan open to two-way trade talks with U.S.  https://t.co/yFVk4qn42q via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis Heads To Japan, Korea: Why Asian Alliances Will Survive TPP’s Death https://t.co/8K0hKTdIEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duterte's Drug War Death Toll Hits 7,000 https://t.co/G5pCETgg7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High-Level North Korean Defector Says Kim’s ‘Days Are Numbered’ https://t.co/QDGc9xEooL via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Won’t Run From a Fight With Trump https://t.co/QWkxlsBVp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Lawmakers Try To Undermine Trump's Power Over US Nuclear Arsenal https://t.co/77H4xQLIOU via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Deploys New Nukes As Trump Talks Tough On China  https://t.co/13o6omBeAL via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Expands It Fleet Of ‘Carrier Killer’ Destroyers https://t.co/CtOsZaBItE via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan launches first military communications satellite https://t.co/FGZC8USVtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain: Withdrawing From TPP Hands ‘American Leadership In Asia To China’ https://t.co/4SSj2GJmGy via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SeanSpicer: Trump Will Challenge China In The #SouthChinaSea To Defend US Interests https://t.co/tOgwgKq7o7 via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea Issues Threats On 49th Anniversary Of US Spy Ship Crisis https://t.co/zR64Pdu1Gd via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kishida says Japan needs to confirm Senkaku commitment by Trump administration | The Japan Times https://t.co/3YY4PlXosM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real secret of Chinese internet censorship? Distraction | John Naughton https://t.co/124Nhn5e3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The myth that China is a global leader https://t.co/1buBlDwrcF via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China sees 'grim' situation in relations with Taiwan this year https://t.co/77o6j0eVc8 via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan envoy hails US ties after Trump inauguration https://t.co/h89nUZZ6dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to watch out for in Donald Trump’s first 100 days in office | South China Morning Post https://t.co/OOTZbGzCgy via @SCMP_news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea,  Japan and US begin three-day naval exercise to counter North’s missile threat https://t.co/FRua5Tm3Bn via @SCMP_news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to defend against a Chinese navy of 500 ships https://t.co/Rfbd97riei via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Media Denounces TV Host Who 'Defamed' Communist Hero https://t.co/kbLSCQ8ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showing off the hardware: China’s first aircraft-carrier bares its teeth https://t.co/WGxmuCt4GH via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China is America’s “vendor,” and needs to treat its biggest customer better, Trump’s commerce pick says https://t.co/PgarH3u1Sm via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Trump adviser Bolton backs U.S. forces in Taiwan, says move could lessen Okinawa burden https://t.co/feM1Ychera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic given the present situation in Asia... https://t.co/8HPclw7M4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commerce nominee Ross calls China 'most protectionist' country https://t.co/awmS5aPe4j via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese billionaire Jack Ma says the US wasted trillions on warfare instead of investing in infrastructure https://t.co/HZcywXIHQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the U.S. Gets for Defending Its Allies and Interests Abroad https://t.co/1Tnhi0r1i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Tries To Tell Trump Who Can Attend His Inauguration https://t.co/HnD3CrSHXR via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-Un Tells Obama To Worry About ‘Packing,’ Not North Korea https://t.co/BLIvntmcqt via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Military Prepares ‘To Throw Punches’ Over Foreign Spying https://t.co/7edCuPiPAs via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese official fired after calling Mao 'a devil' https://t.co/0M1d6SoaMg via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan simulates China attacks as tension rises https://t.co/VMzU3tWT7v via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Xi’s ‘birdcage’ politics: who are the hawks, doves and owls among their advisers? https://t.co/JZWjSutusX via @SCMP_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S.-China Relations: Dates to watch in 2017 https://t.co/GoGM8xkYHN via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beijing Strenghtens Control Over The South China Sea As Its Last Rival Goes Soft via @forbes https://t.co/URiJt0oiaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's booming middle class drives Asia's toxic e-waste mountains https://t.co/EnfGRnamrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China digs in heels, girds for Trump’s unpredictability https://t.co/1WgYnXwFeF via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLA Daily on foreign intelligence threats to China's national security https://t.co/JRycafDfPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China overseas investment spree set to run out of steam https://t.co/Bug0MJr5zy via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shen Dingli: "If Mr. Trump is ready to play with fire, let's play. We can prepare to wage a war to unify China. We… https://t.co/2SMmMpM2wF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yan Xuetong: Without the one-China principle, "China should stop any formal diplomatic relationship with the U.S." https://t.co/S9Rlxtm762]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese experts believe China's official response to Trump too soft https://t.co/o5wLZs3nd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xinhua: China blasts Abe for meddling in South China Sea issue https://t.co/6g3AzDv8Nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan pledges boats to Vietnam as China dispute simmers https://t.co/pyVTM8YO2n via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Can Power a Small Nation. But This Wind Farm in China Is Mostly Idle. https://t.co/PKWsV5BCql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting take on Obama's inaction, and prospects for the incoming administration in the South China Sea https://t.co/07Zu4Ampmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHINA PREPARES FOR ROCKY RELATIONS IN 2017 https://t.co/T1Qco5TcPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China vows to nip patriotic protests in the bud to maintain stability | South China Morning Post https://t.co/3XdABY3DFe via @SCMP_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zhou Youguang, linguist who developed modern China's Pinyin Romanized writing system, dies at 111 https://t.co/76s9R14wwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DJT says one China policy is negotiable, China's MOFA responds https://t.co/QyYdsGkzRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson's SCS strategy would risk war and "undermine the very freedom of navigation rules that the U.S. has been… https://t.co/D19i1ZETH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Walks Back Threats To Label China A ‘Currency Manipulator’ On Day One https://t.co/wDAHAN5tQP via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Willing To Shatter Beijing’s ‘One-China’ Policy https://t.co/QuHVgvh9vj via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan’s cold war island begins to thaw | South China Morning Post https://t.co/gF6Je4RKoX via @SCMP_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson may not have misspoke ... He may have meant what he said about the South China Sea https://t.co/2auxYgHVSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan Unveils Armored Vehicle Prototype for 'Counter Island Invasion' https://t.co/A63IFsTYhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our aluminum war with China has been getting super weird lately https://t.co/g4RggpBvGg via @clusterstock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SE Asia air pollution deaths could triple, report says @CNN https://t.co/z2D88QCTse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A US attempt to blockade the South China Sea would 'end up in a shooting war with China' https://t.co/CvLRlsXJvZ via @BI_Defense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If China's Money Stream Stops Flowing to Hollywood?  https://t.co/qIPhgkedZo via @thr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a busy month for China's carrier battle group. https://t.co/Sj8fegt66f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is the U.S. “One China” Policy, and Why Does it Matter? https://t.co/t9I6dGtgBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting take on the role of China's Global Times. GT "will be an increasingly useful tool for China's governmen… https://t.co/WYAlsrmjXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How legit are a bombastic Chinese paper's warnings of war with U.S.? https://t.co/DAv5lXgu0b via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China, Russia fear the US is boxing them in @CNN https://t.co/DZ6pGf6YmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fluffy toys out, socks off: Japan’s Shinzo Abe treated to some Duterte diplomacy in Philippines https://t.co/SMbWoHgEtW via @SCMP_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump risks 'war' with Beijing if US blocks access to South China Sea, state media warns https://t.co/i0ReAsYlY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S.-China challenges: Time for China to step up https://t.co/hBu5jva1ED via @BrookingsInst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 Cent Party: The Chinese Govt Fabricates Social Media Posts for Strategic Distraction, Not Engaged Argument https://t.co/pAIN8cQY1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson Channels Reagan on South China Sea https://t.co/eun4sX6mEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the World Might Look Like in 5 Years, According to US Intelligence https://t.co/oJJTRHv5be via @defenseone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama to end policy granting residency to Cubans entering US without visas https://t.co/OqbFAhZJgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Countries thought to be unsophisticated have overcome low technological barriers of entry to engage in cyber ops" https://t.co/oQRLC5ESGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson vows to defend ‘durable’ ally Japan over Senkakus but notes Tokyo’s ‘obligations’ https://t.co/X9x0O7CzBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China launches new electronic intelligence naval ship https://t.co/AB4men3pNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Secretary of State Nominee-China Should Be Denied Access to South China Sea Islands https://t.co/Bc4D2agS6W]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>