<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the NZ V Aus ODI. Flippin heck. Josh Hazelwood, how could you? #stoinis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is still my favourite cheating in cycling story. https://t.co/Kbg4LcpgRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had some car battery problems today. @Ask123ie sent an engineer out who got us running and couldn't have been any more helpful. Thankyou!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ell2309 @dangerhere They used to say "look away now" and put the results on screen for a few seconds without reading them out. Seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob I'd say that's quite a list, Joe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyBurke @defensivelob I loved that. "Hear, hear!"
You were always in safe hands with John Hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymacm I think it might have been one rainy morning at Saturday school.
Yes, we had Saturday school then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymacm I remember they sat us down in school, in the main hall, to watch a tape of that whole match. That was long before VHS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vergilsbanter Good man. Must admit I was concentrating more on events on India.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwensDamien Is it Ed Balls day yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vergilsbanter Were you at the cricket today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irelandcricket Is there a recommended/suggested area of the ground where Ireland supporters will gather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's not the final table but someone at @SkySportsRugby needs to slow down and review this graphic. https://t.co/5ZQr2XOiZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The grown-ups are checking his tweets and deleting the ones that are a bit too embarrassing. https://t.co/QBPyaw6fTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvalDigest I never knew Leavy went to Michael's too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarpinOnRugby You're welcome. I had it in my diary for Saturday too.
Always enjoy your blog - thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarpinOnRugby I think the Leinster 'A' game is tonight at 7.30pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wimbledon did the best vines. https://t.co/FSvcmyz3yF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to @Gonzagadublin winning the senior league today. Great effort by all involved. #greenmachine https://t.co/nhrcxnV2W9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiguelDelaney That's @mrdanwalker. Surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure about some of the choices made in the data visualisation accompanying this article in @IrishTimesSport. https://t.co/RJUOMFQ7cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Shane Long doesn't score enough goals but he has a heart the size of a barn door."
Dunno if Lawro does these on purpose but that's genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that amazes me about this UK ambassador to the EU story is that the UK has an ambassador to the EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal2608 @defensivelob Twitter itself is enough of a Donald tweet watch. No need to follow, unless you really want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal2608 I'm ignoring even the question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an interesting one but your version could just as easily  mean that Sean's Mum thinks my child is overweight. https://t.co/l1vopmarkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now that it's dark you can also see Mars on the opposite side of the moon. Look carefully and it appears reddis… https://t.co/5tO8bI9DtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful clear sky over Dublin this evening, with the two brightest objects in the night sky side by side: the moon and Venus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob The fire lit, a glass of wine and the kids all gone out to parties. There are worse ways to see in the new year. HNY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal2608 @EoinAMcCarthy @oliverobrien I will never get past O my good it's good to be alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donal2608 @oliverobrien Wake up, Donal, I think this must be it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larduffy I always preferred 10cc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larduffy I only speak Marion Cotillard. Il y a du monde au balcon. #chakakhan #hootenanny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure they've captured the essential Black Bettyness of the original. #hootenanny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oliverobrien @donal2608 We better wait up, Donal, to find out what the hit was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see they got the bloke on the drums again who looks a bit like Colin Montgomerie. #hootenanny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gregory must be roasting inside that hat. #hootenanny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oliverobrien Seasick Steve seems to have picked up a buddy since last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from kickoffs they hardly got out of their own half. And that was with the wind. https://t.co/Ut8BGkQd5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here. This will save you watching any more of those year in review programmes over the next week or so. https://t.co/ejvWXT5coC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theovaloffice10 You're clearly a man who knows a thing or two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope everyone remembers what happened the last time Leinster demolished Northampton over there. That must not happen again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time you're walking in Herbert Park, try to imagine what it was once like... https://t.co/AmwtuueGxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I saved that dog." Who'd have thought Christy Keane was a PG Wodehouse fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy Possibly. There's an awful lot of football in those sports pages as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, own up tennis fans. Which of you was it? https://t.co/Y9ZFYh6Y9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux Did Ronnie show his medal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On #MOTD2 they just went through 6 of 7 goals in the Bournemouth-Liverpool game, except Origi's which was the most amazing piece of skill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That pass wasn't as forward as the one to Jack Conana couple of minutes earlier. #LeinsterRugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubs is already on his way to the Eye &amp; Ear to have that eye seen to. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy The champ won that one very convincingly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy They do sometimes. Or just offering a solemn handshake will suffice too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob The Russian resigned because his position was hopeless and he was nearly out of time too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy Oh you're right. I didn't read the rules as carefully as you. Carlsen has white in the 4th game and will park the bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although rather a shame the tie break didn't reach the Armageddon stage. #worldchess2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that was an exciting finish. Well done Magnus Carlsen. #worldchess2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy The browser widget is very good. Looks best on a desktop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy The Russian has used up a lot of his time over his last few moves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy A shame the stream isn't on TV or freely available on the internet. Could have been tremendous for promoting the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinAMcCarthy World chess admin has always been dodgy. It's one of its charms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob @EoinAMcCarthy It seems they have a paywalled video stream. There is a live chess page here:
https://t.co/4VtFqtZwmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tie-break in the world chess championship.
I remember the Karpov-Kasparov  match in 1984 which went on for months a… https://t.co/FQorRmNdNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gags_junior Hi Emma! Thanks for that, very interesting. I quite enjoy what @TheSchoolOfLife do. Plenty of helpful insights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Teroid If Israel Folau hadn't butchered a 3 on 1 overlap, it would have ended differently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd have put Garry Ringrose in charge of my crèche. https://t.co/GWJys7f2Rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringrose, along with Conor Murray, looked like the only thing holding our makeshift backline together in the second… https://t.co/RK08AV8qIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our backline in that second half could only have been more makeshift if we'd had Peter O'Mahony on the other wing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can put a back line behind that pack we'll have a decent team. #irevaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noflashingneon Maybe it's to distinguish them. "Saint Thomas? Which one?"
Is there another St Laurence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rocshot James's St, general area of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing. That's one of their second rows so detached from the scrum that he dives into the back of our scrum to kil… https://t.co/qVbPR1tPZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It was a knock on, ref."

No try. Scrum.
...

"IT WAS A DELIBERATE KNOCK ON."

#IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Janko is my favourite hapless Austrian footballer. #AUSvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob @FrankmcnallyIT Highly irresponsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Irelandcricket Yay, go @rocshot !! Well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales should stand in the shape of a poppy while their opponents do the haka.

What?
They're playing who? Serbia? At football?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barneyronay Cool, I'll watch out for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barneyronay Brathwaite, Barney. Where's the thing on Carlos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob If there has to be a haka I always prefer the more traditional Ka Mate one. It reminds me of the great Terry Loader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently the All Blacks did the 'wrong' haka against us. https://t.co/keCAD1GiwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio seems to be a toss up at this stage. https://t.co/DWN89Uuvqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: the state of Virginia is actually called the "Commonwealth of Virginia". #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be nice to think that this election is a low point in US politics and it will get better again. https://t.co/ylEO7YzvIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impossible to imagine the next president being so bright and energetic after 8 years in office. Or even 4. https://t.co/RAuVvCdzhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob Joe, I know you're always interested in new and useful applications for 3D printing. https://t.co/x8e0YwUiB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startling use of the verb "to disclude from" which is a new one to me. https://t.co/SUVQmXvTf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fran Rooney (remember him?) says "these are good commemorative issues" so it'll be grand, FIFA. #poppiesrising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob You may be getting mixed up. I'm a big fan of Garda Paul Reynolds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob @IrishTimesCultr Extraordinary stuff. Thankfully I remain blissfully ignorant of the goings-on on that show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petersuntimes 14-0 down, they were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hairyandbrains Amazing stuff. There are still plenty of us around @LeinsterCC who remember Isolda well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob Perhaps. Montpellier will be kicking themselves not to have made this a 5-0 instead of a 4-1. Leinster have a platform now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@defensivelob Certainly is. Ringrose was brilliant in the second half. Took them on when it was hard to see how Leinster could score.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke Fitz's commentary has a few tells if you listen carefully. Watch out for words like 'disappointing', 'hopefully' and 'we'. #MONvLEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rorymacm @rocshot I see what you did there, Rory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishWomensCric Interesting interview with Mark Robinson, English women's cricket coach (Test Match Special) https://t.co/lnDsJzXwZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two squares behind Liam that can't be identified for legal reasons. #RTEsoccer https://t.co/81R1auDQmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrymcgee @PatLeahyIT @IrishTimes That's a pity. I like the podcast but not enough to pay for it when so many other good ones available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux This isn't what Charles Babbage invented the transistor for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They might have Bolohan, but we've got Holohan. #MOLIRE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>