<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was the Day of Payer for the Legal Protection of Unborn Children.

If you want to learn more about the... https://t.co/Yhy2frS1BL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good idea. I think any American should learn to speak the national language, English. It is one way to... https://t.co/PfczXmU1JI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countless "Thank You" to Americans from President Donald J. Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, President Donald Trump and the Americans who elected you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump will become the 45th United States President in about 30 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is one day before Donald J. Trump becomes our 45th President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the so called celebrities were that important, how did their candidate Hillary Clinton lose the election so... https://t.co/j9vHY1ndFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the so called celebrities were that important, how did their candidate Hillary Clinton lose the election so... https://t.co/IPoNuiP1aB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A large number of Democratic Party leaders hate democracy. Their party could remain in the cold for more than 16... https://t.co/UiNOK1AJez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A large number of Democratic Party leaders hate democracy. Their party could remain in the cold for more than 16... https://t.co/zS9vVpO6c5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank God! Two days before we welcome the death of political correctness and a return to freedom of speech in the... https://t.co/X6705e3AGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank God! Two days before we welcome the death of political correctness and a return to freedom of speech in the... https://t.co/Bt73TDKXdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Kellyanne Conway: Russia 'Did Not Succeed' in Attempts to Sway Election https://t.co/solQE1AdlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Kellyanne Conway: Russia 'Did Not Succeed' in Attempts to Sway Election https://t.co/iw5qjjYHWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year to you, your family and friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Barack Obama is the reason I quit the Democratic Party to vote for Donald J. Trump. I wonder how many... https://t.co/orBXHEwpD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Barack Obama is the reason I quit the Democratic Party to vote for Donal J. Trump. I wonder how many... https://t.co/nTgPtNHYfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attempt by President Obama and some Democratic leaders to eliminate "Merry Christmas!" will haunt their party... https://t.co/IKPyrUEg3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thinking of getting TV and services from AT&amp;T U-verse, think again. My family has been experiencing... https://t.co/cH5mro7GpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thinking of getting TV and services from AT&amp;T U-verse, think again. My family has been experiencing... https://t.co/APKUb8B7hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thinking of getting TV and services from AT&amp;T U-verse, think again. My family has been experiencing... https://t.co/6VwLCfTRvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas, Judge Pirro. No country, except the USA, will welcome these losers who have polluted and buried... https://t.co/N7VeAKgN5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas, Judge Pirro. No country, except the USA, will welcome these losers who have polluted and buried... https://t.co/tRbAFIvb2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use Twitter and Facebook. I never believe NBC News reports. Twitter and Facebook are more reliable than NBC news. https://t.co/6CU349GBKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You speak for me and the silent majority. Merry Christmas, daughter and your lovely family. https://t.co/PoucyQ0Eau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to dissolve philanthropic foundation to avoid conflict of interest via the @FoxNews App https://t.co/ohSImuxg4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Merry Christmas, Mr. President!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a major reason why Americans elected you. https://t.co/XX6dkPBljO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Thank you, Tucker, for educating that ignorant woman. I am not white and voted for Donald J. Trump. He values all Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Mike Pence Gets Pushed Too Far By Stephanopoulos, So He Drops The Hammer https://t.co/xDzuASqMWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he'll nominate retired Marine Gen. Mattis as secretary of defense... https://t.co/FDsiYQGTkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of social media has made it difficult for MSN get away with their distorted information. https://t.co/pe8YQGIdDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Has 1 Demand Before Moving Into White House... Some People Seriously Ticked Off https://t.co/GpDh6eVvIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Has 1 Demand Before Moving Into White House... Some People Seriously Ticked Off https://t.co/5WtxAtJBB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Trump Vows Massive Executive Action On Day 1 In Brand New Video https://t.co/2EIoJk1uaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Trump Vows Massive Executive Action On Day 1 In Brand New Video https://t.co/5gvr9OeB9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why waste time arguing with programmed Juan Williams? https://t.co/bpmEXd4ZOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why waste time arguing with programmed Juan Williams? https://t.co/yNdcMyoCHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think First Lady Melania Trump will stoop that low, and they know it. https://t.co/NSRm8as99h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think First Lady Melania Trump will stoop that low, and they know it. https://t.co/A4Mf88guzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood Hate Fest With Supermodel Who Mocked Melania Trump Just Got Worst Possible News https://t.co/Hck8ZUyQ7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood Hate Fest With Supermodel Who Mocked Melania Trump Just Got Worst Possible News https://t.co/RrfeLNAahO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s New York Times Interview: Full Transcript https://t.co/3JWz7uJsvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s New York Times Interview: Full Transcript https://t.co/sWVvtRAO2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fellow Trump Critics, Maybe Try a Little Listening https://t.co/kJyuPqLOje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fellow Trump Critics, Maybe Try a Little Listening https://t.co/Z8M7H9YMvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Jeanine Pirro Opening Statement Today 11/19/16 Destroys Hamilton. Donald Trump Demands Apology https://t.co/7Ocx1p8S7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Jeanine Pirro Opening Statement Today 11/19/16 Destroys Hamilton. Donald Trump Demands Apology https://t.co/pmOjKEKQA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls I am proud of the work you have done for us to Make America Great Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MALCOLM X ON AMERICAN ELECTIONS https://t.co/Vc1UOyLqLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Buzz: Are media encouraging rioters? https://t.co/IlLqgRRM6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump taps loyalists for Cabinet picks: Session for AG, Pompeo as CIA director via the @FoxNews App https://t.co/UVywbWCkvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West booed for saying he would have voted for Donald Trump via the @FoxNews App https://t.co/lsMFxqF2p8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Most of all I am delighted I we are going a very dignified and proud American as our next First Lady @MELANIATRUMP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am proud of you as my next President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media take hit in polls https://t.co/aGvAEosS9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President, president-elect's relationship evolving https://t.co/b8HxCtEdJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire Soros linked to anti-Trump protests - WikiLeaks https://t.co/2sgcnRFu0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's Police Just Came Forward With Jaw-Dropping Announcement About Trump Protesters https://t.co/TTG2B2NoUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very comprehensive statement and you have spoken for most of us. The Democratic Party leaders and the... https://t.co/w5BfHCdBu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody who had an open mind and enough time to follow the presidential campaigns would have found Donald J.... https://t.co/gWPbPnT3sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, help is about two months away after Donald Trump is sworn in as the 45th US President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a major reason for the humiliation the Democratic have suffered. https://t.co/aEmc18CjeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnomai Thanks Bro. Say hi to family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I join all Americans to thank the heroes who have sacrificed for us to enjoy. https://t.co/dhtUhWLSvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is unfortunate the people who could not find jobs under the Obama Administration, criminal illegal immigrants... https://t.co/mPqQLj5nlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very proud of the Americans, particularly African Americans, who rejected the lies and empty promises from... https://t.co/L8hRfv8Vqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOOK What Just Happened To Trump's Plane Right As He Began Trip To Meet Obama... https://t.co/QEuWpTdALm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The corrupt media in conjunction with the Hillary Clinton campaign are responsible for the demonstrations going... https://t.co/ei4lafIlFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you for your hard cork and giving us hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All they know is destruction. https://t.co/EzOxyW0rEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We should thank social media for helping us to counter the corrupt US mainstream media. @OANN  was very helpful in CA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans have elected the right person, Donald J. Trump, as their next President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Congratulations, Mr. President. At long last we can be free again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how corrupt the system is. https://t.co/YVsFH2zhWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret Service Just Came Forward With Huge Trump Victory Announcement - 'Strong Concern...' https://t.co/2vNsbcrKy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton disappears into thin air after losing the US presidency to Donald J. Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump is the next US President

Congratulations, Donald J. Trump and your committed team and... https://t.co/7Wsx8XumO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama on election: 'The sun will rise in the morning' https://t.co/bVvrCOxMoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You taught the fool. https://t.co/yhUz3GPxkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time for African Americans to vote for Donald J. Trump and the Republican Party to make it absolutely clear... https://t.co/RBwuswzT1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish to share the following mail an American sister sent to me today:

You dont know me but I am an American.... https://t.co/jkSrzDzyo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lyrics are too difficult for Hillary Clinton to understand. https://t.co/RbZvyJ1Jwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump works very hard in whatever he does. He  will make a great US president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: Bill Clinton verbally spars with protester at Bluffton rally https://t.co/Bqe91Gq5u5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoopi is unteachable. She needs a lot more lessons from Kellyanne Conway. https://t.co/EGJd5WN2hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell and Td Cruz Hop on Trump Train https://t.co/aeVD0tMHll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black people have the right to think for themselves. https://t.co/PRXFgy5Cdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is funny how people in power have this wrong notion of owning the people who gave them the power. First Lady... https://t.co/r4FhoCihr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People should boycott DirecTV and anything associated with them until they wake up. https://t.co/y8VePw8oql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton's weakness will make him look really good. https://t.co/3TnyEUTUuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I predicted from the very beginning, Donald Trump will win the presidency. The corrupt mainstream media have... https://t.co/mPUzfmYJpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They wanted a liar to continue misleading and taking advantage of Americans, particularly minorities, forever. https://t.co/xSXmkEvv7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bushes will always be losers.... https://t.co/XzEIwl4uCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Bushes have only two votes, Millions of Americans are voting for Donald Trump. https://t.co/M2Gzxj3A1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway takes on CNN’s Cuomo like nobody's business: 'You sound a little desperate' https://t.co/MtKaohaB5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesse Watters Goes to Fantasy Fest in a Wild Watters' World: 'I Don't Think I Can Say That on Air' https://t.co/kZKJ2z1aic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is struggling to cover her numerous illegal activities. Lies cannot undo what she has done. Americans are not... https://t.co/Bf1SKVrBnw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>