<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If I don't get Ed Sheeran tickets this week I swear I'm gonna cry until the concerts over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please tell me that's all an act with jedward or are them two 25 years olds really that retarded?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly makes me cringe seeing girls bragging about smoking weed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacy would literally make a 4 course meal out of a slice of bread, v dramatic she needs to go!#CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly two girls I know that are paler than milk literally think their bleedin black rappers, give it a rest potato heads..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people really don't have a care in the worldðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryRDelaney ***iPhone 7***]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I really need this job?ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your one of my top friends on snapchat rn I feel sorry for youðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this way too funny. https://t.co/Ge9gx5vTua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone feel free to run me over so I don't have to work until 9, thanks in advance x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early broke my contract about 4 times walking to work... greatðŸ™ƒðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsrobbieyall it was pelting down here, it's only all frosty nowâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraberry_ so creepy!ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiyah standing there waving at nothing and saying hello, I said who are you talking to? As cool as you like she says "the man"ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜© #sendhelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsrobbieyall it's not snowing where you live?ðŸ¤” Clondalkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking home in the snowðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryRDelaney You're not a catfish!! He might be thoughðŸ¤” be careful plsðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryRDelaney most definitely! Does he have snapchat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was the end of that idea folks x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I put gym gear on and fully convinced myself I was going for a jog to start getting fit again, until I sat down and start eating..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously need to start driving, getting blown to work isn't fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to purchase a top lip pronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get caught in the rain and end up looking like cave womanðŸ™ƒðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are jedward still alive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraberry_ sometimes Groupon does deals and they do be great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stop listening to @edsheeran's new songsðŸ˜ that man can do no wrong! Well worth the waitðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go for a dinner date with the girls and end up in diva after a 3 course mealðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the girlos are only short of snapping their backs to get there little arses in pictures, why like!ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day another take awayðŸ•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand when your bus is rallying down the road and you go to grab the bar, miss &amp; almost crack your skull off the staircase, happy FridayðŸ™ƒxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for Ed Sheerans new songs to be released!! Hash tag super fanðŸ’ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If 6 o clock could hurry up that would be great x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could've sworn my bed sang "if you leave me now, you take away the biggest part of me" when I had to get up thismorning...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your try "clean eating" for a day and decide it's not for you, now there's a Chinese on the wayðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely hating my life rn known I'm in work at 7AM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank god today is the last day of this horrendous yearðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently living off 3 hours sleep.. greatðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not mentally prepared for a 5am start tomorrowðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshAimee to brag about things they bought out of their fellas money?ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the girlos in competition wit who go the nicest Louboutins &amp; LV handbag for Xmas, they be fightin over whos fella sold the most ket next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the nicest Christmas with the best bunch, so grateful for them allâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a parent this time of year is the most magical thing, seeing Kiyah's face thismorning for her first proper Christmas was pricelessâ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super excited for Christmas this yearðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12-12 in work should be fun... said no one everðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working 40-50 hours a week is really starting to take its toll.. someone shoot me in the faceðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being up this early for work is already a disgusting start to my MondayðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish these pains would just go away &amp; let me sleepðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having food poisoning is the worst thing ever! Literally feel like I'm on my deathbedðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoiled little prinny for my birthdayðŸ‘¸ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegCarrie Was it meant for your house?ðŸ¤” oh definitely, onwards &amp; upwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegCarrie I even replayed it! Hahahaha! Gas, send me on them signatures pls looking for a bad boy xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not having to set an alarm for tomorrow is possibly the greatest feeling in my life rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I have to go to workðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a shitty week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than spending my day off in bed, being in a headlock choked from the snuggles off KiyahðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can it be Wednesday alreadyðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fell asleep at half 11 and now I'm wide awake... greatðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Charmai64852641 Hope you get somethingâ˜ºï¸x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Charmai64852641 That HCL place in town is always looking for staff x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only Tuesday and I want this week to be over already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how much sleep I get I always wake up tired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Conway honestly makes my day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels great liking your new job &amp; not dreading going every dayðŸ™ƒ #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT THE FUCK! https://t.co/yoomcUT6BA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can 9 o'clock hurry up pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still feel jet lagged is that even possible? &amp; back to work tomorrow lawddddd help mehðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you stop getting notifications of people going live on Instagram? Most pointless thing ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to New York &amp; buy loads for everyone else and get yourself 3 thingsðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I love this city I am honestly dying to get home to a bit of normalityðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshAimee Few more hoursðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only away a day and I miss home so much, such a little faggit bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanKelly_ Yeah it's very mild, thank youâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nerves are getting the better of meðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanKelly_ What's the weather like over there Nathan? Flying out todayâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My flight to New York is in the morning and I had a dream last night that my plane just fell out of the sky... grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashbacks of Megan falling last night are really making my life a bit more bearable atm x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is an alleged rapist, a racist a sexist &amp; a homophobe! Now he's a few votes away from being America's new president... HOW?ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Them Americans are bleedin mad!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did he even qualify for presidencyðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly don't know how Trump is winning the election over a woman that's been in politics most of her life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashamed to say I was one of them mongos that wrote me life story on fb, them memories that come up make me cringe &amp; wanna kill myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating my life getting ready for work rn, but this time next week I'll be getting ready for New YorkðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you overthink about yourself overthinking that's when you know you have a problemðŸ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 o clock on a Friday morning and there's a chase through Greenfort! Dump will never changeðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But of a nervous Nancy starting my new job today... helpðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being overtired = the worst headache ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andddd to top it off I'm up at 6, rip Staceyâ˜¹ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out since half 9 thismorning &amp; only getting into bed nowðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's officially Christmas time in 1hr 22minutesðŸ™ƒðŸŽ…ðŸ¼ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awh the little old couple on first dates is so cute, I literally wanna cryðŸ˜­x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 days til NYCðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awh man thought my last day was gonna be easy &amp; id skip out the door... feel like crying gonna miss all my nextiesðŸ˜­x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swear Amy's only on her second bottle of wkd and she's tipsyðŸ˜‚ how am I gonna cope with her for a weekðŸ™„ðŸ’ƒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like being awake since 4 on a Saturday morning!ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People round here have no fucking respect!! ANIMALSðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 holidays planned for next year alreadyðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard a little rumor the arc is opening back up the 17th of DecemberðŸ¤” Hope it doesðŸ˜ðŸ’ƒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time next week I can start watching Christmas moviesðŸ˜ðŸŽ…ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can this day be over already?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>