<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from these two problems, this is one of Malcolm Turnbull's best ideas #auspol https://t.co/G97Ys3haKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor's Gonski plan asked $1 from states for $2 from Cth. But Libs wanted "no strings attached". 3 years later... https://t.co/rP9HLLaCgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to charity runners @Rebecca_Cody &amp; @PetterssonMLA. Karinya House &amp; Veterans Hospitals the sure winners! https://t.co/kuXjfQfM6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HyperNexus Delighted you enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's Good Life podcast: Patricia Karvelas on resilience &amp; community
Podbean https://t.co/aYZZS8J7tx 
iTunes… https://t.co/rDzjFLWx4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for Malcolm Turnbull's assurance that he is "very confident and satisfied that the arrangement will continu… https://t.co/gBxdCpr9nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tax Office's website has failed. Again. The euphemism for the Turnbull government. #auspol https://t.co/13Qq6iG18a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commonwealth Bank's senior economist: if we want housing affordability, reform negative gearing &amp; CGT… https://t.co/6da8h37Ufo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was at a Burmese refugee camp in Jan. Solar panels galore. If they can back renewables, why can't Turnbull? #auspol https://t.co/zCoZnPHUKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RBA commodity price index keeps rising: up 5% in Jan &amp; 56% in past year. Big fiscal windfall for Turnbull Govt.… https://t.co/YxEN46h6Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt hasn't released any new company tax modelling to back its claims, so here's my analysis of its last lot… https://t.co/Y2BLEIkb3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Wonkish) New US econ paper finds that monopoly power is growing -- and it's hurting workers https://t.co/xDwXZ3Hdvl https://t.co/HH5d02B5b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of the sharing economy has skyrocketed, but Abbott-Turnbull Govt is failing to bring our rules into the C21st… https://t.co/caxGZuhWuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In today's @canberratimes, @georginaconnery reports on the many hit by Centrelink's robo-debt collection debacle https://t.co/8x8QceNrLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone tells you Trump's executive order isn't a "Muslim Ban", ask them why it has a carveout for Christians. https://t.co/XYiOxNGgAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's it like for an Olympian to come back to serious amateur running? Shaun Creighton reveals all… https://t.co/iL2f08esYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Company tax facts:
* Avg in top 10 economies=29%
* 30% with imputation raises as much as 20% without
* Gov predicts tiny benefits of cutting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🆕Good Life podcast: Olympian Shaun Creighton on running, coaching &amp; comebacks
Podbean https://t.co/aYZZS8J7tx
iTune… https://t.co/dNlpk3k5FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NickKristof on Trump ban on funding groups that even discuss abortion: over 20,000 women could die as a result https://t.co/JDgLSZBmaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANU study asks if work pays in our tax &amp; transfer system. Answer: yes, even in extreme case of single mum + 4 kids https://t.co/pqsI7hCunm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some field observations from last week's visit to aid projects in Burma/Myanmar with @savechildrenaus https://t.co/yIKfW9xBY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autolyse pastries used to be sweet, but the way they've apparently treated workers &amp; taxpayers leaves a sour taste https://t.co/DyWvfEsZp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcbmmx Thanks James - will check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to keep up with Coalition advice to young home buyers. 
Get a good job. 
Get rich parents. 
Get out of town. 
https://t.co/Ys5MU0EdGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing cool about Turnbull's pool tax loophole #auspol  https://t.co/Bq6w25yyxg https://t.co/Q5uJBkpR4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be nice if Turnbull decided to stop investing entirely in tax havens &amp; start cracking down on them? https://t.co/cQgfTHjKy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With debt rising, the Turnbull Govt is allowing some to claim a tax deduction for backyard pools #auspol https://t.co/zQY4nXskh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nelanore @HerCanberra Beautiful story! Congratulations to you both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Housing affordability &amp; last week's refugee camp visit. Transcript of my @SkyNewsAust @tomwconnell interview… https://t.co/ke0bwll8ki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time the Australian Honours system recognised men and women equally https://t.co/rzKNqSKKWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering what's written in the heavens? Brian Schmidt talks stargazing &amp; seasonal rhythms.
https://t.co/7vhf5VXKrM… https://t.co/SCo8KhXKpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating to see @WorldVision's projects outside Yangon, Myanmar/Burma. Small-scale finance &amp; ag productivity ref… https://t.co/55TflpppKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have enjoyed time in Burma with @savechildrenaus, but I'm not sure I'll miss morning runs in Yangon.… https://t.co/fg09R27pWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extraordinary factoid, from Michael Lewis's new book "The Undoing Project" about Danny Kahneman &amp; Amos Tversky https://t.co/BIqHqkL7fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local Burma news reports on our meeting with govt, where we raised the treatment of Rohingya in Rakhine… https://t.co/TYv0ndX8ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awful tragedy in Melbourne. My thoughts with all those affected. For the rest of us, hug our kids close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Australia need a new regressive tax break, costing $19 billion a year? Newly promoted @MichaelSukkarMP won't r… https://t.co/xUKsIL3Zxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Obamas were catholic in their tastes not because they had to be, but because that’s what we should be: open." https://t.co/gVANOfgu6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking with community members in Pauktaw Township, outside Sittwe, in Yangon/Burma (thanks to @savechildrenaus fo… https://t.co/DeDDc1SPkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When human resource departments collude- my op-ed in Business Insider https://t.co/2NYcE4tOCw #auspol https://t.co/Zd8cxzHFWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Life podcast is back, @cosmicpinot on stars, wine and the Nobel Prize. 
Podbean https://t.co/aYZZS8J7tx
iTunes… https://t.co/kjZP5GSggM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was the hottest in 115,000 years. Retweet if you think it's time for @turnbullmalcolm to act on #climatechange  https://t.co/RiDf6GvkTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Myanmar/Burma with @savechildrenaus, we visited a Rohingya refugee camp in Sittwe. Extraordinary kids. https://t.co/tJ7wkX4Gll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few leave top political roles on their own terms. Congrats to @mikebairdMP for doing so. Enjoy the newfound time with your family. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My father has penned a fascinating op-ed on what Freiburg, Germany can teach #Canberra about sustainability #auspol  https://t.co/ez0XW5dlvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cracker campaign. Support it if you can. https://t.co/RyCCgROUAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest Chronicle column is on Matt Napier, who walked across Africa to raise awareness of global poverty… https://t.co/fqd5jYZCjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Daniel for helping show us around Myanmar's massive parliament (trip organised by @savechildrenaus &amp; fund… https://t.co/qkXnW0aNFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful NYT piece on how @BarackObama set aside an hour a day in the White House for reading novels &amp; nonfiction  https://t.co/sI2ROd0Ltz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the peak small business group now worries that Barnaby Joyce's whacky effects test could create a "lawyer's pi… https://t.co/9tYVm4SkgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive to have @davidmadden show us @Phandeeyar innovation lab (Myanmar trip organised by @savechildrenaus &amp; fu… https://t.co/iFLct0V5Xh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Malcolm Turnbull is channelling Michael Palin on the Trans-Pacific Partnership #auspol #deadparrot https://t.co/j00JtZ0dSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good call from @fitzhunter: Turnbull should scrap the APVMA relocation. It's not too late. #auspol https://t.co/rLs6FyIkfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of a different setting for my morning run than Canberra + the kangaroos. #myanmar #yangon @savechildrenaus https://t.co/aZEnKRk3z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is our banking sector getting more concentrated? My latest competition op-ed is in today's Tele… https://t.co/ur5997rzyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the digital divide in #Canberra means one side of the street has #NBN &amp; the other doesn't #auspol  https://t.co/QkoTUboGKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuffed to get a mention in the terrific @RunnersWorldmag https://t.co/XiIgXSkatU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freak #Canberra windstorm has taken down half a dozen tree branches on Torrens St Braddon. Ping @ACT_SES https://t.co/3bBBPJ3bwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elias_Hallaj @thmcmahon Yours look very happy! And yes, mine got happier once a photo with dad wasn't standing between them &amp; their dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study finds aid transparency got better under ALP, then worse under Libs. Oh, and Libs halved the aid budget too.… https://t.co/LR88Bg8PXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next week, I'll be in Myanmar visiting aid projects. Trip organised by @savechildrenaus &amp; funded by… https://t.co/myBc3vzVxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking night for a baseball game. Go @CanberraCavalry! #canberra https://t.co/6ilBgxb2vD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Wonkish) Excellent survey article on Australian labour market inequality, by Jeff Borland &amp; Mick Coelli ($)… https://t.co/kxMGpk4fyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always nice to have old research quoted in the press. But as a Labor MP, I'll take substance over surface any day. https://t.co/6tG02npPIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martydent Thanks - that makes sense to me. But he's leading in the majors series at present, so it's a big call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@albertostretti @martydent Marty, what do you think of Kipchoge's decision to skip spring season for Nike "sub-2"? https://t.co/Zvf7NLZgkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattliddy Actually, 4 raters measuring the key variable (also tried it with another 10 raters; it makes no difference). Sample size = 286.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important office in a democracy: citizen". A stemwinder #ObamaFarewell speech https://t.co/VZ8Ln4gUrs https://t.co/t6dvTmsTGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb Sincere condolences. I'm sure she was proud of her granddaughter's successes in each of those domains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoneBonker888 Thanks Marty - that's great to hear. Best of luck with your running.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull Government is slowly getting around to doing something about firms who are slow to pay their bills… https://t.co/OpViFBmUIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just stumbled across RBA stats on (detected) fakes
For $5 notes: 1 in 5 million 
For $50 notes: 1 in 30,000… https://t.co/56PDx6hmDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting one of Fenner's newest constituents to discuss tennis ball and Schmackos prices in the ACT, welcome Bella!… https://t.co/8aAwu0TATe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free to a good home: Hansard Reps 1988-2015 &amp; Senate 1992-95. Email https://t.co/3wiESZBNoA{A}… https://t.co/KSweotqPFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't decide- shall I keep the holiday beard? https://t.co/CsgVxEhp0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly declassified CIA/NSA/FBI report on how Russian hackers influenced the US election makes extraordinary reading… https://t.co/whMBYdXJ7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on summer reading this wk?
Atkinson https://t.co/5smLUqCDC8
False ads https://t.co/nEw8j0VMP5
Monopolie… https://t.co/gFIr2M0ukF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less competition = higher prices, lower quality &amp; more #inequality. My HuffPo oped with Adam Triggs… https://t.co/wRjx7tWS8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TimHammond1 and I need to know: did we go a wee bit overboard with the puns in this piece?… https://t.co/nGw4Jvdwlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the simple things in life are often the best. https://t.co/0RB47EKdRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEOs (whose wages have skyrocketed) use a sailing regatta to argue for low-paid workers to be paid less #inequality  https://t.co/Uj0MemOtED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give false advertising the flush. In today's @dailytelegraph, @TimHammond1 &amp; I lift the lid on some smelly problems… https://t.co/wCCjJN73vU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Wonkish) New research finds that mergers in US manufacturing raise prices, but don't improve productivity  https://t.co/s5xhIsakNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tribute to Tony Atkinson, the economist who was a giant in the field of inequality  @canberratimes  https://t.co/Nfe81O3si3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jefferson argued for a constitutional review once a generation. @ProfGWilliams says Aust needs the same #auspol  https://t.co/sIaDYQwvi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great @UniofOxford inequality scholar Sir Tony Atkinson has died. A friend, mentor &amp; co-author. I'll miss him. https://t.co/f9SqD99rRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss_shiny 4 or 5. I change them every 700-900km.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AidanCDelaney Thanks Aidan. Will reply properly in the new year, but Labor has called for system to be suspended https://t.co/G8y6mF1R2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottyimhoff Mighty impressive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving my running this year. https://t.co/pKbZzXpGWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the Abbott-Turnbull Govt cut more than 3300 tax office jobs, complaints are up by more than 40%… https://t.co/kGUk0RvFD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@booth_alison As Richard Flanagan might put it, Labor's policy is anti-mullet wig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Kerry's speech on resolving the Israel-Palestine conflict is well worth reading in full https://t.co/4CWFlQSToM https://t.co/38jKKGrg3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp @LisaVisentin Actually, I'm pretty sure that bit of Beautiful Mind is wrong. Nash equilibrium in movie (&amp; on NYE!) is mixed strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectly put (assuming Byron was a bit more market-oriented and a lot less poetic) https://t.co/XYMZmL1WJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Turnbull Gov spent $16,500 on a report whose arguments had already been debunked by Treasury #EconomicLeadership  https://t.co/NYSitvbkpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JDVance1's excellent "Hillbilly Elegy" reminded me that the hardest bit of "Battlers &amp; Billionaires" was writing… https://t.co/ZvcSNAxnyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libs cutting real wages of many public servants, yet giving 12 Armidale-Canberra flights to APVMA staff who move https://t.co/GOtIe3UHY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Matt Napier walk 2000km across Africa kicking a soccer ball? Listen to the Good Life podcast to find out… https://t.co/DMtk4WiOGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katinacurtis Like a medieval artist, I like to include deliberate errors to see who picks them up. Full props to you for being 110% right.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>