<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@stanzillaz my ilvl is 878 I do believe though.  Lol.  I've had some good luck with 2 legendaries and world boss titanforge to 890.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stanzillaz Difficult with a healer who hasn't done anything more than +3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will never do M+15 for my artifact stuffs.  :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perculia Lol.. People mindlessly fishing while watching the Superbowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son needed a backpack that closed without the zipper falling off..  Sew I stuck myself with a needle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh... My luck. https://t.co/weMnyrH1ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swotam Shush.. Not happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turned on the kettle 3 times... 3 times I've forgotten it after its gone off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just looking at apps and closing them, when Kindle caught my eye.. https://t.co/OZOJHMUFfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titanforged, 890. Giggity [Windwhipped Greatcloak] https://t.co/uO5hdepW8M #Warcraft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegallyErin @simAlity He has advisors, and he has good advisors. He's ignoring the good advisors for the dumbass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mabusgaming @WarcraftDevs @devolore Is there a place I can make my own gif like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarcraftDevs Can you guys hotfix it so that the various Insignias stack in higher amounts?  5 is kinda silly and insufficient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfmezei I'm now tempted to file opposing costs for @CanadaPIAC Their costs went from reasonable to ridiculous, and making a living off it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfmezei What the Fuck.. More and more or just looks like piac is out to insert themselves and get money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New upstairs neighbors must have gone out..  Their dogs are barking and whining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWSheppard lol..  Ah, but why not show a man some eye candy..  Get them buying more. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWSheppard That's a cute dress.  Sure you wouldn't like it instead? :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tzeriel Magnets + water + fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henderburn As well, if theres a miss for catching someone who was tossed, skin on skin (hand on knee/waist) better than grab loose clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henderburn @RyersonU Honestly, doing gymnastics lines and feeling clothing adjust on the knee is distracting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henderburn @RyersonU You probably haven't seen the Cheerleading competitions with the gymnastics &amp; tosses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShepDanellos @SwiftOnSecurity Tap takes 10 to 20 seconds total provided decent internet access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShepDanellos @SwiftOnSecurity Thats why our cards (and readers) have chip, as well as the tap feature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShepDanellos @SwiftOnSecurity Chip is default in Canada..  It's only US having 'issues' with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Luthvian @vitaemachina Congrats you two! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#judgestamp HOW DID YOU PASS THE BAR?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeeThrPoint29 Why are you spamming me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking like @POTUS immigration agents might get kicked out of Canada. Their Muslim ban might be breaking our laws. https://t.co/aPSaFsD2U1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only reason these poor children won't die, is because Canada is taking them and is doing the life-saving surgeries.  @POTUS is shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not keeping 'evil' out, you're keeping out children who need surgeries to live. @POTUS is a piece of shit. https://t.co/71pJitb0dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Support @Sivation Even in the "Wrong Translation?" option, theres no actual thing to say there was nothing to translate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Support Where's the option for "There was nothing to translate."
cc @Sivation https://t.co/0R8l0dspm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anothershoe @That_AC Yeah.  Good boss and I have a deal to trade any time done on my own time, trade for time off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrGeo_Terra It's just bullshit. I mean, as it is, I'm installing stuff on all systems from home tonight. But that's on my schedule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo..  I lied.  No, I can't do that remotely. No way in hell am I going to be at his beck and call to scan shit for him on weekends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@That_AC No overtime.  I'm on salary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Install scanner software onto a few systems.. Boss asks, 'Can you do that remotely? I want to give you work to do over the weekend.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glen_mcgregor @kevinolearytv Cuz all he cares about is big business. Screw everyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Khaixur I find Caramel Rice Cakes usually work well in this situation. Helps the nausea, dampens the hunger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GhemitHunts Maybe you're overthinking a bit?  Give them a save closed space, warmth, and food for mom. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@devolore @SeTec9 Cardigan is just too much for this generation. Dress shirt &amp; sport coat is still very dashing and handsome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anafielle Wow... How'd it get sent off to a flight to JFK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simAlity And yet, some do it all the time because they think they're all better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Milnoc AND there's no business name on the sign beside the door, or on the directory info for the building.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Milnoc Honestly, I wouldn't be surprised.. They never open the door when someone knocks on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlord doesn't know yet...  Landlord's gonna have a conniption fit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlord informed all units in the office building to let Bell contractors in for Fiber installation.  1 office in building refused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaboboria Something about an enzyme in spit helps break it down. *shrugs*  Small price to pay to get blood out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaboboria Done that once.  I ran up to the local store, bought heavy pads, wipes and new underwear. Wipes cleaned up the jeans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent Yup... They 'forgot' this building when they upgraded the area to FTTN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent There are 3 dslams within 200m of my office building. We're CO-fed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micahwhipple Oh geez..  That would be nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent Plus the other end of the 2nd floor &amp; probably need to do all the offices on the ground floor which have their own entrances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent Still need to bring fiber into the building, and turn up that fiber. We're still CO-fed on copper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent They installed the equipment in the telecom room, and I think half of the offices on the 2nd floor yesterday..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@never99percent Yup... Whenever it goes active and we can order it.. I hate this 6/.8 we're on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micahwhipple Think you'll actually get the actual VR?  Or will they replace it with some cardboard headset?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ShaunKing @ohgoditsranor So we know now, that @POTUS only condemns terrorist incidents caused by Muslims, and not by racist white guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the Fibre to go active, so we can get rid of this @Bell DSL which has been shit for over a year now,… https://t.co/bAVdgU7Ubb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we have Bell Fibre installed..  Just need to wait for it to go active.. https://t.co/DQXey3neWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simAlity Err, can't become unstable if you go off. Its Lifelong fight &amp; no mentally ill person whether medicated or not should have a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simAlity Even if you're medicated, it doesn't mean you're stable. Or become unstable if you go off them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad..  People who are mentally ill shouldn't have access to guns. More mass shootings like Sandy Hook will happe… https://t.co/uc60gC3KOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWSheppard Lol.. I warned them the system was delicate. lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReciRaider Nothing yet?  They're doing the entire city. Can't order until its active - probably a few months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bell contractors installing Fiber to the unit somehow took out our phone lines &amp; DSL...  DSL's back.. Phone lines aren't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giggity.  Bell contractors are in right now, installing Fiber into the office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreadravenanzu @Malkarii_ Yeah, but it's more what someone else might bring while vaccinated..  And give to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreadravenanzu @Malkarii_ oh.  Blech :(
Here's hoping there's no outbreak of anything near her..  :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreadravenanzu @Malkarii_ Vegan is very different from anti vaxx though..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Malkarii_ Can she be talked to?  Told that the guy who came up with it, only did so because he was paid lots of money to say it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuatarTheOdd @Malkarii_ Eh.. Even they don't work well. You just get immunity at a young age to 1 strain.. Not all. My Mom had it 3 times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Khaixur Doesn't matter.. Any sort of 'joke' along those lines will be taken seriously by the country receiving them. He's a fucking idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiedupree @Romaxton Uh oh... Them's firing words for Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spikestabber Very much so. Lol.  She's one of the best in the city..  Still teaches too.  Just meet her yesterday and I love her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yeah.  Lol.  My arm now..  Still hasn't gone down fully in spots after 9hrs &amp; 2 doses of meds. Can you tell they… https://t.co/SB7xGMvugE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightmare pod in a Nightmare Pod, in a Nightmare pod. Giggity. https://t.co/Vo6TzZwtXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is cool..... I can see the results of my blood tests for allergies online before my allergist gets them. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KT_Deathope Mine this morning didn't even have a rollup. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holyzorea @Malkarii_ Gotcha. Didn't know that.  I'm 870, so's my tank.. I upgraded my DHT from +2 to +4 with some crappy dps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Malkarii_ @Holyzorea Any chance they're hoping to upgrade their keystone (I have no idea how this works, I only do +2)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreadWingKnight Yup. Was concerned that it would cover to $500 only, but..  I'm happy. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giggity.  My insurance covers my allergy shots in full.. $660/yr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After I took antihistamines. Still itchy.  Lots of bumps. Stupid allergies. https://t.co/eK8qPwtgmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MercifulDraenei You can't really see all the red in the picture... Its much redder than the picture shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhh! That picture was also after she gave me a shot of antihistamines into my arm. I just took some Claritin on top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBomb @Milnoc Highly allergic to dust mites, trees and grass.  I'm going on allergy shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm itchy.. https://t.co/RiKoNQApF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giggity! Roll up the rim is back! https://t.co/PxgwNepXSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBomb Yeah..  It's why I hate politicians so much. They know they have an interview, but refuse to actually answer questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao.  Got cut off by the interviewer, because she just refuses to say anything other than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Leitch refuses to answer questions in her interview this morning. Just keeps talking about her wanting 'face to face interviews']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogersBiz I'm not? I did say it was for my office. Rogers isn't available in that building since they couldn't bother to run a line in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per Jon Stewart, the new official US language is 'Bullshit'. Heh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohgoditsranor @TheDailyShow @ACLU What the hell..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBomb @jfmezei If it's a big hearing, maybe.  Otherwise, hell no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfmezei @NBomb :/
I'm sorry to hear it all..  I stopped filing after the lawsuit...  Not worth it or the stress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait til Bell brings Fiber to my office building. We're paying over $80/month for 6/.8. Will be able to switch to 50/10 for $71/month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfmezei @NBomb Oh wow.. As of when? Because of the rudeness of some participants?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>