<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Take on gun culture then, you numpty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlinmoran @Jess4_RK Wow. Is that... real..?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's a mirror, dude. #awkward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you half expect to see @mcgregor_ewan on your way back from seeing #T2trainspotting in #Edinburgh. https://t.co/muIPzIQeUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a recent photo, but the message seems very pertinent today. #RefugeesWelcome #scotland https://t.co/k07tpEQ3Ui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk It's the classic. What's the next step?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk It's in the original post, original responder was looking into it?! Netflix app crashes the Youview box just past midnight daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk again, really not addressing the original question, sent weeks ago now. @AJCaledonia, did you ever get an answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk What advice? It seems to be just a link to the forum, but there's no solution to this problem I can see?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk is the answer there? This appears to just be a generic link]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk It's the Youview box, from Talktalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk any update on this..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgregor_ewan @piersmorgan YES TO THIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrisonkt_ I didn't realise you'd left - what new adventure are you on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like a sequel to The Omen. I have the fear. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herring1967 It's like she's mocking us... #GonnaeNoDaeThat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The temptation to photobomb is strong... #Outlander #Edinburgh https://t.co/0hAgYdeFZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enquiring minds want to know... https://t.co/ogcSTl7Zvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There is no good way for you to finish this sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I want all the pretty things and it's your fault @bethjhall https://t.co/P64yJ00agC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @JohnMasonMSP @NicolaSturgeon @theSNP Completely unacceptable, and demands some kind of response, surely?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @JohnMasonMSP I trust @NicolaSturgeon is equally appalled by this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @JohnMasonMSP Did we go back to 1917 at the turn of the bells? This language is beyond creepy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TalkTalk Hope so! App crashes every night at midnight. Don't know if Netflix, YouView or TalkTalk issue but see others have same problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crescent moon, Venus, castle and... bus.  #edinburgh https://t.co/LygLV18XF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joy of a wee bit of George. https://t.co/nT6s4YP23G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've had too much wine to find the damn snowman in your Where's Wally advent calendar. #ChristmasProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellolisadonati Some of my favourite people 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellolisadonati Yup tried there. Sadly need it tomorrow or would order online. Not to worry, just means I have an idea ready for birthdays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellolisadonati Hunted Edinburgh today for fannybaws mug- nae joy. Should've guessed they'd be gone at Xmas! Any tips on stockists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say it ain't so, @michelrouxjr - poor show. https://t.co/qgDg0IZXFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @ewanwilson94 ahhh grannies are the bestest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flamingo is for life, not just for Christmas. #FestiveFlamingo https://t.co/R0v4rPIhmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TweetForShelter https://t.co/SJC46duCi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unplugged70 @rowanmorrison @sophie_aldred What happens in the 80s stays in the 80s...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowanmorrison @unplugged70 @sophie_aldred She's not daft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unplugged70 @rowanmorrison @sophie_aldred Sophie might remember but she won't give away the answer. #sophieisonmyside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unplugged70 @rowanmorrison Logic has been a victim here I feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowanmorrison @unplugged70 @sophie_aldred OH DEAR GOODNESS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlinmoran @realDonaldTrump Clearly too much time on his hands. And not enough self awareness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faither's paintings on show this week at @edinburghart. Worth a visit if you're in an arty mood! #edinburgh https://t.co/4ekW9LESfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lordy. Ed Balls. Can't unsee that. #GangnamStyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LEGO_Group @StopFundingHate ...and I have just bought some Lego to celebrate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 just needs to be taken out back and shot, doesn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad face Rutger Hauer. Contouring on point though. https://t.co/tlHpZV72yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez. When the guy behind a million clown-based nightmares thinks things got ugly... #vote #choosewisely https://t.co/YoWrX86s5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have election fear. Tell me it's all gonna be okay, yeah? https://t.co/MIIxi8oDy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markgatiss Me too. I think it's maybe just Brexit Syndrome By Proxy. I'm hoping it'll pass quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic - hard work pays off, eh @jacobdhay?! https://t.co/pu9qFe9YxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew. Watched #TheWalkingDead and didn't want to throw myself to the walkers at the end. And now I want a tiger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtofallabout Not cool. Poor show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtofallabout @Jonnyishh What a shame. Saw him in Edinburgh last weekend and it was ace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaharri_ I'd suggest watching that episode in 5 minute stints. It's relentlessly traumatising!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaharri_ It is all TOO MUCH. Still haven't unclenched... 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having said that, I may never sleep again 😳   #TheWalkingDead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched #TheWalkingDead and feel like I need to sleep for about a week. EXHAUSTED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo much fun with @TheHorrorMaster in Edinburgh. Bloody good show - and some natty dance moves to boot. https://t.co/k4wo23GNzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisaharri_ *insert joke about how it's the snake that's tweeting*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for you, @DavidHayArt - read it dreckly, share it at your leisure https://t.co/yM20kRxYgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evolution has taken a surprising turn. #NaeKnees https://t.co/wTvZ9N6O9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Yup. We keep it by the corgi-washing station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Your ass would make a better candidate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-watching Halloween ahead of seeing @TheHorrorMaster in Edinburgh on Saturday. Pumpkins at the ready 🎃 🎃 🎃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GabbySidibe It's glorious. Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenKing It's incredible. I'm in Scotland and he scares me witless - there is no safe distance from this man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having myself a wee @toriamos night and singing along loudly and badly. Yes. #NeighboursHateMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyZuker @amyschumer @Variety Womenfolk and their hysterical opinions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennyeclair Never mind theatres - offices, pubs, bus stops...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh man, are you still here? Isn't there a locker room somewhere remote that needs a cave-dweller?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Actual lol. Though it's probably best that all women stay at least at arms length from the man at all times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJoeHarland @sarajcox Exotic, yet accessible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit got real.  https://t.co/Iwxota72Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE this. Good excuse for a visit to @SmithMuseum too! https://t.co/y2u6KZBM5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyZuker Yup, world-leading qualities... 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh @AlisonMoyet on #totp... bloody great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When clearing out a cupboard unearths a piece of your yoof... @NME https://t.co/rozZdlfse5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlinmoran @fleabag I LOVE that show. Bloody brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VueHelp nearly a week on and still no reply from your lost &amp; found folks, and no reply to my follow up email. Really?? @vuecinemas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevRichardColes I've never understood why folk seem to want him to be some gregarious raconteur... is world class tennis not enough?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kinda love that @frankieboyle is wading in on #bakeoff. And is so right.  https://t.co/cTpwwePcLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words to live by. #RoaldDahlDay https://t.co/JE8MPuy3ZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VueHelp There must be some way to contact the cinema, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VueHelp Help! Left scarf of sentimental value in the Edinburgh Omni. Reported to central lost/found - but is there a direct number? Helllp!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMillican75 @StandardIssueUK Me too. Pro standard MegRyan-ing, if I do say so myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janegarvey1 One can't be seen with last season's bleach. Simply wouldn't do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two episodes into @fleabag... she's awful and I kinda love her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenadunham Nicely put.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh.   *mind slightly blown* https://t.co/dBk1WfemwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling @amyschumer Me too. Proper belly laughs... and loved @RachelFeinstein too. Fab night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out with the festival, in with @amyschumer - canny wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never get tired of this view. #Edinburgh https://t.co/fJG85GqLkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tail end of the Fringe... #edfringe https://t.co/tFVEPnJCJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved your sappy songs @Alancumming #EdintFest https://t.co/CyWFOVgb3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @ewanwilson94 I should have guessed. The band wouldn't get a mixed reaction...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobdhay @ewanwilson94 If you mean the band, he is quite correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowanmorrison Wait, you haven't done that yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee children should be with their families. Join @Unicef_UK's campaign #refugeeswelcome https://t.co/TVGAY8KDkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh BLESS. A tale of true love in three photos.  https://t.co/TOlHZkafUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art for art's sake - AND for a good cause. Looking forward to @MacmillanArtSho #edinburgh https://t.co/3LW7UMb5Yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtofallabout @MOO Ordered some for @DavidHayArt that arrived this week too- we both went for multiple images, rounded corners I see! #snap]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>