<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbstractCode @RumpledElf fair enough. Here's an image purporting to be webs built by spiders given drugs instead. https://t.co/k32HSWALF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbstractCode @RumpledElf context? (Ex-scientist here, though I never had to deal with ethics applications myself)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okcupid no Yazidis? Couldn't you say "and other religions"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was an Australian uni I'd be doing a heavy advertising blitz in the #TrumpBan countries right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Patbagley the NYT says it's a technical adjustment supported by the Obama admin https://t.co/iwr4ywTZOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceBergMama @mckinnon_a @yiduiqie or "they changed PMs again?" (Yeah, it's not a new joke)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarioVilas @BenHowe @SavedYouATrick one hour later than Ben's tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenHowe @SavedYouATrick screenshot of @cons_nation one hour later looks different to me. Is there a homoglyph atta… https://t.co/HDS7NSF83Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to stop a heatwave: buy two fans, a pack of Zooper Doopers, and leave your fleece at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheUndefeated @Patriots Show me your friends, and I’ll tell you who you are may have some truth, but applied wrongly leads to McCarthyism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefScientist @mwotton @smh well it is in an early time zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefScientist @smh Australia's finest news source is @TheNTNews !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nelhage @bbatsov how thick is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought тема (theme) would be too abstract to find a photo, but many pictures of theming an operating system. Word repurposing FTW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius perspective, I'm very glad supernova exist. And seeing the night sky in outback Mongolia was cool. Felt like I could reach them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius unlike reality tv stars, astronomical phenomenon don't care what you think of them. They just *are*.

From an anthropocentric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@godfat I don't support One China, but I don't trust him to make a constructive improvement to the situation. Suspect OCP is bargaining chip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starbuxman same for terrorist attacks / hate crimes / other shocking violence. It spreads like wildfire on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Couldn't Stop Chavez. Don't make the same mistakes we did. https://t.co/aybY4zLtIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learnt how to get Anki to actually test your spelling: https://t.co/FrUV5GwiSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Usama_36 The text from "all" onwards is a different colour from the rest of the text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paleofuture I assume some staffer saw it getting heavy traffic and decided to tweet the article. I'm not agreeing with this BTW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paleofuture The article is getting heavy traffic because of posts noting that Obama had a refugee halt, such as https://t.co/QTox1XpCgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussexparty the main thing I notice is the use of what looks like a greek letter for "A".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At first I thought @HostelBookers was trying to be topical, but then it rotated into photos of other destinations. https://t.co/i2kUe7Y82a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjaminNorton @hoaxeye Did you bother going past the headline to reading the rest of the screenshot before tweeting this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfTerryHughes @billshortenmp what are the other two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The eroticism of Russia partly vanished, I think, when she was revealed to be little more than a vulgar, backward version of America."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are 6 official languages in the United Nations." - Like @RawStory and Noor Tagouri, they got the first name… https://t.co/pF4WdsmOHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only Ukrainian teacher in Sydney thinks I should learn Russian instead. Should I learn Ukrainian, Russian individually, or in a class?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned the Ukrainian skill Animals on https://t.co/3f4MC15T4N #duolingo Time to get ready for @shitduosays style sentences!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjgrimm @rubyconf_au any progress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katydid_alot @AlterNet Do you want a long form medical certificate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius I'd suggest Twitter for a more breadth-first search. It gives you exposure to a wider variety of topics in less time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miel The ongoing focus on female members of Trump's family is in no way creepy or misogynistic at all. Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am looking for motivated and serious students learning English, German, Ukrainian or Russian." that rules me out! https://t.co/8DjtfgZy0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned the Ukrainian skill Letters 3 on https://t.co/3f4MC15T4N #duolingo That covers the whole алфавіт (alphabet)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in favour of a variety of people getting the award, including sportspeople, but I'm glad it went to a scientist… https://t.co/unebXL5DkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sea level rises by three metres, we'll lose all our unis! https://t.co/jBtClas4Wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received an unsolicited phone call from a recruiter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius there's a proposal for a Stack Exchange for Ukrainian. If a lot of your followers are from Eastern Europe, they may be interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The proposed Q&amp;A site uses the same software as Stack Overflow. Though it has enough people to launch, it's thought more people would help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stack Exchange Q&amp;A site proposal: Ukrainian Language https://t.co/TN5wDh9Dma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyFeldtmann @ABCaustralia And I strongly suspect the reason they were interviewing him in the first place was to… https://t.co/da4XbQOlA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyFeldtmann @ABCaustralia Most of the other interviews done that day would be the opposite of what he's espousing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcnees @hiro_asari One surprising aspect was this was written before the internet was a really major thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Twitter wouldn't give me the likes of people I've recently unfollowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hiro_asari It's Tuesday in Sydney. #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psyckology sheesh, you'd think George Takei would know about sensitive information being collected/misused for nefarious ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the past used to be in black and white, but never thought the future would be as well. Thankfully it's only… https://t.co/34k8nKiFLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new phrase. Nothing wrong, no stigma, with getting first aid, right? https://t.co/JGwxRNQDea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pwim I can't see the original tweet on my client. Does it still exist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatDamonGuy @aussexparty Is it available as a pill rather than smoked?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case anyone's wondering, Jack Bauer is trending because of the Tour Down Under, not because of US politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hooshanglahooti Too many possible answers, but some countries are regarded as more important, and receive more attention, than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This question isn't trolling. He grew up in Iran, has lived in many countries and now lives in Australia, which had… https://t.co/dypMjPZBLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @guardian is post-truth. They didn't end up fixing their error. https://t.co/VMfBe9o1P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike the "repeat a lie often enough" quote, which originated from the HUAC, this quote is true.… https://t.co/MeuCRdmaix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looked at the "Revolution in Ukraine" pull request again. Just noticed the colour of the labels.… https://t.co/EHwFWT0ckI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msjayele the same Jesus the killer ranted about on Facebook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulfioravanti I was wondering if there was something like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need more unclothed people, less quackery @NatGeo . #posttruth https://t.co/7FNKbKK8st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who commit domestic violence go on to attack other human beings!" - awful but truthful argument for taking DV seriously. #bourkest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarnsGreg men assault women and children because of jail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump @McClatchyDC when his opponent's accused of getting money from Saudi Arabia this isn't likely to harm him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson can you start by not making unfounded claims on Twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marrrrcussss @neiltyson I love the poorly educated too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicola_prigg @neiltyson implying America has never been smart? Sick burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwotton how could you like something with such poor type safety? Two are years, one is a legal code, one is a cryptographic code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arian_marandi @hooshanglahooti @everydayiran thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the Iranian regime hates America, Iranian people held a vigil after 9/11. Please be considerate in what you tweet about #Plasco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hooshanglahooti is this photo Iranian? Is the writing Iranian or Arabic? https://t.co/kGeeR94cnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WTC: caused by Sunni religious extremists. #Plasco: caused by unaccountable, criminally negligent, Shiite theocratic regime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went through 420 profiles of Ukrainian native speakers on lang-8. Only 6 were worth asking for a friend request.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaMielke @DavidZax I think I just read that article. Most of the times they avoided "the", but there was one near the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cute Easter egg if you scroll up too far in DuoLingo. https://t.co/bcNWzLBuHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned the Ukrainian skill Letters 1 on https://t.co/Iwi4hEfgbt (Hey, it's a start!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me :// https://t.co/aFm5XfOrye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on @duolingo now, as I'm learning a language they have (Ukrainian). Friend me if you know me. https://t.co/nxa61K1Get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laura_nobilis the anti-immigration types have been more active in international collaboration than the pro-immigration types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laura_nobilis have you tried Lang-8?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@godfat did you have Wifi turned on? I have photos geolocated to Incheon airport despite not getting a SIM for South Korea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjgrimm autocorrect tried making that "keep Dunlop Volleys saggy" #damnyouautocorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizeburke does "it's bloody/f****** hot" win?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debuggex looks kind of cool. https://t.co/6hJWiNYqlE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanguardVivian @hiro_asari I've heard that claim about snuggies before, on TV Tropes, but I haven't been able to confirm it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe how sloppy the media is. https://t.co/PWlImPTJSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubyconf_au found it: https://t.co/CiTDl7OgoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubyconf_au are there abstracts for the talks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amos_tim serious question. Do Christians believe God communicates directly with ordinary individuals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL the hardest language in the world to learn: Sentinelese. Used by a tribe that refuses contact with outside world https://t.co/8EUm15NWMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izevaka @shanselman @headius the former, sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is prayer your steering wheel or your spare tire?" - what's the correct answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanselman @headius pronouncing OS X Yosemite like "Vegemite", even though I knew of Yosemite Sam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius watching him), and Rolf Harris (probably not well-known in the US. He is a great musician though, had a knack for the quirky.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius FWIW, here's some of the works I've avoided: Michael Jackson until he died, Charlie Sheen (but was totes ok with my flatmate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius BTW, does it sound like George Takei was one of those who were complicit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headius I don't know if I can boycott every rapist, but I might avoid those where it's relevant to their work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pookleblinky was George Takei one of the individuals who were complicit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Way_Things_Work @Yuryu shouldn't that be dadafuq?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>