<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[..or possibly the "majority" made up of very loud minority &amp; a bunch of people unclear as to what they are supporti… https://t.co/7Aao9xUkDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reposting.If you wish to remain politically neutral then define your values and when those values would be breached
 https://t.co/sPETDXqYxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For consideration this &amp; other statements @anzics @CICMANZ . The ICU community is multinational &amp; multiracial 

https://t.co/Eg73eH0KJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh-oh. This is bad. Trump/ Bannon have opened up the access to Hell...

https://t.co/TAcrG1UjOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch might be something for us to consider. I guess unusual times might necessitate unusual measures 

https://t.co/6UbuxjyEMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest danger now is protest fatigue , subsequent normalisation of the highly irregular and emboldened autocracy. Continue to #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is an echo chamber(but useful right now) -scroll to the comments on US media tweets to see what you are up against. Scary. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @icuresearch @ANZICS_CTG Is there a possibility the CTG could make a statement as an internationally respected scientific group?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action point 1-subscribe to high profile media willing to voice dissent @nytimes @washingtonpost @TheAtlantic @guardian. Other ideas welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @iwashyna @ChrisCarrollMD &amp; other US ICU docs keep tweeting as U R - if nothing else reassures us slide to autocracy is not inevitable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for a contrast...
https://t.co/zLKCRKgfZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's useful to keep re focussing the lens here. Basic reality is this man is a total idiot. 

https://t.co/J3mdthBXNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other medical societies should follow suit..

https://t.co/wyj1NESYFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is how it starts - being above the rule of law. Continue the protest or this will end badly.

https://t.co/qOa5XlVqJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch @KathMaitland Good work. Now clocked past the million mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't what this will mean but it is rapidly approaching 1 million signatures; also fun watching the counter zoom up https://t.co/7UbyMKSDQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard not to worry that this level of protest will end up being pointless but then I guess that is exactly what the WH would hope for #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 not for me ... I live in the city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 and the quote in this one...
 "events that seem to happen overnight are the climax of years of complacency."

https://t.co/Ch8yJC7gNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 tweets to highlight that are important to thinking right now and in coming days. Think about this one .....(1/2)

https://t.co/X5SasMw9YX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 @psirides @EnZedGasMan it's getting hard to distinguish real renegades from fake ones now - perhaps it doesn't matter anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 @psirides or possibly invite him then stick him in a room at Heathrow for 48 hrs before turning him back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCarrollMD @thegrandfinalle Agree, ATM protests on SM likely to be fragmented although can amplify people's individual voices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch @Richard56 @richardhorton1 good to think about method of protest but sustained protest needed. You already have the networks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icuresearch I have signed as an overseas citizen - the form allows entry of place of residence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides @barco030 Done, not sure it will influence May's cosying up to an autocrat but voicing protest is important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides is that Rogue KKW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @pmbillenglish &amp; other silent leaders.Look at this cos at some point you will need to speak up,(HT @sama )

 https://t.co/sPETDXqYxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gauloir @psirides Dude my hands are big, the biggest. There have been no hands bigger than mine. 'cept maybe Andre the Giant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gauloir @psirides I think this thread is tangled. Are we still talking Trump here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree -am fine with the idea of medical Twitter.But you know, fighting this BS is currently THE standout use of SM.
https://t.co/6ckcBIeJBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCarrollMD A lot of people feel similarly both in and outside the US. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides @barco030 Check your alt-privilege!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is he signing with crayons do you think @psirides ?

"small hands, smells like cabbage"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get it - how many executive orders are you allowed in 7 days and still get to be called a democracy? https://t.co/SNXO7lU1Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone else out there thinking it might be time to steal the plans to the Death Star? #resist

https://t.co/uXNh89lN3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously if there is going to be one pressing use of SM then supporting protest this way would be it 

https://t.co/eN3ADjv6Xb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news*(alt facts^2)=?

 https://t.co/xs84N2FaUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is well-written and applicable to whatever field you are looking at where the "truth" may be uncertain via… https://t.co/3G7MVq0oJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am no US constitution expert but wasn't the 1st amendment about free speech Mr Trump? This whole shutdown stinks
https://t.co/T9Dn5vKGst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important point about our interactions and the gulf of understanding btwn care providers and patients/families
https://t.co/YykDjROYIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna @HorsleyCarl Great - will do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwashyna We would be interested in being an NZ partner potentially - where would we direct enquiries to? @HorsleyCarl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It started with alt country. Then the alt right. Now we have alt facts. Is there anywhere left to go other than alt-delete?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartened by the broad reaching protests today but will require sustained opposition, apathy may lead to disaster
 https://t.co/VrsZspXwGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep it up. He's only been President for one day and already conventional and social media be like.. https://t.co/iIkFkFtfeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great photos in here

https://t.co/AxoLJMnrj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to cut through the bluster... https://t.co/kfkMCei540]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time was when any link to Russia whether true or not would have ruined a US politician. Strange times indeed.. https://t.co/Wjxtk3E2E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland has some lovely streets which you come across randomly. The result of long ago planning. #auckland https://t.co/P0hPVnSU3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LLocock @HorsleyCarl The name says it all - would anyone drive their car purely looking at the dash? (Self drive cars aside..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 @psirides That is because I am like listening to some phat beats currently innit! booyakashah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides To clarify I presume this is not about being in rude health, being a rudeboy or something being like totally sick ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything I read about Obama lately makes it all the more depressing when set in the context of the Trumpocalypse

https://t.co/MhUR28HF46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ceased to be amazed by the way NZ always has places to enable you to clear your headspace #auckland https://t.co/8BBMw1xwON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 Throw some water on her. If she starts fizzing and smoking then explodes then my theory regarding Trump-bots is confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@precordialthump @conordmcgrath @icuresearch political correctness is a vague term often used to shut down debate

https://t.co/0u5VDTv4kt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't read physicist David Bohm before but I will now... this written 30+years ago but could have been 30 mins ag… https://t.co/W5uUXbGEBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary really.. to paraphrase a reply, seeing both sides is one thing..but lying doesn't constitute a side.

https://t.co/Y539L2cNiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pedonc @adrianplunkett Or the new variation might go wrong in ways never dreamed of as the complexity wasn't appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barco030 try Google images instead. I have spent ages matching my arm to the images. - somewhere in between mild to full coffee depending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More on finding meaningful work rather than blind pursuit of happiness..

 https://t.co/BpBk6Juxpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides Their case is at least partly based on Episodes 1-3.... 'nuff said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaye_rolls @psirides @PeterWJHarrigan That will always be one driver of all human system level decision making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides @PeterWJHarrigan Back in the UK that was what pubs were for ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides @PeterWJHarrigan I have made one firm conclusion. Twitter is rubbish for simultaneous deep conversation 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides i direct you to @HorsleyCarl . He has about a zillion references for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides so why not healthcare? 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides Yup in conjunction with a registry. But this complexity thing still bothers me - it happens in other sciences 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides I haven't a clue how you do but you know it might be that things are not quite on the right track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides 2/2 together or else they are always competing for attention and opposing tensions.Sort of a theory of everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides 1/2 I keep thinking...RCTs, big databases, event monitoring, complex systems theory.. they all need to be knitted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides I still struggle with the basic premise - see VAP monitoring for instance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides Cos it might all boil down to very crude measurements of what is a fundamentally complex system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides Couple of assumptions though right? 1.Event measurement is consistent.
2.Event and any outcome are connected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides @PeterWJHarrigan Well... I have 2017 earmarked as the year of the rational Rebel Alliance fightback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWJHarrigan @psirides and therein is the tension between individual retrospective event analysis &amp; looking wholly at the complex system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides Football results...mostly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides  likewise adverse events in healthcare? Reporting/measurement of events in healthcare is not as simple as media makes out really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psirides Theoretically i suppose reporting quality  should plateau - seems analogous argument to crime stats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a funny and accurate observation on the conundrum of middle age via @brainpicker - prob only meaningful to… https://t.co/3wMNssHUWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right Twitter folks -this ship is sailing in the wrong direction. 2017 might be a good year to start pushing it round towards the right one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even rain doesn't really spoil the summer in NZ https://t.co/OIOxzQdD5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More good advice for approaching 2017

https://t.co/D0aCTehsye via @QuilletteM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great line, not heard often enough - in an uncertain world good decisions start with " I know this might be wrong"

https://t.co/0fVDaSWwss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't Sean Connery's best work to be honest but there is a lot of truth in this article going into 2017

https://t.co/T6L4EO3DpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Xmas from NZ Twittersphere. A good day to be grateful for small things. https://t.co/Ie4R1WEWOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm English and still surprised at the source of this but you know...he is dead right.

https://t.co/SaBpcKPUox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should credit this - from @tferriss show

https://t.co/IoE6meEozP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good cognitive tip heard recently. Before dismissing something make sure the "something" doesn't represent a blindspot in your thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy moly. They are making a sequel... seems like a risky strategy to me. Still just maybe...

https://t.co/5VWWku1cbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland seems to be ready for Christmas, Southern Hemisphere style https://t.co/NF07farka5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gauloir That is definitely my best warrior face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a particularly depressing year on many fronts I am hoping this turns out to be as cool as it looks. 
https://t.co/e3qp7AjMHf via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good summary of motivators at work which may go unrecognised .. worth thinking about this. From @danariely https://t.co/h9RXQknPAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCarrollMD Maybe the rules for engagement need reframing...but when good people disengage bad things often happen history suggests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCarrollMD Human nature has prob not changed over 1000s of years. Nature of forums for group interaction have. How to marry the 2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great photo and highly applicable to the "we have always done it like this so it must be ok" mentality

https://t.co/XiKSfgODW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iceman_ex @ChrisCarrollMD @TimLaheyMD @TomVargheseJr The problem is multifaceted so I guess there won't be any one solution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2..So is it possible to use Twitter to promote political change or is its main use as an alerting system for what is happening?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>