<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[As Toronto home prices soar, commuters will feel the pain via /r/ontario https://t.co/9YiFwN7gsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: Don't try to pay your parking tickets at Metro Hall, as of February 13; the Parking Ticket counter is tempora… https://t.co/VGlBN4Gwnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Daily - Feb 5th 2017 via /r/toronto

Welcome to the Toronto Daily Thread.

This thread serves two purposes:

1) To collect and make…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite view of our city, took this flying with a friend. via /r/toronto https://t.co/JWzioYaPV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If patios get banned we can copy the solution in Brasil. via /r/toronto https://t.co/Arol75iMwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beer Store "sales deals": 5 cents off regular price via /r/ontario

Just browsing the "what's on sale" page on their website to see wha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlord wants to increase rent 10.8% at the end of lease - First time renter via /r/ontario

I currently live in a house we rented back in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge anti-Trump protest on Dundas via /r/toronto https://t.co/rhoxlUsgS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNE, 1956 - Paul Bunyan and Babe the Blue Ox - found while scanning my grandfather's old slide collection via /r/t… https://t.co/EjTPtOxrUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest outside US Consulate. Taken from CN Tower. via /r/toronto https://t.co/bNxqqQY67N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best is the enemy of good. - Voltaire #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the 407 was privatize was it a popular decision ? New immigrant here via /r/ontario

It is so expensive and believe it is most expensi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely view of the city from the CN Tower last night... via /r/toronto https://t.co/n6eiD3CXhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Toronto Brunch Map via /r/toronto https://t.co/PdPup0NZgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally my favorite view of the city via /r/toronto https://t.co/sSIoGKJcHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of fear is to raise your awareness, not to stop your progress. - Steve Maraboli #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Very serious’ allegations over Scarborough subway debate referred to auditor general via /r/toronto https://t.co/68oRQ5U2G2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4-FEB-2017 - Things to do Today via /r/toronto

Toronto Marlies vs Syracuse Crunch at Ricoh Coliseum. 3 pm. Tickets still available.

Red H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada Parks sites near Toronto (and which ones you can reach without a car) via /r/toronto https://t.co/mTpztERuhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last-second minivan crosses 2 lanes to exit the 401, what could possibly go wrong? via /r/toronto https://t.co/Des4taT1qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sale of shark fin in Toronto via /r/toronto

Reading about Rob Stewarts recent death reminded me of something... and correct me if im wrong…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The petty battle against Bike Share in historic Cabbagetown via /r/toronto https://t.co/rm6GtSWvRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Daily - Feb 4th 2017 via /r/toronto

Welcome to the Toronto Daily Thread.

This thread serves two purposes:

1) To collect and make…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocket launcher, woolly mammoth tusk among seized items at Ontario border crossings via /r/ontario https://t.co/kliC87NdbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario to help young patients affected by Trump travel ban via /r/ontario https://t.co/ck3tGJSasy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob Stewart's body has been found. via /r/toronto https://t.co/kjWGA1nXwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents of Ontario: OSAP for child of joint custody? via /r/ontario

Like every other highschool student in Ontario I've spent a fair amoun…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I have any civil recourse for my landlord failing to provide a CO alarm? via /r/ontario

I had thought my smoke alarm was dual purpose a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside local church via /r/toronto https://t.co/TXJXQjKfd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found in Ontario: 5 Neat Facts about HMCS Haida, the "Fightingest" Ship in the Royal Canadian Navy - 1. They had a… https://t.co/5oJn0Wai5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this guy was threatening to kill people on a crowded 111 bus tonight for being too close to him via /r/toronto https://t.co/AmLQJLHlSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Toronto! Streetcar 4431 arrives from Thunder Bay via /r/toronto https://t.co/DPh7CCfUKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who allegedly made hoax CN Tower terror threat denied bail via /r/toronto https://t.co/thpq5dOsve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario is getting 15 new seats in the provincial legislature for the 2018 election next June. Here is a map of th… https://t.co/BXQ3dt9zIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New /r/Ontario Helpful Links via /r/ontario

I know a lot of users have taken issue with the amount of questions that end up on the sub abo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official /r/Ontario 2016 Survey Results via /r/ontario

Let me first take this time to thank you, the community, on behalf of all the moder…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal cabinet minister apologizes for comment about GO train riders via /r/ontario https://t.co/xa8zxvtCuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any room for rent in ontario? via /r/ontario

Hello everyone, I just moved here from San Diego to work at Kaiser as a Data Analyst/Develope…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews to form protective "rings of peace" around GTA mosques via /r/toronto https://t.co/INpjFctJO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't envy what people have, emulate what they did to have it. - Tim Fargo #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use of racial slur makes York school trustee unfit for office, minister says via /r/toronto https://t.co/a1h29REnfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no line wednesdays at blue mountain via /r/ontario https://t.co/kej6OXyByC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tory attempts to distance himself from former campaign strategist Nick Kouvalis via /r/toronto https://t.co/ZdkV4xQtmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home prices up 22% in January compared to last year: Toronto Real Estate Board via /r/toronto https://t.co/xPB0GC9p8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful things happen when you distance yourself from negativity. - Unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Sun Columnists on the Wrong Side of History Through the Ages via /r/toronto https://t.co/nR4Y2ntBSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TTC union leaders fired, including Kinnear: sources via /r/toronto https://t.co/xmwNR8nwcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto housing sales up 12 per cent year-over-year in January: TREB report via /r/ontario https://t.co/zRiDxVQRWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graves discovered beneath downtown elementary school mean no expansion via /r/toronto https://t.co/byhqsQG0Zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you even buy a house for $100K now? via /r/ontario

Can you even buy houses in ON for $100K now, that are not 'fixer uppers' or downrig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rental tenant who told me he's unable to pay his rent this month. via /r/ontario

Hi everyone thanks for your help in advance.

I …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3-FEB-2017 - Things to do Today via /r/toronto

Toronto Rock vs Buffalo Bandits at the ACC. 7:30 pm. Tickets still available.

National Bri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto to get its first dog cafe via /r/toronto https://t.co/x74jwhIIMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynne listened to the 'vocal, selfish, short-sighted' in blocking Toronto road tolls via /r/toronto https://t.co/dDH2Sdh6v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Toronto's architectural 'gems' could get a new lease on life via /r/toronto https://t.co/2hY2rIShlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nexus cards revoked on both sides of border following U.S. executive order via /r/toronto https://t.co/88IC9GsfuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto's economy doesn't get the respect it deserves via /r/toronto https://t.co/TrMXYjZTDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wynne listened to the 'vocal, selfish, short-sighted' in blocking Toronto road tolls via /r/ontario https://t.co/dDH2Sdh6v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT john123521 awesome video looking forward to more great videos by you  :)  https://t.co/8fcqd00RZ1  Keep em coming!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gord Downie just sang with Blue Rodeo at Massey Hall via /r/toronto https://t.co/jb12Se9dZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Daily - Feb 3rd 2017 via /r/toronto

Welcome to the Toronto Daily Thread.

This thread serves two purposes:

1) To collect and make…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Province Announces More Rapid Transit for Hamilton via /r/ontario https://t.co/Mio8etvTKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Kouvalis, controversial campaign manager for Kellie Leitch, resigns via /r/toronto https://t.co/wEQBpRM6M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm Deeply Sorry My Party Broke Its Promise On Electoral Reform" - Toronto MP Nathaniel Erskine-Smith via /r/toro… https://t.co/1LlCs51vvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to send a message about electoral reform? Here are some links. Please add to them! via /r/ontario

Official p… https://t.co/puP7Qz1T1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SETTING THE RECORD STRAIGHT ON THE PRICE OF ELECTRICITY via /r/ontario https://t.co/GmtVnHVZbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shining a light on the true costs of renewable energy in Ontario via /r/ontario https://t.co/zVVV1LlXU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it worth it to take driving classes? via /r/ontario

So I'm currently 24, have had my G1 for 4 years, have no infractions/charges and I'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Make Fighting Climate Change Good for Your Pocketbook via /r/ontario https://t.co/zWlJ0BjQK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Toronto protest is planned after Trudeau government breaks promise of electoral reform via /r/toronto https://t.co/h1vYeAPnT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a former editor allegedly used Vice Canada to recruit drug mules for a global smuggling ring via /r/toronto https://t.co/cyOZpLa30G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Reference Library stabbing was "unprovoked," police say via /r/toronto https://t.co/v73tjIE2aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The city has ordered the College Street Bar to be closed until May 12 after owner &amp; employee were charged in a sex… https://t.co/tkcPnqRhMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drake takes a big piece of Toronto with him on tour via /r/toronto https://t.co/9MMWcYNfZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil servants pay boost defended by Treasury Board president via /r/ontario https://t.co/BijkfzNf2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario Charging Up Electric Vehicle Incentives via /r/ontario https://t.co/jrOB7JV31V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto's monthly transit pass the 5th most expensive in the world, study finds - Toronto via /r/toronto https://t.co/YbIt8oEUK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May your faith be unshakeable and your will, unbreakable. - Tristan Bishop #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are college students making a documentary about Toronto Community Housing via /r/toronto

We're looking for people using Toronto Communi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groundhog Day: Wiarton Willie predicts early spring via /r/toronto https://t.co/wOv6nEuS6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping Toronto "affordable" will cost us all: Keenan via /r/toronto https://t.co/hLWgCvFNQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition to Government of Canada regarding Electoral Reform via /r/ontario https://t.co/OwueecBh7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 3 followers in the past week. This is the app: https://t.co/pJyPrqNUd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens. - Jimi Hendrix #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employee fired from Guelph Walmart over discrimination complaint (xpost from /r/Guelph) via /r/ontario https://t.co/vrPYyuER7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, new costs via /r/ontario https://t.co/SPfKitLRoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto: Sanctuary City via /r/toronto

I am having mixed opinion about this. I am well aware of the charitable nature and feeling warm &amp; f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GO Transit has paid riders nearly $4 million for delays over three years via /r/toronto https://t.co/vMF8UtTiLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extreme cold weather alert issued for Toronto via /r/toronto https://t.co/lRgdkKvkve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Province Holds Basic Income Consultation In London via /r/ontario https://t.co/kCqZt84LYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce Grey Poverty Task Force Respond to the Government’s Proposed Basic Income Pilot via /r/ontario https://t.co/o8PpMS6NMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom outraged after six-year-old daughter handcuffed by police in school via /r/toronto https://t.co/WQRHozOiP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-FEB-2017 - Things to do Today via /r/toronto

Winterlicious at various restaurants throughout the city. Continues until February 9. See w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People of Toronto: Luke Anderson | StopGap Foundation via /r/toronto https://t.co/GUY8klNFQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1895 vintage photo: Library staff at the Mechanics Institute, Church St. &amp; Adelaide St. E. via /r/toronto https://t.co/wQglGCAMSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help for Petition to reverse PM decision for killing Electoral Reform via /r/ontario

Note: Pardon me for posting this again from the Canad…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Daily - Feb 2nd 2017 via /r/toronto

Welcome to the Toronto Daily Thread.

This thread serves two purposes:

1) To collect and make…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made a Documentary on Rural Ontario! See some things you may never see! via /r/ontario https://t.co/rfSpfnVtwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dangerous Dan's is closing via /r/toronto https://t.co/u8OzeyMfGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man taken to hospital after stabbing at Toronto Reference Library via /r/toronto https://t.co/pZHuCWoPsZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>