<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on #ChicagoPD good to see the awesome Aussie director Cherie Nowlan directing an ep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MKR2017 let's see what comments they make about 'babies being ugh' tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay to The Matrix. I'll just forget how the damn trilogy ended. ðŸ˜ˆ https://t.co/1qvh9mnj2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But apart from that nitpick it's the start of a strong back half of #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only nitpick I have is in the previous ep which is based the previous day, George had his wedding ring on &amp; now it's gone. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww happy George and go Monty! Time to rip up that questionnaire and try to find some happiness until Jan drops her bombshell. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I won't be watching 50 Shades tomorrow night. I'd take watching paint dry over that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hand will feel better after some TLC Fiona... #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was not good parenting. Heh. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Constable Tom. He was feeding his ðŸ¦† in the midst of serenity. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely love the score playing over the fight scene. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight. Fight. Fight. ðŸ’ªðŸ‘ŠðŸ’ª oh and Fiona throws a mean punch. If they need a new rugby player see Monty! #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Monty! ðŸ’ª #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woody I haven't taught them that yet! ðŸ˜‚ #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Fiona smack that smug look off Robbie's face? #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. I should have played Oz Lotto would have had 5 numbers. ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great George/Katie scene coming up. George can't find his place in terms of relationships and attempting to be happy again. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woody see what happens when you put your foot in your mouth. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was you Robbie I would hide. Though you deserve what is coming to you in this episode... #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I prefer George and Fiona as a couple, absolutely love Katie. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole point of a soulmate is that there is only one of them. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woody. Foot meet mouth. Better quit while you're ahead.... #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hey Arlo, yeah that's how you want to find out about your father's new potential relationship. Heh. #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 very easy to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I just say I absolutely love Monty and Fiona in this episode? For different reasons but ðŸ’ª #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many double meanings in this episode... #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay #mkr comes to an end while #800words starts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live tweeting of #800words may occur from me. That's if I don't get absorbed in it like the first time I watched it weeks ago. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Bankstown! #mkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently I live in South West Sydney since on the radius my suburb would be in line with Punchbowl.... #mkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mkr followed by #800words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for #800words fans... 800.words @channel7 https://t.co/ptCS4JdMrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those wondering about Henry and his truffle farm *being serious here for a sec* enjoy! https://t.co/U8VljK44oE #mkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey it's Burnie. I know that place, bought an investment property last year about 40 mins from there. #mkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few hours ago Aussie fans were praising Hazlewood for his almost speccie catch, now he's being slamming for losing the match. #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Lithgow has now won in the comedy and drama TV cats at the #SAGAwards ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 thanks! Just a day trip then will go for a week away destination unknown yet on Wed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a cracking match even if my fav Federer won't win it. Time to switch off since I am on the road tomorrow. Buonanotte!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the #Chiko ad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Nature on #AustraliaDayConcert still rocking it all these years! ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AusOpen #AUSvPAK and #BigBlue all on at the same time. Cannot split screen all these.  ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch to his knee. Good catch, but stupid shot by Smith there. #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just put Warner in an ice bath and let him stay there and watch the team defend the total. He's deserved it. #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warner's basically playing on one leg and possibly one arm, but sure no problem to be at 174n.o. #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That montage though at the end of #CodeBlack "Unfinished Business" is a must watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By last week I meant #CodeBlack's last ep from 2 weeks ago. Then again, due to Sweeps starting, half the shows I watch aren't on this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on #CodeBlack and loved last week's episode from Guthrie's POV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennySok damn I loved Lewis and Inspector Morse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennisupdike same, along with theirs and there's. Hence my annoyance when autocorrect kicked in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennisupdike see the tweet I made after that about my grammatical error before replying next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please disregard the damn grammatical error in my previous tweets. Autocorrect changed it from its to it's...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty cool stat that three actresses for The Help got nominated for their films.. #OscarNoms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugarshaz19 yep well usually she gets past the nomination stage and falls at the last hurdle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her performance along with Stone were by far the ones that stood out for me even though I was suffering from heat exhaustion at the time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something quite odd when a film like Arrival gets nominated (deservedly so) for Best Picture but it's lead is snubbed... #OscarNoms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master class tonight. ðŸ‘ https://t.co/B2MzVxpv12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrypotter1994 yep she's good in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Herald let the cat out of the bag unofficially the other day regarding that previous tweet, but good to see it confirmed so soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third season of 800 Words was just announced! #800Words @Channel7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And speaking of #theblacklist it was great seeing @AnastasiaGLive in the episode!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing Jill Hennessy playing the baddie on #theblacklist was a delight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 well The Investigator will probably be paired up with Murder Uncovered as well. TBD in a couple of weeks I guess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 yep to your prediction for Wed. It can be hard to predict because of 7Flix with their dedicated dramas etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bones is after 800 Words on a Tuesday on Channel 7. Only questionable day later on will be a Wed at this stage and post-Hoges on a Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know Stan the Man will probably get through but I would love Fed, Kei or Tsonga or make the final over him. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome work Dasha! All my favs won today. ðŸ‘ You watch them all lose tomorrow now. ðŸ˜¬ #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What else do you expect on the Sat night of Week 1 of the #AusOpen it's going to be a loooonnnnggg night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @7Tennis please have Henri commentating Nadal's match if Monfils wins his match? That would be awesome #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant match. Now two of my favs are going against each other. https://t.co/NcqOiMsUFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sense a trip to Brisbane is definitely on the cards now! https://t.co/VUL3dXp2Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts are with those in Melbourne around Bourke Street now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 yep. As they say there's always more than one road to take in life even if it takes a bit longer. Definitely holds true for me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 @Park_Neighbours hell I had it when it was TER - tertiary entrance rate which is really old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 couldn't agree more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that is what you call a massive upset. Opens up that side of the draw #AusOpen https://t.co/Up8q6ibzwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops did I say Sweden, meant Dominican Republic! But still same case, Tomic is currently winning this match. While I'm off to catch up on TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Tomic broke back in his match right when I said the Swede was serving well. Whoops. ðŸ˜Ž #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's in front again. ðŸ˜ Meanwhile Tomic is also losing. Gotta say the Swede is serving great at the moment #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tweet pretty much sums up this match. #AusOpen ðŸ‘ https://t.co/5Lv8LYeL2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbudd70 @AmandaR327 I think the psychologist may be getting a phone call again tonight. Either by Nick or the ATP...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is wrong how much I am laughing at the #AusOpen right now but yay Ash!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Roger for finishing before midnight! #offtobedigo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eek! This match is going to be over before the Sydney Derby starts in the football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrypotter1994 @Ryno_091 well it was my No 1 film of 2016 with Arrival second but I said that back in Sept lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LaLaLand clean sweep has me scrambling to find my initial comments after I saw it at TIFF (heat exhaustion and all) ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMcKenzie nice little shout-out in THR review to your performance in there! https://t.co/eyIwCNqITv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryno_091 definitely been saying that for many years now :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrypotter1994 yep definitely a shame for Peers, but for long term wise definitely another option, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they can stay fit, we've got our new Davis@Cup doubles pairing. https://t.co/j0JZJiQLEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French are trying to do the double tonight with the #HopmanCup and win the Women's Single at #BrisbaneTennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the third umpire is on, well. I have no idea what he is on but between Smith and this decision, I'll take some thanks! #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuskelson speedy recovery! My dad suffers from AF so definitely know what it can be like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a fan of Josh Hazlewood since he started out at St George, so yay to his 100th wicket! #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um think Fairfax Media got this wrong (apparently Princess Charlotte has jumped in age) https://t.co/ywVXaTGUam https://t.co/jE315Z3ZmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I take the mickey out of the cricket commentators, I do hope Mark Nicholas makes a speedy recovery #AUSvPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day Wild Oats will remember how to start and not leave it to the end only to kick butt ðŸ‘ #sydneytohobart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go WildOatsXI! At least we know the audio is working! #sydneytohobart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Being_Jake @Drama_Queen_94 @bianca_proudman @harrypotter1994 @Ryno_091 thanks and the same to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Place to Call Home Marathon on Showcase means I can delete the eps off my iQ box and put them in order again today! #aptch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrypotter1994 she looked good. Granted that it did get better after the comment I originally made :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>