<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[thank you, I appreciate it ✨ https://t.co/zVMbkAdfFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[patriots wouldn't have won if they played the giants smhhhhhhhhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that catch really looked like a madden glitch lmfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriots decided to finally show up smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[avoiding conflict doesn't make it disappear, just makes it linger for longer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can y'all at least PRETEND you're used to attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people who post screenshots of someone trynna get at them are fucking losers lmfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stop chasing people who ignore you lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[half the girls commenting "dump him" under tweets been single since 2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my biggest pet peeve is people who don't know how to communicate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pay attention to those who only speak to you when it's convenient for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[y'all still dating women who thirst over celebrities? https://t.co/cm4Tz05lM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[some people are so bitter, remove the hate from your heart and find peace 💜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeardedDre maaan I miss him and Desean playing together 😔... dream team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you'll never find me in a place where my presence isn't appreciated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["white on white crime" https://t.co/JG6aMtybrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when they send you a paragraph telling you how much they like you and you tell them to "chill" https://t.co/ybwOBbwCyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommyrosiers WHY ARE YOU YELLING 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really good at putting 2 and 2 together and then pretending like I don't know shit lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlvckExcellence hmmm maybe not ALL of you are psychopaths 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smh y'all ain't shit 😂 https://t.co/LXektgWWqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you think your life is hard, try dating a Pisces lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reward love with loyalty and doubt with distance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[say "lol" after saying something harsh to make it less harsh like "we should break up lol"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going to the same places every weekend to see the same people isn't networking lmfao y'all dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when people who have your number message you on snapchat &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[y'all really gotta learn to keep your business to yourselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[defend him in public, correct him in private]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imagine having to constantly talk to numerous people you don't even care about because you can't stand yourself like pls practice self-love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[make sure whoever "got you" really got you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macktology101 Cory. https://t.co/fAubTqCmg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what else are Tuesdays for? https://t.co/tFbtlaIhKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I used to talk to him" ok and people used to only watch black&amp;white TV until they upgraded to colour, what's your point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate a "I used to talk to him" ass bitch like lol ok and he used to not know me, what's your point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you wake up and he says "good morning beautiful" but really you look like this https://t.co/EvdZvpYZTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["hey, please check out my SoundCloud when you get a chan-" https://t.co/zTYHNPVa4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you can't match my goofy we can't hang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when he remembers little details about you that you didn't even know he was paying attention to https://t.co/CIxKPwkhE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when y'all been hanging out for 72 hours straight and then he says he has to go do something quick https://t.co/XmUCcAtXLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[since Donald Trump is building walls some of you hoes should hit him up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaninyourgirl lmfao food is life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when he's finished, does he step back and adore you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm hungry"
"But didn't you just eat 5 minutes ago?" https://t.co/d8qB9PZQEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nah they dating them lmfaoooo https://t.co/pJr4VdvfMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[goofy + freaky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the loudest person in the room is usually also the least intelligent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Spokesperson Katrina Pierson is a fucking idiot https://t.co/prfRgZxMB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ex bfs be like: "u left one of ur hairs in my car, idk if u want me to drop it off or what's good?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you don't need to raise your voice. you need to raise valid points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if he doesn't dm you dumbass memes is he really your man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[life comes at you fast https://t.co/mmRWqJvux5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he told me he talks to God about me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[subway cookies &amp; chill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sad that most people don't know this https://t.co/YpO5Q4dDOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when the henny kicks in and bae looking scrumptious https://t.co/bcxxRrEEKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lmfao literally tho https://t.co/74imzMWxXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if the whole world was blind, how many people would you impress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when y'all were arguing and then he gets a fresh line-up 🙄 https://t.co/2FzIR5bigp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[miserable people always gravitate towards miserable people lmfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when he's rude af to every girl except his momma and you &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the irony lmfao https://t.co/xfIT26LsJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll beat her ass lmao https://t.co/KeTrfLyIzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[get you a man who remembers that it's been 2 weeks since you last got your nails done 😂🙄😩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brentb25 lmao I wasn't even trynna snitch smh 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you "bad", but you broke and don't own shit https://t.co/TREJfp9z9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[never in the history of calming down has someone calmed down by being told to calm down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[speak on it!!! https://t.co/cTLpfEYabo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Duck_ @TC_Mitch lmfao I'll try again tomorrow 🙄😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[girls getting traded around like they Carmelo 😴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOOOO sounds about white https://t.co/S2fMdYcD8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbrown_2wavey lmmmmao honestly couldn't help myself 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbrown_2wavey smh trynna make me wait 3-5 business days for some damn chicken loool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spicy chicken tenders with blackened ranch pls 😋 https://t.co/h7RkxTnBfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[witchya fine ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me watching my own snapchat story https://t.co/d64Z9788Li]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you accidentally send the screenshot of a convo to the person you were having the convo with https://t.co/eOfLPXuntd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if your man buys you agent provocateur you gotta send him fire nudes every day for at least a week... issa rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and then respond with "wowwwwwwwwwww" when you get caught 😂 https://t.co/t6wY5hzXw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't be the type of person who's comfortable being around people with money but isn't making any of their own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd do anything to make you laugh and you can have anything just ask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone who is 100% good with themselves is literally such a blessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[baby boy say he fuck with me tough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[long distance relationships are lit bc it's like you have 2 homes lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lack of communication will always lead to misinterpretation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChefDomonique @FADEQUIS if you grown enough to have sex you grown enough to sit down &amp; come up with a solution that works for both parties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FADEQUIS ohhhh I already know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the decision to have a baby should be agreed on by both parties - if it's solely your choice, then support ya own damn decisions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's fucked that men get trapped into paying child support for babies they already said they didn't want/aren't ready for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a girl will use her body to attract a man and then sit there wondering why he only wants her body https://t.co/bov1SEkYXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listen, if someone stops fw you over something that can be easily fixed they was never fw you heavy enough to begin with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no problem admitting when I'm wrong. If I owe an apology then I owe an apology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not in the business of forcing shit. Let it be or let it go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fuck a bitch who's down to earth, I'll give you the goddamn sky"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you wanna talk about something but you've already talked about it too much &amp; you don't wanna be annoying so yo… https://t.co/ClB582c7D1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy me chick-fil-a and I'll be your chick-fo-life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[insecure women stir shit up because they have to "win". a secure woman will do nothing because she knows she's the winner either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stop bringing the trust issues from your last relationships into your new ones - don't ever make someone pay for someone else's mistakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["you ever think bout someone you used to trip over and you're like hahahahahahahahahaha"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls don't come to me &amp; talk shit about people I used to have relationships with, I literally don't care lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you're so worried about me that i'm worried for you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>