<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@leinoa I lived there in the mid-80s, lovely country. As is Finland, which I visit as often as I can afford it. Hauskaa lomaa!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Borowitz on Facebook: "Nixon fired his Attorney General in 1973. Nixon was ousted in 1974. So things are on track."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oko99999 Fantastic, thanks for posting. Yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Orleans civil rights pioneer Ernest Wright honored by plaque in A.L. Davis Park https://t.co/yp9kcnniC9 via @theadvocatebr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['People who were praying lost their lives': Multiple killed in Quebec City mosque shooting  https://t.co/6gGDsWxZ7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black-Owned Bookstores: Anchors of the Black Power Movement https://t.co/5vlRQG3R95 via @aaihs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realities faced by Black Canadians are a national shame - https://t.co/5CyvhvCkty via @FahamuAfrica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How African-American Artists Fought to Diversify Museums https://t.co/km9pI0bxrd via @artsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coursey of The Poke on Facebook: https://t.co/q6Z2RLapHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were an elephant … https://t.co/4ZtZZnZDwF  But what's it like being the only one in the room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not news to many of you, but this piece from 2014 is good to know. https://t.co/xRotGRAd49 via @writernthesky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hakimadi1 @kzshabazz @SmithsonianMag They were also split on race: white women marched 1st, then men, black women at the back of the parade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick Cockburn in the #LRB: https://t.co/CUGphjZ0RH via @LRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential Trump Science Adviser: 9 in 10 Colleges Will Fail https://t.co/2W2HxP0PxC via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Umut_Ozsu Would take none at all, which is (luckily) also the number of right connections I have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Sound advice. A lot of vigilance is needed. The just sleep better after counting their retweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Umut_Ozsu After all, the Just sleep much better after having counting their retweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Umut_Ozsu Maybe I should turn it into a New Yorker piece: "How Post-Arguments Are the New Normal".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice piece. My next imaginary article: "'I would argue that...' So Go ahead and Argue It, Motherfucker". https://t.co/5uKbtHtF21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaiians call Mark Zuckerberg 'the face of neocolonialism' over land lawsuits https://t.co/pdK3TohI0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fears Burning The Flag Could Leave Racists Capeless | SBS Comedy https://t.co/05B6ZN1MQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“An Unpopular Opinion on the Women’s March on Washington” by @whatchidid https://t.co/ia8nYUM4Fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent, but why not skip a step and make them taste like pretzels or cheetos? https://t.co/QNuIRR6jhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If there ever was a moment to reexamine the role that traditions play in the inaugural process, this is it.” https://t.co/GPKs7sBcmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nation pats itself on the back for only being pretty racist https://t.co/0Z8SBwnopr via @TheBeaverton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samkbennett @tapeopmag At the same time, my easy invocation of 'the artistic imagination' sidesteps, your point, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Banksy, New Orleans https://t.co/6PQMFRYwoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samkbennett @tapeopmag Agreed! But might acoustic and musical imagination also count as musicality? See https://t.co/WBvIb9tZAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valuable report on changes to the huge Yukon River system - and another reason to insist on the independent integri… https://t.co/CxXXt0beH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tapeopmag @samkbennett Cool, THX. Sez a lot that Flood has to explain that "you've got to have some musicality in order to be a producer".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Commutes Bulk of Chelsea Manning’s Sentence https://t.co/bTCMPORYUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Severe Is Venezuela’s Crisis? via @thenation https://t.co/VudB0JONV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Portland Just Filed a Major Federal Lawsuit against Monsanto: they knew danger of PCBs in 1969. https://t.co/DT7vNCqwxI via @antimedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elephant in the Room: Europeans Debate Nuclear Self-Defense after Trump Win https://t.co/xuCypHNyko via @SPIEGELONLINE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryhindess @LAReviewofBooks Yet lightly skips over CH's issues of self-censorship of satire aimed at Jewish religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few words to enliven tweets - the possibilities for alliteration are nearly endless. (credit to: Writing about Wr… https://t.co/DPBsjP0qRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another timely reminder: Historic Speech by Bolivian leader EVO MORALES on December 21, 2012 https://t.co/ftk0ZUbj3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newscientist It's also important to consider where it goes, e.g. this report: https://t.co/XS3RdfxXh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anatomy of a Myth: the World's Biggest E-Waste Dump Isn't. https://t.co/yx1rllbQx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Betting he'd give up the chocolate if he knew about New Orleans Crystal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alternatives to transport via the Suez Canal mean an estimated 80% reduction in its traffic by 2020". https://t.co/L728hYTza3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oniropolis You might like the owrk on this page: https://t.co/SLBQNR7VoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A treasury of great photographs! https://t.co/WuMiEDocLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klausdodds &amp; why start w neo-colonial claim that Antarctica is "the only continent with no indigenous population"? What is the connection?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lest anyone forget: (Trump’s) America Was Never a Democracy https://t.co/qt16Ar3yil via @aaihs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; at some point up the ladder of success, this sane principle will probably slow her down... https://t.co/dPJuBvJclc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KerrRusskerr older bit of satire, but another reminder of darker times ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrified Shell flees Arctic as quickly as possible https://t.co/NIdvBpJot8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's video of black graduate student getting jumped by gang of police for 'stealing' car he owns https://t.co/nqllGdAt6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“for every $1 of aid that developing countries receive, they lose $24 in net outflows” https://t.co/W1xbXZqCHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrugstorCowboy @PatriotsOfMars Not all of us do, eh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Pretending the Rich Care About You https://t.co/r3PJtlNsaT via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astonishing, rare images of the Vietnam War from the winning side (posted by Steven Rae, Facebook) https://t.co/JobZotMEfD via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(credit: Laurence Bernard, Facebook) https://t.co/r8FGdgvoEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cracks me up. Kripke resigns as report alleges he faked results of thought experiments https://t.co/CzKF01BT1P via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art Divas: I Woke Up by Jameson Fitzpatrick https://t.co/Q3DC2NmNq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, every piece of everything still exists, if u want to express it that way. Not sure such hype helps overmuch. https://t.co/YRbb1YarPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would look much more convincing if he wore those fuzzy little reindeer antlers. https://t.co/A7dFY8NoJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnny_Bravo65 @LiveEUDebate @POLITICOEurope I don't disagree; it's the 2nd highest ranking German politician saying it that's news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests in Mexico Push Country to Brink of Revolution and Nobody’s Talking About It https://t.co/EzxSbkMVxB via @antimedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German vice chancellor said a break up of the European Union is ‘no longer unthinkable.’ https://t.co/cP4TeQfDRy via @POLITICOEurope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin A piece you might like https://t.co/tmLACG8udg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Colonization Society's plans for abolishing slavery | OUPblog https://t.co/FhjWUGoKvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wes Anderson Has Announced The Title And Cast Of His New Stop-Motion Animated Movie (via @GizmodoAU) https://t.co/SCEeNoLW1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel Chiefs Say Trump’s Twitter Account Was Hacked by Four-Year-Old  https://t.co/CzsEBbWghV via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Utopian Design Experiments, from Le Corbusier’s Radiant City to a Ghost Town in China https://t.co/YZlyDbguiH via @artsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American History: The Lynching of Mexicans: https://t.co/wv4PMdrta7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nice photoessay on New Orleans' Second Lines https://t.co/LgFtNbnVaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA's Flickr account is a cartographic dream (or nightmare) resource https://t.co/RlTkT1ReBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Bodies: A Review of Slavery at Sea https://t.co/GsN1JCQ6mr via @thejuntoblog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elephants are now an astronomical unit of measurement: "Jumbo asteroid has close shave with Earth" https://t.co/C9RkAMdFtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White World Order, Black Power Politics: The Birth of American International Relations by Robert Vitalis https://t.co/Ln7F6g20wK via @LRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Walter Benn Michaels, The Beauty of a Social Problem (now out in paperback) https://t.co/OyscjA5Pnc via @lareviewofbooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usually ignore stuff on Trump (think we've got the idea by now), but hell, this is Errol Morris https://t.co/pPG0H4TGKv via @lithub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Strange Story of the Man Behind 'Strange Fruit' - quite a tale via @nprmusic https://t.co/E4qOkgKAJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinmarshall @film_archive No space in previous post to also say thanks - I enjoyed the article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ships built post-1990 are now less efficient; vessels built in 2013 on average 10% less fuel-efficient than their… https://t.co/P3mSCueWdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMAAHC @NHenryFundi Let's use 'terror' with caution. 'Terror' to whom, over what? Revolt killed 2 white men, 95 self-freed slaves executed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many questionable terms of analysis here to be helpful: 'neoliberal', 'populism', 'failed state' to name a few. https://t.co/efS2j7Tt0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Traditional' a tricky word: pansori less 'Korean opera' than it is farmer's dances codified by students in the 197… https://t.co/9lz6VKpbZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ban on political group in Israel leaves Gaza orphans destitute https://t.co/PuAxwIfuoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be an Artist, According to Paul Klee  https://t.co/l6VC2iexww via @artsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite all the self-serving hype about 'role models', this is the more credible moral of Star Wars. https://t.co/rN9tsgDvE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baroque Garage in Skopje. What do you put in this - gilded mining carts? https://t.co/Dt1aCagpws #Architecture #Design #Art via @Arch2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On creativity https://t.co/LYVWDYrGvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugemassiff 2b fair, she wasn't 92 back then :) How many NHL goals wud Rocket Richard score today? Only 30: after all, he'd be 96 yrs old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An insult to 'village idiots', who were at least thought to potentially possess insight into realms beyond the depr… https://t.co/pvHJl0Exxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coastal flooding may force thousands of homes in Louisiana to be elevated or bought out https://t.co/QhGgNiBAH7 via @thelensnola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Black Female Mathematicians Who Sent Astronauts to Space | Mental Floss https://t.co/xyofXVRjXv via @mental_floss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atlasobscura They forgot to mention the plague of wild camels that knock down portions of the fence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhumhorfraser @nevnivague @PartickFeargal Lots of Australians also fall for the "we're civilised" flattery. What part of that is confusing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arch2O gravity, with style https://t.co/vBLM3c3f8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert @MichaelEMann Well, they were consistent: an unethical procedure to dump ethics committee counts as ethical in their world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbleiker @CEENewP @StAndrewsIR Excellent and touching essay, thank you. Exciting to hear of a Magritte biography too. Do keep us posted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to turn Neitzsche into a safe cosmopolitan who would find crude concepts like populism useful. https://t.co/6j3egl5gBk via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One image is worth a 1000 disasters: THE CURE FOR CATASTROPHE by Robert Muir-Wood https://t.co/TC0Y4Wnmck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebration, Florida: Disney’s city of the future https://t.co/05N23VaLZA via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West-Fail-Ya: Foreign Affairs sells a Cold War IR myth for 'the Middle East'. In the immortal words of Tony Stark,… https://t.co/3g5M1mPzQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oniropolis If you haven't aleady seen it, I'd recommend the film too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's as bad as the Bing translator Twitter uses, it should make for some fun conversations. https://t.co/3LYTaRz31B]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>