<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze everything is calculated with Bannon and Conway ... media is being played https://t.co/C7WazgUDmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schwarzenegger @realDonaldTrump Trump forgets his current presidential rating is the lowest in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schwarzenegger IN A HEARTBEAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@axios @AP Bannon might be playing the media for fools with all these "leaks". They want to tire the media and the people. It's working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann he realizes it and wants war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta lol... one way or another, Trump wants a war for his presidential legacy #BOOM https://t.co/ArOn8fJECh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews #FAKENEWS #FASCIST NEWS #Trumpchannel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan #reminder #integrity #americanvalues #dotherightthing https://t.co/ctvTl3ILO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @newtgingrich bankrolling? Let's see, I get in my car, gas up, drive to airport, then protest. I guess… https://t.co/3epeQPPOnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BruceBartlett @tribelaw more like 1/4 to 1/3 of the whole population support the Oompa Loompa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @realDonaldTrump @JessikaJayne @THR @splcenter @NewYorker Bannon is definitely smarter than Trump. He is scary crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wikileaks @YouTube stop misleading ... the list from Obama stated they were "dangerous to visit".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GroverNorquist We need to move people into new modern jobs. It's not the 30's, or even the 80's. Manufacturing is dead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryHogan Hi Larry, Chevy Chase resident here. Where are you on Trump? I want to hear a loud opposition, buddy. Election time is coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Bannon is the architect and true ring leader @realDonaldTrump is the simple puppet #SteveBannon https://t.co/HAd9Js45fI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldmanebro Chic-Fil-A ... say it ain't so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiseGuy317 i feel you man &amp; I appreciate that we can be civil about this. Personally, I hope I am wrong. Nobody gets "points" if I am right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiseGuy317 the exploitation of people's fears, anger and in some cases bigotry and delegitimizing  the media is the NAZI M.O.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiseGuy317 i can tell you as a student of history, there are a lot of parallels with 1933. It could be 1%, 10% or even .005%, it's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow we are gonna have to "arm up"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenRubioPress @marcorubio do something about Bannon. He is a danger to this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @CNN they have "souled" out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump we thought you were Putin's puppet, but I will now refer to Bannon as President Bannon. You are President orange puppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@branden204 @rolandsmartin he is sadly achieving everything he set out to do very quickly. He must know he won't make it to four years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sbg1 @JeffreyGoldberg @TheAtlNews Hitler's reincarnation needs to be stopped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RCcroca145 @TheRickWilson @drMajMaj @AviWoolf Bannon is all about symbolism. There is a "master plan" at play and it smells of 1933.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLU @MariaTCardona we have 200 weeks or so left. Let's do this! #ResistTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibyaLiberty @ASE the real America will fight Trump's tyranny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist nope... a bad man can't be a "good" anything. All action are self serving for men that lack good character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trisagion3 @johnpavlovitz Bannon a danger to national security!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump you have nothing to celebrate... shame on you, your family and your puppet of a father!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze they're in bed with the Devil now https://t.co/lBlnZJKrBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohstopitdonald Steve Bannon is the brains ... Trump is the puppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadande a crazy and scary week one ... Steve Bannon is a one man wrecking machine. Making America Like it's 1933 Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan do something about trump!!! Don't be an ass for this monster?? Checks and balances!! This ban is wrong!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisVanHollen SIR!!! What is going on??? What are you going to do about Trump??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @AmundsenJon @V_of_Europe sounds like most white West Virginians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump when did we become a theocracy? https://t.co/LJng8q2mpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldmanebro @VibeHi I will leave this right here ... sad days https://t.co/YSxORCRR6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCAppelbaum @trump_democrat @mims Steve Jobs father is Syrian!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtyHans @Mwforhr @Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday not arguing Jesus, arguing for human rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njroode @Mwforhr @AtyHans @Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday respect. Right now it's about our human rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @Phil_Mattingly straight hate born of fear and bigotry. Sad days ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mwforhr @AtyHans @Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday this is what people wanted. Now they have it. Sad week in American History]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mwforhr @AtyHans @Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday as a Christian, I am sorry so called "Christians" are behind all this. Jesus loves all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mwforhr @AtyHans @Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday I voted for her. It seems it will all have to suffer this presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hayder_alKhoei @JonathanLanday one day we will look back at Trump as the gravest mistake in American History along with slavery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelani9 @rolandsmartin brown and black people are next. Let's no get it twisted. Arm up!! 2nd amendment in play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood @nytimes that's Steve Brannon's desire to consolidate the FEAR and BIGOTRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou either that, or the resistance will have to do it by force. https://t.co/LjEDzKMql0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @ChrisCuomo @ksadjadpour @voxdotcom The Third Reich 2.0 made it official with the ban https://t.co/IVBe4Osk4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan count down to the third Reich 2.0 started after this ban. Will you just stand idle? https://t.co/oNZOe8y427]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @BostonGlobe only a matter of time #1933 #resistance #NotMyPresidentTrump 2nd Amendment  now in play!… https://t.co/uDaGOsNexy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @maddow #1933 #resistance all of a sudden the 2nd amendment makes sense. #NotMyPresidentTrump https://t.co/OfbFCjK9DN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexwagner @theIRC @DMiliband @nytimes @CharlesMBlow amateur hour at the White House just turned into The Third Reich 2.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylanlscott @donnabrazile @washingtonpost forget Healthcare. the muslim ban proves this is 1933. https://t.co/nPWqkiexup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood the POTUS is bearing hostile attitudes towards America and its founding principles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKristof @nytopinion @nytimes the Trump administration is showing us who the real terrorist group is. Smells of 1933]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaraCalavera and rid the world of Steve Bannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine you have to do something. we can't stay silent. This is 1933 Germany. I am buying guns now to protect myself from the government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffy9999 @TrumpTrash2016 @davidaxelrod fear, anger and bigotry got him elected. 1933 Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @maggieNYT I am arming up as the genius of the 2nd amendment now makes sense with Trump in power. GOP is useless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint it's symbolic of Bannon's master plan. This is now 1933 Germany. Fear-Anger-Bigotry were the tools of the day as they're now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes the GOP and every American supporting the ban. Shame on them. America is now America's biggest threat. #selfdestructmode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze so true and very sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldmanebro @SorayaSoiFree sorry to say it, but white Cubans are more openly racist than just about all white supremacist groups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump wow, you are never gonna let this go. SAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard you're out at elections time https://t.co/QFGpe2TB5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oreillyfactor you have lost all credibility you old crank. Go to bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drmoore God continue blessing you for remaining true to our Lord and Savior, Jesus Christ. My heart aches because many are not recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse @dcexaminer Mr. Toughguy lol... you're a joke dude. You supported this bum, and he now thinks he is your King. Duh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews he likens it to the Great Wall of China is his stupid head. This will be his legacy and he knows it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyO @realDonaldTrump @DavidMuir why isn't Saudi Arabia on the list? They produced 9/11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightline @ABC it will just confirm what we already know: He is crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow seems like they are in a catatonic state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze so much for checks and balances ... the GOP is in a state of shock and are comatose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @ABC i didn't know this was a reality tv show for us to "enjoy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnonPress Trump will singularly be the biggest crisis of our lifetime. #GodHelpUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greta @SpeakerRyan @MSNBC Don't worry? We have a senile oompa loompa with the maturity of a spoiled 9 year old brat making decisions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DavidMuir @ABC enjoy? more like dreading to hear what idiocy comes out of Trumps mouth. #mussolini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oreillyfactor the spin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinhendrix @pbump this pasty and smelly pig, Bannon is the reason the second amendment exists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marclamonthill He is worried people look at him as "THE BASTARD IN CHIEF" https://t.co/xLp7Zsn7Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickygervais it's because there is innate "dick head malady " in humans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is worried he is looked at as the Bastard President in Chief LOL. Worst start to a presidency I have ever see… https://t.co/SjLvnu7aIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkihaley save us from Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindyfinn @Evan_McMullin there is genius in the second amendment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you're not a King nor a dictator, you can't go in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frontlinepbs @seanspicer he will be out before the term is completed. Trump is too impulsive for his own good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoleCollector @UnderArmour just played themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @realDonaldTrump this giant oompa loompa is such a disaster. Even his followers are worrying now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @CNN you idiot loser of a president ... grow a sack and get off twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbydphillip @washingtonpost LIAR IN CHIEF again, wasting his breath on stupidity and his own insecure petulance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @EW @people people were watching hoping hell would freeze over the inauguration. Too bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke you're an idiot... go home and take your nap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Vainglorious Affront to the C.I.A. https://t.co/gzGLbWbwUR via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretBaier @CHForty @BillyHurst14 @FoxNews you are a good man and a good journalist Bret. No alternative facts, the force is with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @CoryBooker he is done... don't run, we need to win in 20']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @pwthornton from "Liar in Chief" to "Robber in Chief"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico first three days are an F]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>