<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaQuinlan by coincidence... https://t.co/Y4nbvSDyk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaQuinlan That antique book shop on Duke Street maybe? Or somewhere on Francis Street?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaQuinlan The gorgeous "A Portrait of Dublin in Maps" (Muiris De Buitleir) has what you need in myriad forms. All good book shops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmflashe @MBTSMovie Great, wasn't it? Saw TrainspottingT2 and La La Land over the past three days, neither holds a candle to MBTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given we're only country in EU with US immigration pre-clearance, guessing our Govt. will be faced with some big decisions over coming days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful and frightening. Forget IT skills, we need to promote the teaching of history as a matter of extreme ur… https://t.co/4eus4UB4JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickgestation Am starting to feel that this should be a minimum qualification for voting also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old history teacher said, re mooted curriculum choice between them, that nobody should be allowed study physics without also taking history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonStopPop very kind words, thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eleventyfour I'm from south Dublin, so I'm told I go for "daw-ta"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanehegarty He's kind of right, mind you. Saw Rihanna last year, like a transistor 200 yards up the beach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanehegarty as I pointed out to @daveGildedALM  y'day Colm's old band regularly hit 130dB, causing "sensory deprivation" (Kevin Shields)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes She was empty vessel in "Black Swan", only when Milla Kunis turns up do the lights turn on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DervalORourke Guinness World Record attempt for longest penalty wall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derekholla @Scannain_com I second that - really appreciate the interest and support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevethewall @IrishArtsCenter Mexico are paying for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveGildedALM @IrishTimes but how would the torturers hear them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveGildedALM @IrishTimes ... and often reached 130db. Shields later remarked "it was so loud it was like sensory deprivation" [Wiki]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveGildedALM @IrishTimes In fairness MBV in live performance performed an interlude known as "the holocaust" which could last half an hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maudymac @tomhappens ironing board cover? I knew yiz were romantic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens @maudymac not even the tiniest sapphire earrings or earthenware cufflinks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maudymac @tomhappens happy anniversary - do you start getting each other good presents yet? Well past paper and pewter by now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for weird online-game related tweets, child briefly wrested control of computer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardenscapes 2 Online Official Site - Playrix Games - Free Online Games https://t.co/nVU8jXDWkk via amazing @Playrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gardenscapes 2 Online Official Site - Playrix Games - Free Online Games https://t.co/nVU8jXDWkk via @Playrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annemccoy @mikartistik Plastic Fox! I'm Turning Into Me Dad! Pocket of Straws! These are universal themes, all should listen and learn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharkastic Hope you're right but fear combination of US companies moving out and lost exports to U.K. will be tough for jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving aside all other obvious horrors, have increasingly bad feeling about Ireland's economic outlook based on this speech &amp; Theresa May's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkFM music industry canary in coal mine for many others. Only viable solution is levy broadband connections, distribute to creators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fanningsessions @talldanhegarty @janicelongdj Genuinely forgotten about it, but big deal for us at time. Intrigued and a little terrified!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens @fionndavenport Michael Flatley is perfect. Same shade of orange. Hard to be an ironist this weather...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talldanhegarty @janicelongdj @fanningsessions oh my word! Have no idea what that will sound like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieholly @LandFMovie @RottenTomatoes @AmazonStudios @CurzonAtHome @transmission @MongrelMedia @TedHope well deserved! Hilarious, flawless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens @fionndavenport It's a travesty! Something is definitely happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevRichardColes Notre Dame? Houses Of Parliament?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandapalmer soul / desolate; new / denuded; air / uncaring; anger / langerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petepaphides @annemccoy @sohoradio "Tracks of My Tears" - outside I'm masquerading, inside my heart is breaking. Story of everyone's life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien very true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien all those people who used to be living "lives of quiet desperation" have somewhere to shout now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevoBerube @JinxLennon @villagevoice @rxgau Wow! Go the Jinx!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelMee_too thank you for that Michael - washing machines not featured enough in pop music today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanMoncrieff The Kids Are All Wives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinser @drumkeeperfilm thanks for your kind wishes Eoin, really appreciated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roisiningle @StefPreissner @funderland @IrishTimes Congratulations, it'll be the Dail for you next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobDoyle1 @RTEArena Heard that, you were great! Really enjoyed our chance encounter in Paris, hope the City of Light is powering the work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very icy on those Dublin side roads, cyclists be careful this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Esthermccarthy @IrishFilmBoard Great to see you there Esther, really appreciate the interest in @drumkeeperfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetoblivion26 Great to meet in person today, hope my chatting was coherent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishFilmBoard @screentraining Thanks so much for your support, today and over the past decade - couldn't have made @drumkeeperfilm without]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallXMurphy ah, thanks a million Niall. I'm as talkative as ever I'm afraid - and very buzzed to be finally talking about this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevRichardColes I second (or thirty-fifth, at current count) that emotion. She is so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandapalmer "discussion"; or use "about" rather than "of" after "question", "debate" or "dispute" which nets out at 4 syllables total]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely feeling best way to ensure benign Trump Presidency is for right-thinking celebs to keep making small digs at him #rumpledthinskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichChappo Such a fantastic read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elementpictures @goldenglobes @lobsterfilm Fantastic performance, deserves to be gonged. Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too (defibrillator at the ready at all times) https://t.co/qT4yBfuImG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Thanks, same to you. As @lizzienugent noted yesterday, JK Rowling's probably knocked off a chapter while we've been tweeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Nor have I personally (though like everyone, it's affected people close to me). Did you see this? https://t.co/gNaElZbCwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua They're  getting to talk about cancer on air for free, in many multiples of 30 seconds. Like I say, let's see how it plays out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Let's see what reaction it does achieve. I notice that ICS are on 98FM in 15 minutes talking about their issue again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua The headline is what makes you read on (or, in most advertising, fails to). Here it's spawning debate. Hard to do with bland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua I'm guessing that having the campaign - and therefore the issue - as third item on RTE News will count as a win for ICS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua It's actually surprisingly hard to alienate people. It's scarily easy to spend 250k (or whatever) with absolutely no impact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Yes, I have (Not on this campaign, I should add). Not looking for a row, btw, just giving alt opinion. "With respect" genuine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Client base isn't target market. If seeking to raise awareness/funding, probably targeting people not currently v cancer-aware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua Most advertising is ignored. I'm guessing the target market here will investigate this campaign further. A win, for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua @IrishCancerSoc Politics - that's a different story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua @IrishCancerSoc Actually, with respect, I think you're wrong. In the world of advertising, when you're noticed you're winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenClouds4 They're delusional, I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenClouds4 Commons not following through on popular vote theoretically possible but not politically. There'd be a revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mark_tuthill Beautifully written and powerful, great work Mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's greatest mag for cartoon thinks (and lots more besides) does it again https://t.co/xELEQbV2HO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland @alienenvoymusic HNY 2 Y'all, thanks for all the plays in 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To quote Noel Coward, "it's extraordinary how potent cheap music is". RIP George Michael, true genius of pop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorker Though now acutely conscious of not having used Oxford Comma in that last tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my greatest pleasures is my @NewYorker subscription. Thought-provoking, consciousness-expanding and side-spl… https://t.co/7kk1VL6FZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotpress @WilliePenroseTD Bill clearly breaches EU competition law. Pointless gesture always destined to fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judykelly50 You're welcome, amazing reaction. Can't wait to see what you (&amp; world) think of my own opus but we'll all have wait to til 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My physical environment. My mental state. https://t.co/yUFqsxuP6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeChester_ @camilleos @cc_irlandais yes! Your own show a lovely bonus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @judykelly50 - #thecrossing is such a great piece of work. Am in awe of both yourself and those young navy personnel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found #thecrossing absolutely compulsive, harrowing, thought-provoking &amp; heroic. Astonishing and essential work by both navy and film-makers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Parents of ASD kids in south ctrl Dublin interested in lobbying for secondary school Special Classes https://t.co/sxrKvKeqkE Pls RT Tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens @NewstalkFM My favourite songwriter. (And a whole bunch of other songwriters' favourite songwriter too.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanmillardub @miriamingram @superboreen @truthiscatching the deal, shaven a, outside London, rock to roll, feel everything &amp; love yrself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sorry to miss tonight's show forHaiti @whelanslive with @KennedySinger  @eleanormcevoy owing to wicked lurgy. With you in spirit Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemcl @stevesilberman Seriously? The worst thing about Trump is his election's empowerment of clowns, goons and the righteously wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quantick As grindingly unfunny as his dimmest right-wing counterparts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alispagnola or just start with a denial: "x denies doing y".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad I braved cold cycle to witness full-on-no-gap @katetempest tonight. And loved her gentle but effective opening plea to put phones away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzienugent Understandable, given the times. You'd get the same at my breakfast table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just me or is @robbiewilliams morphing into #morrissey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeySuperJude @PRRo @BBClamacqshow thanks for that Steve, making a happy man very old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kushinaman @BBC6Music thank you both for cheering up mine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @lizzienugent you expressed that much better than I did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzienugent hold down cmd + Cap + 4 simultaneously - then press and hold down mouse / trackpad as you select area. Release button to snap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wanted to say well done you @RSAGmusic - you've a big heart to go with that big talent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland at risk of parping own piccolo, "small loads" by @alienenvoymusic or "but" by TFLS (on "Johnson")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatTurnerMusic Best excuse ever for 3D glasses: masking floods of parental tears. Properly satisfying close to one of the great franchises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens And so you should be! It was great.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>