<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Robbers vault CVS pharmacy counter, hold gun to head of worker, police say https://t.co/IMK5h0zXNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former D.C. police chief's focus in new NFL gig is protecting the league's image https://t.co/7lUteU6fZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Avenue between 14th and 15th streets closed, as is 15th between H and  G streets. Police investigating suspicious package.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunshots fired into a crowd wound four, including a 17-year-old girl, in Southeast Washington https://t.co/lrYFdnHgPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC police report: "V-2 .. advised he had been shot in the head. After further investigation it was found he had been shot only in the ankle"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatal fire in Trinidad neighborhood ruled intentionally set https://t.co/0ttgNscIFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for a refugee family, in the wake of Trump’s ban https://t.co/IK93sGACvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. group goes from street gang to clothing start-up https://t.co/5h0n3i1BP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP House chair: Maybe we should cut off part of D.C. and send it back to Maryland https://t.co/Z9lAsin7Xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia enters federal court fight against Trump travel ban https://t.co/X80muaixec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six questions about court cases filed after Trump’s immigration order https://t.co/mGrlXpdCyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. group goes from street gang to clothing start-up - The Washington Post https://t.co/oMPAHpc2oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intruder stared at the Zarembas ... He lifted the gun to his head. There was another shot, and he lay dying too. https://t.co/uyPu58jEf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Call 911!’ She fought a masked intruder in her daughter’s bedroom. Then he fired a gun. https://t.co/uyPu58jEf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man reported shot in leg on 11th Street NW, near Cardozo Education Campus. Does not appear at this time related to school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former school aide, choir director pleads guilty to child porn charges https://t.co/PupKZdcZJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors drop rioting charges against four journalists arrested during inauguration protests https://t.co/zn0K5EdCC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who hit female worker with a gun during Gallaudet University burglary pleads guilty https://t.co/XLSS7e4Od2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airport police officer accidentally fires gun at Reagan National Airport https://t.co/5Xxamvwptj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flash, a triple homicide shatters a restaurant dream years in the making https://t.co/HjZfWwoQS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shootout in D.C.’s Brightwood Park https://t.co/Mi1d9YJ4uo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charge dropped against reporter caught up in mass arrests in violent D.C. protest https://t.co/iNPDfEicAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least three journalists caught up in mass arrests during violent D.C. protest https://t.co/L066WCqLJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgetown University student abducted, taken to bank machines, D.C. police say https://t.co/qDEawtDcvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgetown University student was abducted on Georgetown street, taken to bank machines, D.C. police say https://t.co/GipP458ZlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police are investigating multiple deaths at McLean home https://t.co/er97wTp0DX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: Prosecutors drop riot charges against journalist Even Engel. Backstory: Reporters caught up in mass arrests https://t.co/gm6UcbQ2Ov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arlington teacher charged with exposing himself to two teens in locker room https://t.co/cLXQHotuqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revisiting a case from Howard County: Girl, 16, killed by 15-year-old high school classmate was not targeted by him https://t.co/dyp5M9HdaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man was abducted on Georgetown street, taken to bank machines, D.C. police say https://t.co/qDEawtDcvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former elementary school aide charged in child porn case to appear in court Monday https://t.co/xfNtvTjZbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least three journalists caught up in mass arrests during violent D.C. protest https://t.co/2jlRgfAedO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven Greenpeace protesters released from jail; group vows to continue protests. Company lost $500,000 -- https://t.co/wbu8cIX0ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not expected in court: The first lady https://t.co/SNs4vGRU4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenage boy charged in 2 sexual assaults in NE Washington https://t.co/G06vc23y5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serial burglar suspect caught in Alexandria area after tips to police https://t.co/5vhmwS0WCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorities say protest cost company $500,000 https://t.co/XLMf6uXTTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s limo sports D.C.’s protest license plates: ‘Taxation Without Representation’ https://t.co/NHLEhKpSH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. postal carrier assaulted, robbed of mail in Georgetown, police say https://t.co/tPzwePwj6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pedestrian dies after being struck by three cars in Prince George’s County https://t.co/zU4oUIA2Qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling video of fatal shooting in D.C. from Tuesday on Benning Road in NE. https://t.co/sLBVxKXzkm Story: https://t.co/kvFbgCZgiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 official armored and other vehicles stolen from State Dept., prosecutors charge https://t.co/lLKX5IP8kT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. postal carrier assaulted, robbed of mail in Georgetown, police say https://t.co/D4qEHYMttt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here, kitty kitty. D.C. firefighters rescue cat that got stuck in a tree in Georgetown https://t.co/xHSWblj6gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School in Prince George’s County placed on brief lockdown after shots fired nearby https://t.co/1TNi2wbp5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here, kitty kitty. D.C. firefighters rescue cat that got stuck in a tree in Georgetown https://t.co/Y9mRsdttaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man convicted of sex abuse 20 times accused in new incident; will be detained https://t.co/RzVC24QoqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. fights back against lawsuit by victims of L'Enfant Plaza smoke crisis https://t.co/bDlr4fwaHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[String of armed robberies at pharmacies in Montgomery County https://t.co/gYXR2u6SnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayaSchenwar Please call Peter Hermann at the Washington Post, 202-334-9542. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They stayed atop the crane for 18 hours. Now they're down, in jail and facing a variety of charges. https://t.co/RBxOCtGqrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three shootings in an hour on Wednesday in D.C. https://t.co/SQSsBLFgfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘He targeted her.’ Maryland man gets life for raping mentally ill woman, 63 https://t.co/ULzFaMU31I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace protesters climb 270-foot crane in downtown D.C., disrupt traffic https://t.co/o0JYBfNHrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He targeted her.’ Maryland man gets life for raping mentally ill woman, 63 https://t.co/ULzFaMU31I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest on Greenpeace protesters atop 270-foot crane -- they are slowly coming down. https://t.co/yZR5CX1Mmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C., other ‘sanctuary cities’ defiant in the face of Trump’s threats https://t.co/tN5mcFTfUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unclear if shootings related but police say they're investigating. None of the injuries appear to be life threatening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shootings reported in SE after 4 p.m. -- juvenile on Bass Place; 1 juvenile 2 adults on MLK and Melon; 2 juveniles at Gault and Minnesota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two juveniles in late teens shot at Minnesota Ave and Grant Street NE. Reported conscious. Gunman in red jacket in 4 door white hatchback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['That’s not somebody’s Honda': Owner of limo torched on Inauguration Day unsure if insurance will cover damages https://t.co/hhcWtgKR10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace says protesters slowly making way down 270-foot crane carrying 70-pound banner. Might take another hour before in police hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosion erupts in drug vault at D.C. police evidence storage facility https://t.co/2Sas5MnrIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in gat school-bus stop turns himself in to police https://t.co/ryUXVmMoeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosion reported at DC police warehouse that stores evidence. Authorities say occurred in drug vault. One minor injury. Details to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters atop 270-foot crane in downtown DC have rolled up their banner. Pic from Mandy McLaren https://t.co/qvuyg2Cwn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white Trump voter explains why he was inspired to leave a black waitress a $450 tip and an uplifting note https://t.co/SLq88C6GH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest on Greenpeace protester atop 270-foot crane in downtown D.C. Demonstrator on crane says down "soon enough." https://t.co/LiX1ORB8PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protester atop 270-foot crane, Pearl Robinson, says group against "normalization of Trump presidency." Says: "We'll come down soon enough."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lacymacauley Tried again this morning and you didn't pick up. your message box is full. 202-334-9542]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest banner unfurled atop 270-foot crane in downtown DC. Greenpeace protesting Trump, oil pipelines. Watch live: https://t.co/yYR5pHpsXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace says 35x75 foot banner on crane will read, "Resist" to protest oil pipelines. Says they will stay on crane until message heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest from Greenpeace protest in which activists climb 270-foot crane in downtown D.C. https://t.co/oI6bhrsOUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace demonstrators appear to be starting to unfurl banner from 270-foot construction crane. Watch live https://t.co/yYR5pHpsXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More more pics of Greenpeace activists atop 270-foot construction crane, from Valerie O'Keefe. https://t.co/qdWTM8Ai92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post live-stream from downtown protest site where Greenpeace activists have climbed 270-foot construction crane. https://t.co/yYR5pHpsXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One protester is now dangling from atop 270 foot crane. He appears to have a safety harness. Is trying to unfurl a… https://t.co/G3ivjl1ga0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters on the scene of protesters who climbed 270 foot crane in downtown D.C. https://t.co/RZITECHth4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorities say 7 protesters in 270 foot high crane at 15th and L. Unclear what they are protesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters climb construction crane at 15th and L streets. So far police appear to be waiting them out. https://t.co/JiUD9pxUG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new idea to keep D.C. officers from retiring: Double their salaries https://t.co/NKRp5iYmnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the midst of chaotic protests, a coffee-shop manager helped visitors stay safe https://t.co/RylGfJicZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman shot at school bus stop as children watched https://t.co/gm3A4FaeYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. prosecutors offer unspecified plea deal in Comet Ping Pong pizza case https://t.co/qwIbhG8liN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six held at gunpoint in Olney home invasion; not random, police say https://t.co/kegvwt51aR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two robberies in an hour on Capitol Hill Tuesday night https://t.co/061Gfmql65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man fatally shot on Benning Road in Northeast Washington https://t.co/CCi6HkQzQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot on Benning Road this afternoon has died on his injuries. Update coming shortly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman shot at school bus stop as children watched https://t.co/gm3A4FaeYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meetings of activists planning to disrupt inauguration were infiltrated by conservative media group https://t.co/KPCWYHAnbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot about 30 minutes ago 1600 Benning Road NE, near a shopping center and Starburst Plaza. Victim reported unconscious but breathing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot near Nationals Park https://t.co/4gixBzvfYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooting near job fair at Nationals Park was actually man shot behind nearby liquor store. Police said he ran toward stadium. Details on way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. prosecutors offer unspecified plea deal in Comet Ping Pong pizza case https://t.co/qwIbhG8liN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man’s body found off trail near GW Parkway in Arlington https://t.co/QLQ35pXhhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man shot outside Nationals Park https://t.co/4gixBzvfYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One man reported shot outside Nationals Park this morning. Struck in shoulder. Details to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Injured man at Union Station may have been shot or stabbed, police say https://t.co/AZkIW1y5Wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No those aren’t real weapons, and it is not a real SWAT team in Frederick, Md. https://t.co/VaBaBY69qF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCHomicideCount @DCPoliceDept @byjenniferswift @hgil @G_Pem @ByLynhBui There were 2 homicides on each of those days We have names for all 4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>