<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That's about as totalitarian a statement as it gets. https://t.co/PeLpTM12v7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree. https://t.co/SwQSLbMrHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrity is in short supply within the GOP right now. But those of us who vote on character &amp; credentials rather t… https://t.co/0VavxgtXqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melissa McCarthy is brilliant. ‘S.N.L.’ Goes After Trump Again, With Melissa McCarthy as Sean Spicer https://t.co/VZEn8QE74p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | In education, greater choice doesn’t always mean better outcomes https://t.co/O9tW8HV7pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not partisan politics. She simply does not have the appropriate experience, education or fundamental knowle… https://t.co/o8RM0cblrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched  https://t.co/1pjYqjo8Q0 last night &amp; read this today. Stunned by the work of these journalists. https://t.co/XFFyFgBsLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Trump Backers Want Ideology Test For Extreme Vetting https://t.co/dV4k5V57OL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bamaral44 Thank you for live-tweeting this. I'm following along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintSmithIII Agreed, maybe because most humans are a series of contradictions. I thought your point was well made in PBS spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You don’t have to support the methane waste rule to see why repealing it will only make the problem worse,” --Taxp… https://t.co/rWEReAZfHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am trying to resist the mockery, but @HireMeImFunny is just too committed to ignore. https://t.co/a2KiKt5JhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep this one on my fridge to remind me of what my real job is as a parent--to help them find their calling, thei… https://t.co/YxwbvHB6pC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for these. I'm part of a book club that focuses exclusively on narratives adapted for film. So fun to compa… https://t.co/2t4tvGtWs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brief but spectacular, indeed. https://t.co/KStoK169ad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is as telling as it gets. Important to read entire article to make your own conclusion about why Trump employs… https://t.co/RtDfhbQY5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marytheluckyone @LIGAWAB @Ic206Bones @BCatsParanormal @neilr1975 @gahawolf @Raceandrally @ViTweet_ Cannot believe it's Friday again already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One's religion should have no weight in determining his or her immigration status. That's one of the many promises… https://t.co/ognF478TtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A separation of church and state is integral to our democracy. This distinction should be strengthened, not destroy… https://t.co/Xr3x5N8B9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoken w/many people who don't understand this. Even if you're insured through your employer, you're benefiting fro… https://t.co/YO6vZ8xycu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating piece -- The simple trick to getting people to support refugees, immigrants, and Obamacare https://t.co/rtzbqXwtEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House rolls back rule restricting gun sales to mentally ill @CNNPolitics https://t.co/sIUgwFlpVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a question everyone should be asking, regardless of political party. https://t.co/2PrCBjl0oW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They told me they would keep me in this position if I would commit to not disagreeing with our president...." https://t.co/G56BEUmKGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great idea. https://t.co/8z72QBVnx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This comes to mind: https://t.co/4zPwH2UiJM https://t.co/6VFrh9TILX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dangerously Isolated President https://t.co/P9C0htYwx3 via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now we no longer honor existing international agreements with our closest allies? This President is endangering… https://t.co/HQg8GyvLPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needed reprieve from politics, so introduced my boys to https://t.co/GQL0dBzsgV &amp; https://t.co/h3D2y74Ow8. Never gets old, @JKCorden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, this gave me a much-needed laugh tonight. https://t.co/fLgOR2oifq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: What makes Betsy DeVos such an unusual nominee for education secretary https://t.co/efE4YM2hiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a president who's made it clear that he does not respect the basic tenets of democracy, so these are fair q… https://t.co/ngKnCYe7aX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice interview. Viet Thanh Nguyen: By the Book https://t.co/UfDADGKdK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["THE FACTS: The immigration system doesn't allow the kind of "rush" Trump is describing." https://t.co/T6q1Q3ZFfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty brilliant. 'Trump and Dump': When POTUS tweets and stocks fall, this animal charity benefits https://t.co/HOfEevUeYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV 2 | All That We Share https://t.co/DupziulZtr via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son at dinner tonight: "I think robots should take over the world."
Me: "What? Why?"
Son: "Cuz we're doing a pretty lousy job."
#NoHate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Insane people are always sure that they are fine. It is only the sane people who are willing to admit that they are crazy." --Nora Ephron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect Is Held in Quebec Mosque Shooting That Killed 6 https://t.co/SpkPyuo4NU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Examples of regs cited include child labor ban, Americans with Disabilities Act, workplace regs requiring fire exit… https://t.co/LfNnYamB89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unconfirmed: Senate 3 votes short of blocking Betsy DeVos. If you live in ME, TN, AK, GA, UT, NC, WY, LA, KS, SC, or KY, call your senators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important information here. https://t.co/AwXbivpfnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really interesting idea. https://t.co/x34VYlMg3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the difference between a fair &amp; just policy and a policy rooted in bigotry. https://t.co/FlZsA9Fhi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your leadership accountable with calls now and votes next year. https://t.co/HEZIvCw4Ls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting. https://t.co/zkjB0oEGyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We could slip into a very dark place very quickly if people just decide to be indifferent.” https://t.co/mQHOoUdIDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appreciate this reporting--gives me a better understanding of world reaction, along with ongoing analysis. https://t.co/CtxPDLqbQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, a must-read. "...the implications of having an executive this inept are not small and won’t be short-lived." https://t.co/i2dIxmUlrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important points here. "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/XeOQV2CuBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes it is. https://t.co/ng78um4AwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A piece worth revisiting IMO. The Boston Bombers Were Not Refugees--Neither Was the Paris Attacker https://t.co/FsMG2rd7uW via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would have liked stronger language, but I'll take it. https://t.co/Ri59cWuFmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insightful piece. "Protest, the average Iranian can tell you, is the recourse of an  unrepresented people." https://t.co/h5ApBzCzof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for reporting this, @aaronblake: Here's where Republicans stand on Trump's controversial travel ban https://t.co/D0xacj0ZYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently. https://t.co/OANJMJPJEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember this come voting time. https://t.co/SiMWNgiudU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This jeopardizes all Americans: BBC News - Trump puts Bannon on security council, dropping joint chiefs https://t.co/oH4QLIEO5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["President Trump’s executive order violates the due process, religious liberty and  equal protection clauses of the… https://t.co/v0d8horI9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WileyCash A beautiful reminder of a better future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WajahatAli @CNN Just watched. Don't know how anyone justifies this as anti-terrorism measure. There's simply no evidence to support that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the America I believe in. https://t.co/269gMsVSmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump visa ban also applies to citizens with dual nationality, State Department says https://t.co/AHxjyUWSsk via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lab is looking for cures to tuberculosis, Type 1 diabetes, and rheumatoid arthritis." https://t.co/EO3tpjCieY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A Pew Research Center report found that the U.S. admitted nearly equal number of Muslim and Christian refugees in… https://t.co/bPJErGruXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to change this? "If we decided to give green cards only to redheads who can play the spoons, we can do that," https://t.co/r4txUHouEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does seem a terrible way to live, but somehow challenging one's own ideas is more difficult than living like thi… https://t.co/vWLRaPHXmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonpinter You're not alone. I'm trying very hard to channel my anger into meaningful discourse &amp; action, but it's extremely difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant conversation with @jayrosen_nyu this week on how Trump supporters, opposers, and neutrals may digest WH f… https://t.co/JGgbjX4ZwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's fantastic! Congratulations to @WeatherwaxAnnie! https://t.co/lay0Jw41gH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This policy is not only inhumane, unethical &amp; immoral, but it threatens our national security. American soldiers de… https://t.co/78M3Ardsgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The greatest way to live with honor in this world is to be what we pretend to be.”  --Socrates

Will we ever learn? https://t.co/nUL8BF71Jd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot wait for @LastWeekTonight to come back. We need all the voices of reason that we can get right now. https://t.co/5g9IQecWcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Some six million U.S. jobs depend on trade with Mexico.” https://t.co/rkswLG5jHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlights: The Trump presidency on January 27 at 3:39 P.M. EST/2039 GMT https://t.co/GEg14BFj9l via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Haley...has little foreign policy and no U.S. federal government experience." https://t.co/Z3Ok7tOBGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New book will be important read -- How Author Timothy Tyson Found the Woman at the Center of the Emmett Till Case https://t.co/uNyH71sjd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very important distinction; makes system vulnerable to increased corruption. https://t.co/FM2SVKYEEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this @OnPointRadio conversation informative, along with https://t.co/SDeSCadqfk via @RadioBoston https://t.co/WsWIiJDzXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: 'It's A Big One': Iowa Pipeline Leaks Nearly 140,000 Gallons Of Diesel https://t.co/vptiukfCFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully American taxpayers won't pay for it either--Mexico's President Cancels Planned D.C. Trip To Meet W/Trump https://t.co/AIscf4pHIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legitimate reasons to oppose: alumni from DeVos's Christian college oppose her nomination as education secretary https://t.co/IuEdsBVBkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't afford to create any more. Superfund: National Priorities List (NPL) https://t.co/CFLdeZ03Ta via @EPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely obscene. Depicts a man who is in no way motivated to be a public servant. https://t.co/ghZznYtEvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums it up. https://t.co/GPyleaUq1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon registered to vote in two states despite Trump's cries of 'voter fraud' https://t.co/vwCWHpcA43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-existing conditions &amp; tax changes for employer-sponsored plans need to be examined closely. Many falsely believ… https://t.co/79TyfJfr2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this quote. This endeavor is a choice. Multiple day jobs, worn out everything &amp; lots of cheap pasta dinners ar… https://t.co/FmLaK64Imu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possible consequence to be aware of. I've also been thinking how ACA repeal might affect Tricare benefits, should V… https://t.co/sZhRCgwRUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a world we should all aspire to. https://t.co/XNygybMoTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear. #DAPL is about creating profits, not jobs or energy independence: https://t.co/84RzeYvUVt via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this essay. https://t.co/6oFefNF8e6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...the problem is that health care doesn’t work like most other consumer goods." Yes, and many must choose by loca… https://t.co/3vy1CA1oJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: John Lewis' Graphic Memoir Wins 4 American Library Association Awards https://t.co/daTDLwRg7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw @FencesMovie. Wow. Astonishing ensemble performance. @violadavis blew me away. I cried not for Rose, but with her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some important distinctions made here. Point taken. Thanks @willrich45 for your continued commitment to #education. https://t.co/9Pi1sUNxRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fascinating look at a person who apparently values winning over all else, including personal integrity or ideolog… https://t.co/NSKxxmyEaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pursuing a graduate degree in middle age with kids heading off to college means I'll be one of them. https://t.co/mYOZoZZ5xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Ethics Experts To File Lawsuit Saying Trump's Overseas Interests Violate Constitution https://t.co/TQ3qTqtUes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important insight here, for sure. https://t.co/XOS9D4OjK0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>