<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecksWrecks it's the same one! I start with a diagonal-down dash into a jump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecksWrecks I'm jumping through the screen transition to refill my dash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimmyMDx THANK YOU FOR PLAYING! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't get over this https://t.co/eNqf9xobVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashly_burch yessss :) congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaltySharkz oh the map editor is only on PC! It's designed for mouse/keyboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found this old track I wrote back in 2013, still kinda like it :) https://t.co/lGQ3AS4Rkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wikzo no plans yet, but I think it'd be a great fit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@residualagate hmmmm for you I'd guess transistor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest surprise of making Celeste has to be how much I'm getting into writing for it. The second biggest surprise is wow, writing is hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acarboni @legobutts I'm still so close to jumping on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacobCamzabob no plans yet, but I agree it would be really cool :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lena is absolutely killing it with the Celeste soundtrack :) https://t.co/jOr7llTMKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @tomspilman and @MonoGameTeam for the great porting work :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsuttner sweeeeet, let's hang out! Lunch or something. Maybe I'll pay for once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsuttner thanks! Are you going to GDC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TowerFall Ascension and Dark World are out now on XBox One!! :D https://t.co/p8E4qCCm9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NoelFB and Yvonne haven't seen Army of Darkness so https://t.co/WRS9iyyqsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool how Kevin did these sounds. I love working with these guys :) https://t.co/UJNFSgGBHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mortician's Tale x_x this game is going to be amazing https://t.co/d9tOw56mQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although I flip-flop between that and @ChevyRay's Ikenfell https://t.co/DCUaWOB0cT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably my most anticipated game right now is @konjak's Iconoclasts https://t.co/vFBdRcH8AL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver my bad, they aren't buffered!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver it's definitely just grazing the cooldown. Prob buffered the Dodge before the cooldown ended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver what the hell kyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaserCannon that's rough :( sorry man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantkirkhope you have to end it with "PERIOD."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The TowerFall community is so amazing :') what a great tournament full of wonderful people &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also huge thanks to @SD_Siggy for running the tournament, and @Genesis_Smash for including TowerFall as a side event :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TowerFall at @Genesis_Smash results:
1st: @kylepulver 
2nd: @starrrsky 
3rd: @SD_Siggy 
Congrats to the players!! So fun to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The TowerFall @Genesis_Smash tournament is on stream! https://t.co/DqOHASXReK @kylepulver commentating :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabdar it's gorgeous :o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was the first game I made for money, so I made it about collecting money haha https://t.co/5YaO202zXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just finished the layouts for Celeste area 4 hard mode, this is what it looks like in our map editor :D we're at… https://t.co/T8CvOPsHpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mgrviper not right now! We're focused on Celeste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Contz January 25th!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jada_l_gibbs was it super fun? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecksWrecks @dakotathemoose pretty sure we actually have zero RNG so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecksWrecks 270 levels and counting ლ(｀ー´ლ)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see what speedrunners do with Celeste when it's done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DKC RELAY RACE!!! https://t.co/ldyo0tnt9e #AGDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well if I'm going to have insomnia and anxiety, during AGDQ is probably the best time to do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver when I fall into that I try to rediscover why I love making games for their own sake (and my answer is always changing)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinycg still local only!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belbeeno oh and winston. I think if you're stuck it's best to practice new heroes so you can be more versatile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belbeeno yeah solo for the most part. I have a few heroes I'm good at across all roles: roadhog, dva, mei, zen, symm, soldier, reaper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was platinum last season but it is WAY HARDER now for some reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally made it to platinum in Overwatch this season. I'm so happy 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wetalo oh @saint11 did all the pixel art in TowerFall! For Celeste @NoelFB and @saint11 are working together on the game art :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spudzaiah no plans right now, but I agree it would be sweet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TowerFall Ascension and Dark World are releasing for XBox One on January 25th! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_m_wiebe @MllePilgrim thanks Marlon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're updating the Celeste dev blog daily now! https://t.co/bRzABOe5oj (@MllePilgrim is keeping it on schedule)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amora_b she's great but umm pearl is the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreyAlien @psysal @raiganburns @NoelFB @kylepulver haha yeah I believe it, and your games are great. I just couldn't resist :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreyAlien @psysal @raiganburns @NoelFB @kylepulver for those breakneck match 3 speeds :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnyelouPx maybe someday we'll make a towerfall sequel :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnyelouPx it sounds cool but we moved on to our next project already! --&gt; https://t.co/TMOon1iCAs :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnyelouPx sorry, 8-player is a separate EXE. I think you can add it to your steam library somehow though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raiganburns @psysal @NoelFB @kylepulver fixed is better for some games, but there's benefits to using delta in the code even if it's fixed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raiganburns @psysal @NoelFB @kylepulver IMO code everything in delta time, then set it to fixed if it fits the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow those GDCA nominee lists are stacked. What a crazy year for games. Congrats everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes still figuring this stuff out for myself but the amount of "censorship" talk lately feels weird to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes censorship is when the government has to approve and edit your book before it is published, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes I guess my point is we have laws and courts to protect from mob censorship. They def could still print the flag if they want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes sure! I've been bullied for artistic choices, but never censored (thank god)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes censorship is when you take away the ability of an artist to choose. They still have the choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes but they can still decide to keep it. And if people still want it they'll still make $$. Backlash != Censorship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes removing the flag was an artistic choice IMO. Could argue it was a bad one, but not censorship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes I think "self-censorship" is an oxymoron! If no one forced you to change it, it's an artistic choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes I guess they must've weighed that against the amount of potential new fans they'd lose with the racism? Who knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes @floatvoid (if I owned that brand I'd also want to quietly distance it from that flag)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyRefenes @floatvoid looks more like the brand owners want to distance themselves from it than censorship? Doubt anyone forced them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theBanov I'll talk really fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theBanov tuesday works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theBanov when are you recording the VO? :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebbe_linden yep, we'll have a release date soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilsquidlette @residualagate I still want that coat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Jada is beating Thumper for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We played so much Overcooked and Machi Koro last night :D great new years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main thing I'm excited for in 2017 is finally releasing another game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zecmo @itchio sure! Thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zecmo @itchio oh do you have a crash log?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8-Player TowerFall only costs $4.00 now :) https://t.co/NhCCXhBSlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this towerfall highlight video, featuring the infamous @zecmo https://t.co/t7p81aeBWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small detour tonight to get these particles and lighting fades just right. This part of my job is so calming :) https://t.co/AchSTc8E5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabdar yeah let's be honest here that's probably what's going to happen haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amora_b what do you think octaves grow on trees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TowerFall is on sale on Steam if you need some local multiplayer in your life :) happy holidays! https://t.co/DOROJnldyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaggerOriginal that's amazing haha. Hopefully you'll like my next game too (Celeste), it shares a lot with jumper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amora_b i stopped playing when my litten evolved 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legobutts yeah anxiety goes into overdrive at night *hugs* esp. in winter here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADAMATOMIC it's funny bc I wish every F2P game was monetized this way instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MllePilgrim @NoelFB yeah area 3 is gonna be so cool when noel and pedro are done with it haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raiganburns @kylepulver @ColinNorthway haha yeah I've ranted about it in the past too. Literally roadblocks me every time i try unity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raiganburns @kylepulver @ColinNorthway yeah it pretty much sums up the argument to roll your own engine doesn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinNorthway @kylepulver fuuuuck yes this is very good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver @ColinNorthway or does the physics engine need update to run before the overlap "registers"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver @ColinNorthway the real question is: can you move something, check for overlaps, then move it back same frame?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepulver @ColinNorthway solely event-based collisions just don't cut it if your game has to be responsive, imo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>