<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Entitled to own opinion. https://t.co/9TIzYITa14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romans 13:1......The authorities that exist have been established by God https://t.co/NB12r6rpGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The leaders know why they are opting for withdrawal w/o mandate from the ppl of the continent. https://t.co/eUiqa2NYZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenyan slum seeks to turn sewage into gold with recycling plant https://t.co/lQXVJMb25t via @StandardKenya Purify sewage water to b drunk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weapons seized from Gambia ex-leader's home: general https://t.co/MVJmtj82Vt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting rages in east Ukraine for third day https://t.co/uvTEmM8zwW via @FRANCE24 Global condemnation and concern appropriate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In prison for a puff: Cannabis users overcrowding Tunisia’s prisons https://t.co/W0lqs1pZe0 via @FRANCE24 Hw abt legalizing like US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God delivered all these commandments: “I, the LORD, am your God, who  brought you out of the land of Egypt, that place of slavery.”Ex-20:1-2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear friends, let us love one another, for love comes from God. Everyone who loves has been born of God and knows God.  — 1 John 4:7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sheep hear My voice, and I know them, and they follow Me.

John 10:27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Why, O Lord, do you stand far off? Why do you hide yourself in times of trouble?”- Psalm 10:1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Spiritual Tools to Keep Your Spirits Up  https://t.co/vn33c1zdeA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not afraid to follow truth
wherever it may lead,
nor to tolerate any error
so long as reason is left free to combat it.
 -T Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing pains some people more than having to think.
 - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rarely do we find men who willingly engage in hard,solid thinking.Theres an almost universal quest 4 easy answers and half-baked solutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True virtue is life under the direction of reason.
 - Baruch Spinoza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France presidential candidate Fillon’s wife earned over 900,000 euros from alleged ‘fake’ jobs, says report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats announced that they are boycotting a committee vote on two of  Trump's Cabinet nominees, drawing fury from Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine Le Pen refuses to repay  €300,000 to European Parliament in misused funds scandal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['God, please help me’: Inmate claims jailers raped her, refused medicine and left her 'catatonic' https://t.co/zsLawwywEE Even raped!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump Nominates Pro-Life-Friendly Judge Neil Gorsuch to the Supreme Court https://t.co/IZACvmogsd 49yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democ Leader Nancy Pelosi lambasted President Donald Trump's newly named Supreme Court nominee Neil Gorsuch as "a very hostile appointment"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks be to Almighty God our Creator for the gift of life and this Wednesday the 1st February, the 32nd day of the Year 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psalm 30:3- O LORD, my God,
 I cried out to you for help and you healed me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’m Christian but not religious” is contrary to scripture and tradition @AleteiaEn https://t.co/JNzc2pVXrY I disagree totally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better late than never. https://t.co/sLQ2WJzeLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has fired the acting AG who ordered Justice Dept. not to defend president’s travel ban https://t.co/keICgKmN2o Contravened  Ofc oath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to all @MwananchiNews https://t.co/FQJV7o3SgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual people from the ECOWAS have outdone us! https://t.co/0DeqTlYqzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[African Union decides to readmit Morocco https://t.co/yfkrwD6buV via @FRANCE24 Problem with AU- IT'S TOOTHLESS unlike ECOWAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires US attorney general who defied travel ban https://t.co/EPdvvQwQit via @FRANCE24 Saly Yates defied the Prez-it was expected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazilian ex-billionaire Batista jailed in corruption probe https://t.co/l3C7Lb5q8H via @FRANCE24 We hv many of his kind around-untouchable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no good thing does he withhold from those whose walk is blameless.  — Psalm 84:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the LORD God is a sun and shield; the LORD bestows favor and honor;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wives, submit to your own husbands. . . . Husbands, love your wives.

Colossians 3:18-19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And behold, I am with you always, until the end of the age.
             
             Matthew 28:20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows Newark auxiliary bishop being attacked by parishioner https://t.co/7foE9l9iGE Newark's Cathedral Basilica of the Sacred Heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chimps beat up, murder and then cannibalise their former tyrant https://t.co/KgELYKiF6N His name is  Foudouko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman president in SA? Sadly Dlamini-Zuma offers more of the same https://t.co/9Pmk39lEYd You want Zuma the woman after Zuma the man?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A life lived in fear is a life half lived.
- Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremiah 17:9- The heart is deceitful above all things and beyond cure. Who can understand it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not measured by the number of breaths we take,
 but by the moments that take our breath away.
 - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let anyone else take the measure
 of your worth and capabilities.
 Always stand proud in who you are.
 - Margaret Spellings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true measure of a man is how he treats someone
 who can do him absolutely no good.
 - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2- but where he stands at times of challenge and controversy.
 - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2- The ultimate measure of a man is not where he stands
 in moments of comfort and convenience,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To measure the man, measure his heart.
 - Malcolm S. Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't fight mine; flowed freely from my eyes https://t.co/OPPtJAFnfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Approved: New system to replace 8-4-4 https://t.co/Ka2wWwQuJD via @StandardKenya Wa-TZ mpo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Amina lost African Union commission post to Chad candidate  https://t.co/IRvoCOKve7 via @StandardKenya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friendship with one's self is all important, because without it one cannot be friends with anyone else in the world."
 
  Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former President Barack Obama criticized President Donald Trump's executive order curbing immigration in a statement Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Ascribe to the Lord the glory due his name; worship the Lord in the splendor of holiness.”
  
 –Psalm 29:2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexandre Bissonnette acted as a "lone wolf," said Canadian Public Safety Minister Ralph Goodale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The suspect in a shooting at a Quebec City mosque on Sunday that left 6 ppl dead was charged Monday with six counts of first-degree murder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President D Trump Will Announce Supreme Court Nominee Tuesday: “I’ve Made My Decision” https://t.co/OPGbWseXV7 A “truly great Justice.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump fired acting Attorney General Sally Yates for “refusing to enforce a legal order designed to protect the citizens of the US"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mosul: IS threatens to kill 350,000 children trapped in city if they try to leave https://t.co/CrqkvGSfMX via @yahooNewsUK May God intervene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We give due thanks to thee Almighty God for the gift of life and this Tuesday the 31st January, 2017.Bless our work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump Shows Off $5,000 Dress in Midst of Immigration Chaos ... Internet Reacts https://t.co/jvzLDzLmau Fruit falls near the tree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Breathe in I smile, breathe out I calm my body. Dwelling in the present moment, it is a wonderful moment."
 
 ~Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the rookie federal judge who halted Trump's refugee deportations — to save a Syrian https://t.co/HJ2nu32Y5r Ann M. Donnelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss Kenya kicked out of Miss Universe after drawing blank Trump question -VIDEO https://t.co/VK4RsRAiVv via @Nairobi_News Yes, unfairly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Trump reaches majority disapproval in eight days https://t.co/qzmqegfqFI A high 51% on Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss France crowned Miss Universe in the Philippines - https://t.co/A4byzrlqbq - @washtimes Iris Mittenaere-dentist student]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mohamed Abrini in France for questioning over Paris and Brussels terrorist attacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We pray for the best. https://t.co/D2st3RBWPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just dividing the opposition in favor of JUBILEE https://t.co/jTCIWzGtB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James 4:15- Instead you ought to say, “If the Lord wills, we shall live and do this or that.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proverbs 27:1
Do not boast about tomorrow,
For you do not know what a day may bring forth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proverbs 19:1
  Better is the poor who walks in his integrity
Than one who is perverse in his lips, and is a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proverbs 29:1
 He who is often rebuked, and hardens his neck,
Will suddenly be destroyed, and that without remedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt 6: 34 -Therefore do not worry about tomorrow, for tomorrow will worry about its own things. Sufficient for the day is its own trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then Philip opened his mouth and, beginning with this scripture passage, he proclaimed Jesus to him.
             
             Acts  8:35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No good; not expected from the US for certain. https://t.co/RTjA846a6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidero, Kenneth tear each other apart in church https://t.co/d6E7j00tXT via @Nairobi_News Right debate at the wrong place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many are the plans in a man's heart, but it is the LORD's purpose that prevails.  — Proverbs 19:21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Will Make You Cringe! One Of The Weirdest Last Meal Requests Ever! https://t.co/epbkCBHXSt via @SATIXFACTION 8yo for last meal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's first major test is travel ban uproar https://t.co/VPMRZ9YARG Started on the wrong foot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 narrate their ordeal in collapsed mine https://t.co/nCMrZUPBda via @TheCitizenTZ We rejoice and congratulate the rescuers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your best is ALWAYS good enough.
 After you have truly done your best,
 release your attachment to the outcome.
 - Jonathan Lockwood Huie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are attached to what you attack.
 - Robert Shea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2- Work so done is a means to the end, and God is the end.
 - Ramakrishna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2- To work without attachment is to work without the expectation
 of reward or fear of any punishment in this world or the next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attachment is the great fabricator of illusions;
 reality can be attained only by someone who is detached.
 - Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is non-attachment to results;
doing ur best at the moment,
 &amp; letting the results take care of themselves
 J.Walters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people are dead after a shooting at a mosque in Quebec City, police say. 8 people were injured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zambian women's day off for periods stokes debate https://t.co/uGehmqBce5 via @FRANCE24 And you want ur country to develop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mombasa Governor Ali Hassan Joho dealt a big blow politically https://t.co/qWYcwi9Gdq via @UreportKe Defected to Jubilee-makes 2 in Mombasa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No place is safe enough now! https://t.co/0t6NYZyVY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inhumanity at its acme. https://t.co/0nTwjNJmOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Always forgive your enemies - nothing annoys them so much."
 
 -- Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benoît Hamon wins French left-wing presidential primary against Manuel Valls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prez Donald Trump insisted on Sunday that  travel ban on certain  Muslim-majority nations would protect the United States from  terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Oh give thanks to the Lord, for he is good, for his steadfast love endures forever!”
  
 –Psalm 107:1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Pro-life quotes from people you wouldn’t expect @AleteiaEn https://t.co/LJTFXHFeNs An  ‘unborn child’ is a real one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has been a fatal shooting at a mosque in Quebec City, police say. Police would not confirm the number of dead or injured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thank thee Almighty God and Father for the gift of life and this Monday the 30th January, the 5th Week of the Year 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insulting anyone is not positive anyway. https://t.co/fz9Zpgrro2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whither USA? https://t.co/D69tJqvEUK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>