<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that my #boringfootballtweets are always wise and prophetic https://t.co/WvR7TDKMHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix recommendation: Omar is an entertaining Palestinian thriller with a superbly abrupt ending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this tweet remains very relevant tbf https://t.co/GQLlF8ui5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDunt Confused by the implication that Watership Down is a quaint nostalgia-fest when it's essentially rabbit-based survival horror]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rg_wilkinson yes, one or both of those things might help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and just living in a lovely bubble where there are no politics whatsoever. this would probably make me feel less stressed and anxious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just scroll through twitter each day feeling more and more stressed. considering banning myself from twitter and news sites for a while...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the most stressful thing is *i would really like to do something about this*, but there's seemingly nothing i can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the last thing on anyone's mind is global warning, despite effective action on it needing to happen right now. Or yesterday, ideally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, our Thatcherite PM is angling to sell off the NHS, acceding to racists and kowtowing to despots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really horrified by what Trump's doing. I think it's fair and accurate at this point to call him a fascist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if anyone has already mentioned this but everything is well and truly going to shit, politics-wise, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always good to get an insight into the nuances of the creative process https://t.co/GtsMhCz6BH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really good article which I recommend, as someone who retweeted the cartoon without much reflection https://t.co/G2jv5oBpBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently feeling nausea rather than the recent feverishness. This cold/flu/whatever has been a real rollercoaster of shittiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like that Chuck Tingle now gets to put 'Hugo nominated author' on all his books https://t.co/maM5BKlcMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week I have mostly been listening to 2007's Prinzhorn Dance School, authors of indie music's most boring lyrics https://t.co/6Nkkr8sv4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presumably it was guilty of actually having some character and atmosphere, which is damaging to their carefully-cultivated image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brains are so useless that they've decided to close down their only good pub. A pub which is always rammed. Genius.… https://t.co/feLX37H0eB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giroud just scored the best goal of 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't say they weren't warned https://t.co/cf3NE5CQJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[should have been sent off too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Odie1892 I agree, except he's now 23 and if he doesn't improve his decision making this season I don't think he ever will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boringfootballtweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People still rate him because of his technical ability, but that's no good if you have the footballing brain of a backwards child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I watch him, Barkley looks like this is his first time on a football pitch and he's desperately trying to work out what's expected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton that wouldn't surprise me. Maybe with restored scenes giving some degree of depth to the supporting characters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton The uncanny valley CGI really took me out of the scenes, surprised it didn't get cut. Hope 2036 special edition will fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Poioumena obviously trying to start a nuclear war is really stupid in any case...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Trump actually trying to start a nuclear war? Has he calculated that it's good for business or something? Or is he just really stupid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An actual fascist replied to my last tweet. My confusion at the BBC news coverage doesn't mean I sympathise with your love of strongmen mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsurprised by HMP Birmingham riots. Not going to expand on that via social media though. Dunno why BBC aren't covering it on their website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri I found it implausible that that would cause an immediate complete reversal of anybody's values. That's not how people work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri i was just using a score as shorthand for my feelings. I do like the signature one life left 7/10 for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri I did weirdly quite enjoy a lot of it despite this tbf. Battle scenes were great. So maybe 5/10 is a bit harsh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri with other characters, like Jin + Cassius, their motivations do a 180 flip halfway through so they don't make sense as people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri I feel like we get a sense of what sort of person Han is. With some of the main characters in rogue one there's just...nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri I dunno, maybe. What would prior knowledge have helped with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiceroTweets Fair point, usually there's some good lines and you care a bit about some of the characters though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on the plus side, you do feel like you're in the star wars universe (despite it being tonally darker) - not a marvel movie set in space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RogueOne - final third was good, the droid was pretty funny. Zero characterisation, shoddy dialogue, kind of nonsensical in places. 5/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still think Man City will win this. This tweet is going to look pretty damn prescient when they're 4-2 up after 84 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton May, like Cameron, will appreciate having someone who will blindly push through unpopular 'reforms' in spite of any evidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton Grayling's blind loyalty to his bosses and inability to form independent thoughts means he's pretty indestructable IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahaha, I've had this song in my head for the whole season but wasn't expecting this to happen (cc @rg_wilkinson ) https://t.co/1SrvByJ1Fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to decide which Anohni tracks to put on my 'best of year' playlist on spotify; maybe just the whole album?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno why anyone's confused about #westworld when it's obvious there are *counts on fingers* ...7...timelines...and a half. 7 and a half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha, Rorty suddenly becoming really trendy is such a bizarre footnote to Trump's election. Guardian and NYT have articles about him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can grow your own whey (grow your own whey)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curiously inefficient hand dryers in public toilets - what's up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this song a lot even though it features the lyric 'politics - what's up with that?'

https://t.co/4VklPRaghq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will clearly be a Westworld hidden roles board game and it will almost certainly be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton agree, arrival's really good - I'm pretty optimistic about the new blade runner now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went to see the excellent Arrival. By the same guy who directed Sicario and is doing the new Blade Runner, which I'm now excited about!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking hell https://t.co/T9x9YvLYWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Rorty ever been wrong about anything? https://t.co/b4RPfuWxkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning and turning in the widening gyre #TrumpPresident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone seems weirdly optimistic considering that we have no actual results at this point. Think Trump has a good chance, myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomburplebri seen this? https://t.co/vgq5eLToNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BnnnyC If football games accurately modeled player ability then Cherno Samba would have won the Champions League f… https://t.co/WjFZQjoPmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE PEOPLE OF "GREAT BRITAIN " HAVE MADE THERE DEMOCRATIC DESCION https://t.co/3odoXYORlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This'll be status quo for next 10-15 years at least. If Trump doesn't win, then nationalist candidate will beat Clinton next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[symptom of collapse of neo-liberal consensus into a large nationalist movement and a smaller socialist/left one, driven by economic fears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda goes without saying that poppy obsession is a product of the same populist nationalism which has bred Trump, Brexit post-credit crunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate to say I told you sooooo https://t.co/ImFFXLGrui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seriously, you'd get an extra lie-in and to stay up late every day, it'd be brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting the clocks back an hour is great, we should do it every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah right, it's 00:20 because I've now spend 45 minutes listening to Kool AD's Dum Diary on repeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My name is Camilla and I have a strong opinion about a Ken Loach film. I -"

"You didn't like it?"

"How did you KNOW?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeKidneysMoj perhaps the lead character should be Fiona Apple. Fiona Apple &amp; her talking dog Custard, fighting crime. I'd watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cop show idea: Apple P.I. - can this small-town American girl solve the string of grisly murders which etc etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@everycolorbot is on fire today https://t.co/o6utvt8SiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump candidacy is a useful 'are you unconsciously a fascist' test. Have you always had a bit of a thing for strongmen? Into scapegoating?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps he realises that it's a symbol of his transformation into an emblem of an ossifying establishment which younger people oppose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Him ignoring it is pretty funny, mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dylan getting a Nobel prize is really the apogee of baby-boomer domination of culture &amp; politics, a high-water mark before they ebb away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I'm saying is, it's a shit but psychologically revealing insult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helps squash everything to fit your worldview that we are all secretly self-interested &amp; don't give a shit about anyone else, reinforcing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychologically handy to use 'virtue signaling' to dismiss people who care about others &amp; so feel better about your own lack of empathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Laughing stock of Europe' update https://t.co/wO9vt09T9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @DPD_UK , I'd like to complain about a driver and arrange delivery to a pickup shop please. Your system's not letting me do either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The In Rainbows bonus disc is better than their last two studio albums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched Victoria on netflix last night. Two-hour crime drama with no cuts - it's all one single tracking shot! Not perfect but v impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton I just voted for the wrong option by accident, it's like Brexit all over again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Odie1892 yeah, we had a great transfer window - rafa's brought in some real quality like ritchie and gayle and they're working hard too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Odie1892 I think you'll finish in the top four - it's a bit like watching keegan's newcastle, some great attacking play, wobbly defence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Odie1892 Fair point, but he did spend most of this afternoon hitting passes out for goal kicks. Your lot looked good though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hope the 'drinkwater for england' idiots are watching this. i'd look international quality if i was playing next to kante.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[forgot pogba was on the pitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[such a good finish by de bruyne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSBurton Yeah, I watched that recently and thought it was very well executed (as it were)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why #THFC have paid £30 million for Sissoko when better options were available, such as setting fire to the money. #NUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Brom vs Middlesbrough. McClean vs Gibson.The battle for 14th vs the trickling sands of your life. Obvious choice of live game really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched The Lobster, wonderful - by the people behind Dogtooth, one of my favourite films. I should track down all their stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iheanacho will be the best striker in the world one day. Continual goal-threat whenever he comes on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_self so is Thus Spoke Zarathustra non-fiction? Plato's republic? Why? The fiction/non-fiction line is surely culturally determined?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, by @Jam_sponge on No Man's Sky, is actually one of the best bits of critical engagement with a game I've seen https://t.co/XETMd5BqUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(which sounds like I'm distancing myself from this stuff, but I still fucking love it) https://t.co/qdXlom7krR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight in youtube rabbit-holes: uber-camp german electroclash which I was really into circa 2002 https://t.co/ukviSwQjmq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>