<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. https://t.co/HicN6SLHoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I voted for this photo @viewbug https://t.co/FN7bMMkJKi #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start work at 2:30pm this afternoon.  It's 8:50 AM now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubPolitics @NewshubNZ thank fucken God but that took 4 fucken days to clear up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I will be good for him https://t.co/0VydHQfBrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is right though the liquid law changed and buggered it up. Also changing the date buggered it up also https://t.co/NSzsUICgFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaBush some of my best friends are Muslim. In both the states and the uk and I'm worried for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubFeatures @NewshubNZ @realDonaldTrump @reporter__ryan it's breaking the first amendment though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JannickesArt he already has broken the first amendment.  It's my understanding that you aren't supposed to touch the first 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warrenleightTV although a lot of people wonder how boris made minister of security]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warrenleightTV that woman in red is a bloody legend. U know every country of the top 5 (spy 4USA) know passport entry apart from NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I received 2 peer recognitions @Viewbug https://t.co/lYvkoeurFC #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighboNZ fingers crossed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinGFox here they condemn what their American counterpart are doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Dire Straits - Sultans Of Swing https://t.co/o7pPMfBelj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Jason Aldean https://t.co/YB9OkWLQ5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/WrA3Zxj5Om Jason Aldean - Tattoos on This Town]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Models join NYC demonstrators in #NoBanNoWall march https://t.co/sBHR90cfMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life imitates art as Pork Pie boards Interislander  https://t.co/gxf884b7ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets go @AFCWimbledon &amp; @ChelseaFC  today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole shit. tomorrow is the 1st of Feb. first day of most of NZ primary schools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes @DebraMessing yet NZ is one of the 5 spy countries that works with USA and we havent heard shit from trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryJane1080 it's like a face mask that peals off when it dries. and a waste of money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just made a $1 multi with @bet365 which has a return of $75,000. Please please please all games in EPL &amp; ECL come in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sassylibrarian1 I know when Americans are asleep because my trump tweets go quiet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[her people said it and its not even 6 months later an its coming true https://t.co/mCg2FHhtvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just had something sell on @TradeMe for 5 times the reserve price]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Topic: The great Jane Elliot https://t.co/xEuW0vsE9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've signed the open letter in support Andrew Little's Healthy Homes Bill. Will you? https://t.co/Y8sTUnDOol via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition to John Key and Bill English: Don't veto PPL! https://t.co/KHt8c3ufxp via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask PM Bill English to tell President Trump to end Muslim Ban. Sign the petition: https://t.co/OHKgvFr2Xz via @nzlabour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S&gt;A citizens need to watch this video on racism https://t.co/ItUl3zp1M5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaBush i think people in the usa need to watch this  https://t.co/ItUl3zp1M5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warrenleightTV i think people in the states need to listen to Jane Elliot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/pSJvbsQs0f Jane Elliott says that all white people are racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/Xh1nuzjqbv Anti-Racism Activist "Jane Elliott" Speaks On The Psychology Of Racism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Racism Activist "Jane Elliott" Speaks On The Psychology Of Racism! https://t.co/UkdShQbLVV via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting AG after she declines to defend travel ban @CNNPolitics https://t.co/CJ3kPd6IC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Smalley: Child poverty is real https://t.co/du1tYPQ1KY via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I  joined the Mountain Shapes Photo Contest on ViewBug. https://t.co/tmvN8VCrTt #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svuceline I love this guy better than boris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyallbaynz just got home and up Kingston it's just over 22C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svuceline that was worded wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svuceline not when the mayor is Muslim himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Temps yay. @lyallbaynz is 21C with a slight sea breeze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New control tower going up @ Wellington International Airport https://t.co/m9Hv94vw9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[heading out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peston @ScoopNZ great to hear coz only valid passport i have is a uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @bigreunionitv https://t.co/0gAw8Vvu8G B*WITCHED SING 'C'EST LA VIE' LIVE - THE BIG REUNION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: B*Witched v S Club 7 https://t.co/iIrl4jnLzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: BoyZone v Westlife https://t.co/A6ZNjX56Gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: David Bowie https://t.co/w5vEek0lbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Dropkick Murphys https://t.co/iMGWTvRGpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Max Richter https://t.co/4uCwlNTGWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Winston Surfshirt https://t.co/2z6SVmERgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it:         Kehlani https://t.co/xRtUTiFJX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: JapanDriods https://t.co/wgLoEtqH6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ban strands American basketball players in Dubai https://t.co/cqxSLAVD0g via @SInow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmurraypolitics @KevinGFox it's called COPY &amp; Paste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FIFAcom  there is no way those players should have been playing in 38 degree heat. it was not 28 degrees as @ffa s… https://t.co/GBd14YAiQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['How hot does it have to be?': Wellington Phoenix at odds with FFA about Adelaide boiler https://t.co/NCIE53rFsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US corporations fight back over Trump's travel ban https://t.co/WxAuV5ZIBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English expected to announce election date https://t.co/oPlhbxng9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's right https://t.co/aPOviex1ix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL that is one big MF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: NFL v NRL https://t.co/G2aEPKtkRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: NKOTB v Backstreet Boys https://t.co/XUsBiOGGrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: NFL v NRL https://t.co/R0G0VCy9D4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Battle: NKOTB v Backstreet Boys https://t.co/CDxCyzM30u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Wellington Phoenix FC https://t.co/UDoCKoMob3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: NewCastle Jets FC https://t.co/VDzIfSsR6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Adelaide United Fc https://t.co/J4g9klGFmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Wellington Phoenix FC https://t.co/bH15oj8XRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Perth Glory FC https://t.co/shbCL4lC6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Melbourne City (Melbourne Heart) https://t.co/HqQd8JWjrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Melbourne Victory https://t.co/JauxnayJLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: CCM https://t.co/hiLec6hFzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Brisbane Roar https://t.co/3jwnYQniS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Sydney FC https://t.co/EFRKJifk8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: WSW https://t.co/FpDD3RWNj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Miami MLS https://t.co/wHDLMVYGWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Minnesota united FC https://t.co/PFRhR8IQFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Los Angeles FC https://t.co/5Y1unoy8mJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Chivas USA https://t.co/oTOu3iGJdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Atlanta United FC https://t.co/hTEkb4xXrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Philadelphia Union https://t.co/omRyC0lF8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: San jose Earthquakes https://t.co/c2gygWEmze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Chicago fire fc https://t.co/QF1TfMOcEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: FC Dallas https://t.co/TwZXfTMkRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: New England Revolution https://t.co/PWeEuguduo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Colorado rapids https://t.co/9Jrbbq6Fsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Houston dynimo https://t.co/bQkg40Jzcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Real Salt lake  https://t.co/okxjZO9QWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Columbus crew https://t.co/1qW8GRlcBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Sporting Kansas city https://t.co/SMRctHn2HP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Montreal Impact https://t.co/9JEUIYoUO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Portland timbers https://t.co/ZgIMEL2zGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Orlando city FC https://t.co/0vHxJBu66d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: DC united https://t.co/6eSEtWh5eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Thumb it: Toronto FC https://t.co/483EcgNn50]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>