<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mundine already in the running for cheap Shot Dog act of the Year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it odd that a cat goes to the litter tray when you go to the toilet at the same time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Women's AFL happening after what has been a long time in the making]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPomfret Serves are getting hammered which is typical from Nintendo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty cool concert — watching Ziltoid Live at the Royal Albert Hall (Devin Townsend)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinest @DemonicDragon @VOOK64 No but I know it's likely happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DemonicDragon @VOOK64 Hmm alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 Has this been confirmed by EB Games or other people online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about Trump not liking Turnbull, thats why we have a Australian Ambassador to the USA and that is Joe Hockey ... well shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Cupcakes let's not get carried away here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZhugeEX That's a question no one knows the answer to - much like the "What gameplay experiences can we do with the Gamepad??"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMerrick @pokejungle Massive numbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 Headline "Nintendo Switch more conformable in your hands than a MacBook"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch – What Different Console Owners will be thinking https://t.co/xEI8GIlMwG https://t.co/Q83hELab36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been thinking of doing some sort of podcast to host on my web site. Maybe something to do with writing or AFL... https://t.co/v7zYiXZ0Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing you do with your education is to share it. Use it as a light to be a bullshit detector towards the... https://t.co/NdljpsEQ0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to see Fed or Nadal win it but going for Nadal, he's lost three Aust Open Finals and that was painful to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed VS Nadal Final - Its happening!!! — feeling excited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryGolledge or the 90's girl band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 it's a great game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good I have been paid and time to get cat food and ignore my empty fridge for now lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like work will be paying me late due to the public holiday tomorrow. I am furious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigHailFan @jimmygangster95 the breakdown is one in six women (1,479,900) and one in 20 men (448,000)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoTalksGames They are just not very good games to launch a new console from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theSupremeRk9s Pokemon Stars: The Last Pokemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 People want the party but not Shorten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSD_Gaming @THEREALRTU @AshleyJudd @TEDTalks true but Men are not dying unlike women with abuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEREALRTU @AshleyJudd @TEDTalks But far more women get abused and even more in real life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nibellion and looks like the game has had a patch update too - 1.0.2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Cupcakes I see it happening for other games like Mario Party, Trnnis etc. Gonna be good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Cupcakes no one has really called him out on it. He's dead quiet about the leaks he made. Thought about making a video...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtJamz I don't even look at reviews much anymore. You can judge Games yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoTalksGames does it matter how it looks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brent_rc @NintendoAUNZ No online on the go...there's no 4G to it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoNintendoTweet and they want us to pay for this service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveGibbonsXMP @SmartState1 almost impossible to be over educated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZhugeEX The Wii U sold more than Ouya....kinda makes me feel better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's harder than it looks https://t.co/udz0UqAQqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So looks like Flipside has been Sold to the Revolution CD mob. Just wonderful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His tune has changed a lot - he is a smart guy... gonna be a fun four years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awatson_88 @NintendoDads that baby is struggling to see the gameplay :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Malcolm Turnbull needs to be more like Malcolm Tucker to have more control over his MP's and have the... https://t.co/ZmfqNoBNyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 voting system as flawed as the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nanashrew @TheBY2K not really big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people ask me awdward questions like "how's your family" or "how are your parents" I'm going to pretend I... https://t.co/V6ztxXwQIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoNintendoTweet @Gnarsie slow news day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBY2K there's a hive mind on every forum board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEREALRTU @lukerosscooper you should a update vid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on Super Smash Bros 3DS https://t.co/8vEH8nb9Fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion Pieces makes a Return to ChrisTicehurst.me https://t.co/ZGVZACsC6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's true and Greg Hunt takes over the Health portfolio - if you want a preview of his handy work just check... https://t.co/FGZ8htYFE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scottyabody11 @YouNow @mikeininms helps when you buy your way to No.1 for you lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBY2K ah already played hat demo last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pokejungle sounds very salty to me this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nibellion I thought Sony wouldn't be worried about Nintendo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shall be watching — excited for the Australian Open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wario64 so I can fit like 15 Zelda games on it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheesemeister3k or 130 in Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toadsanime @shancake_ @DaxHalo It's just Wifi. Who wants to pay online service fees and 4G on top of that - hard sell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thafer_alfalah @LaurakBuzz No bundle. Reggae explained they wanted a cheaper price for the Switch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMerrick what's the areas that non core gamers are liking in the Switch u been hearing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dyldo77 @LaurakBuzz it's like a 5 sec job to switch over carts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBenBonus Not that I know of. There should be cheaper options towards launch period for charging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBenBonus @SpawnWaveMedia @LaurakBuzz It should, just remember about watts power and maybe overloading the Switch. Typical third party warn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBY2K Laura was right on hardware but all wrong on software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Variety Show Ep 2 https://t.co/OthZqXReRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling and chat https://t.co/HsnA401CiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 Joy Con feels good in the hands?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressStartAU "isn't it so cool!" Docks in and dock out console repeatedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THEREALRTU @ShadyJay1908 it's similar to the 3DS release window. Gonna give it time to warm up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chat, Chill and Video Games https://t.co/pRVsBd0QmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NintenDaan How does the weight of the Switch as a handheld like compared to 3DS, DS etc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch Reaction and Thoughts https://t.co/dDmkmQAt4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NintendoAUNZ It's going to be tough sell PR team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the first two big games for the Switch you can buy for the Wii U and online is free. Just stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMerrick Launch day is weak. Switch will be waiting on Mario Kart in April]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomphillipsEG $470 Aus dollars for console and $120 for Pro controller - fun times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz keep it professional with the wording.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz All in all you got it half right and half wrong. Not bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 the reason for Mario Kart 8 Deluxe in April?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I survived the presentation and a bunch of videos uploaded - I can rest....I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🔴 LIVE on @YouNow - https://t.co/Ap8PKxvGN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Whisk I think any cat smaller than him or under 7kg is underweight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VOOK64 @JoeMerrick @ArcadeGirl64 Should called it Mario Kart and Friends and slap Pikachu, Splatoon, Samus etc in. Picture the tracks made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Woddee All fixed now. Can't believe that option was off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Woddee weird, I'll fix it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Woddee @DYoshiiTV @Twitch_ANZ Send me a DM because my ideas page is empty after many times of trying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Woddee @DYoshiiTV @Twitch_ANZ I have tried with 0.800kb of upload for mainly Nintendo games and it just dies. Maybe 240p is ok lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DYoshiiTV @Twitch_ANZ So how do you stream with that connection? Witchcraft? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DYoshiiTV @Twitch_ANZ If only more people had the NBN...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vooksdotnet There better be enough copies of this game :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ipA0sZyxj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late Night Chat https://t.co/xqyXgO0i6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmberEmotions @andymac_89 @LaurakBuzz I personally don't care what background they have. I don't treat people differently based on gender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NinImpactGaming @nintyninjanews yeah Il do a video on it soon tonight]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>