<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Road Trip Rules: Why We Travel With a Microwave https://t.co/qXkIEIbjs4 https://t.co/KBXfNLDIxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 Weird and Interesting Facts About Ecuador (That You Might Not Know) https://t.co/fmaiR2z4i5 via @BryanMHaines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@czechpragueout thanks for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@St3V3nC14rK what are you studying? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World's Top Destinations For a Fabulous Honeymoon https://t.co/qFRgmEVM4R https://t.co/imDAI1op6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rovaplatforms thanks for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FindingBeyond thanks for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePhotoTrekker thanks for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stagetecture thanks for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hippie_InHeels thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WirelessTopNews thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xwallaceny thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDUtraveler thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KBunn thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017: The Journey Ahead https://t.co/FdfKLgCjaw via @journeycount]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wat Phra That Doi Suthep https://t.co/PYCVe9rLVM via @myVideoMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Summer Travel Reading List: 10 Travel Books You Should Have on Your Shelves https://t.co/quMLTiDvsU https://t.co/ChznlFeC3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tongabezi: A Stay to Remember at One of the Best Lodges in the World https://t.co/K0IvPyqhLG via @TheWorldPursuit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat Local in Tulum - A Guide to Eating Locally in the Mexican Riviera https://t.co/2iYIen5oOC via @PursuitAdventur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Epic Outdoor Adventures in Belize https://t.co/DsZrg88J60 https://t.co/mxL6tuHPey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etihad Widens Reach in East Africa With New Agreement https://t.co/dfRiIf1pG2 via @iamwaleadelani]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Be a Spontaneous Traveler https://t.co/jnJQUNNMwX  #NGTRadar #lp @Skyscanner @flexiroam https://t.co/4dKM4mFTIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring Traveler Interview With Trisha Velarmino: The Right Time to Travel is NOW! https://t.co/jjIxP5tI97 https://t.co/s93LGuzMCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review: Air France Business Class From Lagos to London https://t.co/aFG6F0AE7G via @ZeeGoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why You Should Visit Umbria In Italy https://t.co/v8dyTK57Rx https://t.co/AxonrDgOPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magical Musts for Those Headed to the Wizarding World of Harry Potter in Orlando https://t.co/LwbOtpXQpZ via @Hannahlogan21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budva The Disappointing Jewel of Montenegro https://t.co/urGLSpp0i7 via @totraveltoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Book the Cheapest Flights in 2017 (Based on Recent Travel Trends) https://t.co/oGyyuCmyAq https://t.co/8oZ7FETh4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Travel Photography Tips for the Postcard Perfect Shot https://t.co/rSwTYQkNJH via @RyanBiddulph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Things To Do In Bogota https://t.co/FcOIhonY52 https://t.co/2T9M1dFPdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WIN a Trip to Iceland from @OutdoorFamMag &amp; @TravelEastIce! #OutdoorFamilies #OutFam #TMOM https://t.co/prc2Pw5Lhk via @jen_fontaine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Convert Your Leftover Travel Money into Actual Cash https://t.co/yZKdodxPng https://t.co/DFDhUMCqGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Road Trip on the Algarve Coast, Portugal https://t.co/HwJrzPz8EH via @migratingmiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Here: Four Seasons Resort Orlando at Walt Disney World Resort https://t.co/XlD7RRt6zc via @lajollamom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel in Tanzania: Reflections of a Serengeti Safari https://t.co/zJ1hbitJTb via @L_e_a_h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's More to Argentine Cuisine Than Beef and Malbec Wines https://t.co/1vxRz9OjnX https://t.co/zadseyy7A5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get behind the hottest new app on the travel scene: #GPSmyCity is turning your mobile into a GPS powered tour guide… https://t.co/mX3X8pM5PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intriguing Food Stalls of Jemaa el Fna, Marrakesh https://t.co/X0Wlk8oRef via @corinnevail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you've ever dreamed of will often show up in different packaging than you were envisioning. - Brenden Dilley #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find cheap flights for weekend getaways: Download the @SkyscannerAUS app for free here: https://t.co/CP1TsbFw6M https://t.co/tnELcwl5Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road Trip Rules: The Importance of Not Overloading Your Vehicle. https://t.co/KIvXLdfqIx https://t.co/JKq8h2zkHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bare Naked Nomad: Ultimate Guide To Traveling The World (Book Review) https://t.co/3zTtKwI4fu via @ReesesRoadLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Disney Games and Activities for Kids on a Disney Road Trip https://t.co/FCv5ZMirTK via @MeaganWristen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Beaches in Gold Coast Australia https://t.co/aSygKJTaQR https://t.co/jnBvIaUx58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Get A Cambodia Tourist e-Visa https://t.co/ApLXgam7YG via @familiesgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cycling the Globe with Thomas Andersen: Tips For Cycling Around the World! https://t.co/gtagO0jpm5 https://t.co/lUIg7QL75S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Need to Know Before Visiting the Dominican Republic https://t.co/HVMDLaqbCK via @WanderingEds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canoeing Around the Islands of Phang Nga Bay Thailand https://t.co/8wxQXFiaQ3 https://t.co/hAtgcrt2mN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Things To Do In Jamaica: An Ecotourism Guide https://t.co/CpW3oIFPP2 via @GreenGlobalTrvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning West Coast Of Ireland - The Wild Atlantic Way https://t.co/vbSDgAf4d4 via @touristmtravel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Striking Sea of Red at Tower of London https://t.co/2bepHqGWxr https://t.co/XLicA1KDzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring the Wonders of Texas National Parks (No Deserts or Tumbleweeds, We Promise) https://t.co/yMYpPQmEGv @travelingmoms #Texastodo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Cowboy-Inspired Adventures in Arlington https://t.co/JDlxzZSgvC via @AdventureHan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Your Inner Adrenaline Junkie: 7 Extreme Adventures in the Philippines https://t.co/r374UNt6Dv https://t.co/9TXh5KDEcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get conned into paying too much for flights!! Download the free @SkyscannerAUS app for cheapest deals ----&gt;… https://t.co/Tf0Pg1dAVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Interview With a Traveling Rock Star. Mike Mentz on Life on the Road. https://t.co/dv2jiS2rXM https://t.co/S9FvF4ZWTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to shoot the Northern Lights in #Iceland #photography https://t.co/b4yChe4Ev4 via @GoAwesomePlaces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visit to the Mid-Dnipro Museum of Folk Architecture &amp; Life near #Kiev in #Ukraine #travel https://t.co/GTYc2kJFCC via @KathmanduBeyond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Get the Most Out of Solo Travel https://t.co/cr9kFWrj1S https://t.co/7vusIR7aqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaveSippy thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craw8600 thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@locked2target thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExpatGenius thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aviationadllxx thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ptr thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prettywildw0rld thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spicemylife1 thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1goatroti thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globallynow thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonlewis thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Athreeeighty thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstLeap_China thank-you for sharing! Hope you're having a fabulous start to the week :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need travel inspiration? Use the @SkyscannerAUS app to find cheap flight prices all around the world. Free download… https://t.co/6xvPzYUmtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Travel More https://t.co/vt3r8YBkPM via @grrrltraveler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shamu411 thankyou! Hope you have the chance to jump into travel soon too! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland on a Budget: How to Save Up To $1,000 in Dublin https://t.co/zuaTBw2hHY https://t.co/sn5k0m039K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Sky Tower Review - How to Enjoy an Amazing Skyline? https://t.co/7E6dysWdyw via @ABritSoutherner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Essential Things You Need to Do Before You Travel https://t.co/2VeK5KeO5c https://t.co/nK8IEeqfHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Of Wales - The Perfect UK Road Trip https://t.co/b2uA5du2OK via @Abrokenbackpack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting Activities in Branson for Those Who Don’t Do Theater https://t.co/UQp4aPhOV3 https://t.co/eFg4kXAcHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo: A Stunning Easter Island Sunset https://t.co/pVQNL9kvj3 https://t.co/RLTSjY4ns3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panoramic Himachal Pradesh- Land Of Gods (Dev Boomi) https://t.co/OLRqURh91i via @smallbudgetbigt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the character of someone is not clear to you, look at their friends. - Unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way we read travel articles is about to change! #GPSmyCity is turning your mobile into a GPS powered tour guide… https://t.co/f9MHNHtJ02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Things to Do in Portugal This Summer for Digital Nomads and Startups https://t.co/LcqOZyeDew https://t.co/jznpBItKWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 Wine Dinner Series at Waterline - Balboa Bay Resort https://t.co/iQG2ATWtQl via @shescookin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majorca Blends Old and New https://t.co/ZBaymY2loE via @Travel_Explore1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Travel Accessories You Need To Be Prepared For Anything https://t.co/N6TKgwMHfe https://t.co/Oj97eX5pl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have the @SkyscannerAUS app? We use it for the cheapest flights, hotels &amp; car hire deals. Download free:… https://t.co/ELT1V8eEHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things to do in Anaheim Beyond Disneyland https://t.co/hGlrDFSeoQ via @piggybackrideAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Much to Tip Valet Parking in the United States https://t.co/MEqAzESkxH https://t.co/H8G5mdOUEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffs Harbour to Brisbane: The Perfect Travel Itinerary https://t.co/ZRgq0HGcuP via @bigwsmallp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting the Most Famous Mosque in China; Dongguan Great Mosque, Xining https://t.co/J0G6qtbCoH https://t.co/p1tCpARiw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where To Stay In Waimea, HI https://t.co/q7HTJKK11y via @SilkeJager]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bali Infographic https://t.co/UgKcFIO1s8 via @Chase_adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel Safety: Why Common Sense is The Best Way to Stay Safe Abroad https://t.co/fbgVNsURQV https://t.co/zqesWY2nDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Classic European Ski Resorts https://t.co/1MCUmzS8yt with @Pearlshare https://t.co/swnj4VT2dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why You Should Drop What You're Doing and Travel to Laos Right Now https://t.co/ywAo8tkjw2 https://t.co/cozOkfojMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerial Photos Of Afghanistan https://t.co/N0Q3FWGYjE via @the_HoliDaze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Complete Guide to Food in Cebu City https://t.co/C7vJKhxtWW via @travelgeekery]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>