<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra enjoy the cooler weather today! Rain with a top of 27 @abccanberra @abcnewsCanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drug-driving charges climb in Canberra as drink-driving falls https://t.co/wJOF4s0HNA via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra you can look forward to a possible shower or two later today, top of 34 degrees @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making #Canberra news the new Chief Justice of High Court Susan Kiefel sworn-in, total fire ban in ACT and school's back! @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those wondering what a severe fire danger warning is: https://t.co/JnNtDENe8h #canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra a total fire ban for ACT region with a severe fire danger warning, a top of 39. Stay cool out there! @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News @ 7 on @abccanberra 2 dead in a Perth plane crash, Mexican Pres cancels meeting with US Pres + recovering from the Tarago fire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra happy Friday! A partly cloudy day with a top of 33. A hot &amp; sunny weekend ahead and then 39 on Monday #hothothot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canberra Theatre Centre deletes social media posts about Aust Day ad with 2 Muslim girls after violent threats. More at 12 @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News @ 7 on @abccanberra British Parli needs to formalise Brexit + Barnaby Joyce suggests Sydney home buyers look to the bush #canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACT could ease ban on ad billboards but @ABarrMLA says no suggestion to turn #canberra into Times Square @JamesFettes @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra How stunning was the sunset last night? Cloud clearing to mostly sunny day, morning drizzle top of 29 @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News @ 7 Trump withdraws from TPP, a Canberra man missing in Blue Mountains &amp; last night's vigil for Bourke St victims @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra love the sound of rain in the morning. Early showers, possible thunderstorm. Another hot day with a top of 35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News @ 7 @abccanberra Melbourne vigil for car rampage victims, ACT ranked 3rd eco in nation + Trump response to protests #canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra a mostly sunny morning, chance of showers and possible arvo thunderstorm, top of 35 @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonLoughridge @abcnewsCanberra I wish! Good pick-up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News @ 7 @abccanberra 3 dead &amp; more missing in Italy avalanche, the race for NSW Premier + ACTGreens stand firm on greyhound racing ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra welcome to Friday! Cloudy with rain clearing during the afternoon, a top of 28 @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More brilliant photos last night from @ellinghausen #canberra https://t.co/Q3oriX1LhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sutton fire has been contained, fire near Tarago still out of control but cooler temperatures expected to help @abcnewsCanberra #Canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra did you enjoy the cool change overnight? It was almost cold outside this morning. A partly cloudy day, top of 28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay tuned to @abccanberra this afternoon for news updates on the #tarago fire from @JulianBAbbott + @jessedorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC's @jessedorsett will give an update on the #tarago #fire in the news at 9 @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuning into @RNBreakfast to hear my former colleague @Simon_Cullen talking #brexit and Theresa May's speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #tarago #fire has grown substantially overnight to 3300 hectares &amp; continues to burn out of control. One property damaged @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #tarago #fire continues to burn out of control. Conditions eased overnight with rain but crews face a hot, dry &amp; windy day ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra the first total fire ban of the summer is in force today, top temp of 37. Keep across the latest on @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to more work from @ellinghausen at the Aust Open https://t.co/IML2D5GocH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust govt officials caught up in Yahoo cyber attack + more on firies accom row at #Canberra airport coming up on @abccanberra at 630]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emails of senior politicians compromised in Yahoo hack https://t.co/8DFFxhtJ93 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra you're heading to a top of 37 degrees, stay cool out there. Tune into @abccanberra for the news at 6am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellmahoney thanks, you're too kind as always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for lowering the desk for me @Dan_Bourchier! https://t.co/47RfhQ68aE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomiwoodley thank you! Good to be back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simon_Cullen @abccanberra Thanks! Must be a good time of the day for you😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Marcus, look forward to being joined by my new 'work husband' in a fortnight https://t.co/DMvcSqisvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #Canberra! New year, new job, new wake-up time. Join me on @abccanberra at 530 for the news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be bringing you the news on @666canberra in the AM in 2017 + welcome @danbourchier to the… https://t.co/3za9p2Eq65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott, Credlin and the abuse of power https://t.co/theK94EqZS via @abcthedrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction to earlier direct quote, Health Dept Sec said looking at "commercial possibilities" around the Medicare payment system #estimates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Dept Sec tells #estimates govt not looking at privatisation of Medicare, instead looking at "commercialisation of payments"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Dept Sec tells #estimates Medicare payments system up to 30 years out of date and needs to be revitalised for modern age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oakes: an adventurous Treasurer combined with a more politically cautious Prime Minister is not a bad combination. https://t.co/VpBQkjz9gF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Profound consequences': Media ownership reform gets messy for Malcolm Turnbull -  https://t.co/zW63d07PeL via smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasurer @ScottMorrisonMP is coming up on AM and will be broadcast on @BreakfastNews #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikcub Can you please follow me so I can DM you? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandiHLogan What's the review you tweet of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fraser: Aust blessed with decent eco policy, but wished we recognised bonanza of mining boom and spent proceeds better #backtofutureday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator @mattjcan asks Treasury Sec John Fraser if he had a time machine what eco policy would he change in last 30 years #backtofutureday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electoral Commissioner tells #senateestimates the AEC could close around 800 polling places around Aust at next election #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comms Minister @SenatorFifield says the Children's e-safety Commissioner could be involved in countering violence extremism @abcnews #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @Clarke_Melissa speaks to western Sydney Labor MP @JasonClareMP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill, @Clarke_Melissa speaks to Canegrowers CEO Dan Galligan about Trans-Pacific Partnership deal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you check this out for us @Simon_Cullen :) https://t.co/2xhnkIzdR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill, @CUhlmann speaks to ANU's Prof. Hugh White about Russian airstrikes over Syria #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want my life to change. You'll have to show me some time.  https://t.co/PGxzx6TEe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica Irvine: The battle for equality starts at home http://t.co/zJD97hFNwc via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill, @CUhlmann speaks to Finance Minister @MathiasCormann about the Turnbull Govt's reform agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill, Political Editor Chris Uhlmann speaks to Health Minister @sussanley about Medicare review #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy Turnbull getting just as much attention as @TurnbullMalcolm while walking down Oxford Street in Sydney with cameras in tow #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone ask Jamie Briggs in QT how he hurt his leg?  https://t.co/0EIRTYrdkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up soon on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill: @GregJennett provides a men's health awareness promo with help from @TurnbullMalcolm + @billshortenmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on Reps antics, Labor tried to suspend proceedings to move the same leadership motion TAbbott moved in June 2013 #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nationals are convening a partyroom meeting now to decide Coalition agreement with Turnbull @abcnews #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Morrison @ScottMorrisonMP is supporting Tony Abbott in the ballot #libspill #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LNP backbencher @Wyatt_MP tells 612 Brisbane he will be voting for @TurnbullMalcolm in leadership spill #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett speaks to @Nick_Xenophon on youth dole wait bill going down and his political party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanSheales You're too kind. Come say hi next time you're in the capital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up now on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett is speaking to Defence Minister Kevin Andrews #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett speaks to Labor's Immigration Spokesman @RichardMarlesMP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett speaks to @philipruddockmp about Syria refugee crisis #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand by for a poll fought overthe ‘yellow peril’ http://t.co/o9VyrX7CzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up now on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett 's interview with Labor Assistant Defence Spokesman @Feeney4Batman #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on Capital Hill
  @ABCNews24 @jamesglenday speaks to Finance Minister @MathiasCormann #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett speaks to @JacquiLambie #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should get out of bed now shouldn't I? https://t.co/ki6l4nKNlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Force: preserving freedom doesn't sit well with governments http://t.co/Op11IRHKYd via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @AntonyGreenABC on a seat called Burt http://t.co/IE52LCXibI #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Independent Senator @Nick_Xenophon is "very wary" of the Govt's changes to Fed enviro laws #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandis: Were there to be a popular vote, plainly it would be a plebiscite #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandis: I can't imagine there being a referendum on this issue (gay marriage), High Court spoken on this.. matter for Parliament #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandis happily responding: High Court dealt with this on ACT Govt #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor now asking AG George Brandis about referendum on gay marriage in Senate QT #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG George Brandis tells Senate QT not at all unusual for eminent Australians to address political events #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG George Brandis tells Senate QT for $80/head in Sydney "wouldn't have been much of a fundraiser" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG George Brandis tells Senate QT function Heydon was going to speak at was public function not political function #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#latertweet OL @billshortenmp visiting pollie hotspot solar farm outside Canberra #auspol http://t.co/Ab8nNRTnp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill, @GregJennett poses the question "what do women want?" to make a political career more attractive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terrimbutler love this song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tuning into @612brisbane to listen to my old colleague @EJGriffiths present Drive. Canberra's loss is Brisbane's gain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @Clarke_Melissa speaks to @kanethornton from the Clean Energy Council #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do I have to read this?" @mjrowland68 on reading the State of Origin score on @BreakfastNews #gomaroons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus @GregJennett speaks to security expert Hugh White on @TurnbullMalcolm's warning not to overestimate the threat of IS 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon on @ABCNews24 Capital Hill: we recap @billshortenmp at the Royal Commission 1/2 #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay tuned to @ABCNews24 Capital Hill for Bill Shorten's pub video &amp; Glenn Lazarus' tackle threat to @TonyAbbottMHR #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @ABCNews24 Capital Hill @GregJennett is speaking to Acting Treasurer @BruceBillsonMP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten outlines dreams for Australia in passionate pub speech http://t.co/2gZ78DxpsX via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjosebishop how lovely, it was a memorable story. You can reach me on mcdonald.susan@abc.net.au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjosebishop yes it was, many years ago now.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>