<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If mass protests grow (as they should) will Trump's generals give him his tanks on the streets of Washington DC?  
https://t.co/4jrJ6H8VHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember using his reports in radio newscasts: Bernard Redmont Dies@98; Told World of North Vietnam Call for Peace https://t.co/JMlfcNpwcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured that ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE film has just been invited to FIGRA festival in France.  https://t.co/hYXGp4vaQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is calling the shots in the White House. That's terrifying | Lawrence Douglas   https://t.co/yfKySdD2pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somali-Canadian forced off flight from Toronto because his plane’s route was through U.S. airspace.    https://t.co/Gl6DYQKFJH via @vicenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The venerable journalist Bill Moyers on "Donald Trump’s Demolition Derby"  https://t.co/ytNikEAY2y via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hedges:"Trump &amp; coterie of billionaires, generals, half-wits, Christian fascists, criminals, racists &amp; deviants..."  https://t.co/YE2t2jwhr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have you no sense of decency, sir? At long last, have you left no sense of decency?" --Joseph Welch to Sen. McCarthy @ 1954 Senate hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolt is a political necessity. It is a moral imperative... a defense of the sacred. It allows us to live in truth.
https://t.co/ESICXS4VCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daviddoel   SuperChannel bought it for Canada. No broadcast date yet.  New screenings at https://t.co/p9FTSQYuIH.  Thanks for ur interest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE at DocPoint Helsinki today is sold out!  Finland's YLE network will broadcast it in few weeks - check their website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F.A.I.R.:  CNN is using Trump's propaganda term "Terror-Prone Countries"    https://t.co/whPtA6yfZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times:  Judge Blocks Trump Order on Refugees Amid Chaos and Outcry Worldwide    https://t.co/3QnpYgbPVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Pence, Pompeo and new Congressional liaison in their pockets, do Koch Brothers hold the lease on White House?
https://t.co/nUSAjrLF33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my 1999 doc on "The Godfather of Hip Hop" I interviewed Trump, who praised Russell Simmons "bigly".  Hard to be… https://t.co/AWMIBI8qzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned    https://t.co/tyOCkm0Drt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianaSCalado  Thanks Adriana -- great meeting you, and see you next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prediction:  Trump's undoing will come from whistleblowers, leakers, and investigative journalists.      https://t.co/N9wOcDTIdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reverse is true in this case.  Question and investigate everything.  The documents are out there.  So are whist… https://t.co/Bb44e25ZVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's get masterpiece "Manufacturing Consent" by Noam Chomsky+Ed Herman up there too.  Buy the re-issue - it resona… https://t.co/SwlK3SjbN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy's a big part of the success of our film "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I.F. Stone… https://t.co/G43IP14yR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Q&amp;A at "All Governments Lie" film in London last night.  Next stop Estonia, then Finland. https://t.co/Vq3YXdhY8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway apparently punched one in the face with closed fists at least 3 times, according to stunned onlooker.  https://t.co/fuOejZRTpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desmond Cole: Toronto Mayor John Tory inherited housing neglect &amp; made it worse with empty rhetoric https://t.co/X5Hkia0wXu via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SubversiveFesti Is there a Subversive Festival in May 2017? If so "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE" (Executive Producer Oliver Stone) is a perfect fit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt is a huge part of success of our film "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE": Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I.F. Stone"… https://t.co/HG370QJUV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Brainwashing of  My Dad" is a must-see film.  Jeff is also in "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the… https://t.co/28aPjsJivh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“racial injustice and economic injustice cannot be solved without a radical redistribution of political and economi… https://t.co/SWaOUs2NNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dear journalists: To cover Trump, remember I.F. Stone"   - Michael Enright's essay on CBC Radio.  https://t.co/HCfE8TbPSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@N6RLS 
Thanks for the retweet!     Fred - VE7NYC in Vancouver BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant!  Gotta laugh to keep from crying https://t.co/xj8M55Wend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems kind of wierd.  Is this normal procedure? https://t.co/lJLySz0MB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of D.C. National Guard to be removed from post in middle of inauguration https://t.co/MtJ3FYk7j4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angering Congress, James Comey won't address Trump-Russia inquiry privately.    https://t.co/luYV9pgBQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many Rust Belt whites voted twice for Obama and then Trump.  Not racists.  Working-class of all races screwed by bo… https://t.co/nqHVclIv70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I.F. Stone" film coming to Kingston, Ont. March 2-5.
 https://t.co/Za8M1ntkhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I. F. Stone:  Catch it Jan. 27th in Seattle! https://t.co/CZdKRdpx8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gen. Petraeus’ expertise in these areas unclear. Ability to peddle influence, however, is known and valued commodity https://t.co/B6PXMBxOEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“how to predict those mysterious conflagrations of the human spirit, to detect the mysterious springs of a social e… https://t.co/f7J2lrO5kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or coming to its senses.  That doesn't look like a 4.5 million dollar house to me. https://t.co/aZRwSyrraA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe do this occasionally with the New York Times too -- when they act (as they often do) as the official organ of… https://t.co/84JNwXdHWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legendary independent journalist I. F. Stone would undoubtedly agree.  He nailed it with his oft-quoted comment… https://t.co/54CJOYCxdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Stone was a good man.  He did much to help our film about the journalistic legacy of his father, I. F. Stone  https://t.co/k8ujkbW1Pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Donald Trump is the latest bobble head doll on the dashboard of real [U.S.] power... ultimate enemies are systemic"
https://t.co/VO1prkNVaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dose of sanity and insight from Tom Engelhardt (who's in my new film "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE")  
 https://t.co/m1O1u7YJ82 via @tomdispatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame Putin instead of "longtime fealty to Wall Street that made it impossible for [Hillary] to ride a populist wave"https://t.co/Rez9HFKjtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let us recall that it was the United States that launched the first cyber attacks – some years ago by the NSA."    https://t.co/nP9ocQiQsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airs tomorrow on Fox. Never thought I'd tweet those words. These are wierd times.
Zero Hedge https://t.co/X8wtspvhX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drexel University suffering from severe irony deficiency. https://t.co/tu5J1TtrI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both parties screwing over working-class people for decades is "deplorable".  Some voted twice for Obama, then Trum… https://t.co/b9S1hZ5B4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Trump/Pence/Flynn treat journalists like Putin does?  Criticizing Russian Airstrikes Lands Blogger in Jail https://t.co/PgwD5Uxb83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing says Christmas like an M16.  Thanks NRA. https://t.co/NhELQF0p3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff at NYC's Cooper Union last night.  Check out the livestream (@JeremyScahill rocks the house at  -1:08:1… https://t.co/JoezdjB2b8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawking:  people can see not just their standard of living, but their ability to earn a living at all, disappearing. https://t.co/CyLblmjpXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance Policies on Slaves: New York Life’s Complicated Past https://t.co/BamfVGbNjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time for nation to come together and congratulate the winner of the 2016 presidential election: Goldman Sachs.  https://t.co/2Ndmp0q2xN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds familiar... https://t.co/lO8EZTTCZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican Clown Car is about to roll into Washington.  Evil clowns.  Scary. https://t.co/DjIw1mQIuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good grief!  Seriously?  A failed emoji deal?
Politico: Twitter cut out of Trump tech meeting over failed emoji deal https://t.co/m0YDhL3Nrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists are frantically copying U.S. climate data, fearing it might vanish under Trump - Washington Post  https://t.co/nlE8T7mLTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scahill/Schwarz@The Intercept:  Obama must declassify evidence of Russian hacking. https://t.co/Bxwm4S0Om4 by @jeremyscahill @tinyrevolution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Governments Lie explores the history of fake news.   /via @globeandmail https://t.co/9d0nngLT0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Next Frontier: Trump and Space Weapons https://t.co/bDBlU62lOD by @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 eloquent and brilliant men, Chomsky &amp;  Belafonte, onstage with Amy Goodman
https://t.co/JwZ8jBjOpl via @democracynow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Obama leaving Trump "a loaded revolver in the top desk drawer and a stash of extra ammunition in the closet" ? https://t.co/h6GeHoOh9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revolution of falling expectations, by Arthur Goldhammer (Le Monde diplomatique - English edition, October 2016) https://t.co/QiUzojOYko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Hedges takes down The Mafia State:  https://t.co/HBtX10AHQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Warns That Companies Shipping Jobs Overseas Will Be Slapped with Enormous Bribes     https://t.co/OXPkuQsay6 via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Canada's CBC the canary in the coal mine? https://t.co/abCSKsUvYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Canada's top CBC news anchor, Peter Mansbridge, helped normalize hate and bigotry.   https://t.co/IiShlZ1ErG via @ricochet_en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas elector who criticized Trump says he’s resigning.    https://t.co/UQAASV9Ya1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money down the Pentagon's drain. It’s like going into hock to finance your own imperial decline. https://t.co/ySDL7jzFbq via @tomdispatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Trump adviser says they will eliminate NASA climate research:    https://t.co/hB1IYGOaQp via @BadAstronomer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Bannon Hit With Serious FBI Federal Election Law Complaint By Democratic Coalition.   https://t.co/3F7wlBMFUE via @HuffPostBlog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark Money Billionaire 'Devastating' Pick to Head US Education   https://t.co/wpWDaxbTer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[400 DAPL protesters ‘trapped on bridge’ as police fire tear gas, water cannon (VIDEO) https://t.co/yBQxPIHSLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump in the White House: An Interview With Noam Chomsky https://t.co/Jb8f6arlIV via @truthout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest frm Matt Taibbi -- who's in new film "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I. F. Stone."
 https://t.co/0YWmAIvcqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece by Tom Engelhardt, who's featured in our new film "ALL GOVERNMENTS LIE: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit… https://t.co/ewsOX1XHgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private Prison Stocks Surge After Trump is Elected https://t.co/pSFzPfT6RD via @blackyouthproj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security pro tips on "The Intercept":  Surveillance self-defense against the Trump administration   https://t.co/nS01U5J60i by @micahflee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Bamford's Reuters Commentary: Don't be so sure Russia hacked the Clinton emails  https://t.co/c7FIQKTppU via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREAT REVIEW:  Journalism Icon I.F. Stone’s Words Ring Truer Than Ever in ‘All Governments Lie’ (from @Truthdig)  https://t.co/Q6PyXcf0Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomDispatch 
Thanks for the retweet Tom!
@fredpeabody2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still feel like I'm in the middle of a slo-mo, surreal dream.  If only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All Governments Lie" final 5 showtimes today in NYC + LA. -EXCEPT added LA shows Nov 12,13,19,20 @ 10 am. Must-see film now more than ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age of Ignorance.   https://t.co/gsDip6NPMH via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Angst of Scholarship at the NYRB: Getting Kierkegaard Wrong, Twice    https://t.co/k5ngnI2gyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Governments Lie, The Movie -- showing in NYC &amp; LA thru Nov. 10th https://t.co/bR8U4O2IaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Governments Lie, The Movie https://t.co/bR8U4O2IaQ by @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV network needs grandpa pissed off. Otherwise, he spends the afternoon feeding pigeons...instead of glued to ads   https://t.co/eZAI9rA2EU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyAgides 
Not yet but we're working on it.  Probably in early 2017.  
Fred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentary 'All Governments Lie' takes mainstream media to task https://t.co/MhAcdmCuqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All Governments Lie: Truth, Deception, and the Spirit of I. F. Stone" opens tonight at Cinema Village in NYC &amp; Laemmle Music Hall 3 in L.A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the problem with the story connecting Russia to Trump's server https://t.co/PRYPo7XIpK by @samfbiddle @lhfang @micahflee @headhntr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump’s Media Cheerleaders Turned Campaign Coverage Into a Total Disaster via @thenation https://t.co/iMcmziaDkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. hivemind mulls how Clinton can pass huge corporate tax cut https://t.co/LdSoKQbOOM by @tinyrevolution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin Cancels Campaign Event with Trump https://t.co/J81h7xBdId via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Party Could Recover as Early as 2096, Experts Say https://t.co/1CqyYOixTI via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein urged Clinton campaign to silence Sanders's #BlackLivesMatter message https://t.co/wZpbKgzrdm by @ZaidJilani]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>