<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you @cnn.CNN Just Did To Kellyanne Conway What No Other Network Has Dared To Do - https://t.co/l1bKpbpxGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight Different European Countries Just Made These Trump Parody Videos - https://t.co/EComwywUSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adviser cites non-existent 'massacre' defending ban https://t.co/7PWpgzBeLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Website Lets You Send Pizza to Protestors Around America https://t.co/EDgn9jzWhh via @munchies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Republics End https://t.co/Ya965mYLc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapper hits Spicer for scolding media on 'ban' https://t.co/QmQL9nadnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks pledges to hire thousands of refugees in response to Trump ban https://t.co/A8IxLAFm9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching President Trump with Horror Around the World https://t.co/lGF1htcuIA via @@jonleeanderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a Swirl of ‘Untruths’ and ‘Falsehoods,’ Calling a Lie a Lie https://t.co/PQawZUqPhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are scientists going to march on Washington? https://t.co/GRbKcK3TAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A Grand Old Party For the Grand Old Party: Day One Itinerary (Guest Post Submitted…” by @FullFrontalSamB https://t.co/yYe6dXX4OP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Won’t Back Down From His Voting Fraud Lie. Here Are the Facts. https://t.co/sCU64F9gRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Resistance Plan: Step 2 https://t.co/ze10gfFlti via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Sean Spicer’s Stalinist apparition https://t.co/Y3fZPrCCjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The America We Lost When Trump Won https://t.co/RvlZJn2Alf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Pushes ‘Alternative Facts.’ Here Are the Real Ones. https://t.co/oeUNFaeOGw@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reporting!White House press secretary attacks media for accurately reporting inauguration crowds https://t.co/T597DWNnES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KING: Today is one of the dumbest days in American history https://t.co/gcNs99YQeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viral Video Brilliantly Debunks Trump's Tweets About John Lewis's District @alternet https://t.co/Ue2Zxk0hZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The despair of the Jeff Sessions hearing: https://t.co/5K8ie5ibUe via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin to Sing at Trump Inauguration https://t.co/u302hRgCN5 via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help us diagram this sentence by Donald Trump! https://t.co/h0q04nwa8D via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Least 50 Trump Electors Were Illegitimately Seated as Electoral College Members @alternet https://t.co/DoMV3AYNxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NAACP Just Occupied The Office Of Trump’s Attorney General Pick - https://t.co/3KGoCdlrG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KING: We're not opposing Trump with the fierceness he deserves https://t.co/uc01f7XSWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans just voted to gut the independent office overseeing their ethics https://t.co/6O56LyR056 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America’s largest police union has decided critical media coverage is “fake news” – VICE News https://t.co/1lVvQpS5Yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Moore Just Made Defecting Trump Electors An Offer They Can’t Refuse - https://t.co/4QPjeXkXoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Made Up New Word “Unpresidented.” George Takei’s Reply Was PERFECT - https://t.co/Cjiex3gHTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you can fact-check Trump's tweets — in the tweets themselves https://t.co/k2v6O5JbR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s beginning to look a lot like right before the Great Recession https://t.co/ZjFDxlT6S2 via @vicenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This group is borrowing Gamergate’s tactics to attack Breitbart: https://t.co/3MDCRQK70P via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Perfect Weapon: How Russian Cyberpower Invaded the U.S. https://t.co/2vu9NR6sLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trevor Noah's insight into what is happening to America after Trump's win https://t.co/S0JkyxiL11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a huge win for Standing Rock, the Army has halted construction of the Dakota Access pipeline. https://t.co/WxjPZ1mdvy via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcissist-in-Chief: The Psychopathology That Explains Donald Trump's Depravity @alternet https://t.co/sw1u3bDWKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Victory Tour First Of Its Kind Since Hitler’s Nuremberg Rallies https://t.co/0RSJJH4NBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KING: Louisiana says Joe McKnight’s black life doesn’t matter https://t.co/ORXLK8jN26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of president Donald Trump is replacing https://t.co/CVc6FVncsY via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Making America White Again https://t.co/pKdqYR7m7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Quiet Pick for Legal Adviser Shows He's Dead Set on Nuking Our Democracy @alternet https://t.co/r8UloNGpdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US election recount is a long shot – but the alternative is catastrophe https://t.co/U2AZVrGrdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump became our conspiracy theorist in chief https://t.co/UrVWmaZTDc via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White nationalists? Alt-right? If you see a Nazi, say Nazi | Lindy West https://t.co/kUvssyqJCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Reasons Why We’re Officially Done With Kanye West | News One | Black Lives Matter https://t.co/H90BSq2u7b via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8R5nLqZr1z. #greenday, #amas #notrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We Ain’t Gonna Play Trump City” by Alex Young https://t.co/kMvncXtxgf. #boycottTrumpHouse #TrumpCity #GrabYourWallet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Reich's First 100 Days Resistance Agenda @alternet https://t.co/wdvj0met21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the press stand firm against Trump's secrecy? https://t.co/plVfQGzOT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making America White Again https://t.co/Yrc2WD41Pp via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to pay more attention to Jared Kushner https://t.co/zTWTSXb7cS via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Reportedly Has to Hold Trump's Hand Because He's Clueless About His New Job @alternet https://t.co/I2YAj1WsKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noam Chomsky Just Responded to Trump’s Presidency and It’s Chilling https://t.co/JbtnjXi4gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A List of Pro-Women, Pro-Immigrant, Pro-Earth, Anti-Bigotry Organizations That Need Your Support https://t.co/nM5izka94C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 Famous Women on Resilience and Rebellion https://t.co/PYcZDZz7v4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Note to My Fellow Trump Supporters - McSweeney’s Internet Tendency https://t.co/VXIAyrY1Xe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition · Electoral College Electors: Make Hillary Clinton President on December 19 · https://t.co/UoJk1vGZUb https://t.co/cFtERFc8CO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Fans Just Filmed Themselves Harassing Black Female Students - https://t.co/ZWiY2ENpHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small way to show solidarity after Donald Trump’s presidential win, inspired by Brexit https://t.co/JyTxnQsnNl via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something That Actually "Existed": Trump Policy Shop | Full Frontal with Samantha Bee | TBS https://t.co/k2Ux1vkWUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who studies the spread of ignorance  https://t.co/NzyocUNsa0 via @BBC_Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: It Still Nowhere Near Okay To Act Like Donald Trump https://t.co/5aEZzEtGqX via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas State University police looking into Trump 'vigilante' fliers https://t.co/uLqEhbCwsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the media normalized Trump and demonized Hillary. https://t.co/TGa1QlWBuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Obama Can Do to Make Life Difficult for President Trump https://t.co/ViyIn6AsZ0 via @vice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presidential Election 2016: An American Tragedy - The New Yorker https://t.co/vvqIr84j1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A List of Pro-Women, Pro-Immigrant, Pro-Earth, Anti-Bigotry Organizations That Need Your Support https://t.co/nM5izka94C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There Are 868 Fewer Places to Vote in 2016 Because the Supreme Court Gutted the Voting Rights Act via @thenation https://t.co/Q1NUXXd8QU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: The unauthorized database of false things | Toronto Star https://t.co/gq6d3eUyy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KING: Stopping Trump essential to well-being of many Americans https://t.co/fPUJlTGeLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Election Comes Down to 1 Thing https://t.co/TuLIclOZWz via @TheRoot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Mocks Trump For Getting His Twitter Confiscated https://t.co/RQRbaedK3c via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Celebrities Just Made An Anti-Trump Video For The Ages - https://t.co/GLtnSdFSAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news, exploding on social media, is seeping into the mainstream https://t.co/YrmxDpBYUo via @nationalpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: The Democratic National Committee has told the FBI it found evidence its HQ was bugged https://t.co/rf5CnCk7er via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What We Still Dont Know About Donald Trump https://t.co/DOpLT34hqn via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘No Vacancies’ for Blacks: How Donald Trump Got His Start, and Was First Accused of Bias https://t.co/DSqKpkCuOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Secret Server, A Spy, and the FBI: Three New Explosive Trump Ties to Russia https://t.co/JHHwFvsxMQ via @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch “InFormation” on #Vimeo https://t.co/wplSIPl07m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony Weiner, You Big Fucking Dick https://t.co/B2BwfFSh4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence's Refusal to Pardon an Innocent Man Lays Bare His Cruel Side @alternet https://t.co/vGVJSBVRTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Miss Finland becomes 12th woman to accuse Trump of sexual assault https://t.co/kWvRRWByRr via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Trump rooting against U.S. troops in Mosul? https://t.co/j5nUBg3h6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smyle for Women https://t.co/8BlxINro2U via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call Me a Nasty Woman, Thank You Very Much @alternet https://t.co/29Zs7fu9DV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Diagram Explains Every Conspiracy Against Donald Trump https://t.co/QL2zMdZHMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton has a power that no man can take away: https://t.co/VUzyg7sCtu via @doublexmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's beef with SNL is no laughing matter https://t.co/K7pTEPYeLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalism professor supports People writer's claims against Trump https://t.co/QNNIxxGKgR # via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amy Goodman Is Facing Prison for Reporting on the Dakota Access Pipeline. That Should Scare Us All. via @thenation https://t.co/7UlL7JpN2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fury and Failure of Donald Trump - Rolling Stone https://t.co/pKZjIZEB1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump assault allegations aren't new. Why are we only listening now? | Lucia Graves https://t.co/HOoUniw6WS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama's EPIC Takedown Of Trump's Sexual Behavior (FULL | HD) https://t.co/kD8cWqdf87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Breaks Down How Republicans Ended Up With Trump https://t.co/4PRPP75bCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US election 2016: Trump and his Central Park Five defiance https://t.co/arKluKtdQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren Buffett hits back at Trump over tax comments - Business - CBC News https://t.co/c8WzwhnDlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican leaders knew who Trump was when they endorsed him. Never let them forget it. https://t.co/GT2KINFIAx # via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye Producer Mike Dean Samples Trump on New Track “Grab Em By Da Pussy” https://t.co/4NwEFyATJH via @pitchfork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's tax records: A tale of business failures https://t.co/Ux25kZBQOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not One New York Police Officer Has a Body Camera https://t.co/qcWdwOmaiI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>