<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that would be fun https://t.co/bHqzQGSKMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there we are Patrick Gower, pays to let the govt do its job before making up headlines https://t.co/3DQCxnQKiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mykuhl @NewshubPolitics and radio but Paddy didn't get a personal interview so lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadMaclegend @NewshubPolitics @patrickgowernz @NewshubNZ 
I second that.. the Americans will love him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervRobertson It is brilliant, don't know if it's his laugh or what he says!! Both I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn Okay thanks, there was just no warning by M2PP will take different route tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @NewstalkZB @winstonpeters 
Isn't the Whinnie the non Maori dude that likes old people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh love it, this so funny.. haven't laughed like that for ages https://t.co/1zkVCsSvpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the streaker gets more airtime.. yes I am a star lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn Is the intersection on Statehgwy1  and Popular Raumati going to be fixed tomrow am. 2into1 plus merge was high risk this am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @Whafe I have concrete being laid tomorrow so hoping it's not raining again..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some tell that lefty Mark on ZB that petrol pricing is so different between Levin and City by 40cents.. wrong https://t.co/C4v84GSMnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha Larry Williams put Barry in his place tonight.. Barry had no idea what he was talking about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whafe We now have â˜€ï¸ strange weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @tauhenare "be a bit different" that's an understatement Duncan!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the MOU really is a let's bash National understanding. https://t.co/nOjXmfNFa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whafe Right that's it I am moving. So over this weather. Concrete to be laid tomorrow and not going to happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop @jmodoh @tomwconnell @Thomson_Greg Had to laugh that he was run out with an underarm ðŸ˜„ poor guy never faced a ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in the lower north!! Nothing but rain all summer if you can call it that https://t.co/jBDxtQBDhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radiosportnz @adamcoopnz What an idiot, he knew what he was getting into.. do stupid stuff for 3 mi s of fame get hurt for a few days haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least he is doing what he said!! The people voted for this thinking he would be like every other politician lol https://t.co/D1FbmfAzMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@granto_5 Haha not alone #welly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoo who cares really!! https://t.co/8ofBlYMLjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@All_Blacks15 @MyFoodBagNZ I hope so for you, I love it so much.. don't know what I would cook now..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ Oh wow congratulations, been a tough week for you and wife but now a bundle of joy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZleftrightout Yes poor guy, did all that work. However, other batsman must feel gutted too..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsrosieb Gosh that was amazing, couldn't watch all of it due to having grandkids but caught the last wicket.. awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr and there is that, people are over it really. All grown up and moved on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@88TheDon Really!! Oops sorry, know your pain. Just seeing it on TV made me jealous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr haha National, wow what a stupid statement. Rugby union and WCC plus police]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneforthedr was that caused by that small shake today? I would be worried how many other buildings are hiding stresses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47  knew what you meant lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously!! Cloud and drizzle all day here.. or is this just Auckland https://t.co/AXPcO7YJqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh so Andrew admits we are looked up to as a country that well looking after its vulnerable people wow https://t.co/fv8ZMWCR6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IGottaNumBum @NewshubPolitics 
Did Paddy ask that question? I bet he did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course he wouldn't, we know this https://t.co/kMw5IyRmWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to watch this all over again.. that was magic https://t.co/nW6yuG58dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekiwicanary @Kiwimrsmac @AklCouncil 
Probably thugs keep breaking them, love to ruin it for the other 1.45million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadMaclegend @JoelRowan Media all taken with his charms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 we have overcast conditions again!!!! Drizzle so sick of this weather. Normally great up here but this yr umm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 @JennaRaeburn @jonobasile @JoelRowan 
Wow he's a racist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop it Auckland, I am so jealous you have sun.. go #blackcaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervRobertson @belperi 2 sets of twins first girls second boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 Thanks very interesting read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truck crash death
There have been a lot of accidents involving Trucks. Do we need to look at their logs?  https://t.co/f9QcNbH3aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer hits back over 'cheating'
Yet last night Cash tweeting how amazing he was. Fed does not cheat https://t.co/YGQ4ReGrFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiSAHD I couldn't sleep after that, it's going to be long day for me and have the kids this afternoon. Aww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never will I do that again!! Turn on Breakfast TV.. oops that was 5 mins wasted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww, these two are special https://t.co/PaTAmjqCJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow he won, what a bloody awesome game. Big ups to Nadal.. sad to see anyone lose a game like this..#AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pukeko65 God I stopped breathing on that point #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Roger break it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiSAHD @farmerjase and no tie break.. could be here awhile. My bottle of wine nearly finished lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerjase Oh yes, edge of your seat stuff.. what a final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes back on track.. OmG this match is incredible #AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Roger, let's do this. My heart is thumping with every ball. #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geeze it's going to be a late night.. Roger making too many errors. #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow just wow, stroke making is incredible, this game has everything #federernadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmoscrip Brilliant game, just what I hoped for..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had to share https://t.co/IWkX7xhfLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiSAHD @jonobasile thought the bottle thing was for his sponsors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger always seems to lose concentration.. come on Roger focus #Federer #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiSAHD and undies pulling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG this is why men's tennis is the best.. what a game then by @rogerfederer #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerjase Agree I am a Fed fan but sweet if Rafa wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohthatwelshguy oh gosh they missed you so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go @rogerfederer So nervous but know it will be a great match. #AusOpen #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacDowd @coltheman1 
Nope..addictive personality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @MacDowd 
Oops unlike , can't help myself liking tweets from twitter mates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyoung1409 Nope because your seen as rich, no matter what you live in. Those new state houses are amazing, and get maintained..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacDowd @coltheman1 Lol ðŸ˜‚ always find someone with same thinking as you on a platform this big.. I love that we are cellular mates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyoung1409 and what was the Syae of the Nation? Good bad or just bloody brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkZB Hope it's not like the last one.. no one was there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roonsopo Glad someone else saw this, mentioned it las week.. overkill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait, wine chilling in the fridge and supper ready.. have cheer quietly as hubby has work tomorrow https://t.co/dqwWRhuR0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asteroid47 @coltheman1 Oh Tessy you are wonderful ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 @coltheman1 haha love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ Thank you for keeping us all informed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha that's funny and he Trump wouldn't be allowed in either. Made his mills using polish labour https://t.co/UUr8M3q1Wj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 Think he will find a lot men have this issue with there bits just like women with theirs, in fact women have 2 problem bits lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 @coltheman1 @lindsaymouat @nzlabour Really tired of them putting down young hard working kiwis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irisshackleton Wow that looks great, I need to make bread tomorrow..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewKayNZ The whole show was a comedy fest..  not laughing ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiSAHD Ouch!! Vinegar bath for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzlabour So my sons at 29 brought a house and paid off student loans and have kids are #alternative facts ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadMaclegend @coltheman1 They just don't think about anything, logistically logical or reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 Reds will arm cops and green unarmed. This is the Stop Go party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsrosieb @coltheman1 Anything for a vote!! Change appearance, tell us about his prostrate and give promises.. ugg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have it one Steven, they are just Andy bashing!! Wannabe like Trump lol ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/vynJPn7GPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @1NewsNZ Newshub has led with Paddy and labour greens party talking up change.. laksa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerjase Think it is confusion.. don't agree with what he's done if he he has..political football at present.. I feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47  is Guy Williams a comedian? Mind you the whole Labour Party are comical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 @cjsbishop Oh thanks ðŸ˜š agree he's not funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi @PhilTwyford @nzchinacouncil @Pseudony_Ms 
Think they are trying everything in the book to gain votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember this game, so looking forward to tonight's. Go Roger https://t.co/IbsocbCuhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @NewshubNZ @patrickgowernz 
Lol always thought that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone read the tweet? I am blocked :( just being nosy https://t.co/p7RMPuWQj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 @NewstalkZB since when are stories written without journalists name.. err it's getting worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh watching my twitter feed go nuts about refugees. People need to wait and get the real news not hysteria.. had to mute a few peeps sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 @NewshubPolitics @NewshubNZ @patrickgowernz 
Here and well said. No,thing but an English bash up..Paddy should join stars in my i]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>