<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go. The discreditation of peaceful protest has begun... #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So incompetence or desperation for this mess? I'm going with pre-Brexit desperation. #nostatevisit #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Credible working relationship' means not saying thing he doesn't want to hear... #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you have a reasonable conversation with people like this..is there no end to this parade of freak Trump defenders on R4 today #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is this woman admitting the US had no vetting procedure previously...? #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky for our Nationals we got our butt kissing in last week... #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were all these 'glowing headlines' about #maytrump ? Must've missed those... #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebatclaw @thehugheslady I return the favour. Thus the circle is closed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cinematicsoul @CatfIap can you include me out...I've stopped listening..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebatclaw @thehugheslady errr...no I think the 'burning' was all you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebatclaw @thehugheslady and right wing facist dictators?...the world speaks from that experience... #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehugheslady @thebatclaw No you're right. Bring on the chaos. It'll be entertaining...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You meet such great people on twitter...'high quality' as Farage would say. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebatclaw @thehugheslady Now who's deluded. #wato Debated with many narcissistic grandiose ego maniacs recently?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehugheslady @thebatclaw just remember..whatever happens, it's all on people like you. Own it. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on, you can't be signing off with Trumps alternate reality 'ban imposed with no problems.' #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This person is mentally ill. Do you have children sir? #wato #climatedenier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the 'vast majority of scientists' @Marthakearney 97%. Say it. Over and over.  #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehugheslady we shall see...plenty of people trying to find enough dirt to impeach. Could be a matter of time. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 1 week of Trump chaos, anyone who thinks Trump doesn't need removing asap needs to assess their screw tightness.. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's precisely because it's a symbolic act that it's meaningful. #wato #nostatevisit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly new US administration oblivious to Law of Unintendended Consequences.When you're a Master of the Universe thought is for wimps #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump exhibits classic signs of mental illness: shrinks https://t.co/QL6tMTFcUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day, another paranoid, racist, fantasist voice from USA. 'America might fall to Sharia law!' Delusional. #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#May meets #Trump? #maytrump https://t.co/lPWgVpatY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So she was actually propping up the elderly President. How appropriate. https://t.co/PGT6BbmU3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling and simpering the most when her own country's journalist challenged him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling From Democracy to Facist Dictatorship in one week. 'So easy folks. So great.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100 Good. Truth hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times Kills Comics Best-seller Lists https://t.co/trKbNwJwNm via @vulture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @guardian Says the man who failed 7 times to become a part of the system...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reply to @cathynewman @POTUS @lindseyhilsum Whereas the yearly death toll for 2015 from gun deaths was 13,000....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Britain risks being tarred with his brush, becoming a mini-me to a man already regarded as a global danger.” https://t.co/yyTMb0wQ1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about a leading question. Mythic my arse. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the contrary, 'I hear you' is a phrase we could do with hearing a great deal more these days. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't vote for renewal. They voted for a wrecking ball. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thigh slappingly, hilariously brilliant. Wine helps too... #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archers_fan2015 Get orf my laaand. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Now, do you actually want to buy something?' Fucking brilliant. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you folks will cover the upcoming change in R4 external commissioning from 20 to 60%..at some point #r4feedback @BBCR4Feedback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddwilson Presumeably encountering Charlie Brooker would cause this chap to spontaneously combust..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardly..its in a long tradition of Steve emulating classic works. Wince inducing but emminently appropriate, frankl… https://t.co/uuhdgWwJZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way too late for that. She already looks like a craven lapdog. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell on the special relationship – cartoon https://t.co/k1FmUIlkuj #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliH25 Good. Thought not....it just made me think of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body language experts have analysed Melania at the inauguration and found something disturbing https://t.co/wKhdWyT44y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they are a sensitive generation it's because they've been raised largely indoors staring at screens all the time..no wonder. #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's that 'you should take seriously but not literally' working out for you now, America. Seems pretty literal to me. #BuildTheWall #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh she's finally noticed... #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Roy Roy. Where did you leave those testicles... #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenavvie I don't think that's clear...it could get very complicated, legal battles etc., very quickly.. #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenavvie Bollocks. No one can stop me buying US if I choose. #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for Us food boycotts. #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent Not that X-Men movies have disappeared up their own time-travelling fundament or anything...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's lawyer/mentor in 80's was Sen Joe McCarthy's senior counsellor...pretty jawdropping. And evil looking https://t.co/144YclU9FP #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smokescreen. The Q should be 'how reliable is this 80 billion white elephant..?' Ok slightly biased q. #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brittle, evasive, full of shit....another day with the Tories. #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent Bollocks. He's everybody's problem. He's the world's problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump's Lawyer/Mentor in 80's had been Joseph McCarthy's Chief Counsel...why am I not surprised. https://t.co/144YclU9FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They give trophies when there's only 4 subs? #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholasPegg And if you're both....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewbensonf1 Excellent piece Andrew....sounds like things are moving in the right direction finally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All very neat....and somehow unsatisfying. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having 2 phones worked out so well for Walter White too... #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willbrooker As per the C4 MattFrei doc on the Trump family last week, the truth is there is an emptiness in his soul. He's a hollow man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent Of course, when you can't control them, cut them out altogether.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think they might be trying to write Rob out...? #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helen121 She's his enabler. He's her project. 'This man shall be redeemed!' Or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how everyone becomes an expert on EU law over trivial issues... #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet Monsanto would love to get their claws into the UK. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not funny. He uses it to disguise events like paying off fines for his dodgy university...laugh while his corruptions slides by. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly Mogg and the audience have never read any of Trumps tweets.. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Annette1Hardy my fave was 'I will never ever let you down.' Lets see him front that up. #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you make America Not Talk Shit Again... #Inauguration  #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Annette1Hardy god what a load of garbage...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone hit the off button...I'm coming down with something #Inauguration  #bbcpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well 13,000 people died from citizen on citizen shootings last year, if that's what you mean... #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reply to @bbclaurak I'm the people. No I'M the people! No I am, listen to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Donald, you made the money, you sacked the people. You are the disease. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 years much preferable to 5.... #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US 2% growth..not counting all that money you're printing to prop the whole thing up...just like us. #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Lily read Emma one too many times.... #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dare I say 20million followers not many in country of 350m? A media savvy elite? How much of that is the worlds journos #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many? 2000 in a country of 60m? Not so many. #wato #MoneySupermarket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this person really serious enough for this negotiation...smug, complacent and somewhat deluded. #r4today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCPM People swimming too slow in fast lanes is more my experience..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America: behold, your Snowflake-in-Chief | John Paul Brammer https://t.co/dsG0zfL6LE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope all those who exploited the NI green energy scheme are happy.... #Stormont #wato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's right. We intervene too much and keep people alive too long when they should be let go. We're too afraid of death. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38 million pensioners? Then we really would be in trouble. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're spending money on the young? #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god. Who can I pay STOP to hearing/seeing bloody Jacob Rees-Mogg on the BBC? #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why assume insult? If they're 'blacking'..tho that term is prejudging, lets learn the history, not assume offence. Again. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you be scared if the Gulf Stream switches off Owen? Greenland melting? We're at the latitude of Alaska here. Mental pigmy. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paterson blatantly LYING. Last year was the warmest year on record. And the year before. Temps NOT coming down. #bbcaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonnyBenjamin Just imagine them as teeny tiny pathetic weaklings whose hearts have shrivelled...with every insult they shrink it more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was I not listening properly....there was a longer cut of Margaret that delivers apparently... #wittertainment @KermodeMovie @wittertainment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Mark could shame @movies4men1 into showing #RunSilentRunDeep in the correct ratio... #wittertainment @wittertainment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bleedingcool That's what you get for living in a militant atheist period...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC sets up team to debunk fake news https://t.co/vqalBRWOKA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>