<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA['The American face of ISIS' by Robert Pape, Walker Gunning and @JCarrollASPI in @ASPI_org https://t.co/kWrngQcu4s via @aspi_org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting piece on the Trump administration's China policy by @jacintakeast for @YoungAustIntAff https://t.co/Qe6C8ovSSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most recent @ASPI_org Cyber Wrap looking at the alleged Russia DNC hack &amp; Trump by @Liam_Nevill https://t.co/p35EmJrJhG via @aspi_org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['That phone call: Trump and Turnbull’s alliance challenge' by @camhawker in @ASPI_org https://t.co/Lh8FC5l8Ye via @aspi_org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alliance may very well outlast the Trump admin, but there should be a weary rethink of how australia values historical diplomatic norms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's true that with his fondness to Russia indicates a global order shakeup, today points to that in Trump's FP, the slate is wiped clean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's events make it clear that all hyperbole regarding the shared values of the alliance need to be reassessed. They mean zero to Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBryant151 All my christmases have come at one, one problem is that these christmases are extremely concerning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump's election victory, people called on the institutions to remain strong under his presidency. The ACLU has met the challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to know that the new cyber czar has his priorities in order whilst alleged US spies have been arrested in Russ… https://t.co/jJKXANTuRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S. Bannon having a Masters in National Security does not discount his odious politics rendering him unfit for national security leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly inspiring amongst all the chaos &amp; darkness to see the charity of immigration lawyers donating their time to help detained individuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The historical immigration of US Muslims has been an unequivocal success of integration and contribution to US soci… https://t.co/p9MsAptgYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly shocking if true, so much for the age old historical alliance. https://t.co/7p9F2VWTYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying as to which intelligence experts Trump is talking to. There is a consensus in that torture is inefficient in intelligence gathering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The map to 2018 for House Democrats should be clear: Play by GOP tactics, obstruct until Republican policy is rendered inept &amp; frozen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't make this stuff up. https://t.co/F1r0jquAp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: The Wall. Where are all the fiscally conservative, anti-government spending Republicans who believed healthcare was a waste of money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #WomensMarch matters because in within weeks of planning it eclipsed the coronation of his narcissism he's been planning for decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regarding embracing Putin, it seems as if the Trump team strategy in terms of PR is "If we can get over this hill, the story will go away."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the advent &amp; uncertainty of Trump in the Asia-Pacific, it is reassuring to see allies such as Japan &amp; Australia commit to stronger ties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to the vast organisational structure of the US cyber community, cool heads are needed as C Czar to work with the various institutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of his questionable cybersecurity experience, Giuliani's tone/demeanor of late show a lack of nuance needed in US cybersecurity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denying the freedom of the press in front of the american flag. a harrowing sign of things to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vale 'Keeping It 1600'. One of the most informative &amp; important podcasts of the election cycle. Excited for 'Pod Sa… https://t.co/ieTCG08Exi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever misreading there was of the power of political influence celebrities held in the election, should not be a pejorative going forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @reginald_ramos on joining the @YoungAustIntAff team! Well deserved, give him a follow for insightful pieces on the Indo-Pacific.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to reading the pieces of whomever takes the role of US fellow off my hands, a heavy responsibility as Trump takes office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to thank @YoungAustIntAff for the opportunity given to me as US fellow. A vital organisation for the future of Aus foreign policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My final article of my US Fellowship with @YoungAustIntAff I wrote about Trump's cabinet picks &amp; Obama's legacy https://t.co/yAHCvtW0Nq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On climate change, pragmatism won't save us from Trump" by @ShieldJack in @YoungAustIntAff https://t.co/FYwAv78BLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin Like your campaign I really enjoy the prospect of McMuffins but realize that I get my hopes too high &amp; am left disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really have to question the mental readiness and stability of a man who needs to troll tweet his adversaries at 5.30 am on a saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnellyAL Spot on, despite Tillerson's ties to Putin and Mattis's hawkishness on Iran, they are both not peddlers of fake-news ideologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Democrats Can Bridge Identity Politics and Economic Populism by @grahamvyse in @NewRepublic  https://t.co/HBqq2M5r1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US journalists with an expertise on Russia is essential in the Trump presidency. Let us hope her transition to find a new platform is quick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The news of the Julia Ioffe firing is truly worrying. A bad tweet but she is one of the best foreign policy journos out there re: Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming to the end of my US fellowship with @YoungAustIntAff but I am extremely excited about the future of the organisation &amp; its growth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hope that technology could be used advance a liberal interconnectivity seems to be quickly being replaced by 'Thiel' tech-selfishness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's meeting with tech industry leaders foregrounds the death of silicon valley idealism &amp; only reinforces a growing neolibertarian trend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The challenge of writing a thesis on US/AUS responses to cyberattacks/terrorism in this moment of global intelligence chaos is electrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a never more divided Congress, an effort across the aisle to oppose Russian political influence may be the only chance for bipartisanship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alleged effort to destabilize institutions &amp; order by Putin appears troubling with French, German, Dutch, Italian elections in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the light of the CIA findings on Russia, There needs to be a bipartisan effort to block Tillerson's nomination in the name of democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The likely nomination Tillerson to Sec of State only advances the inevitability of a Trump-Putin coalition. This appears so calculated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Jason Kander Says Democrats Accidentally Divided the Country” by Keepin' It 1600 @JasonKander @JonFavs @DanPfeiffer https://t.co/D5sApJ4G3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ISIS in the Caribbean". Fascinating piece by @simonrcottee in @TheAtlantic https://t.co/QCg2CPgNT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The merits of generals in government by @Jim_Molan in @LowyInstitute https://t.co/Kcx9rOFrrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Mattis: Mad Dog, warrior monk and defence sec nominee by @tonywalker1 in @LowyInstitute https://t.co/oU2A6S570y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia, ANZUS and regional order | Rod Lyon | by @rdyn51 in @APSI_org https://t.co/wJAcOHA9ZQ via @aspi_org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael T. Flynn and America’s new war with ‘radical Islam’ | Greg Austin in @ASPI_org | https://t.co/IlYpgOfp5q via @aspi_org]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump should'nt weaken US sanctions on Russia (part 1) by @actoncavanough in @LowyInstitute https://t.co/CVnHrDUT4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Pizzagate Is Preposterous and Terrifying — and a Sign of What’s to Come” by @claire_mcnear https://t.co/FxJyeEGnBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I Grew With Barack Obama in the White House by @SamuelRWEllison in @thedailybeast https://t.co/rqlZgTIjwj via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already Happening: Media Normalization of Trumpism by @JoyAnnReid in @thedailybeast https://t.co/DZMjCB4nEr via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Dark Side of the Presidential Turkey Pardon” by @claire_mcnear https://t.co/jFIMDXt7Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably the definitive Castro piece you will read today. "Fidel Castro is dead" https://t.co/jWodZuAt9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched a Youtube compilation of the best West Wing speeches last night. The Sorkinist view of American politics feels like a distant memory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @CBryant151 in @YoungAustIntAff on the troublesome economic outlook of the US under President Trump https://t.co/37iBKGlopV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insightful piece by @nicole_2b in @YoungAustIntAff on Trump's diplomatic test with Shinzo Abe &amp; East Asia relations https://t.co/MONDypceDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @ntrego88 in @YoungAustIntAff on the future of Israel/Palestine relations under a Trump Presidency https://t.co/A6kzvewIAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rumors that Trump has been ignoring intelligence briefings, baffling that a man so transfixed on threats to USA is apparently uninterested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a man who for most of his campaign raised fear about foreign threats, he sure is comfortable with taking a phone call on unsecure lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whats most troubling atm is the unwillingness of the Trump transition team to adhere to basic national security protocol regarding diplomacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, what was that again about somebody wanting to "drain the swamp?" https://t.co/r6QF05Xuyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest piece with YAIIA where I discussed how Trump's victory has enabled a rise in hate crimes @FlindersSHIR https://t.co/U2ui2hYYJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest piece with @YoungAustIntAff where I discussed how Trump's victory has enabled a rise in hate crimes. https://t.co/U2ui2hYYJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest piece with YAIIA where I wrote about the rise in hate crimes in America since Trump's victory. https://t.co/Jb8UN26oR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global politics: League of nationalists https://t.co/Fqrhg8Ytx6 via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The In-Law in the Trump Inner Circle: Jared Kushner’s Steadying Hand' by @jonathanmahler &amp; @maggieNYT https://t.co/k3f0Qigv8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Time to take America seriously if we want the alliance' by Peter Jennings in @ASPI_org https://t.co/KjxvfPVd8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Donald Trump won't be to blame for any increase in terror attacks' by @JCarrollASPI in @ASPI_org https://t.co/W0QCSxJEm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“How ‘Saturday Night Live’ Should Handle Donald Trump” by @katiebakes @ringer https://t.co/5m9KwY86Lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Cracks in the ‘Blue Wall’ That Democrats Overlooked” by Keepin' It 1600 @jonfavs @ringer https://t.co/3xO6XhUC4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Inside Chris Christie's fall from grace' by @politcoalex in @politico https://t.co/kS3PXPoFIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The risks and ramifications of Trump's impulsive adventurism' by @graham_euan in @LowyInstitute

https://t.co/H7DJ61UyRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Australia must grimace &amp; bear Donald Trump to keep our alliance on track' by @mfullilove in @LowyInstitute

 https://t.co/zOwbP6wd5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few months ago we were talking about Duterte &amp; Air Force One squabble's weakening Obama's legacy in Asia-Pacific. What a few months can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's deeply poetic &amp; discouraging that TPP dying may end the pivot at the hands of a Hillary Clinton defeat, a major brainchild of rebalance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's failure to pass the TPP will loom negatively on his legacy in the Asia-Pacific &amp; will weaken US power there. This is a reality now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter the result, we all must do a lot of collective soul searching about how comfortable we all got with dismissing the unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold onto hope for Michigan and Pennsylvania people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently streaming live on facebook is @FlindersSHIR with a Q&amp;A commentary with a panel of political experts

https://t.co/Kck4ZsZRhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of urban Florida counties which are over performing in favor for Clinton are still come, may have a huge swing for her at the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs is my voice of calm and reason on #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great live coverage of the results coming in from @ringer @keepingit1600 w/ @jonfavs @jonlovett @TVietor08 

https://t.co/JHaHw2NxqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio, North Carolina &amp; Florida all leaning towards Clinton right now. If it stays this way, Trump's path to victory will be near impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get you an electoral system that can do both #electionday #democracysausage https://t.co/01HdEeQVYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticking my neck out there on this one. For the Iowa's &amp; Ohio's Trump will take. Clinton will take Florida &amp; North Carolina #electionday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got coffee, got twitter, got my @FiveThirtyEight, @UpshotNYT @politico @RealClearNews @washingtonpost tabs open. Ready to rock #electionday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Australia, from afar I have always marvelled at the beauty of The American Experiment. On this #Election2016 vote to preserve that USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited, anxious and nervous from Australia as I get ready for #Election2016 tomorrow. Can't imagine I will get a lot of sleep tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest piece with @YoungAustIntAff where I answer some critical questions about the election tomorrow.

https://t.co/MldHWmAPZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlindersSHIR My latest piece. I answered six critical questions for election day and made some early predictions https://t.co/O1xGKfQwjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Three paths that deliver Trump the win" - 3 scenarios where Trump could clinch the election by @ShaneGoldmacher https://t.co/LiMm3jR3j7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Nate Silver right? - Insightful commentary on why 538's predictions are differant from others by @POLITICO_Steve https://t.co/JSzVJyAdMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Beazley says it's 'not safe to assume a Hillary Clinton victory' - Insightful commentary by Beazley https://t.co/ZvOXk3Hady via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The ‘Extraordinary’ Election of The New York Times” by @bryancurtis @ringer https://t.co/Ctqu8sreL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“These Are the Strange Reasons Peter Thiel Is Supporting Donald Trump” by @alyssabereznak @ringer https://t.co/gAEu54F512]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Republican Mandate on Election Day: Diversify or Die” by @Timodc @ringer https://t.co/DYu9Jjelfq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>