<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsure of the reason why I put off watching Sing Street for so long, but glad I now have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People asking me the name of the trail: who do you think I am? Do I look like I know where I am or where I'm going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is open wide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big fan of the snow thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reasons to cry: someone walked into a good shot today and my subject, who was unaware, noticed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a stranger, and it won't go away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many things to do and to think about have been clouding my focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm also finding it incredibly hard to focus on the things I need to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling slightly heavy hearted and a little bit exhausted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I missed today's gorgeous golden hour because I was stuck in the library studying :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know why the Orion constellation holds so much meaning to me, and I don't know if I ever will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pssssst, @njalii happy birthday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii since 1999, what's up welcome to the club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love is to destroy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is something about folk that tugs on my heart strings. Every note hits me like a wave of warmth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awake and dreaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought we could talk on darker days with our boots kicked off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii sounds about right, no probs. be safe tonight &amp; have fun 💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii i got some if you need it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will I ever not forget I my tea while I leave it brewing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i was right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[boy am I going to be mad at myself when my alarm goes off in a few hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a favourite. https://t.co/HzvVwb7Nz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii your real-est tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are we? What do we do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii turned my world around with mac n' cheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many interesting topics will be discussed BUT I'd have to go to sleep RIGHT NOW, otherwise I won't wake up on time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if I should go to the Humanities &amp; Social Sciences conference tomorrow..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii, @TheEconomist please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summary of the hockey game: @njalii and I missed a goal because we were talking about The Economist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dogspot has gained lots of attention. brb becoming a dog photographer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really enjoy having the house to myself because I can blast the Grease soundtrack to sing and dance my heart out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda getting tired of the amount of personal space that people need here. Like just get into my space a little, bug me, hug me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii my brai(si)n cannot think of anything funny to say. Here's an acknowledgement tweet, i love ya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: raisins are good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did read pretty thoroughly on how the system works so I have a broad understanding of it, so I guess that was good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took an enneagram test and it told me that it is unclear from my results which type I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been drinking more tea than coffee lately. If I'm not a coffee-drinking mess anymore, then who am I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came home for a few hours and was greeted with a "you look tired, you have dark circles under your eyes." https://t.co/aKM6SFgql7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only heartbreak and heartache, and gin made of tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least it will be snowing tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My head hurts so much, I feel like crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This teapot + cup set left me wanting one for myself. https://t.co/7zbUrvjlnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess at least people see me and think "Oh, she seems like a person who knows where she's going" enough to ask me for directions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+ one more right as I was leaving my class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been on campus for 15 mins and already got asked for directions twice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii my dad just asked me what I was giggling about, and I just said "trudeau" and all I got was a sigh as a response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much bubbly has been had, and life is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, how's your new year going? https://t.co/8bOo3s75q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just an hour into 2017, and it already looks promising. Let's hope I don't fuck up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as we're 10 minutes away of ending 2016, I play Catan and listen to Rush. What a way to end the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm out for the night (probably.)So happy late and early new year to all of you who read the stupid things that come out of my head. Love ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did yoga with my sister and we took beer breaks, living the life much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to try to fall asleep now. I'm out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter translations are terrible. I want to apologize to my english speaking followers. I promise I sort of make sense in Spanish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day I'm going to Henry David Thoreau-Walden Pond the shit out of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing else to say. https://t.co/CAvi046rUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm heading out REALLY early tomorrow morning, but I can't fall asleep. Why am I like this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's someone out there who wants someone to watch Gilmore Girls with for the first time, I'd be willing to watch it for the 4th time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njalii i'd rt, but u private.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is almost 5am and I haven't slept, for some reason this song won't leave my head. https://t.co/wUmNVXW64T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a consistent headache for the past 4 hours. I feel like crying. Someone make it stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pages, they turn when you come to stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great one has passed today. Rest easy, Subiela. https://t.co/Rz0xw8j0Pv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flour-y hands. https://t.co/2iibDAVSW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never play Risk with your family. It brings out the worst in everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much is going on. My brain hurts. This family is tearing itself apart. I need a nap. https://t.co/7txACx49cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking with my mom means drinking wine + acting movie-like sob scenes when cutting onions + saying really stupid shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a change of pace and scenery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is leaving Vancouver and I'm stuck here until the 29th :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: I didn't know how to write Christmas properly until I was in like 5th grade, lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, so people celebrate Christmas on the 25th instead of celebrating it on the 24th?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to formally apologize to all of the neighbours who can hear me singing my lungs out to Sarah Jaffe's Suburban Nature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna put some Sarah Jaffe on and feel sorry for myself, bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot my wallet at home and the movie theatre need to prove that I was 19+. Had to come back home while my family stayed for Rogue One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hint: @sam_matute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who's an idiot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shadows and light conspiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm stressed out and I don't know why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new owners renovated, and it's not pretty anymore :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I found out that the old french couple who owned Crêpe &amp; Café sold their coffee shop, and that makes me sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never understand how people can get into bed and fall asleep in less than one minute. It takes me forever to fall asleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized I wrote 'are' twice. I'm a failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I pretentious for drinking wine out of a jam jar? Or are all of my other glasses are dirty? You decide. https://t.co/2JjKkqZUx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love seeing rooms full of plants through people's windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 8:30 am exam was cancelled. Let's celebrate by going immediately back to bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a really long time since I last read it, and I can't wait to revisit my favourite book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to be done with my last final tomorrow so that I can start reading Portrait in Sepia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe even 5-6. Who cares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like 3-4 movies in a row kinda thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be honest I'm so tired I kinda just want to watch movies and cuddle in the sofa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got bored of my readings so I decided to watch Kung Fury. As one does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a final on Monday and there is no way that I'm going to get anything done while at home with everyone here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tired, but happy. happily tired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to enter an economics final, and I can hear a group of people talking about Black Ops. Mechanisms of coping with stress are funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can almost feel the length of 2016 when I think about how it was in January that This Is Acting by Sia came out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally did not use her being done with finals as an excuse to drink wine and eat chocolates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised my friend with wine and chocolates cause she's done with finals. Sad thing is that I'm not even close to done yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though I don't have headphones, I keep music in my phone just in case I'm given the aux cord. You gotta be ready to educate the masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just watched Eddie The Eagle while wearing this jumper and now I'm ready to go to a ski competition in the 80s. https://t.co/zVDKciOcqo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>