<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@danhardymma do you think a counter attack strategy in this fight will serve Holly Holm well against Randamie? InsideTheOctagon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrOakley1689 @Scotttom85 I was just about to get in touch with you about it. Sad to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could be as confident. I am not, but I pray it can be done https://t.co/erG6ytSnjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey bro. Have you seen this? https://t.co/NVnHHEBcRq https://t.co/Ftxfbag37f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danhardymma @arielhelwani I think Usher was performing in Wembley arena at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danhardymma @arielhelwani pretty sure I was sitting with Paul that night in the bar at the hotel in question &amp; he was telling me bout it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danhardymma I was just listening to your interview with @arielhelwani when you were talking about that crazy night before a Cage Rage fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything is possible. Better keep away from anything you have not grown yourself... organically 😜 https://t.co/oMdL5svlj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouch. The way some of the protesters have been behaving, my 2 &amp; 4 year olds would not behave that way https://t.co/4EbtrJQ4fA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the videos coming out of the violent protesters assaulting people, show most of them are covering their faces. Cowards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, it's either laugh or cry at how people are reacting. https://t.co/Z2KdUilDxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic that this guy got sucker punched by a guy in a black outfit covering his face for being a "neo-nazi" or bein… https://t.co/ItZ5lni9Wj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the "just abortions" part of your tweets that alarmed me &amp; how you can deduce perverts from that is also very… https://t.co/nuRd1Y9dB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sad really that the unborn are not protected &amp; it's legal to kill them https://t.co/7mw9Sr1tAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is repeating that suppose to exonerate them for all the abortions they are responsible for? https://t.co/DdJur2P5Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am wondering if Trump gets re-elected &amp; he actually tries, will 8 years be enough to undo the damage of the Obama administration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real pity. Thanks for everything @elwinter. Wishing you &amp; your family the very best in the future https://t.co/YhdUHb0lBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't recall them protesting Obama, what does that tell you? https://t.co/4YEoZ4jWJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They all should be ashamed of themselves. The liberals should come out &amp; condemn this https://t.co/lXqpKH1xWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail done. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail also most mornings on the new schedule we arrive in on the far platforms 7 or 8 which is also not fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail many of the people using this service start work at 8am in city centre &amp; miss the Luas services that will get us in on time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail can this please be changed back to 7.40 if not earlier as I am late most mornings for work now. Those of us commuting need this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishrail since the last timetable change the arrival of the first Carlow train into Heuston has been changed from 7.40 to 7.43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a promoter can sell you a fight that previously you had no interest in they have done their job well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dc_mma just catching up on the @ufc from the weekend. I love your commentary, especially on the wrestling &amp; clinch work.Learning as I watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HolyHEEL The Forgotten Trinity by @DrOakley1689 is a very good book on this topic too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the fight, but the interim belt is a joke. https://t.co/bLhZzW2mOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richblayney providential reading this after the study https://t.co/DOjGqiYCkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richblayney a very good read too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough. Can change 1) Romans 2) Romans 3 &amp; 3) Romans 8:28 https://t.co/Yefjq5temu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birds of a feather https://t.co/hT6cBxZbha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCarlWeathers @Danielmmafan just having a bit of fun, sir. I am a fan of your movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Subfightr @robinblackmma Until marriage yes. However, the starting point of this conversation was just me commending Robin on what he said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep up the good work &amp; enjoying what you too https://t.co/H4rBZhWGTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robinblackmma just listening to your latest #askrobinblack pod. I really appreciate that you are consciously trying to not swear, thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JOEREILLY1689 it's sinful, but it's also unnecessary. We should be able articulate our points without using filth words, just my two cents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I don't like about the podcasting platform is the liberty many podcasters take in using bad language on their podcasts...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HookNShoot Evolution. I seem to remember that being the card that turned @John_Kavanagh on to WMMA 😄 https://t.co/rUJnr3KN82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldymcfc same to you. All the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So do you think Amanda Nunes was wrong in her criticism of Edmund? https://t.co/ZByRMMB0La]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole thing just keeps getting more out there. A judgement of God on society https://t.co/XqRf8BRMBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/6ZigHW0o3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not an advocate for feminism. If anything I feel it is a worldview that has a lot of problems. However, glad t… https://t.co/Jaw8ejZ16E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey thank you for what you have done in the sport. Wishing you all the best. Trust in Christ alone. God bless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up &amp; coming fighters as well as established ones would do well to learn from @DominickCruz The way he's handling himself is class #respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly doubt it https://t.co/c9qKOA0VzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was already overdue. I think we will be hearing @TheNotoriousMMA saying "beg me" again soon https://t.co/jNKzXUG0pH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly, Ronda needed to weather the storm in this one, but it wasn't meant to be https://t.co/iIOexmT7V1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you're right https://t.co/aHuO53rnU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually USADA vs. Cyborg https://t.co/Cvetb0fFOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flawless performance by @Amanda_Leoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amanda Nunes coming out wearing a nose strip. Perhaps it will help her breathing &amp; therefore help her conserve energy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garbrandt Dillashaw will be something else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a moment. Very nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz 10-9 there but too little too late. I have that 48-46 for Garbrandt &amp; new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[39-36 Garbrandt on my unofficial score card. Cruz needs a miracle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough to score, but I have Garbrandt ahead 29-28. Good finish to the third by Cruz though. Championship experience key here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garbrandt looked very composed in that round, but can he maintain it over the distance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to say I am leaning towards a Cruz finish here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does Queen fit into that? https://t.co/mgYdKhJEe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice use of the mic there from Dillashaw &amp; I think he is also spot on in his assessment of the co-main event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice show of class from Lineker there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elliott Marshall giving TJ call out advice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power &amp; good chin no substitute for intelligence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making it look effortless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect Lineker to come out completely wreck less in this round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dillashaw showing he's a level above Lineker in Round 2 there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lineker looks like he is lost in the Matrix right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good 10-9 round from Dillashaw there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice level change there by Dillashaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realising that their reach is the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a big Chilli peppers fan to be honest, but a major improvement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lineker's walkout song just about as exciting as this event so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to the next three bouts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim takes it by split decision, the look on Saffidiene's face when the third scorecard was being read, full of relief &amp; then... "what?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough one to score, but I am leaning 29-28 Kim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your new podcast on itunes? https://t.co/a6Tf2WWkzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robinblackmma Greco Roman experience from Team Quest negating Kim's Judo here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That first round demonstrated one of the inherent weaknesses in Judo throws in the giving up of the back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, I forgot about that https://t.co/nO16chakpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, I think in that case they should give the fighter who made weight the full $100 grand. Still keeps the incen… https://t.co/5z4n1z30eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess it is to discourage further repeats of failing to make weight https://t.co/zvoVMSkE6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you miss weight you are not eligible for a performance bonus full stop https://t.co/3pM7vrXbHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he mean training martial arts? https://t.co/OYNFUrzun3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am picking Borg, Kim, Dillashaw, Cruz &amp; Rousey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta agree. Had it the same. Despite what the crowd think, judges improving as far as active fighters off the bott… https://t.co/VsA8i1rY0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timsylviamma could have told us that https://t.co/6xCdVCW9ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That you did, sir. It's crazy to think he died in prison https://t.co/h2sPC8Aoqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusMacCowan I am with you 100% on that point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallmcgrath4 delighted the mullet is gone. Dreadful hairstyle]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>