<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lefticus neat trick with your profile header image 👌 https://t.co/hN2MXYvaQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae ah, I've mostly been using metal myself recently and was confused since I kind of prefer them, didn't consider the beginner angle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae why not metal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid if I'm honest, I think my favorite is pretty much whichever one I heard most recently, so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid I think my favorite so far is back on black, with smooth criminal and eye of the tiger a close second #mouthmoods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this mentioned by a few people in my feed and decided to check it out, it's quite excellent! https://t.co/SnnG2xrQ5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antumbral at some point I gave up on trying to remember where it had been moved to, now I just use chrome://extensions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh, never noticed before, but the door closing beeps on the train are at slightly different pitches per door, at least on this train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icculus I've watched this so many times I've considered figuring out how to loop it, particularly enjoy the transition from the prev scene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chainedchaos31 Amazon prime video if you were in US/UK, Google play AU has it, assuming iTunes and other digital stores probably too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this was my morning: https://t.co/z5QQHjCRJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millionaire2K @shwood experts expressing concerns send like a hint to me, and point of recount is to determine if there's proof?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Millionaire2K @shwood possible issues with voting machines in those states, afaict they don't expect results to substantially change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thedigitalbug @0xabad1dea @Achifaifa don't forget about "this won't work, oh wait, it does, how?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__hpc__ @zwlegendary @antumbral @sehurlburt also probably most snr/exp dev in a smaller org with mostly juniors, so not exactly typical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__hpc__ @zwlegendary @antumbral @sehurlburt usually not ethical issues, just being better about knowing/using leverage in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__hpc__ @zwlegendary @antumbral @sehurlburt just been much more vocal about what I want/am OK with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zwlegendary @antumbral @sehurlburt @__hpc__ it's caused others to start using theirs too, much easier to confront if you're not alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zwlegendary @antumbral @sehurlburt @__hpc__ I think perhaps the best thing I've done recently is being obvious about using my leverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewtonMark huh, somehow I managed to miss this, guess it's finally time to find out if the man in the high castle is worth watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan yes, though they will be in disguise: https://t.co/QuywHkDw1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan the charater's name is 
Jonathan Pie and this is the YT channel: https://t.co/0PRPkf2YLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan so it occurs to me that while I suggested you might like more of that british guy I never actually mentioned who he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan heat and or a solid thwack will fix that if it ever becomes an issue, it might even dissipate with time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan this seems so obvious in hindsight, would never have occurred to me either. Just don't accidentally make it permanent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it turns out I kind of enjoy cooking https://t.co/yBS6ReNOfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ca1ne @sehurlburt @Biappi https://t.co/g3PstgqjX8 might be useful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllenWebster4th I've used 4coder properly for literally 10 seconds now, and the virtual white-space thing is sublime!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevetranby @chronaldragon almost finished a community re watch, so the much less subtle meowmeowbeans episode might have influenced that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevetranby @chronaldragon this was my takeaway too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Livelyivy I had a teacher in year 7 insist I basically print, started going back a letter at a time in uni, mostly fancy now - esp. f,z,x,b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan limited edition Shenzhen IO printed manual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally: https://t.co/Cs5H7AYiem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yep, exceptions are _definitely_ useful! https://t.co/C9fgntMKlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid of course restarting VS fixed that 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LRT: turns out it's "terminally ill", not dead https://t.co/j5Xj2NwYOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that was a bit of  disaster... https://t.co/3T5KPn5rYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, that went rather poorly. On the upside, I guess yay graphs? https://t.co/a866zvSej5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan I should probably add that's it's kinda TIS-100 where you get to build the circuits, I think you'd enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because my feed is full of depressing US debate tweets: https://t.co/COyuDS7mfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish my Shenzhen IO graphs worked, I have no idea if this is a good result (these low number first tries a… https://t.co/OcscTOpbY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camoprep @FlashbackDaily we have one of these in the office that looks like an iPhone ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rygorous glad it's not just me. Had to make myself focus on just solving some of them to not get stuck trying to get a 'good' solution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shame the post office isn't open on Sundays: https://t.co/AhDKq5BGtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bunch of neat stuff in this thread! https://t.co/YkSoRyvjGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan could work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan hmm, not sure it looks bad enough tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan cool, though I won't be in the office again until next week, could grab it from you on the weekend instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chronaldragon @SanderBoer cool, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chronaldragon curious what you ended up getting? Been considering one myself, 'works out of the box on Linux' is fairly important to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, back to the VPNs etc. I guess? https://t.co/S2P1P66THd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh, why is windows paging *anything* at this point: https://t.co/aoWGGRvFv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently windows thinks I should have almost 50GB of swap space! https://t.co/cEYwBwLvGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently you can't easily just paste into the android emulator: https://t.co/YJqPCmxJKE (the solutions are all ridiculous!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is a thing: https://t.co/BTsYLL83jD , I _think_ I might actually want to play it? and yet I feel a little weird admitting that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icculus this improved my feed a lot, in particular I found a bunch of interesting people when you asked for infosec follow recommendations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might take a little while... https://t.co/MN4hKJm4fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to self, I should do this: https://t.co/yh2JUD7FIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This turned up today: https://t.co/aB2pw8MPnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article contains a hilariously bad graph (look at the numbers): https://t.co/tdua8RmgAC https://t.co/Im9uZhJl4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sigh https://t.co/tyNlf55QqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae fingers vanquished! (that's what you do with evil, right?) https://t.co/RLomj02w8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First pair! https://t.co/Iv2ClxNtJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I have the first half of a pair (happy with attempt #6) https://t.co/dwAB7VFikn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seat is apparently considered a bit of a bellwether: https://t.co/DCc1CIYILl https://t.co/m68SvOrHrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinoBS @drakecode @Jonathan_Blow you can, but the limits imposed would most likely make it not useful here. https://t.co/jvcCAg42rV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new season of OITNB sure is something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid I guess pair programming is a step in that direction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to TV show writer taking about writing room process, makes me wonder if something like it could work for software..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan I take it all back, looks like I just caught it on a few good days at first, seems it just does OK for the most part😞]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan I think it's just really bad at recognising text: https://t.co/fTq7MCbWDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan just impressed that the machine learning stuff works so well most of the time, except when it doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the time I see @picdescbot's results and think we're really getting the hang of this AI thing, then this: https://t.co/nmUpQXZZvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan I don't know what you mean by that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan think I was just too tired that day to realise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan finally got around to reading this, Imposter syndrome in particular I have to remind myself of on almost a weekly basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh https://t.co/vlZdubUDHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid well, that was a slightly disappointing haul... https://t.co/wEHiyaYZ4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently I'm about to pick up ALL THE THINGS! https://t.co/3tY57hAn1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attempt #5, one more to get it exactly right, I think. https://t.co/GAFsoojgAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw Captain America today, glad I decided some movies are worth seeing in a cinema.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human eyes are weird https://t.co/udsYomf0Z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan excellent! If I was less lazy is say we should set one up in Adelaide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan want the fingertips exposed for sense of touch mostly, tried full gloves and found typing/mouse control really weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPaulDuncan yeah, still figuring out exactly how long each finger should be, have just been eyeballing changes, should probably measure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TehNullVoid thinking probably needs one more revision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae eh, I wanted good gloves more than anything else, though I am currently on my third iteration, so you may have a point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae oh, cool, thanks. Will put it to good use once I finally manage a pair of gloves I'm happy with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae does look a little complicated. May try once I've knitted some socks normally, bookmarking for later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae Also, that technique looks amazing/insane!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae thank you for posting all your crafting exploits, it got me back into knitting after ~decade, forgot how much I enjoyed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second attempt, looked up how to do some stuff, fixed some issues, broke some stuff too, on to the next one. https://t.co/jlT2Kqo6iu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First attempt, solely from memory - last time I attempted this was about a decade ago... https://t.co/Usw98Ai6tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theme for today: fuck you, I'll park wherever *I* want https://t.co/TuTTXwKIbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sigh https://t.co/hxfpIQJkWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Johnson, Mr. Speaker, Mr. Chief Justice, President Eisenhower, Vice President Nixon, President Truman, Reverend Clergy, fell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript is amazing/terrifying: https://t.co/5SfzLJQ8q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally saw Star Wars today, seemed like just a decent sci-fi action movie, first time I've kinda regretted going in spoiled though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, definitely renting that one... https://t.co/XhjJ1ke8Vc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Light showers" - apparently this means rain like it's the middle of winter.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>