<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! Catch my Global TV February forecast right here!  https://t.co/TMWQlGaP1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: Avoid shopping &amp; big decisions fr. 12:30 PM to 5 PM EST today (9:30 AM - 2 PM PST). After, the Moon moves from Pisces into Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oops correction for MONDAY:
We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Pisces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY:
After 11:15 AM EST (8:15 AM PST) today, we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Pisces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business until 9:45 pm PST (6:45 pm PST. The Moon is in Aquarius. 
Happy New Year!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The New Moon is in Aquarius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Capricorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good observation: in Dick Van Dyke TV show,  Mary T.M was focused on friends and career, not family and husband. Breakthrough of stereotype.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you can film police. No, they can't seize your phone, lawyer says https://t.co/OFLk8LrHss
Retweeting intimidating police behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you can film police. No, they can't seize your phone, lawyer says https://t.co/OFLk8LrHss
(Shows terrible actions by Toronto police.).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Mary Tyler Moore (age 80) born Dec 29, 1936 - Sun in Capricorn; Moon in Cancer &amp; Pisces Rising. What a smile! Gave pleasure to millions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Capricorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEEK: WED: OK; THURS: OK;  FRI: OK (after 4 AM EST); SAT: OK; SUN:  OK after 11:30 AM EST (8:30 Am PST)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY:Avoid shopping or big decisions from 12:30 PM - 6 PM EST. (9:30 AM- 3 PM PST After, the Moon moves from Sagittarius to Capricorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Review of Shadows: You and Your Future by Georgia Nicols https://t.co/vN7F4ZBI8m via @fatfemnistwitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY:  After 8:15 PM EST today, (5:15 PM PST)  avoid shopping or big decisions. The Moon is in Scorpio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrik Sedin records 1,000th career point against former teammate https://t.co/QAc5KoXhuO  How cool to score w/ Luongo who congratulated him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Scorpio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: Avoid shopping etc. fr. 3:45 AM to 5:30 PM (12:45 Am - 2:30 PM PST) EST today. After that, the Moon moves from Libra into Scorpio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama is Leo w/ Aquarius rising -a king who acts for the people. Donald Trump is Gemini w/ Leo rising -a talker who acts like a king.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama’s 1,385 commutation grants is more than the total number of commutations issued by  the past 12 presidents combined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Libra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBC News nabs dozens of Canadian Screen Awards nominations https://t.co/3YlOy6BmOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: After 6:30 AM EST today,(3:30 AM PST)  we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Libra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SyfyChick13 Yes! I can tell you LOTS about your coming year. Here is 3000 wds about each of the 12 signs for 2017.  https://t.co/18ECTJpX1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Virgo (until 10 PM PST).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Virgo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you know you're not in Manhattan https://t.co/oZjq3oaZ4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY: Avoid shopping etc.from 10 AM to 11 PM EST today (7 AM to 8 PM PST) . After that, the Moon moves from Leo into Virgo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY the 13th: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Leo. Good day to party :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Michelle Obama appears on “Tonight Show,” leaves people in tears https://t.co/l8jBkALlX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caution: Avoid shopping etc. from 6:15 AM - 7:15 PM EST. After, the Moon moves from Cancer into Leo. Cancer Full Moon peaks at 6:34 AM EST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep is Cancer, Moon in Taurus &amp; Leo Rising. Donald Trump is Gemini, Moon in Sagittarius &amp; Leo Rising. Two Leo Risings facing off !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: Avoid shopping &amp; big decisions from 4:30 PM to 6 PM EST (1:30 PM - 3 PM PST). After that, the Moon moves from Gemini into Cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEEK: MON: OK; TUES: avoid 4:30 pm - 6 pm EST;  WED: OK; THURS: avoid 6:30 am-7:30 pm EST:  FRI: OK;  SAT: avoid 10 am  - 11 pm EST: SUN: OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Gemini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hanklerfish_  and how is that working out for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNDAY: Avoid shopping or big decisions until 5:30 PM EST today   (2:30 PM PST). After that, the Moon moves from Taurus into Gemini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNDAY: We have the "all clear" to shop and make decisions until 9:15 PM EST today. The Moon is in Taurus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: Avoid shopping etc.from 1:30 PM to 3:30 PM EST today (10:30 AM to 12:30 PM PST). After that, the Moon moves from Aries into Taurus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon changes signs at 11:15 AM EST from Pisces to Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my 2017 forecast w/ @donaldsonkyle on Breakfast Television @BT_Vancouver  Sagitt.,Capricorn, Aquarius, Pisces https://t.co/ZocFkwB5s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAY!  Here's  my 2017 forecast w/ @donaldsonkyle  on Breakfast Television @BT_Vancouver  Leo, Virgo, Libra &amp; Scorpio https://t.co/4keDPbfXJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's  my 2017 forecast with @donaldsonkyle  on Breakfast Television @BT_Vancouver  Aries, Taurus, Gemini &amp; Cancer  https://t.co/0P31RqDueu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Pisces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAY!! Here is Youtube of my 2017 Forecast with Global TV talking with @LynnColliar  ENJOY!       https://t.co/P7zRl9hJW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mverchere Mercury is retrograde until Jan 8; however if buying a car, computer or cell phone ($$) then wait until Jan 28. happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Mercury retrograde is creating havoc for ground transportation and communications. Power out; cars in ditches! Delays. Yikes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second try 4 U to hear my 1 hr long 2017 forecasts with @jodyvance  Does this one work?
https://t.co/YRpnhhmZeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear my one-hour forecast for 2017  (All 12 signs)  with @jodyvance on  on CKMW (AM 980)  https://t.co/QPK4UBG0Y6 . Lengthy and detailed!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: After 5 AM EST today (2 Am PST), we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Pisces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeypurple sorry no more appearances at the moment plan – and certainly nothing in Toronto but how nice to get your note! Happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OOPS! Correction!! SUNDAY Jan 1, 2017  
We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aquarius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostHunter7 @LynnColliar  So true!! There is an old US Army wives' saying: Three moves are worth a fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcbryer  Send email w/ birth info.get ONE for your Sun sign..and one for your rising Sign if you know birth time georgia@georgianicols.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: January 1, 2017   
We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aquarius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aquarius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALERT!  Catch me tomorrow morning (Friday) on Breakfast Television for your 2017 forecast in 3 segments: 8:10 am; 8:20 am &amp; 8:40 am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Capricorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 Annual Forecasts in the Province out on SUNDAY Jan 1.  (They're 1/3 length of ones for sale on Kindle &amp; on my website.#2017predictions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEEK AHEAD:  WED: OK after 10:30 am EST (7:30 am PST):  THURS: OK;   FRI: avoid all day until 8:45 pm EST (5:45 pm PST) ;  SAT: OK;  SUN: OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Carrie Fisher Oct 21, 1956 Sun in Libra; Moon in Taurus &amp; Capricorn Rising daughter of Debbie Reynolds b 1932 &amp; Eddie Fisher (1928-2010)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: Until 8:30 PM EST today (5:30 Pm PST) , we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Sagittarius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY:  Boxing Day!   We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Sagittarius. (Go crazy.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY: We have the "all clear" to shop &amp; do business. The Moon is in Scorpio.  SUNDAY: Avoid shopping &amp; big decisions until 10:30 PM EST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: After 9:45 AM EST today, (6:45 AM PST) we have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Scorpio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CRTC declares broadband Internet a ‘basic telecom service’ https://t.co/Ork84XDPki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeypurple Yes! each sign has a planetary ruler. both Taurus &amp; Libra are ruled by Venus. Hence their close connection, especially to beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Libra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difference Makers: North Van teen gives the shirt off his back, and then some https://t.co/AJcgPpgF6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY:Avoid shopping etc for one hour from 8:45 PM to 9:45 PM (5:45 PM to 6:45 PM  PST). After that, the Moon moves from Virgo into Libra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillageCakeLady  Some weeks certain servers eat my column. Lately it's yahoo.  Before that it was hotmail.  The column does go out. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEEK: TUES: Avoid 8:45 PM-9:45 PM EST (5:45 PM - 6:45 PM PST); WED: OK; THURS: Avoid after 2:15 PM EST; FRI: OK after 9:45 AM EST; SAT OK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Virgo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY:
We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Leo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love #johnshorthouse!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Shopping times:  FRIDAY: (today) good; SATURDAY:  good;  SUNDAY: Avoid between 11:45 am - 1 pm EST ( 8:45 am- 10 am PST)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: After 8:30 AM EST, (5:30 AM PST( we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Leo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Journalist: “I’m Back From Syria. The Media Is Lying To You!” - https://t.co/H8Tm8F7Dj8 via @KnowledgSharing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillageCakeLady  Send me an email and my web genius guy will check this out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: After 4:30 PM EST today (1:30 PM PST) , avoid shopping or major decisions. The Moon is in Cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: After 7:30 AM EST today (4:30 AM PST), we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Cancer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I had tears in my eyes holding her:' Skin-to-skin care for preemies pays off decades on https://t.co/Km58hrOJPw   (Who is surprised?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TUESDAY: We have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Full Moon in Gemini peaks at 7:05 PM EST (4:04 PST).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Week ahead - finer distinction on TUES.  Tues is OK for EST. but for PST avoid after 9:45 pm PST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MONDAY: After 8 AM EST today (5 AM PST), we have the "all clear" to shop and do business. The Moon is in Gemini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pulling children out of Nepal's prisons @CNN https://t.co/qGDfT1BkbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUNDAY: Until 11 PM EST today (8 PM PST), we have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in. Taurus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATURDAY: After 8 AM EST today, (5 Am PST( we have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Taurus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY:  Sorry... (correction!!) We have the "all clear" to shop today until 8 pm EST (5 PM PST). Not good for BC evening shoppers. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FRIDAY: After 8 PM EST today (5 AM EST) , avoid shopping or big decisions. The Moon is in Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!  John Glenn was the oldest person to travel in space at age 77!!   What a guy!!   (Nothing backward about how he went forward!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Glenn b July 18, 1921. Sun in Cancer; Moon in Capricorn &amp; Sagittarius Rising. Age 95: a long lived Sagittarius and a true traveler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THURSDAY: After 5:30 AM EST today  (2:30 Am PST),  we have the "all clear" today to shop and do business. The Moon is in Aries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WEDNESDAY: Caution: Avoid shopping or big decisions after 9 AM EST today (6 AM PST). The Moon is in Pisces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is! YAY!!  Your December forecasts for all 12 signs!  https://t.co/LZHE40atuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's raise the $1,000,000 the White Helmets would've received in Nobel Prize money. Give to the]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>