<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @_waykay why not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shikadilord wouldn't sand be bad for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marcus_Mosher 90 for brown what am I missing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@El_Knid @Cianaf yeah could be right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf yeah its weird, why were teams so bad this yearY seems to be why the games were bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DynastyFrank tbh he's not good anymore he just has arod. Dude can't separate. Until last year he was gr8 tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillEddowesNFL also he was horrendous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHQ_Jordan kind of makes loss more painful. This team was so stacked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm looks like cover 4? Do we draft D and risk O losing power in effort to be complete or just stay dominant offense just a thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corryjoel even with injury age price concerns doesn't qb market mean romo can net a 1 or 2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YankeesGod2722 @JoeyIckes Yeah ppl mad about the spike this is what actually cost us the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveGalloNFL bradford gets a 1 but Romo can't? It's at least possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyIckes thought overall he was fine outside of last play. Prevent defense never works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JC1053 Yeah blitz and make a tackle they won't have time to get that far down field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanKenyonNFL 80% chance to win nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shikadilord I've been wrong about this with milk before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shikadilord sims are cheap as chips though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shikadilord umm doesn't this happen all the time on wesnoth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf u into bdsm then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KP_Show @Cianaf is GB OL as good as advertised or A rod just make them look great? Thnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf OL less important due to Rodgers' pocket presence and ability to give them leverage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @starwars @ShoreSportsNJ looks like spam. I only gave it a chance because I enjoy your tweets. Just my opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @starwars @ShoreSportsNJ I enjoy some of your articles (i realise this isn't one, great vid tho) but imo the way u tweet them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam how many games the oline win last year? Or the decent running game? Maybe @bburkeESPN can back me up? (I voted Dak obviously)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ASchatz what percentage of interceptable passes are intercepted in NFL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanKenyonNFL just compare last year rankings to this year's play for the answers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @CowboysAddicts I know I know record isn't good way to measure qb's lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @CowboysAddicts Dak is up there and Elliott as RB is alot lower (still love him).Dak gr8 bar 2-3 games and won alot of games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @CowboysAddicts I think unless u give one of them most the credit for boys success then neither win map. Personally I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation so most likely a rematch of "the catch" game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 I mostly agree with your point though, just don't know if this is best example of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 well oak mia are exceptions and also most teams without elite qb aren't expected to make much noise in playoffs this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyIckes true but qb yoyo ain't the answer. Time to sleep in the bed we made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimTrotter_NFL if there's one change nfl needs to make its that all penalties should be reviewable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCoolBTB mmm idk I kinda think the offense just had a bad day rather min d had a good one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF how do u grade Santos on game winning kick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf but we have no home field adv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF this guy must've been bad to be worst at every position. Dat versatility tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf everyone talks about this play like the spike had an effect on the CB, had none, just a great throw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpompei is this David guy a serial blocker? He's blocked me and I've never tweeted him lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam @CrashCombs @mikefreemanNFL u had me confused lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffRisdon when u play madden on highest difficulty and don't even stop the accuracy meter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr @KMart_LI and none good lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FantasyDouche @Eric_Edholm yes. Surely some1 will pay big for him why does no one talk about this option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Mike is that the most separation you've ever seen outside of slips in NFL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Mike did u give him a -3 on the Beasley TD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @thomasjthacker should add option year only for first rounders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @_anthonynash how can we ever really know who's a good leader?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf damn this got alot of rt's must've been posted somewhere biggish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @NFLResearch u can't just sat this and not expand lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phorts @MikeClayNFL ha yes I never read them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 @Marcus_Mosher isn't pushing allowed near LOS? Tbh I'm not strong on the exact rules on this play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 @Marcus_Mosher well just based off what is normally called, pushing is rarely called and jersey grabbing is called alot, also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 @Marcus_Mosher dez contact allowed tho. Jersey grabbing is not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 @DeanBlandino @TroyVincent23 @NFLFootballOps @NFLprguy to be fair they changed rule after dez catch added the be runner part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CowboysNation @SBNation idk bailey's stats on long kicks but from there he'd surely have at least 25% chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marcus_Mosher great teams usually are great on one side of the ball so imo we need to just hope the offense is elite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I click next on the leave a review page nothing happens and I can't find anywhere on your site to contact you about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceMcWicked @iRogue @mizjwilliams @OliverCarle @Dovil @GrumpyYetAmusin @Megapope green wasn't great I was holding out hope for red :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr52pickup lol some1 might pay u for this as an article tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izach120 @Marcus_Mosher Yeah this is why ppl hate cowboys fans. Such homers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Louie @PFF are your screens brighter than the sun or is the photo making it look like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar @Cole_Kev I see this alot from many corners tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF @FO_ScottKacsmar was it u discussing all round team vs one side of ball focused team better? Here's your answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlSafchick ugh I used imo twice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlSafchick Yeah imo this result shows that alot of fantasy players don't understand real football imo as this should be Darby by a mile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DMooreNFL @KDDrummondNFL @King_Yunn @JonahTulsNFL that's just like, your opinion man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EyeoftheGator @Delta the real issue here is why doesn't your seat line up with the seat in front? Is this common in US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlSafchick dynasty Fitz, d Allen, d Henry or Goff (non start up). Thnx in advance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar all the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlSafchick Idk players union is weak. They usually lose the negotiations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald $2 sounds too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar mmm great for me altho some plot holes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewBrandt didn't u get the memo that you're only allowed to say good things about people when they die?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheers_chun by being in town I would guess they can charge what they want tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheers_chun why would a supermarket in town be cheap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar pays not to be too good hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregolsen88 @PFF none of the criticisms of PFF I've seen contain actual arguments/evidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm show much a good running game helps a qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn @greaterwgtn @WgtnCC I matched this chick on tinder lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@my3rdTrip @OCC44 u know we have the internet right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southern_Philly why I like what browns doing. trading down in 1st/getting as many 1-2nds as possible one of few things u can do to win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fbgchase unfortunately this seems like something that will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fbgchase whatever man I trust gut over these analytics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenGretch but nfl coaches don't like x player so neither should we cause they know what they're doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheers_chun I'm leaving twitter rn lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar hoyer goat confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar @Cianaf maybe it doesn't matter much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaymieRay lol way to remember. And obviously not i can barely understand how i thought that now, i think i was bitter from owning him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Southern_Philly @Dmoney87_ @JimmyKempski broncos just won superbowl without qb so can be done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeClayNFL broncos seems most surprising omission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 also, we might not pick high enough to get a qb for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 my overall point was he could get injured and his contract will screw us regardless if we have a backup plan or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 yeah would only happen if he got badly injured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 well I was assuming we weren't talking about this season, overall point was teams eat dead money from cut players all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 @FO_ScottKacsmar @ShroffishBoil @Dustinbradley69 true, but will require a crappy season to get that pick, which we can avoid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toner564 @FO_ScottKacsmar @ShroffishBoil @Dustinbradley69 I see your point but in reality no one's uncuttable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FO_ScottKacsmar @ShroffishBoil @Dustinbradley69 so beats taking the most important position which the Cowboys might not have one soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam @BSDtweet lol u waste so much time on stupid homers xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlSafchick like qb value, RB's expensive but nice, dislike Austin, decker, Matthews, and kelce due to fear of low tds]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>