<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe some rich Marxists should hire Cambridge Analytica and see if they can get the revolution going? https://t.co/SSIZMuKTrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister says an independent crime stats agency for Qld is on the way, as #whistleblowers claim cops fudged figures: https://t.co/rtzLnsrk4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Scientists Are Rebelling Against Trump | Science | National Geographic https://t.co/lKOo7um617]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, there's this bloke who connects it to his theory that team Trump is removing obstacles to unchallenged power… https://t.co/dSIXN6yje3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good theory. https://t.co/murNkWC2vA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#smallbusiness minister was pleased by 2015-16 #procurement statistics (doesn't mention last two years were better) https://t.co/3Z1W2XT8kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: How Does Trump's Immigration Freeze Square With His Business Interests?  https://t.co/ztoqtWpELd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink’s debt-recovery disaster https://t.co/hDtpu5QR85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged neo-Nazi reportedly plotted shooting at New South Wales mall https://t.co/GYcVFf3luB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government's favourite transparency body denounces war on Triggs https://t.co/xU2gH1Y0uG via @crikey_news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#doom Nuclear 'Doomsday Clock' ticks closest to midnight in 64 years https://t.co/G2BoUpmvKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took a peek at the Shakespearian insult for tomorrow. Wasn't disappointed https://t.co/MZrFhrQZuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink's @HankJongen says 'Let's talk about the facts' but mostly makes tedious semantic arguments IMO: https://t.co/4tLrlvJb0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are the biggest cyber security risk, says the PM, as govt reacts to US claims of Russian information warfare: https://t.co/k1tG8JiTei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than a million goes missing from the Mint, misappropriated last May: https://t.co/k0r0cjAIGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual a quote from The Simpsons describes the 'post-truth' era quite well: https://t.co/4rkCzoGWet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junk food industry shaping health policies at public's expense: study https://t.co/OFsNGKHwxx via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Centrelink said their current plan is "compliance reviews will not be undertaken prior to 2010-11 financial year"… https://t.co/xNDrPvXNbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a future for Australia's Digital Transformation Agency? https://t.co/fDCMNLTzTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As expected https://t.co/BaFicb4fo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50%+ of reader feedback: "You wrote about [broad topic] and didn't include [my opinion]. Anything else about [topic] is wrong and bad."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's essential': outback workers fight ABC decision to ditch shortwave radio https://t.co/f9pZTMJX5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC unmoved by pleas to save shortwave radio service for remote areas https://t.co/PAFJ7uPbkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Wyatt gets Indigenous Health and Aged Care portfolios, supporters say he should replace Scullion. https://t.co/5qnn1xunol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA pollies swap $6750/yr travel expense reimbursement for same allowance they get whether they use it or not. Wow. https://t.co/cG6rhzXGC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @TheMandarinAU Headline is just paraphrasing his odd claim that the issue is “staff do not welcome technology driven change”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reheated from 2012 by @MarkusMannheim: if you're angry about politicians rorts, don't think about public servants: https://t.co/X8wlz1TAfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious claims of the #notmydebt campaign yet. The department says they're inaccurate again:… https://t.co/D1GW3IDbUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink staff told not to fix mistakes in debt notices – whistleblower https://t.co/nuXGISoKjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The federal government is open to outsourcing a new website security provider that would run a bug bounty program: https://t.co/h0Jys6qU17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone please shout the ABC a few boom mics so the questions in press conferences are audible on News24 every time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday @mikebairdMP gives public servants a very well-received pep talk in the 2015 Garran Oration: https://t.co/ggOf5yiCJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hypothetical money's on Berejiklian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auditor-general declines to look over Centrelink debt recovery as its staff are warned of "boundaries".. https://t.co/fvPmU1O10J  #notmdebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dept denied this claim after publication, says all payroll records kept as per Archives Act and compliance reviews… https://t.co/Fp7SO7zehi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink staff warned over 'criminal' leaks amid debt recovery row https://t.co/HZZUImW0H9 - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dept of Immigration and Border Protection failed 'Outsourcing 101' with #Manus and #Nauru garrison services: https://t.co/M5D7fwIvQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, great reporting! https://t.co/dQNziMSTpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in October: "...Hank Jongen did not say why his department had not told the Ombudsman the truth." https://t.co/bA52KOPhDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contracting failure: that time when Britain outsourced a fleet to transport convicts to Australia 200 years ago and… https://t.co/7LSerk0cas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal corruption watchdog needed, say 80 per cent of Australians: poll https://t.co/PvAGqim4Q9 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out for the wind in #Canberra! #sailing club instruments recorded 53 knot gust 6m off the lake at 4.12pm. That's just under 100 kmh/h!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but, the thing is, that's not really true at all. Arguably, he's weakly of that view, under some circumstances. https://t.co/jX0iO4fZtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey looking across the Australian workforce shows public sector workers are most likely to join the union: https://t.co/NEyA9csZBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curtin Law School taxation expert Helen Hodgson: Centrelink should learn from the ATO's lighter touch: https://t.co/NzxJtWroaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government knew about discrepancies in data-matching system before reducing human oversight https://t.co/GcczxZBeiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goes together well with "Note to Centrelink: Australian workers' lives have changed."  https://t.co/IFIBlncugM… https://t.co/NfSobtZ15D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to find new ways to measure the Australian labour force https://t.co/tbp4O9X8FI via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["MP/Senator's expense claims all clearly legitimate" That's the story I want to read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal Centrelink records reveal flaws behind debt recovery system

https://t.co/UO89KN69RM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink service staff must not process debt disputes https://t.co/e78nAPwnXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetowncrier @Mumbrellanews  "... during Nine’s 178-hour long daily afternoon news coverage" hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink seeks advanced customer aggression training and looks to virtual assistants as #notmydebt crisis hits: https://t.co/B1HNa3SaAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This system so very obviously just provides a slightly helpful basic indication and needs human oversight to work: https://t.co/V7ai5WZvoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACCC advice implies that normally, the onus of proof is on the one claiming a disputed debt is owed... #notmydebt https://t.co/tKY0dIC6hB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government has brought in 8 corporate heavy hitters to oversee the #NDIS and retained 4 founding board members: https://t.co/6rD91tgo8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANZSOG recruits Queensland's man in London to take over from Gary Banks as dean: https://t.co/TIvHd1V499]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister Alan Tudge confirms he will not stop the automatic debt warning letters from Centrelink:  https://t.co/1ZTO43Nwj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Centrelink debacle: How we got into this mess" - Coalition ramps up simplistic data-matching program Labor created: https://t.co/cwm8Sfj3iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Griffiths_John @brisbanetimes I don't know of any clear diff. I don't always use the word staffer, but when I do it's in a suggested tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['They don't care about average Australians': Centrelink staffer speaks out about debt controversy https://t.co/8Zeg4iyw0a via @brisbanetimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bipartisan politicisation of the public service https://t.co/EBditRUzVC via @FinancialReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey: WA Department of Aboriginal Affairs staff far more negative about their agency than other public servants: https://t.co/IzeXk7JcYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or, more than half of a years worth of fortnightly newstart payments for one person https://t.co/rjrh90pD4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice lookin flag https://t.co/1suIlCMJeH https://t.co/MGrq8RP5lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[East Timor tears up oil and gas treaty with Australia https://t.co/jRmKeGbIST - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to take a while. Ombudsman confirms own-motion investigation into Centrelink debt recovery complaints: https://t.co/WKpdMuTNBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you recently commit the crime of accessing welfare? Juice Media's honest government ads are pretty fantastic. https://t.co/FH6sIAR88F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink crisis 'cataclysmic' says PM's former head of digital transformation https://t.co/dXLntNVyoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian Porter's tips for ministers: changes to the pension asset test take effect January 1? Hold your press conference on New years eve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bjelke-Petersen's 30-year-old secret documents revealed https://t.co/k3ppyFQwJE via @brisbanetimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull's former digital tsar says 'blind faith' in data led to the Centrelink debt debacle (via @BIAUS) https://t.co/5kkulcdJpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will government techno fails be big news again in 2017? https://t.co/zJKfIrUstp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery as NATO Auditor General is found shot dead in suspicious circumstances https://t.co/jkFcJSlBIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently the @marieclaire feature "Welcome to Death Island" wasn't up to Mr Pezzullo's standards (it's a high bar) https://t.co/8r4aAiN6sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, the idea you can get ppl to "make better life choices leading to a virtuous circle" almost seems 'tailored' fo… https://t.co/g3vgE63c70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some stakeholders not so happy about ATO's borkened website. Views ranging from "absolute joke" to "beyond a joke" https://t.co/qAWJVFSv2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The PM must be pleased with how Rosemary Huxtable has filled the big shoes of Jane Halton at the Dept of Finance: https://t.co/igNkCmV4Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law Society slams push to privatise state "jewel" https://t.co/GzQwd7zUC9 via @indaily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government's welfare crackdown #fail is exactly how not to do #data and #digital government  https://t.co/JuP2tNQlRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian embassy defends diplomats' driving skills in Canberra. C'mon mate we've all seen those Russian dashcam vids https://t.co/3tQDO3KcbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New arrangements for putting a value on Snowy Hydro | The Mandarin https://t.co/aq0vwNqVBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications are now open for second round of the APS Data Fellowship program: https://t.co/pAJ6ZPXdH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The benefits of "workforce flexibility" for employers are clear. For workers, not so much. https://t.co/0HQyR2nSnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASIC registry sell-off sunk. Will data become free? |The Mandarin https://t.co/4UvtrSlWxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANU's long running Australian Election Study 2016 results tomorrow night:   https://t.co/42McfyPeIt via @anumedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not much now, but a new myWA website will take shape over 2017. All members of public invited to help build it: https://t.co/9xb1KxfKkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who'd want to lead #ICAC after the "sustained, personal, vituperative attack" on Megan Latham inc. by News Corp?  https://t.co/KmieUY3ddX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone supports corruption fighters as long as they're not too effective, says head of WA's #ICAC counterpart: https://t.co/UEjGVlZJ3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA minister settles defamation suit brought by former Corrections Dept CFO, blames department's 'incorrect' advice: https://t.co/ZKDvV3aZNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Transformation Agency cuts 22 projects down to five https://t.co/sPv1V6HpId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bubblers aka drinking fountains in captivity. I prefer free range https://t.co/hCuQgASKgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsourcing government computers supply could breach security: union https://t.co/DLYI85D5kA - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports vary wildly: Aquaman film will create 600 or maybe 1200 jobs, and inject like $100 or idk maybe $160 million into the economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noel Pearson says release of confidential school audits ‘unlawful’ https://t.co/1MnHFhcH6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cvharrop pretty sure it's an MSM conspiracy. I was a two-spacer once.. till I took a news writing course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was on the department's advice that the minister threw the public servant under the bus, he claims: https://t.co/kADVxvag7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Stephen Donaghue restore the Solicitor-General's independence? Find out when Australian Parliament returns... https://t.co/f6YrGe95YA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queensland premier has "concerns" about the proposal (which she can't put into words very well tbh)… https://t.co/kNhehiqBKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scullion’s disastrous indigenous work-for-the-dole mainly leads to financial penalties https://t.co/nFcOGouu0I via @crikey_news]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>