<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Orlaweafer1 stop orla can't deal with him vile aswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Jess she's honest why else would you wanna go into big brother and not want to win it ðŸ™‰ fair play to her she gets a hard time #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that Nicola one I swear slyest bitch even though the twins are annoying pity she wouldn't stand up to speidi like that ðŸ˜³ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie is so up Nicholas Arse ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜· absolute snake cant stand them ðŸ˜¡ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually feel sorry for Heidi she's mentally drained from that mental case control freak #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you haven't got half of your shopping done and realise Christmas is 1 week ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜° https://t.co/2an4VpHGY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't even deal thinking of all the people that spend Christmas by themselves ðŸ˜° no one should be alone this time of year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate a bragger âœ‹ðŸ½ ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jodiemitch20 that is the cutest thing ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best times being a kid at Christmas ðŸ™Š trying to bait down at every chance you get ðŸ˜… #needtogotoiletma https://t.co/9dbLHBxSEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love her ðŸ˜ðŸ˜° so humble and down to earth #KatieTaylor ðŸ’šâ˜˜ðŸ’ªðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Katie Taylor â˜˜ðŸ’š #nationaltreasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obsessed Vikki Dougan style from the 50s ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyGough can't wait Lu ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caoimheeyx only said that earlier Caoi it's one of those days ðŸ’¤ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body is aching my skin even hurts ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜° the flu is brewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Accountant ðŸ™ŒðŸ½ brilliant movie ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jodiemitch20 @Ryanair thanks JS dm your number xxxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the chillness of #ASeatAtTheTable #Solange ðŸ™ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casiechambers @Jodiemitch20 witches all the same though ðŸ˜¹ðŸ™ƒ https://t.co/C39lgqFgY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That heat is vile ðŸ˜·ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished "the night of" such a good watch ðŸ™‰ðŸ™ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect weather to just nap and watch movies all day â˜”ï¸ðŸ’¨ https://t.co/eGhpiWZkv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally any sight of a bed and I get sleepy ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Orlaweafer1 happy birthday orla ðŸ˜ŠðŸŽˆ have a good one X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sticky heat I can't deal ðŸ˜· wake me up when it's winter â˜”ï¸â„ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious girl crush on Cassie ðŸ˜ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_lornaxx oh my god ðŸ™‰ðŸ™‰ I'd say you're delighted great present ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn you always say no in the whatsapp ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ take a leaf out of that book they can't sack ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn say no you header ðŸ™‰ bastids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kings of Leon / Beautiful war is a favourite ðŸŽ§.ðŸŽ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisebrennan__ yeah exactly at least you'll be comfortable and won't be sweating last minute tryna get money together you did right ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisebrennan__ ah here Louise ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I was like she had to have gone in all by now ðŸ™ˆ will fly now though .. Shit can't wait to be back to meðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always have  the urge for a nap after a Sunday roast ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#socialnetworkillusions https://t.co/KPB6rHgd0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love lateysha ðŸ™‰ðŸ™‰ so down to earth #bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking bitch that Georgina one is, so bitter no wonder she went so early ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜· #bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_lornaxx boils my blood can't stand him not one tear coming out of his eye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ you know it's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn you could definitely perfect this. https://t.co/Di4eacmp0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and I wish Andy would shut the fuckkkkkk up such a pest #bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boils my blood how fake that Jackson fella is ðŸ‘¿ #bbuk find more water in a desert than those crocodile tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn @DanCrimmins couldn't be arsed doing all that ðŸ˜¹âœ‹ðŸ½ðŸ‘ŽðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanCrimmins @MeganMorannn which one did you download Dan I read you can't get it on iPhone ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn @DanCrimmins not available on the iPhone Meg ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh they all actually go through my brain but can't stop watching it #bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That pancake argument on big brother fs ðŸ™‰ hilarious ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this little island we call home so proud to be Irish #COYBIG ðŸ’šâ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We put up a fight ðŸ’šâ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always too good to be true for us poor Irish ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FM104Phoneshow traveller children? The worst type of kids you deal with in retail are actually upper class kids majority of them !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanCrimmins literally out of this world the city was on wheels ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GAME OF THRONES!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganjohnston_ think it all the time Meg ðŸ™‰ headers leave nothing for the imagination ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeeeee she's my sister ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜ƒ #lovespreads #thestoneroses https://t.co/8rGdWVftAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't get over the #stoneroses best gig I was ever at ðŸ‹ðŸ‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a weekend, Manchester never fails what a city ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchester today for the stone roses tomorrow ðŸ‘€ðŸ‹ðŸ‹ðŸ‹ðŸ‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn be massive ðŸ˜ your hair grows so quick as well so no need to worry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UoME7nnEfV can't stop listening ðŸ™‰ roll on the etihad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional wreck after Beaches ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜¥ favourite chic flick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Irish lad is gas in big brother ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgot about this little gem https://t.co/h5hrqvWikR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cassie's photo https://t.co/acvrREsOOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn sorry I've go to 9 o'clock mass.. Grand be in at 12 .. I've to go to that one too sorry ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jodiemitch20 willy cough x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_lornaxx this is what will happen you next ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/R5GTrsIppa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gameofthronesscenes's video https://t.co/tdj1ZmQDCk ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyGough we love you to Aunty Lu Lu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally balling reading all those stories on Humans of New York ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stan Smiths #adidas #courtvintage https://t.co/hY2xHaBHFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jodiemitch20 #Angelica ðŸ˜cute though ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieWarner scum!! They'll get what they deserve ðŸ’›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_lornaxx orange ones all the way l dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caoimheeyx @Aoifeob125 I need a new book! Is it good? What's it about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting the Sopranos from scratch ðŸ“º #toniii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud #allirelandchampion ðŸ™ŒðŸ½  https://t.co/LwdP1NYMbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's getting closer to Game of Thrones âš”ðŸ’€ðŸ™€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieWarner so much too look forward to Kell ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ it'll fly x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love when Red hot chilli peppers come on shuffle ðŸ‘ðŸ½ ðŸŒž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn best way to be though especially in that weather ðŸ™ˆ &amp; sure wrights tomorrow for you's, did you sort an outfit?ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stand those people that think they can speak to people anyway they want âœ‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caoimheeyx rotten nothing like the original âœ‹ðŸ½ and time outs are my favourites ðŸ˜¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why on earth did they feel the need to change timeout bars ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganMorannn love that ðŸ’›ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SHANNONSiMONE I do be trying not to look at the mirror ðŸ˜°ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No I'm sorry I think those extensions in North West' hair are a disgrace âœ‹ðŸ½ if any normal mother done that they'd be slated ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunnnnaShoe I think so too ðŸ‘¿ Mark definitely knew how to manipulate the media and Jury and so good and playing the racial card âœ‹ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunnnnaShoe it's mad the amount of manipulating that went on isn't it I never realised, do you think he was guilty? ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannenmcgrane9 happy 21st birthday ðŸ˜Š have a good one! ðŸŽˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You honestly don't realise how ugly you are until you're sitting looking in a mirror with your hair wet in the hair dressers ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aoifeob125 did Ann leave you out the back again? @Aileengoughh ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jodiemitch20 he's actually rocking the new look fair play ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly don't know what I would do without my Mam ðŸ’›ðŸ˜© never too old for some tlc in her eyes ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aileengoughh there now and that what Mary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only @Aileengoughh would mention herself in a comment on Facebook! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™„ #leaveherbesure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caoimheeyx ðŸ’› thinking of you Caoi x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 nephews won the Dublin championships.. all Ireland's next ðŸ€ðŸ’ªðŸ½@MONKSTOWNBC #burstingwithpride ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanieTToner I know you weren't seanie t ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚ Awh thanks so much ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanieTToner don't be jeal when it's your birthday you'll get some too we all love you millions ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>