<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see media coverage of Higgins by @The_RiotACT  Please read @Gordon_R_Ramsay @YvetteSBerry @canberratimes https://t.co/V32pxYUMBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After watching Trump news yesterday, calming therapy is: Anders Roland &amp; Finn Olafsson guitar "Back to the present" cd. Relief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to think of what to tweet Trumpy, but all I can think of is "enter hamar". 
@realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible service from Beacon Lighting Gungahlin. Ordered &amp; paid on phone, they said pick up, but when pick up, a big stuff up.Waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need one of these in West Belco for 45,000 humans. Tight, cosy squeeze... VJ @canberratimes @fischerkim https://t.co/Ekat1S59ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it legal to gamble/bet on: will Kippax get weekend blue rapid buses before the 2 tram lines are finished? We could maybe bet on it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there plans for a weekend blue rapid bus to Kippax, as I have requested from the ACT government? What is the truth? @Transport_CBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Kippax get a weekend blue rapid bus in 2017 or not? Your office said probably yes in 2016, but now I hear no.Truth? @MeeganFitzMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it acceptable that West Belco is the only area without any of the new drink fountains in CBR? Why? @MeeganFitzMLA @Gordon_R_Ramsay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it acceptable that West Belco is the only area without any of the new drink fountains in CBR? @The_RiotACT @abccanberra @JohnThistleton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it acceptable that West Belco is the only area without any of the new drink fountains in CBR? @ABarrMLA @canberratimes @kirstenlawsonCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it acceptable that West Belco is the only area without any of the new drink fountains in CBR? @carolinelec @markparton @ElizabethLeeCBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TexanInOz you'll have to do a recipe...and try comfrey one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever tried smoking comfrey? @TexanInOz https://t.co/1iys7WXmjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It must be nice to earn over $200,000 per year, but will you both fix Hudson St Higgins playground? @Gordon_R_Ramsay @YvetteSBerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how the ALP keep West Belco so under resourced,then assemble Christmas hampers- so offensive/patronising.Fund the area @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 tram lines for Canberra but Higgins playground water bubbler not fixed and no new water fountains for West Belco. Povo CBR @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the children of Higgins deserve a broken water bubbler in Hudson st playground? I asked politicians to fix. Poverty land. @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the ALP want to keep West Belco run down and povo- no new water fountains, no weekend rapid buses. @canberratimes @YvetteSBerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if West Belco will get any of the new water fountains in 2017. I have asked all politicians for my area. @ABarrMLA @Gordon_R_Ramsay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if local Labor politicians will fix the water bubbler in my local playground? It does not work. @Gordon_R_Ramsay @YvetteSBerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need govt buses to CBR airport for workers and lower income people. If we have 2 tram lines then have airport bu… https://t.co/L3qnibGxCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope you read my comment re rapid buses @FlanneryDavid  . It used to be thought socially responsible, to think 4… https://t.co/ZNP9gpxchg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me old fashioned, but this dress looks nice on MS. Good when not EVERYTHING is on show... the right balance...… https://t.co/LCo5dJTIq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so hot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seeds I planted on New Year's Day have come up- 2 days ago. Simple pleasures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tiffany_King @SBS I am going ok with choc as no resolution was made! But English mince pie enjoyment has gone well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @andrewwhiteau I was serious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau I think we should start it. A tribute to George Michael &amp; Olive Cotton's "Max After Surfing" photo! I'd be happy to judge!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau Gay men might like a male wet tshirt comp- a good tourist draw card... or topless...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau Oh, what a shame. I thought, in the name of equality, it might drag me there for the first time ever!!!! Good idea though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau can women watch, or is it only men, for men to watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so, men wear the tshirts?! or no shirts?! https://t.co/dXqd7YIaIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow, they included a couple of Belco ones.... https://t.co/sjZXSlvcly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSpenceAU I don't think I'd be able to breathe, going by all the pics...like Parramatta Road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuckyOZBloke @abcnews Germans have 10k items per home? Wow, what is Oz average?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joy and bliss of living in safe Labor seats. Wow. https://t.co/qmkadKehD6 @Gordon_R_Ramsay @YvetteSBerry @ABarrMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local playground needs help. Why isn't the water fountain working? Safe Labor seats https://t.co/qmkadKehD6 @canberratimes @kirstenlawsonCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A job for your Labor government https://t.co/qmkadKehD6 @ABarrMLA @YvetteSBerry @Gordon_R_Ramsay @VickiDunneMLA @canberratimes @666Canberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think all of Canberra's Greek biscuit gifts have been given to me via a neighbour. Hard to resist. New Year cake, baklava, shortbread. umm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am sorry re your aircon @Elias_Hallaj  . You can tell me re a good one from your research.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSpenceAU I just let a kid use one of those, an old one of mine- works fine. Cool and simple. #retrocool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really missing rapid buses out here in the sticks. We are on the so slow weekend timetable here in CBR. @Transport_CBR @MeeganFitzMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SachaBlumen I remember a school mate who'd get bashed up, as gay and he copied Boy George hair dos. I hope times have changed so much...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit like waiting for a Sunday bus to West Belco!! VJ https://t.co/p6Br9qoOf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After shopping at Belco today, I went to bus stop. Had to wait 40 mins for bus to my area. Need blue rapid asap to Kippax. @MeeganFitzMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would help the city &amp; Belco economy if people from West Belco could get blue rapid buses to Belco and Civic on weekends. @MeeganFitzMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wanted to go into Civic by bus yesterday- but no rapids Kippax to Civic on Sat/Sun. When will Kippax get blue rapids? @MeeganFitzMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw this on abc 24 news @mrngunnawal  https://t.co/YUAT0TxAdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see focus on buses but what about a weekend blue rapid bus to Kippax? @Transport_CBR @ABarrMLA @alistair_coe https://t.co/UGctU4HY15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonjaBarfoed @SachaBlumen @AdamSpenceAU West Belco about 5min drive/5km to Belco- so close but so neglected- easy 4 rapid to go on weekends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer It was "The Mix", see the end part of this- great colours https://t.co/L5chBBX4xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer I don't watch much tv, so I'm a bit out of date re tv program titles. It was an arts program in afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good fitness idea, whatever else it achieves
https://t.co/ZPUN0b3nTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer They made fabric for dolls from old blankets, and dyed fabric with plants and car parts for colour- v hipster!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer It was Sun afternoon arts program 2 days ago. Maybe on ABC 24 news, re sewn dolls, then embroidered, exhibited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer Did you see abc program re dolls made by artists in ?NT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @SimonHayHealer need blokey ones for teen boys who think hats are uncool!! says a Mum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney &amp; Canberra BOTH avoid developing wealthier areas, &amp; instead develop/wreck less wealthy/poorer areas. Elitism. https://t.co/KQOoVQa26Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do we buy them? @mrngunnawal https://t.co/GYXa0lDvSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know Inner North is getting the tram but I have to say: Kippax rapid buses every 10 mins are better than Lyneham city buses every 30 mins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magsgboro French hospitals provide free healthcare for illegal immigrants-the French need them to do the dirty work,which they refuse to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magsgboro she's just looking for votes. being Trumpish. sadly, it works...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 Pizza Hut? Turkish Pide is better. We have many local ones :-P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to Tilley's today &amp; asked which cakes are locally made.They said all from Sydney boo hoo.Local is better. I want local cakes in cafes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SachaBlumen @AdamSpenceAU The south are very vocal complaining on fb ct, but they get weekend rapid blue buses! Marginal seats- good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need articles re this in Oz.The privatisation of disability care has been bad for care workers-the NDIS is not good… https://t.co/lk7HxXSJAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and what are you doing for the poor in your country @BorisJohnson  ? VJ https://t.co/Jgg218z8Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leah_CBR even if last, good to have fun and keep fit :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I worked with Anne in 1993, in her East Balmain home. Goodbye Anne.
https://t.co/LdDErXoSSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSpenceAU @abcnewsCanberra When I see local government housing homes leave hoses on all night, I think water should not be free. Waste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer @Luke_FoleyNSW When will Parramatta get a national level art gallery- Parra to be Oz's 3rd biggest CBD...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting that the Belconnen Community Council is so pro development- are they so vocal about a Belco tram?Where will new units' rates go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really my thing, so far...VJ https://t.co/q63iirr8LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admired mine in the kitchen then popped out for a pic! https://t.co/D0ektjlhbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For International Day with Disability I hope for 1. Blue weekend rapids to Kippax 2. Bus shelters all main streets in CBR. @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkusMannheim A blind man said he's sick of getting rained on, many would benefit from bus shelters (city gets tram...) and free to get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkusMannheim Please see text link I sent re ad bus shelters. Ad co build for free if they can put ads in them. Non drivers would benefit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These texts sum up bus needs. Include re disability. https://t.co/tcvGyygi9m and https://t.co/Tkt70H28t0 @MarkusMannheim @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the CT is doing a disability supplement, why not discuss weekend bus rapids to Kippax &amp; building free ad bus shelters? @MarkusMannheim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful coolish weather at 5.22 am. Now, can it stay like this all day?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girrali @mrngunnawal Personally, I think people like Pat O'Shane should be discussed and celebrated. Establishment might think differently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @Girrali I think there should be a doco re Pat O'Shane &amp; her life/work, as I suggested to @chrisgatlarge  or did I miss one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Girrali @mrngunnawal Could always plan a new one, this time have it include Pat O'Shane. Use the same site?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for Parra and outer Syd. Now can Parra have a major art gallery? Why not? @mikebairdMP  @Luke_FoleyNSW https://t.co/UbZ9gZBHSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrHWoo @SachaBlumen how cool. soon it will be an antique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSpenceAU @marcuskelson There should be a Binalong Butcher sign instead!! Go the small guy. Stuff the big guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day of summer and oh I miss cardigan-polar fleece weather (but not scarf weather). #cardigansook  #cardigangeek #toohot #siestaweather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrHWoo @SachaBlumen does it have a coin slot?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have asked the ACT govt for water fountains, public pool &amp; gym equipment 4 West Belco- where is it? @canberratimes https://t.co/egC9v2YKMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles Yummy &amp; affordable! Also, teaches ppl skills for life, for every Xmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles Then every Xmas, people can bake gifts &amp; Xmas food. There's only so much people can eat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles If you bake, then flour etc not expensive. Fun to make, get someone to teach others baking skills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles I was thinking: why not bake Xmas shaped biscuits- good to eat &amp; wrap nicely as gifts for family/friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles @joewilliams_tew some extended families only give to kids and not adults. Have cash limits on kid gifts too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrngunnawal @woolworths @Coles @joewilliams_tew What do people need? Sometimes good to reject the consumerism, some ppl only give to kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'd be nice to have a local public pool to go to, for 45,000 people... but will the elite ABC discuss such average… https://t.co/yDdIjHHyDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did anyone else get 2 gas bills this month? This happened about 6 months ago. Are they estimating bills now? Stuff around. @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take note Canberrans. But when will Kippax get a line? Ever?  @canberratimes https://t.co/G5fGS15EN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, let women be Catholic priests, mate. Help them out. VJ @Pontifex https://t.co/i0zpB4XAkZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>