<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride And in the end, you'll fall, betrayed by one of the socks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride And be disappointed that it's gone all politically correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman Yes. The link works but the page is broken because the web server doesn't quite handle the broken URL. Edge case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman By the by, you put a sort-of broken link into your article about Snugborough junction - extra '.' after '.ie' in the URL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman Ha ha, I will. And stay off Twitter on Sunday, no good will come of it :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman &gt; routing some cycle/pedestrian traffic there. Just a thought, but I've come across it numerous times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman &gt; linking the two parks via the existing paths. You have an opportunity to link the parks, increasing use of both and &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodericogorman Just got your flier about the Snugborough interch. One thought - seems like you're missing one trick, with (1/34)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallohiggins I don't know how sturdy it will be in the long run though. Air and water pressure are hard work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallohiggins It builds up actual air pressure. It's quite clever, and I was a bit obsessed with getting hold of a manual espresso maker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallohiggins Not quite. This is much closer to an espresso mechanism and it makes a genuine espresso. Aeropress is a nice filter coffee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staresso espresso maker. Forget the Aeropress, this is where it is at for manual espresso making. https://t.co/glGb71VFAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvddnh No worries mate, if any other part of the Internet is giving you trouble then give me a shout I'm always here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill @RudyHellzapop ”Lucky escape for Arsenal if it did.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill @RudyHellzapop ”Oh yes, sir, so you said,” said the barman, looking over his glasses this time at Arthur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill @RudyHellzapop ”No, no,” said Ford, ”it’s just that the world’s about to end.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHellzapop @MajorThrill Or the end of the world. A lot of that in the air too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I am, posting on Twitter. But I'm going to get into distributed social media. We all should. This isn't healthy for society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail Looking good, Martin. The ECT is going well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvddnh It's an interesting read, but don't take it as canonical. It's very hyperbolic, subject to confirmation bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail Either that or the salt mines. It would be a close call if you had to choose your post-Brexit lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oceanclub I used to have fucks to give about it but sadly now I don’t.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail That’s not comedy, that’s what it’s like in every household living in Dublin. You, post-Brexit, I might add.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHonestPaddy No. I'd look down at him, and tell him to get on his bike, and chuckle like a clever, witty granddad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHonestPaddy THEY'RE NOT TERRORISTS THEY'RE JUST TERMINALLY FIT GUYS ON BICYCLES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he was more of a drug dealer than a... Ahh, but the lines can get blurred in practice. Sharp! @TheHonestPaddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Ireland we are concerned about terrorists sneaking in. We've never had terrorists here, not even the world's most successful terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alotron I was one of millions in my class who did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUMP IS GREAT TRUMP IS GREAT TRU.

Damn new chip. https://t.co/g7Ftl1iIyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By a curious co-incidence, there's an interview with Ruth Negga which is worth reading. You'll see why. The Irish Times is in a dark place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was going to do one of my mock-ups on the idea of it, but actually the Irish Times has gone there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Irish Times effectively running a piece on upside of Eugenics. https://t.co/6vS7fEqVMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oceanclub @IrishTimes I still can't believe that they would run that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrowadat Ha ha, imagine some lad in the office telling you that if you ask him what's going to happen while the data centre's down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSeducktress I could've done so much more though. Could've.

But. Vin Diesel et al.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could've read an interesting book about autism. Could've. Instead, I watched people blow up a military plane by driving very fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail You've become very naive since starting that Instagram account. It's like you're turning your cop-on into paint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Any nefarious organisation, fictional or real, would look at Trump’s win &amp; go “Shit… Look at that. He did it like it was easy”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHonestPaddy OH FUCK I SHOULDVE KNOWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, everything's going to be ok. It's snowing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016: The year Western Civilisation jumped the shark. This year we start the disorderly wind-down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily Also, he is being hosed down in the dark. He is basically being waterboarded, no wonder he is sick-feeling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What up with framework love bro. What up. https://t.co/sdyn7a9Gy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfox THEY HAVE IDENTIFIED YOU AS ONE OF THE WEAK ONES OF THE HERD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Podgeypoos79 "AngularJS - Bureaucracy for JavaScript" - I should get it made into a t-shirt and make my millions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Podgeypoos79 &gt; Angular, I mean. Not your workshop. That would be creepy. Thanks for jumpstarting me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Podgeypoos79 Hey, I don’t know if you remember but I went to your Angular workshop last year. Now I’m spending a lot of time in it! &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfox Have you tried installing an iOS content blocker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail “Been down here 71 years, mate. Don’t see me whinging about it. Have they got the flying cars yet?”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHellzapop @johnorthside It would be a terrible shame for the State to fall asunder for want of a booking or a bit of planning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHellzapop @johnorthside Shit, time has flown faster than I had realised. Really enjoyed the commentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ, I find and share this on Sunday afternoon. I should get behind this in a big way. https://t.co/0XZtRd2TVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHellzapop @johnorthside Thought you were there last year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any way of telling is someone’s going to Nazi? There must be some symptoms or indication? @Fergal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Did they try to sell you extended product warranty with that? It’s basically Argos with food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily @dvddnh So snared. He doesn’t have a hope of being president after this debacle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electionlit I used to. A bad habit. You can get mind cancer from doing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKavOfficial Ha ha, that’s hilarious. Nice strategy on your part, hat off to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt; Far Right - was a great idea. And then attempted to argue the toss afterwards. All this has happened before, etc).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(For context, the Irish Times thought that running an article explaining the Far Right's terminology - written by a member of the &gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that escalated quickly. https://t.co/4yjMkdkG3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily Fucking posting photos of it everywhere like a one-man tabloid operation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily There's a frustrating lack of detail here that makes a statistical analysis next to impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily Seriously though, on a plane. That's rough. Were they on the way back from somewhere or going there? Married?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lads, tomorrow morning I'm get my Chrome dev tools out and editing the Irish Times front page again. Big stick time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tupp_Ed I think we’re going to have to nationalise your Twitter feed in the greater social interest. Just for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily In real-time? You’re live-tweeting a break-up?

I have hyphenated-everything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alex_meehan Leave it in. It’s only a puncture when it comes out. Until then, it is decorative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfox Reporting you to your employer for malthinkance tbh @carolynmoore_ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfox That made me laugh loudly. 5kg would last me at least 3 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSeducktress ANIMALS DONT HAVE SEX PARTS THEY ARRIVE BY STORK I SAW IT IN A MOVIE ONCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlashBrady Also, reference: https://t.co/Uor9Cc1nzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlashBrady How’s that even a burn. They’re selling sticks of titanium with styrofoam for mental money. But I’m going one better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buying a load of these and marketing them in a foil wrapper as the ultimate programming focus aid for a 20x mark-up. https://t.co/u8K79xF3EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Seriously, Gerry. You can get beer all year, but you can only get Christmas stollen between September and February.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also looking to challenge Dwayne Johnson and Kanye West in a surprise upset for the 2020 US presidential election.… https://t.co/L9oB6Ml67c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Me with chocolate. And the Christmas mince pies. And the stollen, which is going cheap now. Fuck it, the food, generally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill The 44 is a rough odyssey. That’s why he went when the usual suspects are still asleep. It’s not a posh route.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeniPim Are you going to be ok? That doesn’t look like a happy place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubot I'm not even worried about the Clinton paedophilia network against the white night of Trump statements any more. Just the noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubot I got him to take the rotting fruit off his desk but the coding aloud thing, that'll take violence or worse. I accept this truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubot He's not going to. I've been sitting next to him for months and he's not going to have it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlashBrady I think it can be implemented now by plugin but it's not as safe a system-wide blocklist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlashBrady Maybe. But apparently they sold out. You can get whitelisted if they like you. So I read a while back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should send that guy some money. He's doing it out of his own time, collating from all the sources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't help you with doing it but I'll find some links to help people. If you can, do it. Filter the stream of shit out of your Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to share. The world would be a very slightly better place if a lot of this stuff didn't make it to people's browsers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little New year's gift, in light of some of what made 2016 a little rougher: a hosts file. Read attached image to… https://t.co/CUC2ABp9f9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atoast2toast @dvddnh @neilcreagh Well, that took an unexpected turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone out there? Any hints? I love a new meme that's a mashup of Gladwell, TV3 and fake news, but I need to unders… https://t.co/MRrZJbeMRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvddnh @neilcreagh Exactly. I bid 20 quatloos on the newcomer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilcreagh I don’t get the joke but I’m buying in. Let’s see how this unfolds. My money’s on the table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily Nice beard and excellent Grohl positioning. Very tasteful. I’ll have two beards please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Ah here. The beer done you harm, boy. https://t.co/5e4GhSn5N2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@munitionsfamily *Aim for New Year: Taking and keeping Arch Music Troll title. Off to a thunderous opening gambit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride I’ve seen things you people wouldn’t believe. Attack lanterns on fire off the shoulder of McBride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wefail A new low in turtle photography focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmcgovern I think it’s a sign-post to the decay of what we understand to be Western culture. Not for everyone else, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Back up a bit here, McBride. I read your Virgin Megastore story with tears in my eyes. You’ve just torn it all down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXECUTIVESTEVE I am eating drop right now. In my mother's house, in Wexford. No hagelslag, however. White bread, butter and hagelslag. Aww.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>