<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@UmlandAndreas @TheEconomist "Predictably, both sides blame one another" only reinforces Trump and Putin's misguided moral equivalency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machiavellian thinking which will surely lead to the deterioration of the entire system. Exactly what Trump wants.… https://t.co/EyaPIsAhfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SC nominee Neil M. Gorsuch has disagreed with 'retroactive interpretations of the law to disfavor immigrants'.  https://t.co/HzzHnBd0Dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. There's now a whole company dedicated to saving #immigrant SV employees from #Trump's executive orders. https://t.co/8j0dMK87jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters Oh, I get it. Trump was just jealous of China. This whole time the plan was to copy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your eyes peeled. This Friday is the first meeting of #Trump's economic advisors. CEO advisers all rely on immigrant employees. Tense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump paralyzes immigration and our only hope is #Uber's Travis Kalanick talking to him. This is the state of US politics right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really great resource tracking all Trump-affiliated business deals. 
https://t.co/TI297vRGJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gains in productivity = loss in #jobs https://t.co/qvtHMZ09n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evolution of Theresa May. #UK #Trump #May https://t.co/ikNMqv4tCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norm and I are friends on Facebook. I will remember this day for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stroke of the pen, law of the land." https://t.co/KHrdaK5lAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will just leave this here ... #alternativefacts  https://t.co/DXqInt7oTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Caltrain is completely packed -- with women. #WomensMarch #SanFrancisco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @rortybomb How in the world does a broken EU benefit Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej exactly right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukrainian section at #runnymede library. https://t.co/JtGHJlgBcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. This is a drug store in a historic theatre. #toronto https://t.co/uNfMILTqO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumofalltrades There's a lot of fall out alright ... https://t.co/9YyVbVst8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump won't sell his company, but the Trump Tower in #Toronto is up for sale! Bidding starts at $298 million.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Not sure if Weekend Update sketch or real life ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting interesting. https://t.co/pR8043ypc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway looking into #Trump's heart is like Bush seeing into Putin's soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never realized how much #Freud's Civilisation and its Discontents borrows from Locke. Strange that left venerates such conservative thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... thank God? https://t.co/3iP6ScdUkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60% of the great American #Exxon-Mobil's employees are not American. Rex #Tillerson is stealing our jobs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excellent book on the history of critical #theory by Stuart Jeffries. More relevant than ever. https://t.co/G1PnN06vEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But people's minds were ... https://t.co/hgUwDktcCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TODreamsProject Very excited to read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the land that may be ugly, and inhabited by drugstores, hot dogs and cards, but is at least safe to some extent atm." #Adorno on America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1938, H. G. Wells' War of the Worlds was read on #CBS Radio on Halloween. Listeners thought aliens or Germany re… https://t.co/0MfGa1rTgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walter Benjamin's arcades, insulating privileged classes from the hardships of others, greatly resemble media-made… https://t.co/sCDiFkVQDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkably, President John Adams had in fact served as defense counsel during the Boston Massacre Trial. https://t.co/e9k9ZikoWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams packed the courts with friends, only for all to be removed by Jefferson in following term.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adams made the presidency a family affair, making son John Quincy Adams minister to Prussia and son-in-law William Smith federal officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President John Adams' Alien and Sedition Acts of 1798 are frightening precedents of paranoiac and unscrupulous pres… https://t.co/Gl2SNCEAhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This deal never got the same attention that pipelines got. That's a problem.  https://t.co/QlqcVgBJdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two best ways to relieve humanity’s suffering, ExxonMobil believes, are  providing energy and tackling malaria. https://t.co/kos2csDzeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What good is it to save the planet if humanity suffers?” -- Rex Tillerson 
Reminiscent of effective altruism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Walter Benjamin wrote that "moving on" is fascist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Councillor @norm, I'm a Torontonian at Stanford -- and I've come to learn that you're a star there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This university is making pieces of metal smarter than the students damaging its reputation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree. https://t.co/UZGFqGfrpO https://t.co/ZKNRKrEEwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology these days ... https://t.co/qnbNrlAYQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terrifying alliance. https://t.co/faggfYFmwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once, Bob Dylan asked Leonard how long it took him to write Hallelujah, Leonard said 2 years -- it was really 5. https://t.co/RDJzUzBHfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really nice collection of thoughts. https://t.co/7xY2gTelRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Stanford and #Berkeley's message for international students following the election. https://t.co/gsj5HUAHZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@b_judah Are you in New York for long? I would love to interview you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only green magical idealism can turn this around. https://t.co/xOqlmfS2tM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music blasted by my dorm is wishing,"if we could turn back time to the good old days." #toosoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GLocal sounds like a GObject in Java. https://t.co/iaqJFSlLcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the accessible and flexible nature of technology, 'dem rat' should be easier to implement now than ever before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people should read about Feenberg's 'democratic rationalization'. I wrote an article about why we need it. https://t.co/HDtJixtdRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuen Pau Woo, a formidably impressive Pearson alumnus! https://t.co/d6NGvjDBhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shame that only after I move away from Toronto do I realize how cool Marshall McLuhan was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, Andrew Feenberg. Design is not a zero-sum game. If optimization is treated as a 'cost', there's a flaw i… https://t.co/lNjJEJrqWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manipulating thoughts is much more difficult than manipulating a GOval.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christianity itself is incompatible with nativism. Even God mandated ethnic and linguistic diversity. https://t.co/BU7GIVIJuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've missed him. https://t.co/kD7n1ylXDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autumn is the season where we learn to appreciate both the sun and the breeze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to bring that private circulation of funds for those same essential services back into the public realm so they can be regulated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'upside down' is where essential services are provided by private groups circling money internally, out of the government's reach. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Stranger Things' offer great insight into how corrupt regimes work. Our dimension is where funds circulate to provide public services. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a cry for help. Help.  https://t.co/ch7OFop2k8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the 122 TTC line a myth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know there's an issue when ... https://t.co/RXqvJnD28p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well worth a read.  https://t.co/jEqoWswPjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because, why check grammar before printing a bunch of crazy hats? https://t.co/4gvIugNFTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@b_judah Research for a new book?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironically, 'alcohol' comes from 'al-kohl' in Arabic, meaning 'the purified'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald It's a Soviet strategy. "We have to wait 5 hours in line for butter, but at least we're good at sports."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This code looks great! I am smar -- ... https://t.co/WejYbk54GM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists don't even have to out the misadventures of public figures anymore. They can be conspicuously horrible. People don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: 'Yeah, the system is rigged, but I won so it doesn't matter.'
People: "omg. so honest. must be prez nao."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Brazil's closing ceremony will be equally creepy .. https://t.co/YPVTjBOhgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pokemon Go got too real at Cornell. https://t.co/tb4ejo4bYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans selling their churches for $40K. https://t.co/lvapoaWrYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton's mass investment plan into infrastructure sounds a lot like Trudeau's new infrastructure plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rochester. The city purchased by a company of 14 people. https://t.co/5dAYFXBH6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Badiou says new bourgeoisie depicts resistance over oppression in cinema -- so does fem/marx lib film Born in Flames https://t.co/eZ6ZoSTNaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej the support of particular individuals is secondary to the support of the masses; which Trump has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Žižek's 'trouble in paradise' is found in the 'business' section of the library. Well played, Toronto Public Library, well played.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej political narrative. The idea of being united by one voice is symbolically acceptable for them whereas left sees this as oppressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej yes, there are interest groups etc, but my point is that despite such nuances they are all comfortable with identifying with one ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej there's no such thing as a micronarrative for the right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej Then take a look at the supporter base. The right has staunch, vehement supporters whereas left only has niches of support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej a profound ability to overcome conflict which is not as apparent in the left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej I think that when McCain! and Paul Ryan endorse Trump who claims to be 'the voice' of the American people, it shows ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmaslej both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out, deconstructing 'truth' can be used to oppressive ends too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich said facts are a matter of 'perspective'. It's easy to laugh off 'silly Republicans', but this is a product of relativism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing multiples voices and micro narratives is great --- until it's not. Today's shattered left is why the right is so strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It really is quite spectacular when leftists think it's not bourgeois to oppose Hillary simply because they preferred Bernie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. New America speaks in Russian slang. https://t.co/icjrNy2x9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Salon @SimonMaloy Finally a non-sociopathic populist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia is so far down the capitalist rabbit hole, it's practically feudal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow the anti-US bias of the left turns into subliminal support of Russia. Strange considering Russia's oligarchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LyleBoggs The argument at the moment is about Trump, not Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LyleBoggs Yes. But -- bit of a non sequitur, don't you think?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>