<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria conflict: Thousands hanged at Saydnaya prison, Amnesty says https://t.co/k9GTkuNZVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder do these boys regret leaving Newstalk -Second Captains announce daily podcasts with - https://t.co/2LSqUVzGPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Socrates is full of it.. https://t.co/LELIwBtAss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trainspotting2 - pure nostalgia. Just roll with it. 😱]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A People's History of American Empire by Howard Zinn https://t.co/MBStZAsIib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look a bit dodgy to you? Can't even spell ! @PayPalSecurity https://t.co/nu0X19Cvrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know the feeling 😆 https://t.co/f91af4i2Gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only Jurgen would listen to these guys - Leggsy and Biccy rant at Klopp https://t.co/hoG8WPuGsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there nothing else on TV but these fekin wannabe shows of a weekend?? https://t.co/RIoQ15nM7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all your GAA fixtures for this weekend https://t.co/DeeDpFknG2 via @NewstalkFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah here...Don't be at it... https://t.co/aPhdWmpdVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad predicted Trump in 1985 – it's not Orwell, he warned, it's Brave New World https://t.co/0EAO7CjkvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all happened before.. https://t.co/QLhkkPHakZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S Immigration - Foil Arms and Hog https://t.co/sboeqEOBeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man for all seasons with ambitions to be Taoiseach.  #chancer https://t.co/fJ8azDTSzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High school students give Nazi salute and shout ‘Heil Trump' https://t.co/fDaVU1qbrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, I take it myself, says he.. https://t.co/4W4bBEDB2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One pissed off manager - but what the hell is he talking about?? https://t.co/cFl74f92Ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The beginning of limiting free inquiry?? https://t.co/FXeryfC4gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha - American clothes company selling into France. 😂 https://t.co/Fm1OawAJkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Paisley: My dad prayed with Martin McGuinness... and the first time we met I made a quip about balaclavas https://t.co/R3Vq1bWNIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald and Melania Trump's first dance at inaugural ball https://t.co/WGSrPxTSW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Tries To Ignore Pale Horse That Just Appeared Beside Trump https://t.co/hQo9peXwI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A fractured media', says he - not fractured enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mannicmo2001 - True - and if only he was...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratically elected so deserves fair wind - just hope he's learned from Hitler and doesn't overstretch himself.. https://t.co/dL72RFWgUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I used to be such a good sleeper.. 😬 https://t.co/jb6rlJRIHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Fanning's Irish Crossroads https://t.co/o3CIkDGrC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong: Twenty years later https://t.co/vctMrCRmX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ye oright there luv? - https://t.co/ZZApwvZ5vU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you believe? It's 20 years since this song - Robbie Williams - Angels https://t.co/IWJsH4opO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the World’s Oldest Computer Worked: Reconstructing the 2,200-Year-Old Antikythera Mechanism https://t.co/7FFToLoihJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aid in reverse: how poor countries develop rich countries | Jason Hickel https://t.co/i2LqeDPccJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man lives alone in the snow for 40 years and scientists love him - Holy Kaw! https://t.co/7e5G4F6qNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A highly entertaining ( &amp; hypocritical ) speech from Samantha Power - expect the same in Putin's response. 😉😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrice Lumumba: the most important assassination of the 20th century | Georges Nzongola-Ntalaja https://t.co/ltQClozx8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A case for Irexit?? - George Lee: Brexit impact may be worse than feared https://t.co/HqzIrUn6ZL  #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the British get their way a new EU will emerge - all states accessing single market without most of the other stuff - prob happen anyway👣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASimpleJan - psst -you're in the wrong classroom..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintan O’Toole: DUP must be punished for its Brexit folly https://t.co/u7kD9SdRzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May threatening EU with sanctions if they play hardball with them in negotiations. #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain looking for new 'Free trade agreement' - not in single market - good luck with that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't mess with the 'roos.. https://t.co/PIFChNcUaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well obviously... (and make sure you're biting down on your tongue properly) 😉 https://t.co/fvTreAPJXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real freedom is freedom to criticize and amend.. https://t.co/GJAN4Oy8Qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Articulate and to the point - https://t.co/2N5pKegxhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laptop seems to have crashed after downloading McAfee anti- viral software. Hope it's not a virus! 😠]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian Archbishop says Europe will be a Muslim continent in a decade https://t.co/FuHwTsPYbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems more like a white Friday for some.. https://t.co/n5H0nv0byz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A ‘surprise’ asteroid just flew past Earth closer than the moon https://t.co/ra06VjdHQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASimpleJan - Put up on the Amazon - NOW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is out there hey... https://t.co/8PQaw5k2Xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High neck Burberry dress only £1495 - https://t.co/YTi9z4YYvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's snow time! https://t.co/h9xbHvdEO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity they're taking it down. Christmas fun Dublin 15. https://t.co/dGnOyxz0p8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day violent thugs were driven out by hippies with glowsticks | Craig Stone https://t.co/ehqNe9hSso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duckanddodge - Which one are you in the photo then??   #confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This better be good or it will spoil memories of the first one - T2 Trainspotting Official Trailer – https://t.co/P2gxLw2v7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man jumps out of plane with no parachute, lands on trampoline https://t.co/cSaksBBYnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch what must be the outrageous trick shot ever attempted https://t.co/XEgCJBahPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appear?? https://t.co/JJTkiupYDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laid up with the flu and enjoying Ottessa Moshfegh's 'Eileen' -  building up to an intriguing final third  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha - on this day of all days for the Roon! https://t.co/nqVxWgsONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fekin car insurance up by €190 despite 15 years no claims - FFS DRIVE SAFELY!!! https://t.co/mWXI3hspKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final abuse report spanning a century concluded https://t.co/WAfA2Ec3Ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a lost city in the Antarctica? https://t.co/VgAcoesJOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Burns offers blistering takedown of Donald Trump in epic commencement speech https://t.co/dbOJ1CyU2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadrian's Wall Aerial Video https://t.co/jLxq1xrkoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the Trump Presidency looms - "Who does control the world?" - Noam Chomsky - BBC interview 2003 https://t.co/1BMAc5yiwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why it's time to end EU free movement https://t.co/TGeCtWz5ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaJaneDempsey - Did it have Garda written on the side?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were you a decade ago?? https://t.co/j90gz2z5Nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more on this read The Dargan Prophecy   
 #justsaying https://t.co/S1BcCBZOqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite the the old man of the sea - https://t.co/A3YXEk8nX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael's boyfriend alleges singer committed suicide - report https://t.co/S3PZxYx7IB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seamus Heaney's Advice to the Young https://t.co/ldMsrr2csc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Declassified files: Top lawyer scathing about RUC and UDR https://t.co/M0E1eyssGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens dead in attack at Istanbul nightclub -  https://t.co/VrJ7JkN4rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes folks, it's a new year and here we go again... https://t.co/IfwpqQmZK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that include cigars?? https://t.co/BdPH4NqD8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S'truth.. https://t.co/Jl9p5kiEVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha - I mean, Oh - George Michael Hoax - British TV Show EastEnders "Last Christmas" Predic... https://t.co/y9sUVx16P9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony Cronin: The End of the Modern World, my elegy for our capitalist era https://t.co/0DOFgn9HRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo too -https://t.co/xtqmmB3eEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: Asher's bakery test case https://t.co/E4fnoulLcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?? https://t.co/USbzLcw7h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhotosAllan @mofitzmaurice - I'm sure that's Tony Blair on the right -If only he'd made a success of it. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaJaneDempsey - Is George Michael still dead? That's all I heard any time I turned it on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not gone by the end of the year I'll carry an inferiority complex into 2017 :( https://t.co/IdTSnswdBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop star George Michael dies peacefully at home aged 53 – live https://t.co/EYe6cSxTbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All partied out... https://t.co/3vYlqvai4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected prezy frm the 4 yr old niece. Warmer bottle 4 d single man &amp;  notebook for those moments of inspiration. https://t.co/CAF6maLh7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The three disgraces with Lillypups ready to jump into bed at the first sign of Santa.. https://t.co/NgwiNiMDNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any truth to the rumours that Crystal Palace have now sacked Sam Allardyce??     #bbcsportsday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah poor oul Pardew.. https://t.co/G6RKYFnjyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands queue for food parcels in Dublin city centre https://t.co/LJ3YKqfxBz via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quare stretch in the evenings hey.. https://t.co/MiZiscqqh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just heard rumours that the Germans were dispatching gun-boats to be sailed up the Liffey to dislodge the rebels from #apollohouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda cool this - https://t.co/fCqNA2arCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might'nt like it but it's 'realpolitik' at this stage to negotiate an Islamic State in exchange for European security.  #berlinchristmas]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>