<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If I ever see Daniel in real life, he's probably my favourite person ever #TheUndateables https://t.co/aDT6rLWPAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it they live in number 36 #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah it is Robbie in the AIG ad so every time we see it now 'there's Robbie, nice bloke, nice gaff, fantastic beard'.  #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Des Cahill dancing. The man is a legend #DWTSIRL https://t.co/TYlBBVYqjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LateLateShow Dermot Bannan 'we should be renting more' a bit of the auld Lyle Lanley about him. https://t.co/Eln5YhkNR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks like we're getting that island lads. Packing my bags as we speak 🇮🇪🇮🇪 #EuroMillions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I just want a job' this lad certainly echoes how I feel went to college got qualifications and still it's a NO from employers #GenerationFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FirstDatesIRL Antonio is the real Tony Angelino he's probably from Leitrim. https://t.co/jlz3n14DAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you 100% Irish? Because I wanna eat you like a Big Mac that's where I thought that was going.  #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1000 episode of pointless was on yesterday and the 998 episode is on today. Ok #pointless https://t.co/auhy5yCRC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see Daniel is back on the #undateables my favourite person ever. https://t.co/MIHpq0HpRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your mate gets you the wrong beer at the bar. #pep #EVEMCI https://t.co/QLMHZFT94j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the #raydarcyshow like. Strange happenings https://t.co/fwy5QK623e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is George Hook getting Botox tonight? #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in Ireland when it snows #sneachta https://t.co/ueYQFK4DUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the live band? Oh this is RTÉ not BBC, btw the music sounds like it's being played on an iPhone #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing with the Stars? Nah it's Dancing with the RTÉ Canteen would be more appropriate  #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postman Sam, postman Sam and his jar of jam.still a better rhymer than Honey G. #undateables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamTrevitt8 I'll push it as far as I can lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia is gone #pointless https://t.co/BJoKDlkTZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamTrevitt8 haha if comes to that so be it, I'll fight a 1000 men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Georgia #pointless https://t.co/MbQoa0USzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Sutton should be given a knighthood for services to trolling. An expert at winding people up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only the French had reverted to type and surrendered that day, who knows what would have happened.  #TwoShadesOfGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only time I ever cried about football was when Brady scored that goal, I was so totes emotes like.  #TwoShadesofGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buseireann is the Naas to Dublin service running a normal Saturday service today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The g string king says it's all about 'sexual intimidation' the courts say that's a 12 month suspended sentence.  #carrickonstag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland thanks for your help and Happy Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland from the redeem button on the email you sent me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland no it keeps telling me 'we've encountered a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland Hi guys, I received an email today regarding a €16.99 voucher for a movie but when I go to retrieve it won't let me sign in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Byrne is like the mate who told a funny joke once abd keeps repeating 10 years later.  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going for pints with Miriam Margolyes, she's off her head I love it.  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's that young his vegetables haven't dropped yet, going by the sound of his voice #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously these people have never listened to a radio. Worst contestants ever.  #pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It always takes kids to realise we are no different. What a thing to do it probably changed many a life and attitude.  #projectchildren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got the mmr vaccine as kid my friends got it, everyone I know got it and we're all fine. Again vultures targeting idiots.   #ThisIsIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#latelate the face you pull when Tubridy tells you he's on 400 odd grand a year. https://t.co/oc9TW5sL5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asking Aled Jones does he like Christmas is like asking Tubridy does he like surveying the RTÉ canteen for guests for the #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CuttingEdge old Hooky saying he's never been in Aldi or Lidl, of course you haven't https://t.co/xz3VtOV3tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you switched from whatever Virgin Media used to be called to their rival and never had a problem since you swi… https://t.co/cVGFS3SqrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked the way they exposed all the charlatans who spout shite about healthy living to con idiots out of their money #ThisIsIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tara the lamb, Ireland's Harambe so so sad I'll think about her next time I munch a kebab at half 3 in the morning.  #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alfie: oh thank you so much.               Evil Alfie: sell the book, its worth a shitload.  #LateLateToyShow https://t.co/a5ud9dFwKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two Ballyfermot girls in 30 years time #beaches #LateLateToyShow https://t.co/FUUlLYCwE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Allardyce has got himself a new job. #bigsam https://t.co/iNPN7k4olH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine going for a pint with Paul Williams, two pints in 'here barman gis a Whiskey and make it a double. The man is intense.  #StateofFear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My parents always loved Joe Dolan, never ever got why they did, until I turned 30 now I rock out to Joe all the time #legend  #JoeDolan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eamo loves little Wes, he has posters all over his bedroom wall of him.  #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a bloke with a plastic bag to come on the telly and talk nothing but sense imagine our dear leaders talking like this.  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think a programme about the digital age, they'd be able to get the sound and picture in sync. #CloudControl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As soon as you pick your phone up you're being targeted by companies through your data footprint to buy/use their product.  #CloudControl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only George Hamilton would go on about the wording on tv scoreboard. The chap is a mine of information #COYBIG #AUSvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talks about bullying, calls overweight people 'nuisances'. The absolute wagon.  #cuttingedge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pointless has a round on famous walls today, too soon lads too soon #pointless #ElectionResults]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My prediction for Tubridy after the Paxman interview #LateLateShow https://t.co/HPAUhgcxXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LateLateShow Tubridy when your man is going on about his dresses. He hasn't a clue what's going on. https://t.co/rsoNXN2DYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see TV3 are showing Celtic over City and Barca. A bunch of chancers Bill. #TV3UCL https://t.co/5N6kfTeiW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#raydarcyshow what is this lip sync battle thing. People pay a tv licence so we can have this 'banter'. Well done R… https://t.co/UTBAg1EyQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If our politicians had half the integrity that Peter McVerry has, the country would be a much fairer place to live #raydarcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason there's no women on the #LateLateShow is because Tubridy is Dougal in disguise. He can't talk to women. https://t.co/gPxGPMWAvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LateLateShow "ladies and gentlemen Graham Norton". Back to the live recording 'clap ya shower of gurriers' so it l… https://t.co/VeExe5VFTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMovieGame I like Wes, he's brilliant for Ireland. But to say Messi is in decline is ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Messi at 29 is in decline while Wes Hoolahan at 34 is a superstar. Dunphy logic, the man is off his head #RTEsoccer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Ayoade doing 48 hours in Magaluf would make for possibly the best half an hour of tv ever. He'd love it there. Maybe not  #TravelMan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NolanLive Two mad nordy women screaming at each other is a sight to behold. https://t.co/sUv24KTcjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jasus fair play to ya, your arse must be killing ya. Only an Irishman could utter those words.  #KevinsAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that didn't take Long  #MOLIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ENGMAL trying to watch that match like https://t.co/FkeWOOz3zP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your man Michael Harding reminds me of that drunk old fella in the pub who starts talking to ya and won't fuck off then.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_W2172 yep, that's what I suspected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think this Gavin Robinson lad has ever gone on a lads holiday to Magaluf. Something tells me he isn't the type.  #NolanLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in the Republic whenever I watch #NolanLIVE I do be like. https://t.co/9ZdJ8mVQDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#KevinsAmerica every time I see right wing Americans going on about shite they're paranoid about. https://t.co/oFlWoSo88B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Dublin win Cluxton will celebrate by organizing his CDs into genres and alphabetical order #DUBvMAYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A game of football might break out between the MMA fighting.  #DUBvMAYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Philip was straight and shagging a 22 year old girl, people would be calling him a hero not a creep #firstdates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jess and Tom are gonna go to a bondage club for their next date. They seem the type #firstdates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Michael D Higgins doesn't go for a second term I'd like to employ him as my bedtime story teller it would be epic. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[used to watch people watching tv in their house by standing outside their window but thankfully #GoggleboxIRL is on now No more awakardness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A unicorn is a very rare and precious thing yeah they're so rare they don't fucking exist.  #firstdates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DUBvMAYO The GAA right now https://t.co/iFrbsGy7jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunphy is like the pissed up uncle at a wedding trying to out shout his niece and nephew. Who he still thinks are about 7yo #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare I rang 3 to pay my bill over the phone and agent confirmed the systems are down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare is there a problem with your payment system. It's taking ages to process my payment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true measure of a man is how he treats someone who can do him absolutely no good. Peter McVerry is some geezer.  #petermcverry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I took from the match. . Ivanovic looks a gestapo officer and the stadium looked like a Fifa 96 stadium. #coybig #SRBvIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland getting rode by a ref, that has never happened before.  #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DingDanggDo I like cheese and Wallace &amp; Gromit, fuck Tesco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DingDanggDo aye, but the moon doesn't have a Tesco Extra and a Tesco Metro. Naas does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Nas had another 'a' in his name he would be a town in Kildare. True story. #ElectricPicnic #naas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I was watching Noel Gallagher until RTE2 cut to ads the scoundrels. Typical #ElectricPicnic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting in on a Saturday night drinking tea while watching Noel Gallagher at #EP2016 I'm the real winner folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RoseofTralee Kilkenny Rose to the judges. https://t.co/9toHVdPtgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarah_o_grady Ah they're all just so lovely I wouldn't be able to choose between any of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kilkenny rose after that result 'they're fucking cheats they're cheating bastards the  #RoseofTralee stinks from the core to the top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait for the long dramatic suspense when Daithi is about to announce the winner.  #RoseofTralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you don't have a gaa jersey can you still be an escort? #RoseofTralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just too risky for me tattoos, rapping and divorce I'm switching over to naked attraction. Bring back the lovely girls #RoseofTralee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richie_c23 #yawn #musttrybetter]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>