<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Say her name, say her name.  Sing her name, sing her name.  "Sally Yates"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejoined the Wellington Chess club for the Summer Cup tournament tonight and blew my first game big time. #rusty and #WideAwake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An open letter by our MP Peter Dunne to that VULGAR_ian comedian using the  #WhiteHouse as his stage.  https://t.co/Q3XfZ2cR79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY, the VULGAR_ian comedian @realDonaldTrump takes the #WhiteHouse as his stage. #trumping starts today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's harvest for #dinner https://t.co/Kg5MbN8TfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worry more as there's a #peetus  vulgar_ian comedian replacing him. https://t.co/AKdcYliQGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should have harvested this #courgette 2 days before the #Welly #WeatherBomb It's now a #marrow https://t.co/I7pQavsUZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #linkedin profile has been hacked. Got acceptances from lots of people I don't know and my namesake is inviting me to link up too 😈 LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is just about him really so just forgive this VULGAR_ian comedian who's about to make the Oval Office hi… https://t.co/KbvwGZtApD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long company Christmas/New Year shutdown, we're all back at work today. #BOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giant size exhibits about the Gallipoli war is still depressing. #TePapa https://t.co/fFyKXWQRn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally saw the Gallipoli exhibit at Te Papa. https://t.co/XDDp16eH5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrong timing to watch a badly reviewed movie of #AssassinsCreed. Long queue even for etickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7  At least someone clueless about anything can learn a thing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye 2016. Welcome 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UFC207 Another over hyped event for Rousey but she got KO'ed nonetheless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So are we technically at war with Israel now, if there is ever such a technicality? https://t.co/wLyXlDMHgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock star Prince died earlier so Grim Reaper has to claim a princess too. #RIPCarrieFisher  #CarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learned that an office mate died from a motorcycling accident on Christmas day. #sad  #RIPCliff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gift I bought just the other day for someone just went down by 50% today being #BoxingDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BoxingDay sale. Just bought a $229 shoes for $90.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamteyee @nzzenmaster @u1traq  Same to you Thei. May you have the blessings of Christmas and the joys of New Year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was that 1 day in a year that we really worked hard. Disposed 2 ham legs and fridge full of beers/wine. #Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex ICMS member still working for us https://t.co/nGhoH4SNvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should have bought that gift 2 days ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending a funeral for an ICMS ex worker instead of #shopping today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah #RogueOne is pretty amazing. #4Stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #Christmas shopping time at #NorthCityPlaza when you cannot find a seat for your meal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, let me see if #RogueOne is really as fantastic as they say it is. #watchthisspace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see #Aleppo destruction/death and it just hinder you somehow about thinking about #Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Funny is when your officemate paid for his meal via #iPhone pay and then they ask him to sign the vendor's receipt too. Back to the '80's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to donate blood again. #nzblood https://t.co/BSf9ccf7tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found out last night that I'm useless at wrapping gifts. #christmasgift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching a streaming #ParkerRuiz title fight for free courtesy of UK internet site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not blinking but a swimming star https://t.co/pXubEA47j1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really nice of you #California https://t.co/8FfG81IGhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VULGAR_ian comedian elected to the WH is also the person of the year for the Time Magazine. Good choice #USA.… https://t.co/KzPHarzoyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VULGAR_ian comedian who made the WH his stage is not liking another comedian how he makes his living. https://t.co/ZUFJsVwNoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wind gust factored into the making of the video? #Wellington https://t.co/ohWEtI28HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I voted Amy Adams for the next PM in both the NBR and Sharetrader forum polls. https://t.co/bhSagy1Lg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true.  TY and GL @johnkeypm https://t.co/yVlwgZ1hhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pick is for Parket to win on the 7th round. 
Pick Your Champion https://t.co/fdZkm4qLFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on them. https://t.co/ZVEMaFl2Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Mana electorate will finally get a National MP after 2017 election. #interesting https://t.co/SHDxVWNWdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The solution! https://t.co/qfBTVfp4Xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely going to beat Apple's Airpod. https://t.co/zFnepMZERa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder Oh yes. #TGIF https://t.co/VmuQQ0nStO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. Let's call it the #stupidity of humans. https://t.co/BpicCXAxpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate it when all d news is about d analysis-paralysis of how the Vulgar_ian comedian made it to the Oval Stage. Saying #stupidity is enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump won so every moron in the world is now making a beeline to be heard just like the head of this Destiny Church. https://t.co/AYFSShAnPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW.  A leaf-mimicking spider..... https://t.co/3gV5ajJFTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump I cannot be surprised anymore. "Brian Tamaki"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would the Donald say? https://t.co/z3oYWAtijo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She could have won had she talked this way? https://t.co/r6SrMQialO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we being contacted?  What are those "crop circles" really? https://t.co/4nvZ56mLUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four years in a row. Our airline https://t.co/EcP1gd6vjq #best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just instead of being #NuclearFree What about New Zealand being #donaldtrump free too so he does not show, if ever, show his face here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, really good. https://t.co/Gy0Tep2JSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap poor choice of snack food for lunch is my  #burgerking 10 pcs of chicken nuggets today. #TrumpDay2 https://t.co/E8RYexrVhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sorry here too. #WhatTheTrump #WTF https://t.co/QzXYLe0pA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MorningAfter  is when saying #WhatTheTrump is a lot worse than using #WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#today on my way to #work https://t.co/6amnGbUkHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You always want to beat Great Britain, don't you?  Well, you're on top now. Congrats or condolence, whatever. https://t.co/iE8jsGQriI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USElection2016  Good night US of A.  You had one task and wat da pak did you do with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USElection2016 US of A, the land of the brave and free guns for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nate Silver" There's a 70% chance of Hillary............. ahh never mind. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ will probably take more american immigrants soon too. https://t.co/QqBsP8CpXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're not even an american and you felt f..ked about the result #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ElectionNight Looks like that Vulgar_ian comedian aspiring for the White House will make the Oval office his stage after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For sure, New Zealand will get more American immigrants from now on #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#electionday   Hoping that US of A is not the day it becomes dumb and dumber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're not sure on what you do https://t.co/qTKSV32pXH #electionday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriandayton I'm not unfollowing you. I like what you post and like what you said, 3x is not really noticeable.  And that's great.  GL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay.  Thanks.  Might cull who I am following after this #electionday as lots just keep on tweeting the same crazy… https://t.co/kGYNRjZizL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be it a girl please https://t.co/S8bLCE5J5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mock #electionday being done at  the #Welly train station. I voted for #HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the rain, more #asparagus. They're a bit slanders now though. #homeveggiepatch https://t.co/di7ltS9Xex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like everybody is running useless Twitter polls. Can you just vote and wait for the result?   #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As an outsider, I could be wrong or I'll be right.  So I'm saying it here, it will be .@HillaryClinton on a landslide.  #USElections2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Sad but FYI theNZ @AllBlacks was finally beaten too by Ireland last weekend after 111 years at Chicago #SoldierField  #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the film too. https://t.co/7C0xrXZy3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable to think that the race would be even close. https://t.co/DevWYEIlCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USAvMaoriABs  Just half time and the Eagles look tired already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching almost super hero #SherlockHolmes as #DrStrange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parking wrongly is how they teach new drivers. #A1Driving #Wellington https://t.co/Oo1o6lIgcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those "stray cats" will nowhere to hide now. GL to this opportunistic party. https://t.co/qxvZ9YH3LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VULGAR_ian comedian aspiring for the White House still has a 25% chance of making the Oval office his stage at… https://t.co/8wWpZZCNxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A year ago already?  We still have the buzz feel of it and can't wait for the next one! https://t.co/rWcsZShf9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fifth #asparagus harvest and probably last for the season. Not bad from just 7 plants. #veggiegarden https://t.co/vMUvlSvMcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how soon will this be broken?  Today, tomorrow? https://t.co/mDCVJbX67T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AIGRugby @AllBlacks Wish I can. But no.  Now saving though for the @rugbyworldcup in #Japan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And just in time for Christmas, another #adidas improvement on that @AllBlacks shirt  .....  https://t.co/FVEpD6R7I7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ranked #1?  No correlation maybe but does not help the NZ ShareMarket a bit today. https://t.co/1HI0FQ32vV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 4th harvest, looking like this will be 2nd to the last #asparagus batch from my #homepatch #veggie garden. https://t.co/kvxciszftC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You did NZ proud!!! Thanks a lot @AllBlacks https://t.co/DFTZEiSF3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, the #nasty woman won over that one that has more respect for women. #Debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm done listening. Everything has been discussed before so good luck US of A. #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another endorsement for Trump, this from the Generals  #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on Immigration: Build The Wall  #debatenight
Trump on Economy: Make Mexico pay for the Wall built.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point Hillary is killing Trump with good arguments #debatenight]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>