<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great proposal for @POTUS - Bureaucrats Attempting to Sabotage Trump with Leaks - Breitbart https://t.co/epM0a7zkpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIRE the leakers! These saboteurs must be found and dealt with. @POTUS https://t.co/I9RDr6ZKiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous pick! We know it's great when Dems go nuts. @POTUS https://t.co/wQrMgsCXL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refreshing viewpoint. https://t.co/zGP2wSb9Ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media is in chaos saying STUPID things. @dmartosko https://t.co/Kh59AcXwng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES, call out media for false and misleading reporting! @PressSec @POTUS https://t.co/hDaNzvBRql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, way to go @POTUS ! Such disrespect must not be tolerated. https://t.co/sRmf2bsEc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU'RE FIRED! @POTUS  https://t.co/qAc9GWdwSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says Chris Wallace knows the facts when he has been wrong on so many things. https://t.co/kDgedTffE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares? https://t.co/JVugLvn0mS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She does NOT define the world. https://t.co/0QN4u0qLwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why @POTUS won the election! https://t.co/hhllB8jHlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowardKurtz panel today was awful. Voter fraud occurs. The extent is the question. To call @POTUS a liar on the issue is despicable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we will hold the press accountable for bias, rude language and spreading falsehoods. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/Jcq0OZPWhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes 100% agree! https://t.co/Ao5ECKihQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A total butt head with no credibility. https://t.co/vpG4anD3n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the facts and move to prevent fraud. https://t.co/yac2O0btCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, get the facts rather than that buffoon Jake Tapper declaring no fraud with no facts. https://t.co/nZvfdx6ry6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a buffoon! Will be great to see him back track when investigation shows the extent of voter fraud. https://t.co/okTtu8FtpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put Big Joe on TV! - Watch ‘Big Joe’ go off on anti-Trump protesters @foxandfriends @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/yIvoGAmJqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GAO, 2004 to 2012, the federal non-postal civilian workforce grew by 258,882 employees, from 1.88 million to 2.13 m… https://t.co/iNGEUzD7KQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you @ABC pledge to always tell the unbiased truth, DOUBTFUL! What an asinine question by abc news. https://t.co/r8Wq20lTKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News: Three Mainstream Media Lies on Trump's First Day https://t.co/hEHMylZqvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo!   Trump targets three liberal favorites with ambitious budget cuts | BizPac Review https://t.co/4QiKTiAQb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news. There are consequences for doing a poor job. https://t.co/8G6uiCkt9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["WH Press Secretary Bravo!  Sean Spicer Blasts Media’s ‘Deliberately False Reporting’" #generalnews #feedly https://t.co/HvDUHmpExU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tancredo: We Must Thank Barack Obama for Making Donald Trump Possible – And Inevitable" #generalnews #feedly https://t.co/YY3SrOVJrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific article on @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/nrKEGZNHFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, more tickets for wounded warriors! @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/uXDNdeRrvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, smaller government on its way! @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/ahPnUGokf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Trump Viewed Favorably by More than Half of US Voters » Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind! https://t.co/SIi4nOxX8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["CNN president: Our credibility is 'higher than ever'" #generalnews #feedly - Delusional CNN at it again.  https://t.co/q7IFv3joPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not this hopeful since Reagan" #generalnews #feedly - Bravo! @realDonaldTrump  https://t.co/eBCaOWQd7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A “Trumpian” Approach to Balancing the Budget - Excellent roadmap for @realDonaldTrump  https://t.co/HB3uxGXVrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold media accountable for poll manipulation to skew data, #fakenews https://t.co/FRUFbEv9Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that idea!@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/wDnHxNsNKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Fades Away As Trump Laughs At His Enemies - Kurt Schlichter https://t.co/XvsEo1yRQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Tapson: Trump’s Big Agenda: David Horowitz’s New Book Lays Out the Plan https://t.co/v7c85GpAVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theTunnelBear Free space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was Hillary Clinton's Nomination Legitimate? Six Reasons to Say No - Breitbart https://t.co/8KD7UlUFHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd vote for that! https://t.co/YNJq2UDnkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobel Laureate Smashes the Global Warming Hoax - YouTube. Worth watching. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/QnELeMT0b6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific article!  Newt Gingrich: Trump, New York’s Wollman Rink and the Congressional Budget Office | Fox News https://t.co/sdlVfAWrrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good, fair summary of two presidents and the PEOTUS. Worth reading. https://t.co/9xsv0Qwbgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read book, full of great facts. https://t.co/0lED9TcvEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total NYT B.S.  BLS data states 93 million not in labor force. @realDonaldTrump number valid! https://t.co/7Lj9tnzt1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell - Thomas Sowell https://t.co/QMUDw5U588]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unemployment rate is misleading! https://t.co/gyU3RILT3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA Today: Trump Has 'Broad Powers' To Prosecute Sanctuary Cities https://t.co/yrMUVjTh2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive — ‘Dream Team’: Sean Spicer Explains Donald Trump’s ‘Most Talented Cabinet in Modern History,’ https://t.co/RDFduFQy9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the cats! @mike_pence https://t.co/RA6bGZbil8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cudos to @mgoodwin_nypost for seeing through all these democrat distractions.  https://t.co/DrgexTutjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call out media lies. Hold media accountable. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/kXPs1bhFyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold the media accountable! https://t.co/d8uN5tFqug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the MOST qualified! @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/54BDmp90H0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great leaders in Trump administration. Business is making a comback - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette https://t.co/Vslnr5LXP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good article on Trump-pence leadership. One administration, two styles: Trump the brawler and Pence the cajoler https://t.co/mnV9Ae8tk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Rise and Fall of The Great Powers for why @realDonaldTrump is on the right track. https://t.co/G1EglMeMGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like a high priority for @realDonaldTrump  https://t.co/bw7qYz3Aw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only challenge is @RuthMarcus hugely negative bias towards all @realDonaldTrump thinks, says, does. Lot of positive… https://t.co/aTpbhGvK36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another STUPID WORTHLESS story. Where do they get this garbage? https://t.co/QjbXc70K1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the most personally successful and results oriented cabinet. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/rfjHLRTp2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Times ignores key line from intel report in rush to make Trump look bad | BizPac Review https://t.co/MagcNrQCV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Policy Was Always to Get Mexico to Reimburse Us for the Border Wall - Breitbart. Refreshing facts! https://t.co/RioZZtQGmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSM should report full time and part time jobs. That data shows dismal job creation over last 8 years. https://t.co/E0JXN5F6kj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does the intelligence community claim any credibility when they were so wrong on Iraq WMDs?@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/Kfh3qUd9c8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely! https://t.co/UMeJYRstYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 in Charts. (And Can Trump Deliver in 2017?) https://t.co/3VAOP6OGCo Totally biased NYT data. @realDonaldTrump @mitchellvii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful. He's the best! Will not miss "all about her Megan". https://t.co/nMKeHktFxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts not propaganda. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/qOt3lKwaOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye bye intellectual elite who are all talk and no results. https://t.co/LKhjyD8UcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tancredo: Biggest Fake News Story of the Year Is Russia Hacking the 2016 Election - Breitbart https://t.co/U9Ex5J7RfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eleven Great Thomas Sowell Quotes https://t.co/Ezp7cY26Kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Backfire: Obama's Israel slap could prompt U.S. to leave U.N." #generalnews #feedly https://t.co/aY1UsyxmM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Here's what 'free trade' really does to U.S." #generalnews #feedly https://t.co/8SRXJT1BM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN is just a debating club. @realDonaldTrump will totally transform. https://t.co/SNmsCUoh6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, four more years of failed leadership. We're much smarter. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/p0HcVd7z7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad to see Thomas Sowell retire. His great thinking and truth telling writings will be greatly missed. True Amer… https://t.co/RDwnv6RiTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["basic consensus around things like climate change, or how the economy works" - more delusional idealism from Obama… https://t.co/gNfhnHW0AD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theTunnelBear free space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So delusional. Do you think it might be his world view is just wrong and out of sync with Americans? https://t.co/Pd8OUpWLm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pointed this out to major pollster and he was in denial. Will continue to be fake news issue. https://t.co/yyHNubd4CE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press are largely elitist intellectual ideologues out of touch with reality. @realDonaldTrump must go direct to peo… https://t.co/TiQBLuJ2nF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'Diversity' Fraud - Thomas Sowell; Common sense on diversity. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/GCEYqiaLQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Public Service - Thomas Sowell; Terrific article calling NYT to task on concealed carry. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/u4O67zntwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it. Break the rules. Seek an alternative. Very smart. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/6nXdBK8KAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very revealing! @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/pg8STQsnxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Apple engaging in productive discussions with PEOTUS. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/evjjipI8MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's why our founders put the electoral college in place and why it must be preserved. https://t.co/TzIgGpuc0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll BS again. Pollsters have no credibility. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/DjyIerIFOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delusional Obama ideology killed competition and saddled the economy with job killing regulation. https://t.co/EioHQjF4Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fakenews Total BS! https://t.co/CsnI794AhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree 100%. Take out all the unneeded cost and fund the military’s real needs. https://t.co/NVNDStmyH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, follow or get out of the way. Pundits need to get out of the way and admire all the positive action to come. https://t.co/B6THk1Ff6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not about perfection, it’s about progress and bold action. https://t.co/UBXMAbC3zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, it's a new era in news. Press so biased and must be bypassed to get the truth. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/ZbphQ6vb85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @NavyFederal, I'm rooting for Navy, you should too! #GoNavy https://t.co/e4xnEEFhys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All true. Put Mattis on this to fund military build up. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/rCnPStE2fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific article on the facts of hiring illegal immigrants. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/zjRJDWd7Wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific Thomas Sowell article o Immigration Controversies @realDonaldTrump - https://t.co/GsjyafoaEY via @Instapaper]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>