<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz well you must have led a very unembarrassing life. Until now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 listen, end of Jan, 2pts off 2nd. Everyone stfu and look at were we are/were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Id prefer @TheNotoriousMMA to have a go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan will always be a hero of mine after his handling of @JKCorden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faipdeooiad @StephenMangan so many falsehoods &amp; now Im getting caught up in it...😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenMangan False reporting AGAIN. I can see 3 (three) women in that room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke got to be 7. @Theismann7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rAyIzQdAuh
Was worried about you @MCATEER4 
2 &amp; 1/2 yrs, you'd have missed out on our title celebrations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @SkyIreland, looking at switching broadband from Virgin to yourselves. Already have sky q, wondering if there is a setup charge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisanfield wijnaldum out, Lallana back to mid &amp; Origi up front. Wijnaldum slows everything down. Origi suits system better than Daniel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HenryJackson87 Absolutely. Biggest mistake Wijnaldum. Takes the air out of the ball, too slow. Did well for 2nd goal but other than that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4th person up this morning &amp; for the 527th day running they haven't emptied the dishwasher... #DishwasherGate https://t.co/Wkex9QDttX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportingintel the other 21 were also run by athletes who were, at one point, clean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to bed now fully confident that @Patriots will beat the spread and move to the AFC champs game...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Absolutely bullin here sittin on train after Coolmine for the last 75 mins. If warned could have got off prev stop. DISASTER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke hope falcons, pats, chiefs &amp; packers but I have a horrible feeling the seahawks will overturn the Falcons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casemann @ArcaneAce @pretareporter @THR excellent. Cant believe I didnt think of that one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke hopefully tonight will be different...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btsportfootball @LFC @DesKellyBTS Hey BT, sick of getting these 'Video blocked cos of ur location' messages...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke as a @Redskins fan, interest in the nfl goes from 100% to 5% from what feels like every January. Love the xtra week(s)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke well not being an arse  but it won't be 7-9 now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins You won that award!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeCallaghan @samuelJayC @TheSun well Freddie must be in his 40's now. No pace at his age...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 u keep saying that, but I disagree. Will be far tougher nxt season w Europe. Not winning won't be failure though #ynwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieHolt22 good at the Hollywood stuff Ollie but misses far too much of the bread &amp; butter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan_B94 @Timwatson78 @DjLeeC Imo Jones reaction is what got the lad sent off. Playing with too many South Americans...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonSpittle I'm confused...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux @Conconmonkey nah that's just 3 different blokes getting a pic with Shaggy on a random weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens is that you speaking or Bill Cullen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 will be sad to see him go. Obvious he loves club &amp; city...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisOBrien83 think of it more as hoping for a @Lions defeat. But I'm with ye...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisOBrien83 @steveohrourke Howard playing @Redskins so he'll prob have his game of the season! #HTTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glauncel he's the greatest cheat the sporting world has EVER known. Shows no contrition. He doesn't deserve my (or anyones) forgiveness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glauncel @mrhappyontherun @lancearmstrong @UCI_cycling @wada_ama @DrErinSaltzman @nzherald @nzheraldsport oh well that's OK then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Realaldo474 'drink' singular???
Carlsberg don't make Xmas nights out, but if they did....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisanfield @HenryJackson87 but it's early yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisanfield @HenryJackson87 no. I think he's slow &amp; doesn't know what to do with the ball high up pitch. Pricey for what he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Santa, could you PLS stop @RTE2fm &amp; @rte playing those #Fertility adds during EVERY add break? Promise Ill be a good boy... @vhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisOBrien83 horrible thing to wake up in the morning disappointed with a @dallascowboys loss...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh @AtlantaFalcons what are u doing with all these tds? I need Matt Bryant to be scoring FGS!!! #ramsvfal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Redskins @RyanKerrigan91 &amp; Trent Murphy. Gotta be some Irish in those??? #httr #WASvsPHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsBreakfast all they deserve...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Redskins can't lose this against a team with no snapper for all of 4th qtr... #httr #WASvsPHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarlanCoben is there a body in there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanWilsonMusic Secret Smile kicks off on @Republic2fm just as I get to work. Gonna be a good day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux Malcolm Kelly former Washington Redskins receiver, or Malcolm O'Kelly, former Irish rugby intl. Thinking they forgot the 'O'...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gokathrynthomas hope he behaves himself better than the last time he was here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke hope ur right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke it looks good alright. Also Tampa Bay getting 2.5 off San Diego. Tampa flying atm AND a better team away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ARSBOU that non decision for Bournemouth pen in 2nd half prob the worst so far this season. Shocking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tukeke70 Hope ur boys played fair this time. How many yellow cards? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ocean_handrail @KellySotherton I think you've enlightened her, Rob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liquid_atheist sorry Mr Atheist, I think that person is u...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liquid_atheist @GodlessInOK @AmandaJudge1 so ur saying @justinbieber is American then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobeCullen Meh... Skins should have taken them but for their wastefulness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@somerville73 @Taraustralis @IrishNetworkMN A true fan of the Hammer there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gordaz1981 @indykaila Liverpool fan here. Not wild. Have seen this so many times in last year, either Gotze or this lad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taraustralis sure it's 'mostly dry'. I don't see a problem...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 here's hoping...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieward2_ward @ward_des Jesus Julie he's a teenage boy, dont be going into his bedroom without telling him!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VueHelp Will do, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @VueHelp, problem with booking seats to the cinema (Liffey Valley) tonight. Can u help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS! @vuecinemas Trip RUINED!!!!! https://t.co/to7sHU7TmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 LOVE Sturridge, but with Mane/Lalanna/Firmino &amp; Coutinho on the pitch were a diff team. Movement/chasing all better w/o.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HueySweeney I just raised my left eye brow at that. 89!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evrobinson21 @dariusrucker @GamecockWSoccer Ahhh come on, its gotta be @PDMusic. Id never heard of u till I started listening to him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke @Medium Excellent. Just surprised there was no mention of him being an Oakland Raider...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryArnettCG if they end up winning, where's the harm? Do many have done it before, in so many sports...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conor_pope her names prob not Tracy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanMacKenna calling the other guy an arse, not u!
Misunderstanding always a prob with the char limit on twitter. My bad...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanMacKenna hope yer still getting paid...
What an arse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke @football_ie :)
Raiders looking good for Sunday? 1.5 points on the Jags? 😅😅😅🤕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke @football_ie fair enuff, but seems that way to me after ur tweets Monday...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke @football_ie kno ur getting at 'pool supporters re Mon match, but amt of £ Utd spent over Summer Pool shudnt be superior...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMerseyEminem pissed off I never thought of that description...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMerseyEminem sorry, almost forgot. What the fuck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMerseyEminem National game of Bangladesh.  Mix of Rover &amp; Dodge ball.  Thinking of entering a team for next world's.  U interested?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisOBrien83 @steveohrourke u have all of those in ur panel? Wow, some squad. Headaches EVERY week over who to drop...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News @pamfoundation @ghook hope ur watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The42_ie does he play rugby for Australia too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Munchious he was only there for the Rovers games, don't be trying to claim him as one of your own!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats on the W yesterday @steveohrourke . Thought I had u going into the 9pm games but Witten, Sanders &amp; Denver D were rubbish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @SethWickersham, put a bit of grass seed down there will ya? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 def Westwood or Elliott shud b no.1. Shudnt have signed long term deal in Summer when he'll always be no.2 at the club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanMacKenna when u look at the figures involved its blatantly unfair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanMacKenna U have expressed in 1100-ish words EXACTLY why I cannot get excited by Dub All Ireland win. Fantastic article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching at home in Kildare, Ireland!!! #NFLREDZONE https://t.co/KTgRtkLOHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan23_92 really need to sort out defending of set pieces. Pressure put on Swans in 2nd half was unbelievable at times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pdiddley Cant believe I did this and didnt include:

Feeling Strangely Fine - Semisonic

I am ETERNALLY sorry @DanWilsonMusic.
Seal out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke Went against Bucs twice last yr &amp; they won both times. Bogey team for me, but that -3 does look generous. Thks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke is that against the spread? What u think of Denver -3 vs the Bucs Sunday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisanfield oh please... This shite is what gives @LFC supporters a bad name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveohrourke as long as it doesn't stop Shady carrying on last weeks work I wont care. #FantasyNeeds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas @AndreaBocelli @3Arena 'Minor crowds', I'm sure Andrea will be delighted to hear the confidence u have in him filling the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanCollymore @NewsUK Good luck getting an answer to that one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancearmstrong @steveohrourke @PaulKimmage @OneZeroCon think someone else has the job. Just sayin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattholland8 @btsportfootball hate when I lose a game of scissors/paper/stone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HenryMcKean have just seen a clip of ur mum on youtube/newstalk. It's not her. Sorry for the confusion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HenryMcKean thought one of the mothers on 50 ways was ur mum. Sounded very like her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bazashmawy was one of the other mothers last night @HenryMcKean s?
Looks like u have such good craic.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>