<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Right now . https://t.co/YHyhy0sTWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The research linking autism to vaccines is even more bogus than you think - Vox https://t.co/u54vkG0DV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immediate travel ban on white supremists? 
Quebec Terror Suspect Alexandre Bissonnette https://t.co/3B9ag2chxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartRance sorry yes you did.  Referenced now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move from change control to change facilitation | The IT Skeptic https://t.co/3YtOHcT8BG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoreilly and it's an unstoppable avalanche now, worldwide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Muslim nations should follow suit
RT @baghdadinvest: Iraqi parliament blocks visas for all Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A working definition of stupidity: people who ask a question online whose answer is 10 seconds away on Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" if you can differentiate between Christians and the KKK, you can differentiate between Muslims and ISIS"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not alternative facts.  Listen to BBC More or Less: Counting Crowds
https://t.co/bwm7SeSPYs https://t.co/SUM47hKfay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecampin doesn't matter. Good service is not an essential part of every business model. It's not a given.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we have learnt anything from history it is that this is not the time to remain silent or do nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecampin what if users complain and staff are embarassed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Canada somehow siphon all the humanity out of the USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDalgarno precisely. Shitty service is a rational business decision. Ask Microsoft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vitruejoe Trump affects all of us.  It's the dumbest thing a country has done since 1933.  Nobody should stay silent over that twat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never forget that everything Hitler did in Germany was legal."
- Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q: is our shitty service affecting our revenue?
A: no.
Q: there is no next question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time I moved my websites out of the USA to somewhere more stable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky Trump pissed off the spooks. Makes it less likely to nail @RoguePOTUSStaff. Stay safe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDalgarno I did that walk in 1980.  The cicadas were deafening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually to be fair to Trump he's no worse than Robert Mugabe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" in Australia feral camels come up to houses and antagonize people"
" they are just trying to blend in"
- NSTTaaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out how many fake "BBC World News" pages there are on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Alkaline (pH) Diet https://t.co/a0vn57hx8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's team right now.
Watch "'Are we the Baddies?' Mitchell and Webb" on YouTube https://t.co/GdTwC8dM7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The loneliest whale in the world  https://t.co/HSMV0ub7Lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microwaves are the new VCR.
I've never met an intuitive one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flip the management team so it is BELOW the value stream.  Servant leader.
#devops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly John and Jackie is it?
RT @gregmottola: Now available from the Franklin Mint https://t.co/LNtyxRM0nE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a loyal user of HTC phones and my next one will be again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dkod19 yeah but much of the whole fricken world detests Trump and even before inauguration!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They can remove your kidney through your navel now".
Jimmy Carr: "They'd have to ask first".
QI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinshed sure but Trump is despised and mocked much more widely, and internationally. You should hear it here in NZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not support #OxFam. They are a political group who abuse fact, not a charity. https://t.co/pL2mRHC4tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveBremer @AcousticNut yeah social media makes it hard to compare.  Nixon and Lincoln were certainly vilified, and Ronnie RayGun. But...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of talk about how AI will take jobs. Machinery and computing took billions of jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, I would appreciate some historical perspective.  Has any president ever been as hated, mocked, and scorned as Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really https://t.co/bALeLQl7Mp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did we decide that there is some fundamental human right to not be offended?  Free speech makes it inevitable that we will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is no longer possible to deny that Trump is a lying weasel with much to hide https://t.co/FLthEAmf9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maknf America great again, Trump administration tells EPA to freeze all grants, contracts https://t.co/JeqBQJzbNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good!
RT @ITSMNinja: The top 7 IT pitfalls, and how to avoid them https://t.co/rKxnpw1qOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Magnus919 looks like I lost two followers so far.  Gonna miss them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_peters it's great. Overseas buyers pay high. One day they need to liquidate. They get screwed, leave their $$ in NZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlorianHeigl1 Trump is just one symptom of the rise of antiscience, the triumph of stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the post-fact world where ignorance is glorified and emotion displaces reason.
This can't end well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope all those who supported Trump are starting to feel really stupid (if they weren't already)
https://t.co/xLlRsoK2Ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two features of modern Hollywood: implausible and psychotic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should be on organic and anti-GMO foods https://t.co/pRPklo4x62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["..if all others accepted the lie, which the party imposed... then the lie passed into history and became truth" 1984 - George Orwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several times lately a useful thing is a discontinued line. Marketing people are idiots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Truth.
White House press secretary lies and yells at media. https://t.co/Qx2yuxyXnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be the two megalomaniacs Trump and Putin vs China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump wasn't already insane he will be now after the constant barrage of scorn and mockery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to all my followers for the political tweeting.  This really is different: a landmark of future history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DigitalFiona @AtomicAdMan @tom_peters @kpronn @mgallagh68 China has opened up land channels to Europe. Bye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can reason prevail over Trump?
Senators on key panel reject Trump's skepticism about vaccines https://t.co/ecaoQ16skY
There is hope...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicAdMan @tom_peters @kpronn @mgallagh68 Actually many of us stopped considering the USA "leader of the free world" long ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot on.... https://t.co/niuqXGvdkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man of the people... https://t.co/Myvy6jsPGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Thanksgiving the Rapture for turkeys?
- Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is old enough to remember when you did most things in silence?  When the world didn't have a soundtrack...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In business, we usually manage to ignore people's policial alignment, but Trump is changing that.  I find it hard to cope with supporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news for the world: Trump's ultranationalist speech https://t.co/UkoH1awiHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dkod19 arggh I hate being snopesed.  Thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who let the dogs out?  Trump is already unravelling liberal America.
It is easy to fuck a country.  It is very hard to unfuck it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not alternative medicine, it's an alternative TO medicine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best News You Don’t Know - global poverty https://t.co/7rvEKR2hmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why We Didn't Vaccinate Our Child https://t.co/WGFQSNNsfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Ready for Gene Editing https://t.co/neGRNgS9oM
And get ready for the eco-loons to lose their minds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_L you're right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kieranwalsh in comparison to Trump, George the Beady is looking pretty good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance Australia fair
RT @Regrettedzulu: Australia Day billboard featuring women in hijabs removed after threats https://t.co/cyCsGROZD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_peters @Sharnarthee you're not that interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megh_wright in New Zealand, the total cost of my wife's chemo and radiotherapy was about $300.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to shut down stupid.
Stand up for science. https://t.co/M5UxdNeBDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measure Sustainability. Nothing to do with ecology: technical and cultural debt. Is the unit working at an indefinitely sustainable rate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @repjohnlewis: Never become bitter or hostile. Accept the way of peace, believe in the philosophy &amp; the discipline of nonviolence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neontaster the backlash is from her fans not the industry. Trump is loathsome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["frozen ice".  Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DEVOPSINST that's very kind thankyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States already has a vaccine safety commission. And it works really well, experts say. https://t.co/hiFnSJ1YvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make the Most of the Free Intro to #DevOps Course from @botchagalupe https://t.co/jxRzBstPXx.
Nice work dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arstechnica @BethMarieMole more accurately: confirms a couple of benefits of cannabis amongst the many claimed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um....
RT @arstechnica: Massive scientific report on marijuana confirms medical benefits https://t.co/RH77lJovCz by @BethMarieMole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lest we forget that the USA elected an enthusiastic pussy grabber https://t.co/BIgIivnFjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireAgutter @kaimarkaru I'm presenting this at #PINK17 https://t.co/INkgGY6sPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireAgutter @kaimarkaru in the most mature level, #DevOps drives transformation of the org model: product not project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["no paper allowed on walls".
Fine.  Make some walls you control yourself.
#devops #jfdi https://t.co/fngMWiZa8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote from today: "why have we been hurting ourselves that way for 20 years?"
#devops works.  The proof is in the eating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dougtedder that's the distinction between service request and product, not between service and service request https://t.co/VubSbjJzQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, duh.
A new study says compound in turmeric has 'no specific therapeutic benefits' | https://t.co/7ipIdO4Eyr https://t.co/F6tW9iKSbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DaveBremer we.may never know the truth about Trump's golden shower with hookers, but the relevance is that it is entirely believable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone uses a "I used this simple trick" headline on LinkedIn, you know corporate marketing has gone to hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news about fake news is that it might finally teach the public the necessity of critical thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @newscientist: Extinct giant goose used its wings to fight rather than fly https://t.co/cyyvO2G6ji https://t.co/utn7gFVngG @GanderSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it a bad thing that I know my Qantas frequent flyer login by heart?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[itSMF 2016 Survey on #ITSM https://t.co/hEEKb081qA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5.2 earthquake.
Nobody in the open plan office even got up or raised their voice.
#WellingtonLife]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>