<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kiwiseabreeze as they arise. But I'd be very interested to hear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In NZ we have https://t.co/kWwhabsOLx, and https://t.co/cBvs9F1d0N. I'm unsure to what extent either org is geared up to take on battles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@szechuan thank you! I was putting my own list together - and wonder if you know of any NZ groups like ACLU?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fancy plane... https://t.co/89KTQ5QcDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This made me smile :) https://t.co/UCEqsbDAJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badtom @keith_ng all of the constitutional back stops rely on everyone minding the conventions. It can all fall apart quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs no mean feat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon oh Pepper no! So sorry. Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarb sorry it's not sunnier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parking meter will have run out while I'm waiting to get blood tests. I had more coins, but the coin slot kept closing.gah!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peter_tan in a holster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuralOrgasim it was fine ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren you go to your GP, and they tell you you're overdue your tetanus booster. Now waiting for the pain...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriankingston take care...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skyrize @Medium this is really frightening to read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile the news in NZ https://t.co/DLToH9KpZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Elizabeth Warren be the next president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuralOrgasim @Covlin "nothing about me without me" &lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Manipulative and unprofessional. https://t.co/3cQwT7F9re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikapearson @kyhwana @secvalve snacks sounds very important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You feel like your kid picked the right high school when all your tech community colleagues are there with their kids too ;) @kalena]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nayag76 thx! Your lot too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I have a kid in the house all ready to start high school. Whew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanielflick I still have a photobucket account!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_turtle you're not wrong.  Google photos a reasonable backstop until I get my external HD. cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_turtle doing that too - just want to store in cloud first.  Until I get the hard drive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoslimo might just go with google photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoslimo @Flickr sign up a new account because that email is taken by old account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timoslimo @Flickr I meant flickr.  I have seriously had nothing but aggravation. It won't recognise my email address, but won't let me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay. After about five attempts I absolutely refuse to use https://t.co/uc8ReHPhGs - most ridiculous sign in ever.  Other suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BF remembered Big Audio Dynamite exists and our day got better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PINKYFANG which should be illegal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always refused to use Uber because of concerns about the effect on marginalized people. Pretty stoked now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife in the garden https://t.co/SwAs1V4SIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah @markboynz we have professional colleagues who won't be able to work on U.S. based jobs (which are frequent enough).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkdeedle well fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Felt like I really need to do something. Anything. So I cleaned my bathroom to within an inch of its life. That will help battle fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuOld @DearMama_ I found it funnier than I expected to as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They even have the cat's baby photos. https://t.co/xnHetw6Wbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike absolutely. And to an external hard drive I am buying tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kiwiseabreeze I can't explain to you how amazing this is.  Me and Mr 12 on his 1st birthday https://t.co/3VqjxBlkLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So freaking happy. I just got my laptop off daughter, and discovered I had saved all their baby photos after all. Thought lost forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee the awful tummy bug a week ago is a major suspect. I don't have an appendix anymore, so its not that ;).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_vitaminK @thelemonofpink the only 2 people I saw dressed up today were ladies in their 70s. True story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have had an intensely sore stomach for a week. It has just finally started to feel better. Thank god for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theunfocused @LittleCatDesign that's me right now. Trying not to be silenced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffinmum @Becs @GrumpyYetAmusin but that to remember we will most likely be ok in time. And there arte lots of good people doing  gd shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffinmum @Becs @GrumpyYetAmusin I remember being terrified world affairs. Especially nuclear threat. I try to explain that we're concerned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin I'm trying to reassure 2 of my kids...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just getting in some research should it become necessary https://t.co/6C5VBKIJRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon he went to a salon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caption this: https://t.co/QANJA9dGIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dairymanNZ oh well ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally feel hungry. Making schnitzel, corn on cob, potatoes etc. Brb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dairymanNZ loads for me. Perhaps you're blocked?? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have these feels from time to time... https://t.co/L73NJO3FP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nayag76 you're in the right place!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't been outside today, hurry up! Summer has arrived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived at rendezvous point 8 minutes early. Who am I even?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting the weekend by being picked up early from work due to intense stomach pain is not ideal. Has subsided after a sleep, but wtf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mokai77 Hunters &amp; Collectors at the Power station in 1986.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming I hope so! He seems to be very happy to see me. So probably is :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightweight @JaneyGodley oh seriously shut up Dave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JusticeWillett the stapler also works sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty awesome... https://t.co/78wEePjKHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race relations Commissioner Susan Devoy - asking government to do more about hate speech *approves*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliCopeman yep. It's pretty shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect food costs in the U.S. are about to increase. Just a hunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Michael_J_Parry @ParryKylie cute!! Happy Anniversary!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwipaula @glibnotion I just looked at a lease doc with a final expiry date when I'm 71.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbowtie "Make America Great Britain Again"? (Not my genius).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwipaula @glibnotion I finished in '86, and again in '88...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glibnotion @kiwipaula I got married in 1991 #apocolyptic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of the day off for Keegan has been better if I was lucky to be talked about. https://t.co/VPy5QNeZzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really liking @MacsBeerandWine raspberry wheat beer (low alcohol too).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicken kebabs on rice with boiled veges is amazing when you're starving hungry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently my garden bag has arrived and I'm ridiculously excited about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glibnotion yep. I really hope too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patho_gin open plan office joys??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else got the Mary Tyler Moore Show theme song going through their head right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinRBanks latest album is not a bad place to start. The Hope Six Demolition Project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce it'll probably be Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CriminelleLaw is it as surreal watching this from inside the US as it is from the outside?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BF got some pretty great tickets for PJ Harvey tonight... https://t.co/feCPCzpjpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis @YvonneMilroy thank god for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elpie @lightweight so pleased you are again "with dog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elpie @lightweight *gasp* I did not know you had a PUP!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightweight @thomasbeagle @paulbrislen does Luna retrieve things for you? Like your pipe, slippers or newspaper? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Removing sexist language from templates. On fire today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @thomasbeagle she can't even manage a poodle then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle @paulbrislen I can highly recommend the poodle x types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle @paulbrislen a beagle would be awesome though right??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle @paulbrislen squee! What flavor dog??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oharris69 have a good one O!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @danslevin for alerting me to https://t.co/IZF9pOIHP8 - a subscription service for arty fatty movies ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuralOrgasim my office mate is coming...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing new shoes to work. They're so quiet I keep sneaking up on people and frightening them. #excellent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just removed "ameliorate" from my advice and used simpler words. Am good lawyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belacqua66 #nickcave was intense (in a great way!) I'm off to see PJ for the first time tonight! Were there seating issues last night??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor puppy put in pen. Practicing for tomorrow. https://t.co/WwQYNhDfLt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>