<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGeeConor should we send you some money for the bribe for the officer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGeeConor is it true that you are in prison now??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birthday lunch at @michiesushi IFSC #japanesefood https://t.co/Ns6bk8PIzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from @michiesushi IFSC #japanesefood https://t.co/mnDvIlt0dw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusBurtBKK it's cool, but I prefer Battlefront to be honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't play #Battlefield1 for too long, it makes me anxious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sufman He is rather funny to watch :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-birthday present for me! #lego #legobatmanmovie https://t.co/03BO0ZTSl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sufman I think I just found one of your colleagues :D https://t.co/mmkKrS177F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homemade spelt bread #food https://t.co/Yx8IWS6YI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RxJS Observables Crash Course https://t.co/zyBXHj13mb via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit too cloudy today #fujifilmxt1 @ Dalkey Island https://t.co/lHJpGrvHZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please stop worrying about Angular 3 https://t.co/UMrgqAFra9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any good alternative to Phantomjs that I can use with jasmine + karma?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was finally doing a decent match on BF1 and all the sudden I got disconnected from the server. Rather disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/7iXiDH0eVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Star Trek Discovery has been delayed to May 2017 because they figured out that the ship they showed us in the teaser is ugly has hell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I got rid of the flu yesterday, but nope, it's back -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MumblinDeafRo @LEGO_Group and apparently the set doesn't exists on the lego missing bricks website -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MumblinDeafRo @LEGO_Group plate 2x1 light bluish gray for this set https://t.co/IAScBeTG5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for the first time in years one of the lego sets I bought recently is missing one brick -_- @LEGO_Group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally saw #RogueOne, still not sure if it's my favourite Star Wars movie, but it's definitely a great war movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn that's what I said when I figured it out :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized that I booked the ticket for tonite and not tomorrow night #RogueOne BIGGEST FAIL EVER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_cpp wait a minute, was the show tonite and not tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Friday deal on @OriginInsider, so I couldn't resist to get #Battlefield1 https://t.co/HL50fQhCKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnazzyQ quick question: did you had any issues with your hackintosh after a few months of use? Does it handle updates well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland essentially when it started a black overlay appeared on top of the app and you weren't able to tap on anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland only after I've updated to iOS 10, on 9 it just didn't want to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans you just proved that you are even dumber than brits, well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally Series 16 is complete! #afol #lego https://t.co/yprbcasKw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Dear Microsoft,” by @SlackHQ https://t.co/UPL2fQXgLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanhogan Nope, I meant this (see picture) https://t.co/NnyXuoOMDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanhogan wait, are you suggesting that we should drop bombs over our clients?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-pro users asking why you need 32GB of RAM to a pro is like asking to an F1 pilot why you need an F1 car to race instead of a FIAT 500.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @Apple, you know it's 2016 and 8GB of RAM don't cost €240, but €40.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn and it's really dangerous as will shorten any ssd drive's life by quite a good margin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melgabored In case you haven't noticed, it wasn't about the female cast, but the story was the problem, nothing to do with gender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to have an happy SSD drive, stop using the @spotify client, just use the web player. https://t.co/l68SmeuDXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock at the vet #kittens @ Sandymount Pet Hospital https://t.co/DQTdjLzT5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArindamRoyC anyway, if you have issue with SSH, that's the fix https://t.co/efoF8GqtaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frost_ie I read it yesterday, I laugh a lot about it :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArindamRoyC Installation was fine, but took far too long in my opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upgraded my mac mini to macOS Sierra and I already regretted it. SSH is completely fucked. #macOSSierra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @YouTube, why you keep showing bollywood movies and trailers on my youtube page? WTF is wrong with your algorithm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just can't wait to go to #PredictConf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the #PredictConf is gonna be great this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally I had the chance to go to shoot some seascape photos, and to try some presets from @sleeklens! Article soon! https://t.co/HHrzE7NPjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport yeah I received the correct access codes a half hour later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport also I tried to login, but the code I get via email is invalid, is because of the same problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last two pieces for my gaming rig are finally arrived! #gaming https://t.co/LqXPPqtcGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland btw, iOS app is not working for me from weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland renew the SSL for your domain, and start to consider to find a new CTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renew the SSL certificate... And by the way, the app on iOS doesn't work for me https://t.co/UFwkYT7QcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn I found this case that goes nicely under my telly https://t.co/q4ME6Wv50N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn That's what I'm trying to achieve, on the couch, but with a keyboard and a mouse :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn not a big gamer, but I wanted to invest some money on a good pc for the living room, I can't stand consoles, especially controllers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn I would like to play with Battlefield or No Man's Sky, and to be fair I feel like a newbie in games, didn't play in a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn Like I can barely play with Insurgency at the lowest settings with the mac mini :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threnn at the moment not much, using my Mac Mini for casual gaming, but I think it's time to have a proper gaming rig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motherboard and liquid cooler arrived, only graphic card and RAM are missing now https://t.co/7xerJqe5VP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPU is here! Getting closer to my gaming pc https://t.co/LeTc7qgUzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If All The Ice Melted On Earth? ft. Bill Nye https://t.co/9dV65Ley3C via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarsCuriosity how's the weather on Mars today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddmotto you can always learn a new framework, as long as you have a good knowledge of a language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordered all the parts for my gaming desktop :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland took the car in shelbourne rd, it was left open bt the previous customer, oil has to be changed and it needs a wash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland can I unlock the car with the card as before or I can only do it with the phone now? App keeps crashing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Ireland not to authorise Bayer’s latest bee-harming insecticide. https://t.co/6RN1MNqTAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I retired from music photography / I'm still alive https://t.co/fBfVkRz9rZ #musicphotography https://t.co/gi4rnSnYby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Guy Claims Sony ‘Scammed’ Him, Shares Customer Service Horror Story https://t.co/2sOaF4eK37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alltvvins's album it's just great, one of the best albums that came out of Ireland in the past few years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunflowers fields https://t.co/uUPwRK5EUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #CrystalPepsi ad that @Pepsi will never show you [video] #conflictpalmoil https://t.co/ARnTyXwBQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbubinas perhaps they don't want the photog to be sued?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go ahead, animal abuser, sue us for printing your photo https://t.co/E7KxYg4w4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bread for tomorrow #baking #bread https://t.co/g0PNkhYASk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can somebody nuke Donald Trump? https://t.co/VH7D5oaAUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I Post-Process Hard Light and Overwhelming Tones https://t.co/8KerF4Suvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@insurgencygame are the servers down? Can't see any in game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazingAncap @KateMariaGlobal Because in Italy we never rest, constantly working 24/7 :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateMariaGlobal ahaha that's brilliant :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My work has just been featured on the RB homepage @redbubble https://t.co/3UmQcylGfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/ZMDXIBrKWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A picture of a @BiffyClyro's live show I took a couple of years ago #biffyclyro https://t.co/7VF9PJEXEM https://t.co/CE6qcj2ZcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hand drawn by a computer https://t.co/Yo4cx8CRYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Week Tonight with John Oliver: Republican National Convention (HBO) https://t.co/VcKOWsSYYY via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you didn't know, I have a shop on @redbubble https://t.co/0T9WFrbapk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trailingjohnson I owe you an apology, I thought you were the wrong director for Star Trek, but you did a marvelous job #StarTrekBeyond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to see #StarTrekBeyond yesterday: it surpassed my expectation by quite a lot, trailer was shit, but the movie was very good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock the cat #kitten #cat https://t.co/8EsUtQOqBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the next number of Playcat ... #cats https://t.co/LgIJ163Bnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Howth at sunset #landscapephotography https://t.co/HzLdkVRxqf https://t.co/LbIyM5FN5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoCarIreland how come that all my previous bookings are not in the system and I have to use my old pin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frannina yeah I think that the fluency thing is completely off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duolingo says that I'm 38% fluent in swedish, but I feel it's more like 3.8%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Coffee Commercials Were Honest - Honest Ads https://t.co/kb103VsgB7 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Brits that are still hoping for a "better deal", you still don't get that the only think you will get from the EU is loads of Vaseline?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking news: Portugal's defence has been found. They are still at the airport.#POLPOR #EURO2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that Portugal should try a different formation, the 0-0-Ronaldo doesn't work anymore #POLPOR #EURO2016]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>