<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Banger of a tune to start the working week. #NowPlaying Life Itself by Glass Animals ♫ https://t.co/oxJ5Y2fs3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second @janellemonae movie in a week. If it's anywhere near as good as Moonlight, we're in for a treat (@ Cineworld) https://t.co/GHvThSPBEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharononeill I missed your birthday! So soz. Looking forward to catching up soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New on the blog: Damien Dempsey – It’s All Good (Live at Vicar St) - https://t.co/GSEUNyc5Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amanda234 Can't wait to see what Sean Spicer says about this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brady says they "never felt out of it". Fake news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkenealy Some comeback this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane catch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noel's half time stew? Tasty. Massive half ahead for the Patriots. #SB51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkenealy @amylong Hadn't thought of that... Big game ahead for the Pats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkenealy @amylong Hope ye get the result tonight. Presume the little man won't be staying up to watch 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's right sports fans https://t.co/bd5Wl4uy2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You beauty. Mata makes it three. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ibra!! Two in two minutes #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GET IN THERE!! Miki makes it one nil #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mata is lucky there. Could have gone. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite bit of McCarthy as Spicer is using the podium as a battering ram. Clearly improv-ing through that bit and so funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on United #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foot tennis or Six Nations? :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fehler Good day for ye and intensity in defence won it. Enjoy mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck it anyway. Well done Scotland. On balance the better team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Ireland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not wrong https://t.co/sXBY2pq0xH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boucherhayes Sideways rain, sunny spell, overcast, freezing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A billboard for 'pulled chicken' on a pizza. Are we any better than Trump's America? Really?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to graffiti but want it to fit in 😂 #dublin https://t.co/qUolJqea1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're rare but some days in work are like: https://t.co/JI6CfpmPAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneaking a subtle @Elbow reference into @Dublin_ie's production schedule. Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's #dublin alright https://t.co/z0CO6hyBHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll take your mates for a night of VR in the not so distant future: https://t.co/49ApDa6sgb Places who do it right will make cash money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meemmaaa @ciaraobrien Combination of a high tide, wind from south east and rainfall. New flood protection works along IFSC etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Love* this https://t.co/RFt9qHXgFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget what Fianna Fáil did to this country. Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly *So* frustrating https://t.co/zAP30FT9Qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was muck and a big opportunity missed #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make your voice heard on the Public Health (Alcohol) Bill: https://t.co/as4Cfn9ep0 Literally took two minutes to do this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riptidemovement Alright lads. Does Gar have his photos of Dublin online anywhere? Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamSMoloney @keyofdchoir Nice one. Will give them a buzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterMcGuireIE @TimForde @dublinbusnews @NextBusDublin is the app you need. It's superb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to get a couple of pull ups done for @keyofdchoir. Anyone able to recommend somewhere that's decent and won't cost the earth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darraghdoyle @clydecarroll That's brilliant. Wouldn't imitate it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the @GlendaloughDist gin launch @JTPims. Tasty stuff! Doubling as a meeting with @DublinByMouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never half-ass two things. Whole-ass one thing."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmccallions Lovely shot. Will link the piece here when it's live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to self: get the story of this for Dublin.ie https://t.co/KQlHdwtapr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moonlight is one of those special movies. Entire cast is superb and the way it's shot really suits the subject. See it if you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at Cineworld for Moonlight in Dublin w/ @tikkin https://t.co/QYU8f6HluN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a guy looking for somewhere to live in #dublin, there's a room to rent @DarrenByrne's old place here: https://t.co/hCOp0lMCGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In and out of IKEA in 50 minutes with all bits got. Benefits of going on a weekday probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attempting a straight forward IKEA run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find large mails in Gmail, use 'size:'. For example, size:5000000 will pull up mails larger than 5Mb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaLucas @colmtobin It's right feckin here: https://t.co/ibZt85yvai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DamoDempsey's It's All Good (Live @Vicar_Street ): https://t.co/3uhWoIXCp6 Never seen the place bounce like that. Incredible gig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence hasn't deleted that tweet ffs. It's here: https://t.co/ibZt85yvai Don't blindly RT stuff that isn't true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, who had a week for "when law and order break down in the US"? https://t.co/kbAd3EC6EI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BSchweinsteiger makes it 4 with his first goal at OT. *Delighted* for him. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martial with the setup again. It's three. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ball from Martial. Two up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It hasn't been pretty but #mufc go one up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can everyone check their sheds to see if @EndaKennyTD is hiding there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe how quick @ManUtd got that Rooney clip and tweet ready. Impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patphelan Absolutely. Speaking personally, I've never seen him do anything I'd admire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was there for @WayneRooney's favourite goal against Man City. OT exploded with the noise. What a finish. #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital subscription to @nytimes is €9 a month. I'm in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised but happy that the #mufc FA Cup game is on BBC today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenmcguire I'd say so yeah. Looks like a hell of a stadium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamngr Absolutely. Curious to know who put it together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, the rain is back https://t.co/h8DUxA28OB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiriamDevitt Enjoy. Really looking forward to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the time to make some sense of what you wanna say and cast your words away upon the waves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who made this?! https://t.co/6yEuxqiucQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of the fact that we have a progressive, intelligent, compassionate and truthful @PresidentIRL. Vital in the days to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenmcguire You in Engerland for the weekend? Spurs almost slipped up too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudsteph Dat name tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of the day is being spent organising @keyofdchoir's first foray off the island for a gig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenmcguire It's been some day already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A company called NerdWallet. Nerd. Wallet. Right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifestylesports Needed a pair urgently. Thanks for the help anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Last Sunday Funday is one of the best episodes of You're The Worst. Marrying ridiculousness with marriage breakdown &amp; PTSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is crazy. https://t.co/GX5kYfTy7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell John Hurt. Rest well. If I ever get to this level of badass, I'll be ecstatic https://t.co/xRzcNa7scE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain seems to be the only Republican with the balls to say anything contrary to Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say a good 75% of @Boojum_Dublin's customers are students. Place is always busy with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever designed @GoCarIreland's new site is completely clueless on UX. Awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifestylesports Okay, great. Are these in stock: https://t.co/7ikLeRdkOi in a 10/11 in Dublin city centre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With places like @lifestylesports and @Elverys, I'd love to be able to check live stock levels in stores. In this case, astro boots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban foxes move fast, hence the last of focus #Sandymount https://t.co/TNANmGGHrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LolsyByrne The smiley face rescues anything though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulleeRed Traffic data seems to say it's moving now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DermotTodayFM Lobster burnt t'fuck all round. 😂 At least it was open air. Lille was a sauna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flowers? A romantic getaway? Fancy dinner? Nope, get your lover a Ronaldo blanket. https://t.co/g0uM7gvQfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky Sports News with a countdown ticker for Deadline Day. That's 6 days away. 🤔🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DermotTodayFM The absolute craic! https://t.co/08U5foUo6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's disappointing. Can only imagine she's gutted https://t.co/8egd9bmkP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O.J.: Made In America is a hell of a watch and I'm only two parts in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not me anyway. Family WhatsApp groups across the country are doing some business tonight I'd say. #EuroMillions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryDunne Good stuff. I'll respond to that mail in the morn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryDunne When is that btw? #vestedinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OJ: Made In America - Part 2 #NowWatching]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>