<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A #Believer in #Jesus #Christ should be Fearless_Living totally independent of all worldly systems-established in #God's Love &amp; His #Kingdom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #Jesus #Christ has said it-you the believer can do it-Jesus isn't speaking in riddles-He wants you to know &amp; accomplish His will-Eph5:17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's Absolutely No Passivity_No Uncertainty when a believer has Faith in #God's Integrity_Blessed Are Those Who Overcome NOT get over run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faced with a major decision &amp; haven't a clue what to do_Don't Panic-#Jesus #Christ is &amp; has your answer-Peace Be Still &amp; Listen To Him Say-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In times of trouble James declares to count it all Joy-NOW how could you do that without knowing you'd win_that everything works out fine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For of whom a man is overcome,of the same is bought unto bondage"#Jesus #Christ delivered you from the pit_Be sure you stay out of vomit-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen if #Jesus #Christ in you is greater than anything facing you_Why the Fear_apprehension_inadequacy_inferiority when facing a mountain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Go A Day Without #Jesus Is To Hazard The Possibility Of Losing Your Saltiness &amp; Being Good For Nothing Except Be… https://t.co/7b7jtbjQTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember - the Holy Spirit #Jesus sent to you to lead you into all the Truth is your helper not your servant - He w… https://t.co/SOcR9PUbNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it wasn't for the active vital faith &amp; living relationship with God Almighty of Elisha the servant would have be… https://t.co/KECapG2NPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ flows through all those abiding in Him - the rest perish - having lost their saltiness thus good for… https://t.co/9tjlC5GSFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Centurion's great #faith was based on his experiential understanding of #authority-He recognised #Jesus #Christ's Authority to command!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith Without Action Is Dead_a #christian is to fight the good fight of #faith &amp; win_Not bundle up in a corner hiding from the scary devil-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOTHING CAN STOP #JESUS #CHRIST'S PLAN FOR YOUR LIFE - EXCEPT YOU - take the Israelites' at the Promised Land's Bor… https://t.co/vSRF8oDR0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Are The #PRAYER WARRIORS who are awake to stop the Anti-Christ's ploy  - to plant tares in their Nations whilst the #Church sleeps?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was a time in the #Church of #Jesus #Christ that prayer power warriors would scared the Hell out of opposing Kings let alone their own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INTERSESSION SHOULD BE A DAILY WORK OF THE #CHURCH OF #JESUS #CHRIST - every Church everywhere should be interceding for God's Kingdom Come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't face another day_thinking of ending it all BUT all you need is for something to go right for a change-#Jesus #Christ can sort it - ASK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #Christian - if you're not INTERCEDING FOR YOUR NATION cause your too busy for that - UNDERSTAND WHILST YOU SLEEP ANTI-CHRIST IS AT WORK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Simple #Christian - NO INTERCESSION - NO SUPERNATURAL MANIFESTATION OF #JESUS #CHRIST'S POWER INTERVENTIONS FOR YOUR NATION - Wake Up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Christian you needs wake up-The Anti-Christ Spirit Has Declared War On You-if your not prayed &amp; fasted up - Satan will run right over you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Those Who Abide In The Secret Place of #Jesus #Christ who fear no evil, who are blessed under His ever present loving protection - Amen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not ABIDING IN THE VINE of #Jesus #Christ what if any protection do you have in these uncertain times - AWAKE SLOTHFUL SLEEPER -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Was The Last Time You INTERCEDED FOR NATIONAL LEADERSHIP - hope you're not one who takes your Liberty for granted - Needs God's Wisdom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Christian if you're not strong in your faith- if you're not competent in your authority in #Jesus #Christ you'll deny Christ under pressure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awake you that sleep - arise from the dead &amp; #Christ shall give you light - see then you walk diligent-Redeem The Time For The Days Are Evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ Is A Soul Winner &amp; So Am I_what about you_What do you do for Jesus_Attending Church isn't enough - Win Souls! #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interceding #Christian of #Jesus #Christ ushers' in His power &amp; might -  dynamic in it's working - forwarding His Kingdom - are you one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Church of #Jesus #Christ is asleep &amp; the Anti Christ Spirit is planting tares everywhere - What Price Liberty - Eternal Vigilance -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your fight's against Satan's anti-christ spirit - Don't be offended by or afraid of people - INTERCEDE FOR #CHRIST'S POWER TO MANIFEST NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's Nothing you can't overcome in #Jesus #Christ-Jesus with all His Power to overcome is Living IN You-Why Not Let Him Empower You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fear has no place in the heart of a #Christian in fact it can't elsewise #Jesus #Christ is a liar-Fear is torment in your head-Kick IT OUT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You the born again believer-a Son of God have been authorised through your faith in #Jesus #Christ to operate in His Authority over all evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ lives in &amp; has his expression through the believer-He lives in you NOT beside you-He fights through you NOT apart from you-NT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've made changes at work_you've been laid off_You don't know what's going to happen BUT #Jesus #Christ does &amp; will help you sort it-ASK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OPEN YOUR EYES &amp; SEE #CHURCH - ALL IS NOT WELL- you've taken your liberty in #Jesus #Christ for granted &amp; now face losing it #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIGHT THE GOOD FIGHT OF FAITH - having everything laid out for you on a plate is over #CHURCH- Obey #Jesus #Christ INTERCEDE #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Current #Church Has Been Coasting On the #INTERCESSION of past generations of #believers but that's finished now #JESUS #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus admonishes you not to be afraid OR troubled by anything-giving you His confident Peace that Knows-Nothing by any means will harm you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Wait Till The Enemy's At Your Door - it'll be far too late then to prevent the bloodshed- INTERCESSION MAKES FOR PEACE #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Doctrines of demons promote self interest - a lethargic towards their responsibility for the #Intercession of Rulers #Jesus #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruel mockings &amp; scourgings- bonds &amp; imprisonment- believers slain with swords awaits a sleeping church-Arise #Jesus #Christ #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE MAJOR EVENT IN EVERY CHURCH SHOULD BE INTERCESSION to break Satan's end time take over plan through faith #Jesus #Christ #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believers in #Jesus #Christ wax valiant in fight through faith - the #God kind of faith that moves mountains in INTERCESSION #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO POINT HAVING #JESUS #CHRIST'S POWER &amp; AUTHORITY if you don't use it #Church - Every Church Should Sound Of Intercession #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ HAS ALL AUTHORITY - in His Name that contains all this authority-the gates of Hell won't overpower His Church #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO THROUGH FAITH SUBDUED KINGDOMS - A Church asleep is a push over for the devil's henchman- WAKE UP #CHURCH #Jesus #Christ #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHERE IS THE #CHURCH_there will be no turning to flight the armies of the aliens whithout aggressive faith &amp; go intercession #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first responsibility of #Jesus #Christ's Church is intercession for Rulers' of Nations-Pathetic To Think Things Are Good #EuropaAfricaUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in the Old Testatment #Bible #Jesus #Christ expects His servants to move the mountains defiantly standing in their way- MOUTAINS MOVE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't renew the Spirit of your mind to embrace the integral certainty of #Jesus #Christ's Word you'll drown in Fear &amp; insignificance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't you read #Jesus #Christ declared a house divided can't stand-Why then would Jesus want you battling with uncertainty-Be Single Eyed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The believer in #Jesus #Christ potentially is an extraordinary individual-once they've renewed their mind to align with His abiding presence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to the end of your rope_Seems there's nobody to help OR even cares if your live OR die-#Jesus #Christ cares &amp; will help you sort it-ASK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the things that happen which you can't explain intellectually change the Integrity of #Jesus #Christ? Not at all-Take Abraham's example-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ's Church has a dilemma-It's full of immature pathetically weak babies totally self absorbed &amp; their #Pastors are allowing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I AM A Christian because I've become One Spirit with #Jesus #Christ &amp; know that #GodIsHope &amp; Loves me just like #JesusLovesYou-Yes You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to understand intellectually how faith in #Jesus #Christ works His #Kingdom provision just act on it &amp; enjoy the results!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN YOU SAY_as a believer in #Jesus #Christ's Integral Authority-stuff happens in Heaven-Earth-Hell &amp; that Authority Is In His Name JESUS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Results are governed by how you see things &amp; the heart committed Faith action you put into doing what you believe you'll harvest 30-60-100%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #hate my #life-Well what are you going to do about it-JesusChristEmpowersAwesomeChanges-ASK Now &amp; Live Blessed #teen #pain #ouch #sosore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Faith in God's Integrity will be tested_You need to study &amp; apply God's Word daily to strengthen it_Pass the tests &amp; enjoy the spoils!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puzzling_that a Born Again Child of God who worships #Jesus #Christ has no experiential understanding that Christ's in them NOT beside them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ wants you to be confident to act on the #certainty of His #Promises so He swore an oath to confirm His intent to you - #Truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever Increasing Faith_It's your responsibility to build yourself up &amp; keep built up in #Jesus #Christ-Your Faith in Him Works-In Him You Win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And let us not weary in well doing: for in due season we shall reap, if we faint not. "There it is "IF" Never forget you have an adversary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Integrity of #Jesus #Christ gives His believers certainty in their believing-they rest assured-they're accepted_blessed_loved_empowered!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Behold I have given you my authority to advance all over the power &amp; ability of the enemy &amp; nothing in any case harm you'"(Lk 10:19) #JESUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Christ in you is greater than anything opposing you &amp; that's why you can be bolder than a conqueror-#Jesus the Conqueror empowers you to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ has exalted His #Covenant #Word of Promises above His Name-He in fact is subservient to His Word of promise to you-Act On It!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bible Hope Is Based Entirely On The Promises Of #God's Integrity-Ensuring Hope's Certainty-thus the joy &amp; peace in the believer's believing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Mark 10:29-31 #Jesus #Christ is expounding on the 100 fold return for prioritizing &amp; proclaiming with demonstrations His Kingdom Message!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cast not away your confidence_your Faith in #Jesus #Christ due to circumstantial pressures-don't let go of your harvests now due to reap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ declared "IF" you believe_the "Works I do" you will do - seems there's no catch here except you have to Believe-DevelopFaith!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let #Jesus #Christ Arise in you &amp; your enemies will scatter-There Is No #Fear In The Spirit Of Christ In You-Why should you be afraid-PRAISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ was amazed at His disciples'unbelief given their imparted authority to do miracles in His Name-He gave them Power Of Attorney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every #Believer should have "The Attitude Of Faith in #Jesus #Christ"-Fearless &amp; Bold in the knowledge-His Integrity gives them Certainty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satan attacks believers provision flowing from their #prayer of #faith-by harassing their minds circumstantially_in a bid to make them quit-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now the just shall live by #faith: but if he draw back in fear, My soul shall have no pleasure in him"Use your Faith in #Jesus OR lose it-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The period between believing prayer &amp; it's results being manifested are to be filled entirely with the CERTAINTY of Jesus Christ's Integrity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus On The Integrity Of #Jesus #Christ's Word To You &amp; you won't doubt in your heart-your faith will develop &amp; grow strong-Mountains Move!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in possession of the promises of God by faith-the Grace of #Christ's Power Works Miraculously - It's through faith action one receives!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith in God's Word takes possession of things promised &amp; receives them in Jesus Name-There's Never Any-lets wait &amp; see if something happens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The prayer of faith- You don't pray &amp; wait to see if something happens- You know something happened- You don't need to see it to believe it-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ dealt with unexpected disastrous circumstances the same as you BUT He used His Faith &amp; commanded it to Stop &amp; You Can Too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Love of #Jesus #Christ for you is never in question but yours that's another matter! #Bible #Truth #God #Love #Life #Lord #Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Church Leadership are responsible before #Jesus Christ-to recruit &amp; Train Soldiers_To do the work of the Evangelist &amp; reap Cities for Christ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Develop your #Faith Attitude in #Jesus #Christ-A mindset fixed on triumph-knowing Love never fails to work miracles for those who believe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spiritual force PATIENCE_WORKS_there's nothing passive bout patience_It is a Never Will I Quit Winning Faith Attitude in #Jesus #Christ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Faith in #Jesus #Christ two fish &amp; five loaves is enough to meet any need you have with plenty left over.My Cup Is Full &amp; Running Over!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storms come &amp; they go-If you're prepared to handle come what may in #Jesus #Christ you'll fare well &amp; blaze a path of Faith Glorifying Jesus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jesus #Christ never stops loving you BUT He has to stop Blessing you when you allow yourself to become a Hearer only!  #Christian #Kingdom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Therefore if any man be in #Jesus Christ he has become a NEW MAN-old things have passed away-behold all things have become new  #bible #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Shattered-he's just walked out-you haven't a clue what went wrong_You're blaming yourself &amp; just want to die-Don't-#Jesus will help you-ASK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To him who overcometh"our resurrected #Jesus #Christ appears to have a vastly different view than most #Christians wanting to flee earth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cares Of This World choke out #Jesus #Christ's Solutions_So Clear Your Thinking-Deliberately Remove ALL Care Now &amp; affirm IN HIM I WIN!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can do all things through #Christ who strengthens me" Abiding in the Vine has the power of God empowering you to accomplish His exploits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes #Jesus #Christ's Love for you is unconditional BUT His promises are conditional upon you're being a Doer of His #Word NOT just a hearer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Christian if you're living your Life in the flesh now by faith in #Jesus #Christ-the power of His Name is at your disposal to work miracles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Kingdom of #God is within_You need be God Inside Minded-#Jesus' Glory &amp; Power flows from within-that's why You Can DO All Things In Him]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>