<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing effort. Not long left, very inspiring! #RowGavRow :D https://t.co/K3qlQJp9ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this #swimming video :) https://t.co/osReMDj4wK "man was made to fear the deep, but you, you are here to find it".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V impressive facilities in the new @sportireland National Indoor Arena. Great 2 get the chance 2 do some of the soc… https://t.co/u7FUzfa3IM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was on snapchat, instagram, Facebook live and twitter this morning for @SportIreland, this was one of my favourite… https://t.co/42NbvP6QVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will hopefully be snapping from the Indoor Arena Opening tomorrow morning if anyone is interested. Username SportIr… https://t.co/RCBOWvVuK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear @soulogav being interviewed on the radio from the Atlantic! #RowGavRow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @CathalRonan @cian_spillane @Carroll90Lily Cathal are you just catching up now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must resist urge to high five people trying to wave down the bus...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FairGameCast @RagNBoneManUK 'wolves' is a great one to keep you going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname *should have been going for a coffee instead of the tea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname not my best moment.  Probably should have been going for a coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyismyname once put coffee in my tea instead of milk at start of meeting. Panicked 4some reason &amp; just sat down with it #professionalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback to possibly 1999. Bitta motivation for @cian_spillane's swimming lesson this morning 😂😇 #gettingthere https://t.co/VOPfInN9Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_Bathke serious forward thinking! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skipped the Christmas swim this year but massive respect to everyone who braved the weather today for charity!… https://t.co/q1CjHdu39N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like getting a serious dose of the giggles at mass and your sibling taking the blame for it all 😂 #Christmasbanter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a rare sequence of events the weather has continuously improved while driving towards #Galway. Stay tuned kids... #drivinghomeforxmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some inspiring rowing from @soulogav so far! #RowGavRow #twac2016 https://t.co/Npf0zoWjkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Irish Olympians reflect on what happened after their Rio odyssey https://t.co/LdT8Sljxtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@porter337 @cian_spillane when do you want to start this aspect of the training?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent night out with @KatieReilly88 last night 😃 brilliant performance by @gavinjames https://t.co/hAQfjPnck9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff @Fionamdoyle! 😃 https://t.co/pMW0vE4CnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gavan's off to row the Atlantic solo very soon. Serious challenge! Best of luck @soulogav #RowGavRow https://t.co/xq77dWPfGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is beautiful https://t.co/bUaPIdWJ9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the @gavinjames binge begins... https://t.co/7ngawZ5w5K roll on Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieReilly88 @cian_spillane no bother kiiiiiid! See you Friday for the real fun ya?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niamhcosullivan @cian_spillane thanks Niamh! Hope the exams went well 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We scrub up well 😊 https://t.co/6Jud3DEGVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some very cool art work here, and she's selling a few pieces off to fund some over seas volunteering next summer. D… https://t.co/3qrzkYbBH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane it's one of those real life useful skills I've been working on for my CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Graduating on Tuesday, feeling smart. Proceeds to burn microwave popcorn... 😞 https://t.co/0V7Xl6mcfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane so what you're saying is the rest of us don't have to worry about getting you anything? 😇]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some really interesting tech emerging to measure head injury impact in sport and likely warn about concussions. Fir… https://t.co/HvFERHDFV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fionamdoyle best of luck Fiona! Have fun 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mona McSharry is flying it at SC Nats. Very impressive #SwimFast https://t.co/LIKPLwrlv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That voice! Wow... #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane you might get some money for your car yet @niamhcosullivan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UL really is an amazing spot 😃 https://t.co/alIZcE8WM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiefbreenie @cian_spillane what do we want?! Time travel! When do we want it?! It's irrelevant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiefbreenie @cian_spillane at this rate I'm leaning towards learning to time travel 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiefbreenie @cian_spillane but then I would never have learned to time travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiefbreenie @cian_spillane I've been working on a variety of useful real life skills to add to my CV while job hunting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane on my way 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedy798 Just watching it now, too funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niamhcosullivan @cian_spillane 😂 he's an awful messer in the pool, you're better off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed @saspler @mars_bar01 #KeyRaceAlert 😋]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedy798 @the_folk_diva @UL he loves visiting UL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane @Aldi_Ireland legends aren't born, they're grown 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so impressed with #planetearth2 already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire on, re-watched the match and now #PlanetEarth2 :) not a bad evening at home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELangfordMusic covering @Rubberbandits in Dolans Limerick. Unreal! 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tony_j_g is it good? Was toying with picking it up a few weeks back but didn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limerick people! This lady is crazy talented, get yourselves to Dolans on November 5th :) https://t.co/sHmIBupFwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AskingForIt is an excellent documentary. Should definitely be incorporated into sex ed for all young people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passed my fundraising goal 4 @SpinalIreland :) delighted to have taken part in the #DublinMarathon but glad its over https://t.co/XRrJwmbxeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really can't wait to see @oneilllo's documentary tonight! 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 10years since I've been to a #Macnas parade. Still as amazing as ever 😃 https://t.co/3Y1zHLgovl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedy798 sound! I am in bits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty scary alright... https://t.co/h1hGKwjskz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fundraising goal hit for @SpinalIreland 😃 https://t.co/jelv9ytEid delighted! Still terrified about the distance tomorrow! #dublinmarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Humanity's misuse of natural resources is threatening habitats, ... and threatening the stability of our climate." https://t.co/NAPz2SjdvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulKimmage hahaha @cian_spillane think you'll like this one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU is reviewing the policy that makes its appliances so energy efficient https://t.co/jIVrvN6ydA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long left til the @dublinmarathon &amp; not far off the fundraising goal :) https://t.co/VdJZs5Fru1 #somuchfear #firstmarathon #fundraising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I never thought I'd b doing - planning a route for 20mile run. #prayformojo #DublinMarathon last long run :) https://t.co/VdJZs5Fru1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[''Nobody has more respect for women than I do.'' Trump. Ugh... Unbelievable this man is a presidential candidate #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuckooEvents @cian_spillane @dublinmarathon haha thanks guys! fingers crossed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuckooEvents @cian_spillane @dublinmarathon interesting... :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleSRapp Spurrier's comments hit the nail on the head really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 miles done today, only 3 weeks til the #DublinMarathon running 4 @SpinalIreland if any1 else would like to donate https://t.co/VdJZs5Fru1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed Young Offenders this evening with @cian_spillane  Very funny, the 2 lads were excellent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dkYQLcPZdJ 😂 #triathlon still one of the best ads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_hennessy @kennedy798 there'd be much whining the next day tho. Hungover and blistered!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedy798 @carol_hennessy things I wouldn't recommend. So much cake...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedy798 @carol_hennessy for best effect see Morgan Freeman narrations of said penguin videos while making way through box of Capri Suns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_hennessy penguin videos Carol. It won't ease the physical pain but it might help the psychological pain 😋]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland has failed Europe’s refugees once again https://t.co/oz2YfeMB26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 @Truman_Black @TheSun wtf?! That's ridiculous even by their standards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 there was a really good atmosphere from where I was marching! Very impressed, especially with the rain 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 LOADS of people out there marching! Was great to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 seemed quite well organised from my experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 I think I saw one pro life person with a sign near the top of o Connell street. Nothing else I saw while out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#repealthe8th #marchforchoice kicking off at the top of O'Connell street earlier. (3rd time tweetings the charm...) https://t.co/ckN8tEMnuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekstar5000 the march today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the way to the garden of remembrance. Looks like a a great number of students on the way  to #marchforchoice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tracker for the Dublin half marathon is actually pretty decent, come on @cian_spillane :) flying it despite the flu!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some very interesting discussions taking place at #DGD16 re childrens health and rights and clean environment. https://t.co/JRfLlT54vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackers89 definitely give me a shout!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackers89 preferably stay here for awhile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackers89 that flew by! The million $ question. looking at charity/not-for-profit sector mostly at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackers89 haha excellent! Finished 😊 waiting on results and job hunting at the moment. Time to be a real adult again... How's all in UL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mackers89 is it too early to scare kids the day before halloween? :P will you eventually have an office door sign that reads Dr. C-POW? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the donation @mackers89! Very much appreciated 😃 congrats on the first publication btw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cian_spillane it isn't anyone's friend 😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mars_bar01 one of the best ones I've ever read is "change wrangler".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter friends, running @dublinmarathon 4 @SpinalIreland would sincerely appreciate if any1 would like 2 donate/RT https://t.co/2JMwScVQNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sent the dog downstairs with his most obnoxious squeaky toys to ease my sisters hangover 😂 #evilgenius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing some of this! #Rio2016Paralympics  https://t.co/32DKZqi3wu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The toll at Ballinasloe is like a border 4 the weather. Rest of country is beautiful, pay toll, go through barrier, sky turns grey 4 Galway😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really interesting re Paralympics classifications https://t.co/ZtckM59Pbe]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>