<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 22% of parliamentarians are women. Anna Adeke in #Uganda is helping to buck that trend. #WomenInPolitics… https://t.co/EYfQgrPsop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very disappointing. The only winner here is #corruption. https://t.co/5cT8lW43nI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC #Tshisekedi was courageous. Arrested many times for #peacefulprotest. Here is @HRW on his 1998 arrest. RIP… https://t.co/2SdlujVWxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC Etienne Tshisekedi stood for peaceful resistance against dictatorship. So sad to hear about his death. #Congo… https://t.co/cPKdgAG8Iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Threat by US congress to cancel #Oil transparency rule could seriously undermine fight against #corruption… https://t.co/AAWbftbBNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moussa Faki Mahama of Chad wins top job at the #AfricanUnion. Urge him to make #HumanRights a top priority #Africa.… https://t.co/m3AY03hZRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UK focused on getting exemptions for UK citizens to the #muslinban rather than denouncing the vile policy. Shamefu… https://t.co/Gkj99tocfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One leader stands up for #HumanRights. The other shows cowardice and stays silent. I know which one I would vote fo… https://t.co/1kX2Cy4ZiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And while you are on the phone with him, also reinforce that #torture does not work. You cannot be silent on this a… https://t.co/Pcas1t6V2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UK ruling on #Shell #Nigeria oil pollution case gives green light for corporations to profit from abuse overseas. https://t.co/rKuFPXauj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sent Home for Not Wearing Heels, She Ignited a British Rebellion https://t.co/LlsJTt4IBM #womensmarch #WhyIMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK judge rejects #Nigeria community demand for @Shell to clean up toxic oil spill. Lawyers appeal harmful decision.… https://t.co/kcVFRH3aYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderful man. The #humanrights movement will miss him greatly. https://t.co/i2642HSLjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliament says UK equality &amp; rights commission to fund judicial test cases on high heels &amp; dress discrimination. L… https://t.co/SNRnybfOnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmclaren @MishalHusainBBC Today program should try again tomorrow and invite lawyer from @LeighDay_Law and Sophie Walker from @WEP_UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmclaren @MishalHusainBBC We need to hear about what is needed to better enforce the current law on discrimination and the gaps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is about sexism in the workplace. @BBCRadio4 totally out of touch with women's issues. #whyIMarch #womensmarch  https://t.co/vmi3m8uZgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BBCRadio4 should be ashamed. The issue of what women are forced to wear is about sexism, not the comfort of high heels. #everydaysexism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UKSupremeCourt decision on #Brexit is good for #humanrights. Great news when rights have seemed so under threat.  https://t.co/sXt5vjKnYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like there is no opening up of political space or respect for human rights in #DRC #Congo. Ridiculous to expe… https://t.co/9X2Z0aFFit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter marched with gusto on Saturday. Will do these #10actions100days for her future #womensmarch #whyIMarch… https://t.co/r58EoOqXut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sent email to #TheresaMay to urge her to tell Trump that #womensrightsarehumanrights. #womensmarch… https://t.co/aiDnucZeHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesting young. Girl power! #WomensMarch #womensmarchlondon https://t.co/kFLZsTHUYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive turnout at #womensmarchlondon. Hear us ROAR @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/rDtj6p8AHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @ida_sawyer from @hrw permitted to return to #Congo. Hope this means the release of #DRC political pri… https://t.co/yPZxwpvA4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the best books on #Lumumba assassination. #Belgium's role cannot be ignored. Shocking that there is… https://t.co/v9bMrxh5Kr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[56 years ago #Congo's Patrice #Lumumba was assassinated. Never too late for investigation into the role of #Belgium… https://t.co/5ysJrn8ESh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A look back at 2016 in #DRC. New @hrw report on the intense political violence as #Kabila clung to power. #WR2017… https://t.co/mIVimI9dpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child victim or brutal warlord? #ICC weighs the fate of #LRA's Dominic Ongwen. #Uganda #DRC #ChildSoldiers… https://t.co/N86xbZ6sVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Volkswagen managers face criminal charges in #US. Should set example for criminal acts by executives in #Africa.… https://t.co/yZtDtWh3tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two versions of the stories to watch in #Africa in 2017. https://t.co/zIDSiC2c7e https://t.co/QFwC3Ra8q0 https://t.co/8k7xkoU2fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC among top bug eating countries. Personally, I love fried grasshoppers. If you can eat prawns, you can eat inse… https://t.co/4sqs8Qc9Ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am going to #WomensMarchLondon on Jan 21 to stand against politics of fear and the misogyny shown by #Trump campaig… https://t.co/4f7u4VLGkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GOLD is the mineral most used to finance rebel and criminal groups in #DRC #Congo say UN experts. #metals… https://t.co/XmLToxTNWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UK financial regulators fail to stop corrupt practices in #DRC and #Zimbabwe that pass through #Finance #London… https://t.co/Ifb7IxPk42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICC judges say #DRC warlord Bosco Ntaganda can be tried for raping his own soldiers.Was it even in doubt? #Congo… https://t.co/99jtnRnjc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for #UK authorities to strengthen regulations and hold to account those using #London markets to steal from… https://t.co/ZGWj64yPPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profts at Och-Ziff hedgefund (found guilty of mass corruption in #DRC and #Zimbabwe) are down. No tears from me.… https://t.co/sWfemMeJbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New report reveals #UK role in sheltering those involved in corrupt deals with #Kabila in #Congo @raidukorg… https://t.co/2h1aensSH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kabila has been offered the best and only available exit plan in #DRC He should take it says the @nytimes. I agree… https://t.co/agzO1aTwU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news for #Congo. @tomperriello has done a great job as US special envoy and pushed for sanctions against abuser… https://t.co/bOcxq3Qsg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scores killed or maimed at North Mara gold mine in #Tanzania run by #UK company. Here is just one story.… https://t.co/v0yj16e4UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zakaria was paralysed at North Mara gold mine in #Tanzania, yet UK company gave no compensation. That's just wrong.… https://t.co/DXaI3RpkRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC agreement would force #Kabila out of office. That is, of course, if he agrees, says @nytimes  #congocrisis… https://t.co/7eHOPQo6UD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #Kabila is truly committed to stepping down, he should personally sign the #DRC deal negotiated by the bishops.… https://t.co/flLxqCsME5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female judge breaks her silence and reveals #Kabila's dirty tactics to stay in power in #DRC. #Congocrisis… https://t.co/iy1Hqim0WD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop dealing with #Kabila, says main opposition leader to diplomats as president's term in office ends.… https://t.co/JZr0swTmO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phone companies in #DRC should stand up for free speech. @Vodacomcongo @airtelrdc @orangerdc say no to #Kabila thre… https://t.co/EDGjGrzm4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PierreTshimuan1 Have passed on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tactics of repression. #Kabila govt preparing to cut social media in #DRC ahead of 19 December deadline.… https://t.co/nMGR0KpH8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kabila places not only his reign, but also his personal profit above welfare of #DRC people.… https://t.co/ruEhWFj6Du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human rights abuses are increasing in #Swaziland. Turning @TheNationalMag into a digital force will help get critic… https://t.co/qsIOtxWxK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kabila and his family are getting rich off #Congo's wealth. Hard hitting new report on his vast business empire.… https://t.co/PKtjWU9Hh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postal services restart in #Kinshasa #DRC. Good time to send #Kabila a letter urging him to step down.… https://t.co/MbFyUvY2NH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to the last surviving prosecutor of Nuremberg trials who still urges for international justice. #Humanrights… https://t.co/SWsEtlPHpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jeremycorbyn I am a constituent. Pls ensure you &amp; all #Labour MPs vote on Friday for #IstanbulConvention to tackl… https://t.co/JRwguSfWIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uni_rdc Of course. Except the newspaper they published in is English and the advert is likely to have cost over $100,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #DRC govt publishes a full page ad in the New York Times. If you are going to spread lies, at least check the E… https://t.co/U94NTvItNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[87 #HumanRights groups say #EU sanctions on #DRC officials can pull Congo back from the brink. Are you listening EU… https://t.co/7rjjcsXY94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courageous #virunga park rangers take extraordinary risks to protect #Congo gorillas &amp; wildlife. This @NatGeo best… https://t.co/VPFbJF3Lg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a young university student at the time and remember the #montrealmassacre so vividly.  I won't forget. It mad… https://t.co/xZCcE7spSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LRA #Ongwen says he is a victim. But he was a perpetrator too. Ask the families of 321 #DRC victims killed in 2009… https://t.co/QP5Jk1b75g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is helpful, but only if  #MONUSCO will act forcibly when civilians are at risk. Far too often peacekeepers onl… https://t.co/ZsGmVs59p6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK pushes for independence of judges in #Africa and abroad. It should respect the same at home. Apply the law, not… https://t.co/U67J2lqx5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ByeByeKabila - a peaceful protest against #Kabila's stay in office - is gaining momentum in #Congo. Policy makers… https://t.co/551Qpkd6Qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In UK court last week, #Shell lawyers tried to shift blame for pollution in #Nigeria to anyone but itself. Shameful… https://t.co/cFv1BhBEnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Violence against those protesting #Kabila staying in power is becoming far too common in #Congo. Policy makers shou… https://t.co/s2v7pLcGHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After years of drinking polluted water, #Nigeria King takes on #Shell in London to demand clean-up. #Right2Water… https://t.co/wd3F3k6Gh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Shell faces new lawsuit in UK for blighting the lives of thousands by repeat oil spills in #Nigeria. @LeighDay_Law… https://t.co/fygsuH5qPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President #Kabila: Free the 29 political prisoners on this list. Locking up rights activists does not help #Congo.… https://t.co/9jOjaKASB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Africa states withdrawing from the #ICC only serves to send a message that they do not value justice, even if they… https://t.co/6JBVCb08EJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil in #Nigeria continues to cause trouble with few benefits for people in the Niger Delta. Can #Buhari change that… https://t.co/tj5ecpgMkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know what has happened to the #LRA? @LedioCakaj discusses his new book on #Kony at #LSE on Nov 23.… https://t.co/RBTNFDnRI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backing from #Africa region is the worst possible outcome for elections in #Congo #DRC says @ISSAfrica.… https://t.co/WWQamhGZ8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC govt claims election delayed due to lack of funds, yet election body paid millions to a #Kabila-linked bank.… https://t.co/FxQz94xDBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Canada should address violence by its mining companies. Shocking deaths &amp; rapes at @acadia gold mine in #Tanzania.… https://t.co/YHtefCcqmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking how directly involved #Bemba was in corrupting witnesses in #ICC case. #DRC #CARcrisis Full details here:… https://t.co/owUtGgGKV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out great new human rights blog from @hrw on continuing crisis in #DRC. https://t.co/LO19zU3cZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kabila's supposed national dialogue was one-way and there is still no clear date for elections. No wonder #DRC rem… https://t.co/cxgXLBaywO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump's ridiculous rhetoric about jailing a political opponent gives succour to dictators in #Africa who use such… https://t.co/C3ILpg8gT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gedeon was found guilty of crimes against humanity in landmark 2009 trial. He should be returned to jail. His #DRC… https://t.co/MTzpcf93YZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2009, #DRC warlord #Gedeon was found guilty of terrible atrocities as reported by @hrw. He should return to jail… https://t.co/D7M8cKhHeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheresaMay's attempt to shield #British soldiers from #humanrights crimes gets the law very wrong say legal expert… https://t.co/TBmqTnSYKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UK govt strives to protect human rights lawyers abroad, but at home #TheresaMay is targeting them. Its wrong.… https://t.co/CenXt42eiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is certainly no time to lose.  If France is serious they need to urgently push for #EU sanctions on #DRC top… https://t.co/L74ob2ryh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #UN and #DRC army are clearly failing to protect people in #Beni.  A shocking 700 dead since 2014. @hrw… https://t.co/h1OZDufTdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High time for the #EU and #UN to follow the American lead and also implement sanctions against #DRC officials. https://t.co/7UucHXjqS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US hedge fund Och-Ziff to plead guilty to brbery in #Africa, #DRC #Zimbabwe. What will Africa's citizens get?… https://t.co/doVGt23ZPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US slaps sanctions on #Congo officials after recent violence. #DRC https://t.co/dI16Iih64f https://t.co/8apl96Acau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolences important. But justice for the crimes and sanctions against those responsible will do more to held end… https://t.co/b6veBogRhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No smiles as #PopeFrancis meets #DRC president. Last week Catholic bishops urged #Kabila to respect law &amp; step down… https://t.co/Wixj6tbsSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRC warlord Bosco #Ntaganda ends his hunger strike at the #ICC. Still faces accusation of witness tampering.… https://t.co/ld4ddEk79h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increased repression and still no electoral calendar for elections. #Congo is at a dangerous juncture. #DRC https://t.co/suB0T6374n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Yale students question #Rwanda's dismal human rights record ahead of #Kagame speech .#KagameAtYale… https://t.co/m0IM0RNeT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New play on #Congo showing at Almeida Theatre in #London and its worth seeing. #DRC #TheyDrinkItInTheCongo… https://t.co/lVM409LARq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICC judges frustrated with #DRC warlord Bosco Ntaganda on 12th day of his hunger strike. https://t.co/Zw5ZRF6EBp https://t.co/ghhi5nuZUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ntaganda not a victim. Family contact restricted because #ICC judges found him intimidating witnesses from prison. https://t.co/uEXk2IoUta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ntaganda not a victim. Family contact restricted because #ICC judges found him intimidating witnesses from prison. https://t.co/ziasYbUdni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kinzonzi Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's this growing youth bulge who demand more responsible government yet so often face repression. #Congo @luchaRDC  https://t.co/lxMtFlUQr4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>