<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJames_D @JamTarts I'm leaving for Inverness soon so it's going to be hard on my mobile battery ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJames_D @JamTarts Aye every time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many phone operatives do they have at @JamTarts ticket centre.....1 I'd say ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't understand all the hatred towards Trump, I'm watching the news and the world is chock a block full of folk far worse than him ðŸ˜•ðŸ˜®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T5040 Aye it's a nice part of the world....nearly as good as Stow ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted I'm missing Jambos game though   #shitplanning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T5040 Elgin and Inverness, I've got cousins from up there as that's where my mum is from..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading up North tomorrow for a few days...âœˆðŸš„ðŸš—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinburghpaper I pass that pub regularly and I'm sure the doorman hands out gum shields to punters as they go inðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul1874Herriot A pic you posted was just on my timeline but it's disappeared now....strange  ðŸ˜¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartmackay96 There gone, I've gave them back to the club to sell again..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul1874Herriot Just see a blank white screen pal â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a God ðŸ˜Š ðŸ‘‡ https://t.co/WleXmav8FK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Nichol I'll look out for you ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Nichol Maybe further than you think I should have said Block S row O...I'm a bit dyslexic ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamb0skickback @lindataylor64 Aye will do that if I get no takers cheers ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got 2 tickets available in the main stand (section O) for the Rangers game. 1 adult, 1 junior if anybody can use them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@masonh52 @CapitalsMaroon Jesus man what are you on ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grummy_grummy Exactly, pointless waste of time..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandieAndrew Cheers Bill and yes I had a few Fiors ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamTarts Pleased with that..ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/duDz6yCbY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Scottish band and Stuart Adamson died the day before my boy was born in 2001   :-(

https://t.co/CaqLB0tInZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency march....is that in place of the normal march, get a life ðŸ˜¨ https://t.co/oC0dlofwmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamb0skickback That pics been doctored....it's been my sreen saved for years  ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xxp123 Aye it will only be 4-0 now  ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Brendan Rodgers,, he's a decent guy...nice things to say about Ian Cathro  ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidtaylor57 Ha ha stranger things and all that ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Jambos get a point at Parkhead today I'll be gobsmacked...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eckauskas Aye maybes your right, I'm missing the Rangers game and I'm gutted ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmadaleHearts Thanks pal, we had a great day â˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Jambos know when the Hibs tickets go on sale?  as I'll be out of signal for most of next week. ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Davie Dodds The Elephant Man"...an old shed chant  ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't beat family, everything else is secondary...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ps://t.co/l0fEvvkQE4 forever freddie mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanJWallace69 Cheers pal she's had a top day..ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The birthday girl...ðŸ˜Š https://t.co/QeFYKaQW1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This  ðŸ‘‡ðŸ‘‡ https://t.co/5pAB3L7Eks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeW1874 @JamTarts Happy days, I stood just along from there in the 1980s ðŸ‘âœ‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryhope10 Very true Mary I made it a biggy ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottylar Thanks for that Scott much appreciated pal ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dear old mum is 80 today, I'm going to give her a big hug soon  ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/duDz6yCbY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickkinley @iandicko73 I have been Richard and I'm retiring to a lovely wee village 20 miles from Malaga ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 I just try and get on with folk, from anywhere in the world, granted some are total arseholes..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 Maybe your right, but we all share a small planet and we should try to get on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 I like to think when I'm lying on the beach on the Costa del sol every summer that we are culturally reasonably close..ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 Because Ian our great county is part of the continent of Europe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoamingArgyle @edinburghpaper Aye ok hibs class ðŸ˜ƒðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoamingArgyle @edinburghpaper Your taking the piss I take it ðŸ˜®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PudgieTheSheep @JamTarts @spfl Ryan Christie ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rangers fan gets tattoo on his back of gates of Ibrox in GREEN ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/ovxao6Eiaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireHammond @jamb0skickback @YouTube Makes Connor Salmon look like.....well a wet fish ðŸ˜ðŸŸðŸŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the Doomsday folk are predicting the world is getting close to the end,..just hope it's no before we give the hibees a caning in the SC ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinburghpaper He used to live a scrap with Maggie back in the day RIP big fella...ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViewfromGorgie Goes without saying ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dumbarton's new no2 Ian Durrant is the double of my old mucker Swany ðŸ˜€ https://t.co/Ua9iIwnuDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have these wierd dreams where sometimes I'm a gazebo or a tipi. My psychiatrist thinks I'm just being two tents...ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReidBrianreid1 Aye too right it'll be like watching a different game next season ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJames_D One tired Danny Logan the night  ðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First penalty from my seat... https://t.co/oysEnEzOlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good result eventually and good to have @MrJames_D watching with me ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good result but going to be a late night ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get in there  ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extra time here and me and @MrJames_D are about ripping oor hair out ðŸ˜£ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJames_D Do you know where The Golden Rule is at Fountainbridge ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJames_D Where you want to meet me James ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanJWallace69 But we're biased Ian ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad I'm Scottish #burnsnight #proudscot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a tree falls in a forest and no one is around to hear it, does it make a sound?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bastin1874 As long as you're back now pal. ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bastin1874 I've been there through thick and thin since November 1971 so I'm in the hardcore section ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Mike Bennet and his pal are getting the 3.30 train ðŸ˜€. Ok catch you the morn pal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Aye getting train, probably 4 or 4.30 but it's nae hassle can meet you up the toon if that's too early.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Tickets available if you want it James..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@galleonskip @JamTarts Either or I've got one of each pal..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Ok James will let you know later ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Might have... will know in a wee while if the guy wants it but doubt he will, you got somebody in mind ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/duDz6yCbY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@producelesloges Aye true ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how a bit of fame can make some folk total arseholes..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddieNisbet Ditto mate, he was my old mans hero and his only one I think. He loved watching him..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 Why...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts I've got a ticket and have a spare one for the main stand if anyone's interested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts @Ross_H1874 Will you boys be getting the train up then ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Border_Hearts Any idea what time bus is leaving ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_JDrummond @POTUS Aye ah never thought of that ðŸ˜¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_JDrummond @POTUS Ther'e probably rifling through your knicker drawer as we speak...ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_JDrummond @POTUS Well nout to worry about then ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_JDrummond @POTUS Your house has probably been bugged and you're bank account will soon be frozen..ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ticket bought for Wednesday night's game..better bloody win ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandicko73 Wasn't aware it was locked Ian.. is it ok now ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Across Yair Forrest this morning.. https://t.co/c0XHhCbluf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Mondays ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWinNFFC I know but we shouldn't have to be playing a replay....we should have been out of sight by half time today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWinNFFC Aye massive game pal....but at the moment every games a big if ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWinNFFC Hope he makes a speedy recovery, not what you'd expect when playing a game of football ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmadaleHearts @JamieDevlin1988 No you were right first time -  Idiot....ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the patter for tickets for Wednesday's replay fellow Jambos.. ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a bit of writers block tonight, maybe a Stella will help a bit...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>