<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally have the answer to who is the good boy: https://t.co/fsKGS4ocI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHickman clear this is fake cos Money Pit isn't on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull will say anything to save face. His entire political strategy is attacking labor to try and keep his head… https://t.co/l2WkCcQyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hawleyrose I read it and immediately thought it was humiliating for Turnbull and terrifying for Australia's security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely terrified we have spineless corporate lackeys like Bishop and Turnbull defending Australia's interests during the time of Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was that Keating was saying about getting closer to China? https://t.co/Dl5JuXzinp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barba was obviously homesick for France https://t.co/Vw67ibUXNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a genuinely positive development that liberals have replaced the "Putin's puppet" hysteria with concern about… https://t.co/bfZHWmN8Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donahue uses plot of Who Framed Roger Rabbit? to defend Joey Buttafuoco https://t.co/mjI3PNYTKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmberALeeFrost you will love Australia. Beetroot on practically every burger/sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Intrsctnldrone what she'd do? Her tweets are protected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing gets past this guy https://t.co/di6ilkh8KT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found your CD on eBay https://t.co/HkecVApnoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjoregan his twitter game has improved since https://t.co/yZPphIYPjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjoregan Cruz won. I like deadspin, but they got owned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull: the hollowest of hollow men. https://t.co/Dr9UrhgwnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think Trump jokes would already be stale. But not in Smigel's hands https://t.co/twx69XK7AR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit https://t.co/YuplQpbSbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missykaybm @BadlandsNPS so cool driving around in there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've reached peak nonsensical Australian journalist  observation about the US election: https://t.co/k4IRYxeZEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samangell2007 yeah, he's playing two shows in Brisbane, and im at least going to the second night. Setlist is promisingly political!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dirrty has triumphed over evil! https://t.co/u1RM7MUAHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest tweet of 2017 https://t.co/hBYVWuFbbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you oppose capitalism you cannot purchase water or brownies - add them to the list! https://t.co/YndCgxKrnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about safety pins? https://t.co/kEclTq4dzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phillutton78 he's known as canberra's answer to sean baby baumgart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BaltimoreMatt sometimes those young girls get their man: https://t.co/FDy7pnJI4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teen_archer undisputed best tweet of all time: https://t.co/60FwXxo3pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TISM were irony bros before it was cool: Humphrey B. Flaubert calls out Waleed Aly with a little help from… https://t.co/CvYuNMjksk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There won't be 8 years of Trump. There will be at least 12: https://t.co/LwmJEfv9Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump is the next chapter in Adam Curtis's Hypernormalisation playing out infront of our eyes:… https://t.co/8IiPiv3Rry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronAtfield you weren't the only one happy with the result https://t.co/5at0KDud19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep has a point about football given how bad the first week of the playoffs were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every wild card team lost first week. Each game a blowout. What a mediocre league the NFL has become. Hopefully next 4 weeks make up for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mountain_goats please record this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This first week of the NFL playoffs - such a snooze fest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crewsett and this was recorded after the dv stuff? Yikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crewsett is he rapping about playing baseball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pair are as far from a boy band as you can get https://t.co/pnxVfcjoen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, why don't you marry it? https://t.co/2USQKhqap4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few things more gross in sports than when fans use abuse of women by players as fodder for banter/jeers. https://t.co/Li5mC8Izts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, please watch Hypernormalisation: https://t.co/h0fxtwnao9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teen_archer such a great film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missykaybm they ain't listening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would really appreciate it if the Buckeyes could at least put up a fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pete_Begins that is strange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benmckelvey her "guard" was pretty poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamfan40 @ClayTravis love the dude mentions Freddy adu- hahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Bogut is such right wing bozo I wouldn't be surprised if he played this angle up to get his own radio show https://t.co/7637Pa6Hmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me so happy https://t.co/xTUOZJQgDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is still the best thing I read all year https://t.co/UFexi5h5at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlBeijer he's such a coward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Zobrist is inhuman. That collision at the plate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ReWatching game 6 with Pat and Ron. Had the most fun watching this game at Murphy's, but was way too drunk to remem… https://t.co/sZrRN18Bf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently I'm blocked by the guy who thinks Margaret Thatcher was progressive? https://t.co/AnCNhNc9KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isikbreen the spokesman for mariner fans everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missykaybm @DEvanAltman the removal of yub nub from Jedi is the greatest crime in human history https://t.co/fuuCSPjD1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cushbomb must hold back nerd rage at this cushbomb or I might go full rapaport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much going on here https://t.co/Tj520yb6NE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the funniest stuff I've seen for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today on twitter I learnt there is a Michael rapaport podcast and he will get mad on twitter at those who talk crap about his pod guests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryExile @johnb78 yeah genuine doesn't equal legitimate - so it shouldn't hold weight with an informed deputy PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those brave Nationals protecting Australia from the most nefarious of interest groups - food certification? https://t.co/ApYHeK8o5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaLGraney I reckon it would be the ultimate troll move if Dylan died on Jan 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamFriedland yeah but you always fall asleep after jacking off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crawf33 not to the customers of the many malls he so valiantly protects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crawf33 if he dies before the year's out and we don't get Paul Blart 4 it's on you man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rodders666 @harrypav pretty sure they are androids that cannot be destroyed by conventional means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crawf33 if we can just get through this year with no more celeb deaths Kevin James will live forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a hot tip to everyone - you're favourite celebrities won't stop dying on January 1, 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the best pop songs ever recorded https://t.co/4ggkbVbDX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Satire so extreme it isn't funny or nuanced" https://t.co/IJU6W50Z95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was really disappointed that they ran out of these Joe Maddon bobbleheads - until I saw the head mould #thatsnotJoe… https://t.co/BpGHD2x2wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice cool breeze in Gympie this evening for Christmas Eve https://t.co/GkhqtFh0UQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenRazer is great tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HitlerPuncher it's not stupid when you apply some game theory to it. Everything goes better with game theory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to Mrs @king4kallangur for helping me hook up this in my office. #cubs https://t.co/ezAOs9OIDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More HOF ballots like this please https://t.co/QhLWUyewPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_P_Grant this is a good ballot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyRemeikis @HeathJAston Richard Marx is a pretty intense dude https://t.co/Ekx6gGIOiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdNgaluafe I had to google what chasing cars was. I didn't know there was a market for "Coldplay, but less macho."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdNgaluafe they certainly are broriffic bros - not just because they ripped that song off Tom petty https://t.co/seGGSsaUXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again the comments on this Courier article are largely supportive of One Nation. https://t.co/pBywIWGKF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hope the Australian Conservative Party can fill the conservative void in Australian politics... https://t.co/Rp3IfMJRPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four years of impotent symbolism, scapegoating and platitudes from the American liberal left. Anything but examine… https://t.co/thjlpRl5K8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely infuriating that someone would bring Gough's sacking up as an example of how to get rid of someone like… https://t.co/pa8IwQnenH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd after brexit and trump I won't rule out anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd we'll see. They'd prefer Hanson as a third party force over someone like palmer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd right wingers are hypocritical by nature. They are snake oil salesmen. But pointing that out only gets the left so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd the Courier know the LNP's only chance to win the next election is a power-sharing arrangement with Hanson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd Courier wouldn't give One Nation such positive coverage if they didn't believe One Nation had LNP's best interests at heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd they preach protectionism like Trump but like trump they'll let the LNP's mates in the 1% free reign once they're in power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd One Nation can only be stopped by voters being confronted with the truth - they are just the radical wing of the LNP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd I disagree. At the very least you can assume they dislike the major parties. And there are plenty of people in that boat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd leftist parties have to push own positive vision first and foremost. &amp; rejecting disgruntled voters as stupid will prove fatal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoughEnd US elections showed obsessing over supporters' supposed racism or intellect gets progressives...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanson is a master at manipulating her celebrity in the media for free press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelmingly positive comments on Courier's One Nation candidates in QLD article. They won't have to pay for ads https://t.co/mfYEvEUoRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy hell this is terrible https://t.co/16iJjb5fuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Cowardly garbage https://t.co/icu1rVF9Fk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>