<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @oreillyfactor Sorry, I will be watching CNN all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evil VP Pence is  scheduled to be on all the cable news networks tomorrow except CNN. #Lets all watch CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill   We should all watch CNN all day tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  I guess I will watch only CNN on Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Honey17011 @washingtonpost       when hell freezes over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RBReich @washingtonpost Sure, what could go wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill What's wrong with the rest of you people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTylt Sure, What could go wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpDefined No. Trump is too far gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpDefined I think that shipped has sailed for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann What makes you think he's not beige paid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @Reuters And who is surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump -STFU you ass!  You have gotten all the publicity you can over this photo op.  You have no soul!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @mike_pence OMG, what a nightmare, a honeymoon with Mike Pence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann He is both, Keith and no one is better at being both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes check with Mike pence.  Oh wait, the child has already been born?  Never mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Oh no, not full time hours for Congress!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  Reoublicans taking care of the miners again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Every sane American should be terrified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLastWord I'm not from New York, but if she ever runs for national office, I will remember her and she will have my vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Thanknyou!  It's difficult to focus on his many, many crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the American nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammypolsen12 @suejohnston56 @realDonaldTrump Fabulous!  I can't say it either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Thank you, sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes I know that I will be more cautious of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @TheFix @JoeNBC @morningmika @MSNBC   I am disgusted by this attempt to treat Trump and his puppets as sane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Will Dem Senators withhold consent for votes on Trump's nominees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Thank you to the mayor of NYC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill OMG I am retweeting Republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Wow. First time I have ever re tweeted a Kardashian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Thanks to LAPD Chief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill OMG I am starting to have faith in Republicans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Spicer has sold his soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill But will McCain withhold consent for votes on Sessions and Devos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN  But will Booker withhold consent for votes for Trumps nominees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill As a Christian, I find Trump deplorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill re: Starbucks. I will now patronize them daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @marty_walsh @SenMarkey @CAIRMass And will the senators from MA withhold consent for Sessions + Devos votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Rihanna should not make insult pigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Excuse me, Speaker Ryan, your spine is missing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharyp @speakup4rights Thank you to the governor of Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman I think it will start with the flaming stupid wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSherrodBrown Thank you, sir.  Now please withhold consent on votes for Devos and Sessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Thank you to the Mayor of New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has heard Speaker Ryan  condemn Trumps illegal ban?  Anyone? Anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ speaker Ryan. I must have missed your statement condemning Trumps illegal actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Thank you to the governor of New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump As have Muslims, women and gays, you ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @jimsciutto  And it's working so well. What could go wrong?   Trump is an ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Withold consent for Senate votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Thanks Chuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samsteinhp But Trump is a flaming idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmika Still too high.  Trump is a criminal ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Honey17011 @BI_contributors Another well thought out move from the Emperor of Orange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ Apparently only pro life that's white, Christian, or inside the womb.  Not poor, brown or black.   Not my Christianity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill  Paul Ryan thinks the stupid wall is more important than health care for Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddow What about the fact that Trump 's ban won't affect the countries where he has properties?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time ever, I saw Ivanks Trump clothes for sale at a Marshall's store. Might never go back.  Thoughts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sure you will be with me as long as I am not brown or black or female or poor or "foreign".  Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @usedgov  Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Thank you, sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianCastro More divided, and in an uglier way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill So, postponed, like releasing tax returns and press conference on the wife's immigration records?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews No I won't watch and I certainly would not enjoy more of this shit show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mradamtaylor @Honey17011 @washingtonpost Thanks Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marstu67 No one that I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfTowanda @Aurelius3395 @joanwalsh @JamesMartinSJ Thanks to these good people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesSmith123 Great way to waste taxpayers' money!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill But, will McCain have the guts to vote against?   Not t likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni Really, they need a "get away" to screw us over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix @washingtonpost Sadly, another Republican fails to grow a pair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill This is sad. I thought McCain was growing a pair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@axios Sean Spicer is a sad little man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedNews Trump lies about the size of many things!,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico And so the censorship begins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Whi is surprised, and, more importantly, who cares.  Trump is an ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner @LOLGOP @JFKucinich Do they think that we will forget?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Fabulous!  What could go wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics @NPR I just can't watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Chris Mathews' special report on President Obama. Worth a look in anticipation of tomorrow's disaster!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pittgriffin @JoyAnnReid Let's hope that Trump does not take this as a challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#InsteadofWatchingTheUnauguration I wil be desperately trying to fit in a root canal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Disappointed in Corey Booker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leyawn @chrislhayes And he is wrong again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Honey17011 Where are the rest of the Democrats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marmel Hey, don't insult nurses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilfredchan @JoyAnnReid @RepEspaillat Thank you,sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What's wrong Trump, are you asleep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilfredchan @RepJudyChu Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  I shall stay home and mourn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Could anyone be less aware of the world around him than Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@resnikoff @DavidCornDC @thinkprogress Thanks, Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill What part of meaningless do they not understand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Chavez is another idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marstu67 @thinkprogress Trump,is,a flaming idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Sadly, I love LL Bean products, but will no longer buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LOLGOP It might be ubpresidented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trollin_Trump @realDonaldTrump OK with me if he sits on any other exit row.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Fake press conference, fake paperwork, fake president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Phony president-elect.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>