<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Guyon espiner did well coping with winston peters alternative reality on morning report this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ScottBaio if you mess with @AJemaineClement you mess with all nz. Pull your head in chachi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time in 34 years at work I have an office.....feeling productive. https://t.co/BN6H1gYAoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems deathly quiet at westpac stadium today....are the sevens still on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rest of the world should vet u.s. Travellers and bar any that voted trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ fed express all the way!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan well I hope she took the opportunity to tell him what an unmitigated disaster his presidency has become!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could nz lead the world again and break all official ties with the United States until the removal of Donald trump as president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald so why not say "in America" in your headline???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald fuck off herald this story is from Cleveland in the us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does rnz let Jane Kelsey continue to present her alternate facts on tpp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob jones opinions useful in showing us how far we have come. But the personal villification of sir bob suggests we have a way to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Barack parting is such sweet sweet sorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever happened to Pokemon go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted on @sciblogsnz: "Large Swedish study finds no effect of fluoride on IQ" https://t.co/AjMxEx7YoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe lion are paying lance armstrong to be in a promotional video. Not spending my beersie money on a drug cheat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @KeirLeslie of course it does Phil! Exclusive intolerance the hallmark of a cult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National's leadership spill over in less than a week, labour still bleeding after 8 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point pakeha seem more prone to this and in any case teen pregnancy is dropping. https://t.co/Ikevj9VhC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @kaupapa agree with your reaction to this. It seems more prevalent against pakeha. Btw teen pregnancy down under key!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transparency_a1 I've never denied there is a climate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My partner paid 20 bucks to join up with Gareth Morgan. Now finds he wants to tax her parents home. Has sent them a message "count me out"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe an English versus little election would by necessity focus on policy rather than personality. That might be a good thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlos6212  yup got ten days booked on the Tongariro and the dog is excited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour would do well to remember oppositions don't win elections governments lose them. We may be witnessing just that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can nick leggatt stand for national party leader?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DevlinLive all good we should catch up for a bevy sometime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is how it is done Helen Clark! #JohnKey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was all class and an appropriate way to end a remarkable tenure #johnkey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go easy into the night Gordon McBride. "Drop kick me Jesus through the goalposts of life"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any one else got rain fade in the middle of the all black French test?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please watch and share:  https://t.co/5U3Dab6XlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does any one else think the TV 1 beach ball is bit like one of those balloons that chased Patrick mcgoohan in THE PRISONER?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good. https://t.co/eBi1Dtk1kY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No bread at croftin downs countdown, or water, or milk. https://t.co/NQtFMZuvPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the new media. No tv or paper in our house today but rnz and ou smart phones have kept us up with the play!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have my friends and tenants from Greta point staying at mine in Wadestown tonight. Strange way to catch up libby and Jane!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlos6212 yup Clinton had no chance of taking votes off trump, Bernie represented change so would have competed for the disaffected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I think about the trump thing the more I blame democrats for picking Hilary. Bernie would have beaten him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulSavageNZ yup they did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama must start campaigning now to beat trump in 2020]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gareth Morgan, Donald trump, open season on pussies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So maybe this is what those 99% protestors were on about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well it's not like idiots haven't been president before and your fear over trump may be as ethereal as your euphoria over Obama was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about trump when you live in a country that keeps a terminally ill woman in prison!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I was in Dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight @bryce_edwards what a whack job conspiracy theorist Sarandon has become!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on Morgan for having a crack. But mustn't say he is like trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't hosking front spellbound? It would be amazing watching him talk over and belittle the contestants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots has been said about Helen Kelly. For me one word says it all "Respect"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the republicans should dump trump and put up Bruce Willis, the rock or clint Eastwood to blow Hilary away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jo coughlan wished Justin well in a very classy speech to supporters at the Shepard's arms in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hobson's Choice=believing in freedom of speech+putting up with racist bs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindaclark1 why do we need a Chinese friendship garden? What about some friendship social housing or a friendship underpass?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnpagani @philquin funnier still that the story quotes coughlin at the same time it says she didn't want to go on the record!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is jo coffey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin sorry Phil just at cased purposes just wondering why jo coffey wanted to remain anon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @nmjyoung but why did jo coffey want to remain anonymous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure the nzrfu should be held accountable for the actions of the judiciary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HDPA thank Christ I don't have a Japanese car!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re the brangilina break up: George Clooney should get custody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been hearing a lot about "unconscious bias" George Orwell just called it thought crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The self entitlement of the illegal working foul mouthed French hitchhiker is precisely why thumbing a lift is dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difference between violent crime and terrorism? White people commit crimes everyone else commits terrorism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could someone please tell me wtf is wrong with the name ministry for "vulnerable" children?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzspew and you have a limited vocabulary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzspew @five15design see you are a friend of gridiron that explains a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have decided to #gojo and back Jo Coughlin for the Wellington mayoralty. A local with good vision to make the city better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americas cup victory beckons https://t.co/FZBelncBjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why try and hurt wine industry workers because you are upset at what a judge did???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ well that worries me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ are you aware nano girl has a strong commercial relationship with spark as a public speaker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ what is cool about toys being used to promote phone sales???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ so where will I see the robot queues are ther any?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ did you actually interview anyone for this story??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 reporter has told me the story is informative as it needs to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ so you didn't get a phone and newshub got no ads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ and honestly Stewart "as informative as it needs to be"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ  was nano girl paid by spark? Did spark buy newshub ads? Where are the photos from? Did you ask?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ so did the robots actually purchase the phone or hold a place in a queue? Did you get a phone or or pr releases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ did you or anyone at newshub get a phone to play with? Did you get a or release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StewartLundNZ  Stewart it's not personal but honestly how did you find this story? A or release? And do you think the headline is factual?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What bullshit advertorial parading as news.....it's called newshub,  should be adhub. https://t.co/HrF6zEuGRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rugby faces it biggest cultural challenge since the tour. At present it is failing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ButterworthJR John where are your workers from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZWatcher My point being if the wineries orchards etc offered better pay and conditions more kiwis would do the work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tepoakaroro Paul if we didn't import seasonal agricultural workers presumably pay rates would rise to attract more locals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be honest low skilled foreign workers are simply a cost saving for employers not a result of drugged lazy locals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guyon espiner is really hitting his straps on morning report. Great Iv with key this am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't we make non fossil fuel  cars a higher priority than driverless cars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice interview with Phil Twyford by Todd Niall on morning report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling up Quade cooper is like saying "dad burnt dinner, let's get the dog to cook."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll eat my hat the day a pizza drone delivery service actually works in windy Wellington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done parliament another step in living in a truly secular country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if winston will join trump and the Aussies by deporting and stripping of citizenship naturalised criminals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key's people find bugs all the time.....pity none of them live in havelock north!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ yeah I thought he was bloody good aswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't the ethical funding issue simple. If a fund has broken the law investigate and prosecute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelRowan then we should cease taxpayer funding of athletes who compete in such events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If our taxes pay to develop our top athletes why can't we watch them compete for free????]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>