<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bewarethefish @badtom no, nor me - am working later than expected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid and the acting Immigration and Customs Enforcement director, Ragsdale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad Ah.They always know. As soon as said cat is lulled into a false sense of security and comes inside, lock all exits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kittengloves and hung out to dry by his father (cough). I wonder what Fred would make of this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ I now have the theme as an earworm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad rustle a bag of Temptations ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad it's like the mother cat picking up the kitten on the back of the neck (supposedly) and the cat relaxes*

*not guaranteed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad peg on the neck? (cat not toddler)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee yes it was! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee see you on the flip side!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee hmmm, not sure I remember that one, but that's a cracking old-school narrator voice. Right I need to call it quits for the night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee it is Thigmund the Theamonthter, yes! Was having a retro moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee get a lot of mangled spaniards in chch then? ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee @gilfer that is indeed excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee I think your time has come...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee ha! Although possibly more e or special k alphabet generation...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee *saunterers (I changed that twice!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee I suspect the pension day sauntered would be more comfortable with Neil Diamond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee I should patent it before it's turned into a craft beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzJayZee 6pm perky loop with Men at Work and Zed. Can't spot FFD, but can't deny it was there either ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin there's rather a lot of buzzy easy listening music...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you inadvertently record your trip to the supermarket on your phone. 
If you need any ambient supermarket background noise, hmu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriankingston @librarykris I like it's broader category
&lt;projectiles with nonexplosive propellant&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@librarykris do eeeeet - then you can throw things at @adriankingston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be a Digital Editor at Te Papa?
https://t.co/kJNBwJzfID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin I hope they're on a slide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be of (general) interest to yourself, @ParryForte 
https://t.co/01ZOj8jkR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully It was! But I now know to stir it frequently as there were actual ðŸŒ¶ ðŸŒ¶ in the bottom of the glass...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully Oh dear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Amazon: join 750+ corporations &amp; stop advertising w/ Breitbart. Breitbart's brand of bigotry is bad for business. https://t.co/crQDMfnSfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might help your nerves @Megapope https://t.co/3j19lZmC1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh. https://t.co/57q45TWElI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may or may not be playing this at top volume rn
https://t.co/ZjaDAZS2XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelBarrowman oh god yes, one of those times you may actually want a weather bomb ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelBarrowman oh yay!

Arrghhpeopleargh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, YOU were woken at 5 by teenagers downstairs and their boyfriends arriving home in a doof doof car that idled for half an hour.
#fucksake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven I suspect you may be right, there x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day twenty-three:
https://t.co/XBPsIknA8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven those are a bit cute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day twenty-two:
https://t.co/EmcyFhl4r1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatydidNZ @AndrewPaulWood yep, this is a whitetail
https://t.co/B6Pk0qUcYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanleyBigFeet @KatydidNZ yep, agree
https://t.co/8pvZ6zN1Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen I still miss Six Volts though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen When I left NZ in 1995, I took ten tapes(!) with me and four of them were Front Lawn and Mutton Birds. They saved me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen I think the word absofuckenlutely is appropriate here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacobunny not ALL of them are on there. Or there wasn't a vid for CR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day twenty-one:
https://t.co/eexlPgKWNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad And then Juggernaut interaction at your 2nd to last employ ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad That you need a handy set of polite retorts would be exhausting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bad_emma_bad ARGHHHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin It's quite a violent mantis though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teh_aimee I loved this game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ @plinythemidlkid school holidays used to be around the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ @plinythemidlkid teachers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid So many birthdays. (With mine being the most important)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tklauren wtf is the QR code for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tis a good day for listening to The Broken Heartbreakers
https://t.co/SYEGw4xKM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tklauren suspect waiting till mid-thirties all good :-) Will poss depend on capturing 'pre-existing conditions'. etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tklauren so fun. However, I DO recommend health insurance...not sure how that works with your imminent departure though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf arg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eXDeeNZ @StuFlemingNZ prices always lower when there's a Gull station nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bewarethefish so much muting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day twenty:
https://t.co/9ZdvuXPzdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully coughbrowniecough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badtom @bewarethefish @raena @powderkeig erg arg, had 2 hours of sleep (for non-nefarious reasons) and cannae brain or people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BooksellersNZ I imagine Muppet Books is also an infringement. Not to mention explanatory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin At least Gert looks contained. Peggy C could get a door inna face at any moment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully and a gorgeous in-focus photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully still enough for an in-focus photo, though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I WAS trying to watch the TEDx Antarctica, but apparently I'm not right now. https://t.co/5k8BRk3tZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like the threat of visitors to get the housework done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ of course by calm I mean Wellington calm ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ calm here in Wellington today, should be a smooth crossing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ my spider senses tell me you're on a road trip...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even my Spotify is protesting https://t.co/sGKozMeQN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qbig project.
Fearing Trump will delete climate data, scientists are banding together to archive whatever they can https://t.co/NL5pYCRqvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bewarethefish They also do a great cover of Guns of Brixton :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day fifteen:
https://t.co/GkPsKJm0VT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid hmm- it does anyway, don't remember that from the first viewing months ago :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day fourteen:
https://t.co/kgZk92tFQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid except that version has sound! So reposting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikinajar @wellykowhai with a sub-set of those doing both, presumably!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wellykowhai @nikinajar mates. But there are still historical / random tensions. Families are weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wellykowhai @nikinajar  Ha! I escape to the loo frequently. Although, I am super lucky in that we are a large family and yet we're all good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikinajar also: neat. â˜„ï¸ðŸ”¥ðŸ¥€â›‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikinajar If it wasn't the initial point, I'd say wine stat! Delayed processing of grief is such an odd experience (from my own), kia kaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikinajar Do you find yourself falling into old patterns of behaviour? Exhausting (but interesting!) to skew them a little.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TracieAlmond I considered that as an option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully Part of your 5 a day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tklauren it is totally thriller bear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo__Scully yep. I really wanted to be able to pick it up (while driving obv) and throw it back in his window (while driving obv).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lesser-known New Zealand Woofwoof
#behindthescenesatthemuseum https://t.co/LNbdNnNvGy https://t.co/C7DdI5kNVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drawers
#behindthescenesatthemuseum 
#andacowboydog https://t.co/E70AOgp8a5 https://t.co/k3jFtaVx18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet of curiosities 
#behindthescenesatthemuseum https://t.co/2jGKVNbV0v https://t.co/YzC79U2OC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rows of bones
#behindthescenesatthemuseum https://t.co/Rp14NsCLeh https://t.co/OS9oAcCs2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAAR
Bare bear
#behindthescenesatthemuseum 
@bearnui https://t.co/vuIQZ2orPl https://t.co/S8p59yissX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moa toes
#behindthescenesatthemuseum https://t.co/vad06fTiXh https://t.co/1AmyEqyXmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Particularly revolted by guy driving along and chucking cigarette plastic wrap and foil out the window as he cracked a new pack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuFlemingNZ Christ on a cracker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day thirteen:
https://t.co/ARAphDNMsq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>