<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We can see why Penny Marshall divorced that fat foul sad waste of space https://t.co/Xj4Xn9HUBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Pelosi is just Bat Shit Crazzy https://t.co/eZkJzW8bgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nia4_trump @bfraser747 When that Old Bat wakes up tell her She Is FIRED! https://t.co/4sW89xOAsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily News Segment - John B shares critical info today! - CTM Episode 681 https://t.co/EsCgs0p3mY via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker calls for Melania Trump's immigration papers. But Her Mirage License to Donald makes her an American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of Massachusetts caught using falsified lab tests in convictions; fake science exposed https://t.co/rAlm30lm2I @FromtheTrenches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget the (HGH) Human Groth Hormones https://t.co/VJEAmoddqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who ?Ooh yea Miss Piggy's first aborted piglet Amy shit mouth https://t.co/k13KfOpkqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dingle Berry was in his dorm smoking crack and not in class https://t.co/2pGy0angCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why GOD gave Island more land and rose it up 6 foot Allah had nothing to do with it stupid cock sucking Imam https://t.co/bMVMTcqbWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the chain Smoking Burnt Cracker Mad, Fuck Off and Die Dingle Berry Obammy https://t.co/MWTEWfvSN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat: Why Was I Banned From U.S.? https://t.co/wGwHWzdBaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayZClassicBars Hay J Turd what was it like to entertain Slave Owners in DUBI did it get your rocks off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama Comes Out of Vacation to Spread Hate https://t.co/8WDzR6f4Ek via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libtards creating a Bio Hazard call in the EPA https://t.co/5GpLgKzs3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change is real it fallows like this Spring Summer Fall Winter and back to Spring see climate change all yea… https://t.co/xhHJxASftQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OOPS: Starbucks’ New Pro-Refugee Hiring Policy Against The LAW… https://t.co/pvXjcF1lhG via @Patriotic_Folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to add a Lucy in honer of Lucille Ball these Bigoted Oscars are a joke https://t.co/BtfGjqwDVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's called TAX EVASION and its Illegal https://t.co/5ppxhXNT5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StopStopHillary @YouTube That's why this piece of trash Warren Jeffs is in prison Polygamy and chid abuse https://t.co/jkZ9AlzHAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that the same Nixon where hillary rotten ass clinton Lied and was fired off the case that Nixon https://t.co/sVzPxPResQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo Love it. Keep up the good fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#1 Why are Christians Forbidden to enter MECA https://t.co/xhhZ0XZw1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that Islam Stink finger! I do not whant to know where that bloody yeast infected Stink finger has been https://t.co/fL7sBCQVN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that Monica's Blue Dress ---------YUCK https://t.co/WFlMYNG0YY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank God https://t.co/UdkJkvXGC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newborn Seized After ‘Off-Grid’ Parents Refuse Social Security Number https://t.co/wCxeqoCsCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First the stink pig has to be charged then convicted before a parden https://t.co/yhi3EoaF3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And all her sister wives to be https://t.co/gDE5aeOMQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airport's are not Public Property! https://t.co/gPW1jJoRuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Is A Foreigner, Say College Records That Have Been Uncovered.Obama Can’t Retire/Get Away With Crime (Video) https://t.co/MH7NXUVvH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @POTUS should designate the #MuslimBrotherhood as a terrorist organization! https://t.co/TR0Ded2Kus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where you can get real baby back ribs https://t.co/AsIpmmTFzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems only Gay Men get thrown off the roofs in the Middle East not Gay Women https://t.co/nRROawZ0xC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer Obviously has some Monetary investment in Islamic terrorism like selling Guns and OPIUM ie.. Heroin https://t.co/eVfjJFqGoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dairy Industry To Pump Milk With Brain Tumor Chemicals https://t.co/K0Ue2k3Rhg via @yournewswire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NPR:  "25 Million Votes  For Hillary Clinton  ‘Completely Fake’  - She L... https://t.co/ADa1rY6MnX via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pontifex  We the Children of Light will not put up with your FOUL MOUTH! you are not a CHRISTIAN your Jesuit Scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Clintons Selling Uranium from Ranchers’ Land was set with Diamonds from an Arkansas Corn Farmer’s Land https://t.co/tTMoHCBKHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chili’s restaurants hold fundraisers for Planned Parenthood https://t.co/K0h9zruFtv via @DCClothesline Real Baby Baby Back Ribs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: U.S. Congress Order  FBI To Hand Over Hillary Clinton’s  Email... https://t.co/4CriJmIHzi via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucktodd &lt;--- Wast of Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susan Rice the Lying Whore who clamed a Video caused 911 https://t.co/WrIfDry8Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I now have some new respect for Kim Kardashian as she responds to Donald Trump 'Muslim ban' https://t.co/w6Mlno90iZ via @DailyMailCeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Shall It Be https://t.co/0ob3mu72Zo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles will not be King! William is to be crowned King! Charles is a Bumbling Fool and that Horse Face Bitch is wh… https://t.co/iT7uhUYjNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is an Obama appointee That in itself is telling enough https://t.co/zpsN2nsKuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING! Look what was just discovered about Judge who halted Trump's i... https://t.co/BdSfNz9uLQ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should have turnd that shit hole into a sheet of glass a long time ago https://t.co/vO3EG0y2Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God Speed he will be missed https://t.co/n2YjpxYYwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Marine's Epic Rant Proves That Liberalism Is A Mental Disorder https://t.co/xsS1Ee6P6i via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@youngturksrec What is Islam so afraid of is it that Christians will get into Heaven on Faith Alone? Or that they worship a Graven Image?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Russia told us they were bad news and that son of a Whore Obama let them run free to kill https://t.co/2SBGEEe7dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh well then Zero Federal Funding for all them Welfare Recipients https://t.co/uWknrJa2TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Obama Crimes - 75+  Times Obama Broke The Law During His  Pres... https://t.co/E4NLXbBSZ8 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Will Not Forget https://t.co/pPNtgcExzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Why is this Psychopathic Scum Sucking Swamp Thing not in JAIL https://t.co/gPTh4GSU0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did they teach in school oh yea Carbon is the most abundant material in the entire universe the building block… https://t.co/KlZkBMHjx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi forces 'discover mustard gas' in ISIS warehouse https://t.co/sxIBm1lqnm via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scum Sucking Swamp Thing Elizabeth Warren Exposes Greedy Nazi Hillary Clinton Corruption https://t.co/TplcfMba8m via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PriceIsRight Drew let his Fire Bug child break the Law disgusting https://t.co/SiZpBHNP3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Recieved One Million Votes From Illegal Aliens https://t.co/czzERlUa66 via @yournewswire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yea the catch 22 no crime no cops! It's the Judge Hooker Cop circle to frame the john and keep money flowing int… https://t.co/nl9lCegmEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NAACP must be involved or they would not care. Me thinks they protest to much https://t.co/x7o1R0bcNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's called barring false witness and they will burn in hell for it https://t.co/TvWgMUMsQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ts that why the Mexican Prk doesn't want a wall he promist ISIS they could cross our border https://t.co/Iy7uOIxV6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealroseanne @TMZ The Price is Right and TMZ https://t.co/35KI5dEJcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boycott the https://t.co/MrffvO5xLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can't get a proper ID because they are Illegal or Criminals doesn't have anything to do with IQ https://t.co/UBoFUEB05v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closed Walmart opens as shelter for illegals https://t.co/proye9b9fn via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh what sticky webs they weave when first they practice to diceive https://t.co/sneFpN5ZUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USFreedomArmy @whateverbarry We could care less what the Marxist Heshe said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd Delete @facebook if I wasn't addicted to Angry Birds https://t.co/nMLJenxO4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos Pamela for being a real Journalist a true to self Reporter https://t.co/8mpGeq5FMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rogue Planet Alert: MSM  Disclosure - "Is a Huge Celestial Object  Near ... https://t.co/G7jawG2UiY via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hay Twitter where are the BLOCK buttons they have been removed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman who set fire to Trump supporter’s hair is identified https://t.co/FbFWAJtDiJ via @DCClothesline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHTF is she doing with a GUN in A School https://t.co/JQRossFKPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stick your head between your knees and kiss your ass good by https://t.co/bSPmYyouPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Orders Removal Of Pagan Islamic Symbols, Practices In The White House Do You Support Him ? Yes we do http://support-him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton 's Cult of Pesonality is a Symphony of Destruction https://t.co/VslH0IK18d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not if she only Cast one Vote numb nut https://t.co/l8DFYYdHxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large Crack in Earth here in the Michigan Upper Penninsula.wmv https://t.co/PkuujfzhNQ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge half-mile crack opens in the ground in Mexico https://t.co/91FEAExXcr via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge Crack in the Earth Opens Up East of Yellowstone Caldera by Big Horn... https://t.co/A5d0l8Vmf6 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TAKE THE POLL: Would You Support Trey Gowdy As Trump’s Attorney General? https://t.co/Ouxrg8ZKBX via @Patriotic_Folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive fissure stretching almost two miles opens up in Arizona desert https://t.co/dw8pfcAQPZ via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA Bank Accounts Suspended - Media Black Out - Except Here https://t.co/niOg9N6NXs via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Voter's did not vote for OB Care! That Nazi Nancy Pelosi passed that bill without reading it. So Illegal https://t.co/cbOda2l1Pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 of Obama JV Muslim teem is there proper name https://t.co/PYE2qqTfZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of them they were to damaged to attend Public School https://t.co/A8FQ3zokar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BUSTED: Elizabeth Warren Evades Ethics Laws… https://t.co/xlqpCbYymv via @Patriotic_Folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOOM! China Admits to Aerosol Campaign to Control Weather https://t.co/qihJyUF9Rm via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Clinton Supporters Are Scientifically ‘Psychotic’ https://t.co/JvIYuMiwLG via @yournewswire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liars the Lead comes from the damn pipes in the buildings and the ground running to the buildings not the water tre… https://t.co/vNGRAcc7EC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheView So Low Rent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask @SpeakerRyan (AKA power of the Purse) Whare did Obama got the Money?  That's right @SpeakerRyan gave it Obama https://t.co/VDsZ7W2msz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgendaOfEvil Tell Afghanistan we will Round Up every God Damn Heroin Poppy https://t.co/WThpbesox2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mining, fracking and construction are triggering more EARTHQUAKES https://t.co/S1HCOVjF6F via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving sexual favers for votes is Illegal like Blow Jobs for Hillary https://t.co/3xlEei3yvY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>