<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyTusheets: I accept that non sequitur as the towel. Will leave it there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyTusheets: Check country she's from against ban list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyTusheets: That is not responsive to point that it's false to call them illegal immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoPiercy: They traveled there from other places: Midde East, Africa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also 1,250 is not "thousands."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These refugees fleeing war would not be "illegal immigrants" if admitted to the U.S. https://t.co/eIl9ejlh51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B0rdertourista: Despite what his doctor says, his weave suggests he remains mostly bald. Drug failed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ollie became a folk hero in part because her quest for a better life caused unfounded fears not unlike those besett… https://t.co/4Jwfms4ifg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he not know Boston bombers were U.S. citizens? https://t.co/QvMrCrTiL7 https://t.co/qgKavaelxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarynthumps: Great point. Lot riding on that little red panda now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom takes another hit. https://t.co/YLpXYDPyIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The federal Gun Free School Zones Act, a law passed by Congress, on its face precludes such an executive order.… https://t.co/bE8ftQZCHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lack of "the" before country sounds Russian. https://t.co/4MpnicORRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rapid Trump Administration cave on hiring freeze for VA shows ineptitude. https://t.co/05mdO8whwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet when you factor race, income, education it's ~35. https://t.co/lnjF8z6lDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch is trending. But if it's not him or Hardiman, that would be strong. https://t.co/P5YRxwaP42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelsey_snell @jenhab: Why irrational? Because she's female? Her actions that we know of -- fleeing captivity -- are quite rational.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take: Ollie the escaped bobcat is all Trump is not: Shy, crafty, real hair-covered, outdoorsy, freedom loving. She… https://t.co/3WdT6U4tse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider how embarrassing this goofy claim would be for Trump were it true. https://t.co/OYDhKdfz6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per Durbin, Sessions said he'd continue investigation "if there's a basis," but "Congress also has investigations." https://t.co/JKerWSQ7PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durbin asked if Sessions read classified or unclassified ODNI report on Russian hacking. https://t.co/1YAqz7Ab47 Se… https://t.co/fkiJxQZa3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grassley notes Dems could cite 'two hour rule" to delay Sessions vote until Weds. Says if so, he'll hold roll call first thing in morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I hope that at some point our Democratic colleagues will get past their anger and come to accept the verdict of the American people."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cornyn pretty much fully taunting Democrats over election: Says they are going through stages of grief and are currently on anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durbin says refusal by Sessions "give us his word" he will not impede FBI investigation into Russian interference "to me is disqualifying."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durbin: "I have to question" Sessions's statement that he was "not involved" in the drafting of Trump's immigrant ban order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should count plagiarized answers?https://t.co/pwxEsiN3et https://t.co/MEDb8Tk4le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leahy on Sessions not faulting Trump voting lie.
"Of course he didn't know what data. There is not such data. He oughta just admit that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leahy rips Sessions for refusing to condemn Trump’s illegal voting claims. Notes Sessions said he doesn’t know what data Trump used.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy when you use other people's answers. https://t.co/77VGMcfFy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Feinstein, Leahy compares Yates to Richardson and Ruckelshaus, who refused Nixon. But Leahy adds: "I knew them both personally."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feinstein says Sally Yates showed "what a truly independent Attorney General does" while explaining she is voting against Sessions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says State's Director of Policy Planning under George W. Bush. https://t.co/AfXoMTDj4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will the President use a question mark correctly? https://t.co/qCz6oTJUnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those tracking the political karma of the Superbowl, new left hero Sally Yates is from Atlanta. https://t.co/Q7gMrMe8kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White House backs Trump on Jew omission." - forthcoming Fox headline. https://t.co/gksAUygBCL https://t.co/F6ri5BXDTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's still eligible to seek a second term. https://t.co/e4Fn03NxPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump terribly ill-served by the 31-year old flack/speechwriter ideologue he put in a powerful policy job. https://t.co/pX61WRQ4QS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsteadWH: I mean the chant, not lack of collaboration. So many syllables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsteadWH: Sounds hard to sustain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston becomes a temporary haven for Muslim ban targets. Brady does not see "big deal" in Trump palling.… https://t.co/oVKVdFITnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what a version. https://t.co/T4KVaoRqLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connorobrienNH: I do. Tony has made the surprising shift to professional dance; is struggling; lives in Manhattan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanyon Sturtze (@sturtze56) is 46 years old. In 2002, he went 4-18. https://t.co/rI15nTEKFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former NBA player to fellow pro Nazr Mohammed, a Muslim who expressed dismay at Muslim ban. https://t.co/5bPULIVuTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why this crowd repeated Sen. Warren's words, but the effect is unfortunate. https://t.co/XtKsymXHRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU lawyers high-fiving cheering throng outside federal courthouse. https://t.co/BsQMgcDV5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxAbrahms @strategyrick: I'd guess incompetence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be a mistake to frame the order as actual anti-terror policy rather than a xenophobic pander to fear of Musl… https://t.co/whmgCr1FIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craven cave-in is a fun phrase. https://t.co/iG5MRsB00Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, how is decreeing refugees from certain countries cannot come here "extreme vetting?" (Or "xtreme?") Wher… https://t.co/p05yM5KwW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banning Muslim refugees from certain countries is not "extreme vetting," a bullshit phrase. It's a ban. https://t.co/MbRpr8nvA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or he would have adjusted his ideology along with the rest of his party. https://t.co/zknmwrzJWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Promised Crackdown on Gun Crimes Is Coming into Focus https://t.co/imKEqdi8WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta think social media is causing more people to get caught doing this, as much as causing more of it.… https://t.co/7dnnVNfU24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His situation is the reverse. https://t.co/gVXPCifbpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobtaber: Langer isn't a dual citizen though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we have the Bernhard-Langer-maybe-tried-to-vote-despite-being-a-German-citizen data point. But they stopped him… https://t.co/Ou7g7H6xpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: Many Dems did not want to pass it and thus would not vote for it. Can argue they are wrong,  but not with resulting situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: Even if PO could have passed via reconciliation, I believe senators who said it would have screwed deal for main ACA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: That piece cites a story based on one I wrote. So I feel some authority to say nothing there challenges view it couldn't pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: Seems like a bit of lefty canard to say could have passed, without evidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: What is the basis for the claim? Many Democrats who voted for the bill said they would not support it with a public option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsonenstein: If it was included, the Senate would not have passed the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Langer think the "media" report on Trump telling the story to Hill leaders, rather than the Trump, did the… https://t.co/nB6z9WtxlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One of the suspects was wearing Hernandez's watch [engraved with his nickname, King Felix'] when he was arrested. https://t.co/s26GcRDDiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump voter fraud example's from a pro-golfer who is a German citizen who thought he, but not Hispanics, could vote. https://t.co/oLVrHKHIwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds big, but is the Undersecretary of State for Management and his 3 top staff the same as State's 'entire senio… https://t.co/fmYHURHPWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps the first congressional bill in history where the offset is a they-owe-us to Mexico. https://t.co/4evri1orSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickJSalem: Yes, and is saying explicitly that he thinks more prosecutions, not more resources, is the ticket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmkent: He's president now. And story is about plan by Sessions to fight gun crime with federal prosecutions. https://t.co/XckePGKBNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickJSalem" “With proper support and with vigorous prosecutions, ATF can be more productive without large increases in funding..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions' plan use more fed prosecutions to combat gun crime is a gamble. There's little evidence that works. https://t.co/XckePGKBNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps Mexicans will mostly build it. https://t.co/Eo1nQb1VSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevieDougie: To reduce the time we spend listening to him say things. And the active voice is egalitarian. It is not fancy, just better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awzurcher: It's not a sexy cause, but it's mine. I will not let them make me use arbitrary ellipses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not our top issue, but this country is due for a reckoning on punctuation. I'd fight to stop random capitalization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendoody: Also, you know, almost VP in one case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't he at least embrace the active voice? https://t.co/hvtnIZpDre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70% "don't know/refused" on impression of gov candidate Gillespie, though he almost upset Warner in '14 Senate race… https://t.co/B5jFbIZ3B0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow, Rep. Hakeem Jeffries, from Brooklyn, will give a "state of the district" speech titled “Rise of the Resistance," per announcement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Combining the Dakotas would create an admirably square state with a tighter name and an Idaho-level population of 1… https://t.co/bDzFYMN5Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot less. https://t.co/byK6WrIFa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeBoland78: I was worried about where we were headed after "campground." Way to keep it SFW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidence does not support this claim. https://t.co/ojHVG8mSN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @MikeBoland78, look at this dude. https://t.co/2Con5kljMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorter Brady: 'I have not personally been groped by Trump. Everyone is nice to me.' https://t.co/fDSeloRzxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacyLeMelle: Maybe terminology differs in Nebraska.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if the rabbit uses the platform to come out? https://t.co/bozIIE1loj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Trump claims illegal ballots cost him popular vote, https://t.co/Ub9O0AZ75p Sessions in written answer insist… https://t.co/7K9tSQ6DJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions on voter fraud claims: "I believe fraudulent activities regularly occur during election[s]," including '16. https://t.co/UyRiY33epc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: The bill's goal was to make defeating Manchin-Toomey easier. That's why it exists. Not to pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: If Cruz was serious about it, how many times did he seek a vote in committee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: Because it wasn't gonna pass, &amp; NRA backed/helped write it. Easy points. Doesn't make it real effort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: I know. And you either know that bill was not written to pass or you drank too much Kool-Aid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: If you worked in Senate at the time, you know it was there as an excuse for background check foes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJoshPerry @brianros1 @sarahmquinlan: The Grassley/Cruz bill existed as excuse to oppose expanded background checks with no chance to pass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["..and I should have been more careful with my words." 
He did seem irked at that moment under Blumenthal's questio… https://t.co/6iwgSmef9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docjorich: Seems unlikely. Not his agency and gun lobby backing him opposes it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio previously suggested other factors, like national security, topped his considerations. https://t.co/WwWdPHXsyY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>