<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just received an email that @AerLingus have cancelled the Dublin - Porto route. I had been really looking forward to that weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HailoIreland thank you!! Did not see that :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HailoIreland That's a pity. I pre-book for the 5am trips and there's no option there to request Hailo+ (that I can see).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being Irish: @PresidentIRL flies on a public flight just like all of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @AerLingus pilot kicks off the pre-flight announcement with "Uachtarán na hÉireann, a dhaoine uaisle, tá fáilte romhat"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael D is in the house!! Well, on my flight at least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Aer Lingus Lounge early in the morning. Bastion of suited businessmen. Easily 90% male passengers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HailoIreland is there any way to request "no vans" on my profile? I really don't like getting vans, especially for the 5am airport runs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gluten-free chicken tenders from @mandsireland aware really quite good, they crisp up nicely in the oven. Great freezer food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First class of WSET Level 3 done with @1erWineTraining Really excited to get going on this journey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite a nice sounding bar menu from the St Stephens Green hotel. Must give it a try sometime https://t.co/DPI7orBfyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProperFood_ie @SabrinaGhayour It's a fantastic cookbook. Everything I've tried from it has been delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @GinandGriddle @LucindasIreland @Mcmillanchef ...but that's not necessarily negative. Perhaps more to do with superficiality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @GinandGriddle @LucindasIreland @Mcmillanchef I think the younger generation have a greater sense of entitlement...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @LucindasIreland @Mcmillanchef It can be very amusing to later see which bloggers have accepted the offer :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @LucindasIreland @Mcmillanchef Ditto here. I politely decline any offers of free meals in return for coverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe ...but I'm really glad to see it working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe It's really hard, I simply don't have the time to do that. Every two days is about right for me at the moment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a result, I've seen a definite uptick in followers, which is rewarding. It also challenges me to have photos ready (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the start of Jan, I decided to increase my posting rate to Instagram. I went from 1-2 times per week, to posting every second day.. (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[BLOGGED] A short review of the new &amp; tasty Kyoto Asian Street Food in Waterford https://t.co/BEuzk3glTc https://t.co/0Wa0e6ATPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cork people, you are lucky! Last night, we dined greenescork as part of a family celebration.… https://t.co/Xie5o9RyPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED - Irish wine tastings and events https://t.co/T2bUaO8o2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updating my Wine Tasting events page - any new events that I should add?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishshiitake All I know is that we were eating chicken all the way to Wednesday! Enjoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishshiitake I got a 3kg free range chicken last Sunday. Chicken wasn't really the word for that beast. Thundering mini-dinosaur perhaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So impressed by @cheftomkerridge on TV this morning. Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utterly miserable today. So bunged up. Fecking cold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very curious to see @cask_cork Great concept of cocktails &amp; changing small plates from @Greenescork @newfoodie2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newfoodie2012 @Greenescork We were peeking in the windows @cask_cork. Looks very exciting, best of luck with it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big thank you to @Greenescork @newfoodie2012 for a lovely meal tonight https://t.co/Jk9y8S74XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eimearlucey @RobinStrahan @dmarrinan Always a great choice, have a lovely night out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what the world is coming to... https://t.co/CcWUx0bGXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eimearlucey @RobinStrahan @dmarrinan what have you chosen??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madaemz Always lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays @Jacquescork23 @mccarthykanturk @gubbeen @fia_cafe that sounds wonderful too. Irish toasties for the win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic toastie with Jack McCarthy's black pudding &amp; Coolea cheese @Jacquescork23 https://t.co/9ShwahaKyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to dinner tonight @Greenescork Haven't been there in years and I read such good things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for a Dutch classic but with a little twist - Goats cheese bitterballen pomms.nl… https://t.co/1ELJwENjy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Dublin rule in Cork! https://t.co/zacA6SYrLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmulley sorely needed. Working with too many D4 loike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrkkk! I'm home boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burger &amp; pint for €10 during all 6 Nations games @TheHill_Pub - Great burger too!! https://t.co/TMtbeq2V3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AerLingus Is it possible to speak with someone about the migration of my AerClub account? The online info is useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets bought already! Do I get a prize for being an early bird?? https://t.co/lvQscb0tCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing at all to be proud of. I'd go so far as to say an embarrassment to Ireland https://t.co/lw8AezYYLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eimearlucey @RobinStrahan @dmarrinan great wine selection by the glass in F&amp;M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could possibly go wrong? https://t.co/N8dFTRbfne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank god for @hailoireland - so efficient!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there's never any fecking passport control staff at Pier B to allow us to exit directly into T1 @dublinairport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cronin Rule of Flying #1. when I'm grumpy &amp; feet are sore, @dublinairport are guaranteed to park us at Pier B &amp; make us walk to T2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U15 @FAIreland squad is on the @AerLingus flight home following a friendly draw with NL. Well done lads!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmarrinan @eimearlucey Have you been to Forest &amp; Marcy yet? Would also recommend Locks, Bastible, Craft, Charlotte Quay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmarrinan @eimearlucey but baby puke is soooo interesting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thursday treat @pomms_nl fanstastic mayo! https://t.co/NSCBuPk28I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cork Burger Festival is ongoing until Feb 5th @festival_cork More details here https://t.co/D2Mh9B8MY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to learn that the next #elybigtasting takes place March 3rd. Tickets on sale tomorrow so get in there fast!! @elywinebars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulshoebox it's a wonderful city. I've spent over 2 years working here at different times. Love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulshoebox more time at home. Dropping down to three days/week abroad. Every little helps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulshoebox @EatDrinkRunFun I did L2 about 2 years ago now. Really enjoyed it but work stopped me from moving on...until now!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting WSET Level 3 on Monday. Very eager to get going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EatDrinkRunFun @GastroGays nothing wrong with going. Just say or hashtag that you are a guest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GastroGays I'm beginning to suspect not!! It's so tedious when everyone is posting, but I haven't seen anyone saying they're a guest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people at a restaurant PR event tonight. Would be nice to see some mention of "invited" or "guest" on their Insta stories etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes a bento box? A Benton of is a great way to enjoy lots of small things for your lunch.… https://t.co/L1g3Rh1fV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipping 'Eck, he just can't let it go and conduct himself with some dignity https://t.co/LONXMSEKfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iyerscafe and now I'm thinking about them too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock @DonnellyStephen if you plan to do something about ticket prices, how about starting with Ticketmaster's atrocious fees &amp; charges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stopped watching Designated Survivor a while back because it was getting a bit far-fetched. It's looking a whole lot more attractive now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I attended a tutored wine masterclass featured some. Innovative and modern wines from the… https://t.co/BNhqXjwqti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks the beast-sized free range chicken I got from @ranelaghbutcher yesterday, I have a bucket of leftovers. chicken masala I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these little notes attached to the focus table wines at #ADTwine tasting today @wine_australia @campbellliam222 https://t.co/MeKq1mmAqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarinaOLoughlin not quite what you're looking for but... https://t.co/UOkw8FoA8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exquisite finish with @darenbergwine Nostalgia Rare Tawny NV at @wine_australia #ADTwine tasting with… https://t.co/wYdSDdgRuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_RPM @campbellliam222 @KooyongWines @10XTractor both very distinctive wines!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinesDirect @campbellliam222 just tried that one. Very attractive &amp; refreshing. Great example of CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuriosityLiquid @campbellliam222 quite a unique wine. Good chew in it for a Pinot Noir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to Australia Day wine tasting #ADTwine from #wine_australia led by @campbellliam222 https://t.co/GjHNywmK03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what Queen Elizabeth II, who has held her role for 65 years and served in WWII, will think of Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM Sorry I can't share, but it's straightforward content on BIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM I only saw it in the Irish Bloggers FB page, which is closed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM The lifestyle/beauty blogger /influencer section is where I'd look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM Finally, I think the food blogging section is largely OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM for me the easiest way is to have no marketing content at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM in parallel Revenue also issued a statement on BIK for bloggers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethOnFood @OnlyOneReynard @FrenchfoodieinD @kateskabin @NewstalkFM we've had a lot of discussion on the Irish Bloggers FB page]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poke has been up and coming for a few years now in the US and Europe. It's healthy, tasty and adaptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a poke bowl? It's essentially a Hawaiian raw fish salad. Think marinated raw tuna chunks, mixed with veg, on rice or salad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poke bowls coming soon to Dublin - keep an eye on @DublinPoke for more news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aerogaby @corkscrewnation @richiemagnier @frankstero @campbellliam222 @suzisgrapecrush @TheIrishWino It's absolutely delicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahwhiteacre Excellent! Thanks for letting me know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone tried this beef dripping from @lidl_ireland ? https://t.co/yOzWo89Xfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to prep the remaining veg now. Roast potatoes and parsnips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fine glass of Joseph Drouhin Fleurie from @Whelehanswines while waiting for roast chicken. A very elegant wine with slight violet notes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetandmeat @GinandGriddle Thanks so much for the RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishFoodGuide Thanks for the RT Zack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a little request - Would appreciate immensely if you'd help push my Instagram account over the magic 1k!!  https://t.co/fwkQNc2YXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big bag of carrots starting to show a little green. Solution, peel, prep then freeze for later use https://t.co/7c6bbaDa5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being able to return home to my family. Oh wait... https://t.co/Ibh1dKCJd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic fish. &amp; chips from fishbarsaltzer in Amsterdam Centraal station. Fresh cod, cooked… https://t.co/hm5IoQVPce]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>