<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That isn't going to make the water any nicer. https://t.co/qeT1yq1gFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was great to hear the thoughts of one of Ecan's new councillors for #Insight 8 @RNZSunday https://t.co/TMnUjvslQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow that looks amazing https://t.co/v02CKfslVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased with that clarifaction. The only chopping @InsightRNZ this afternoon was indeed audio and the odd edge to a… https://t.co/g20nTBvoSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodeos - Should They Stay or Go? https://t.co/aD2Y6v2XRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could make decisions over new drugs even harder. https://t.co/pDVzUpfy4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@pmigone heads to the rodeo on this week's Insight and asks should it stay or should it go? https://t.co/yJ1i47LCxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know they are very nutritious, but the yuck factor is immediate. https://t.co/8NzCZbp6Y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So predictions for who next at the Christmas regeneration? https://t.co/3LXdufZ14f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much better reference https://t.co/c5h84b2K8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He dosen't have to cut it does he ? https://t.co/JDDQB1pLZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is some serious trimming there. https://t.co/Rk9T9YtRv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArielaZibiah in for a penny ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get out of the office and great great stories for @InsightRNZ https://t.co/xdywbbsDWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of sun pictures being posted to entice you back. https://t.co/3EXX3Ce1vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to fly to Auck for #Insight interviews @RNZteresacowie turns storm reporter. Weather 'bomb low' barrels in https://t.co/aM5wj52P4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emails a bit sorted, interviews almost organised. That's it for first day back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outspoken: Big pants needed for pension age debate, says commissioner https://t.co/9ZuTeP1Z3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TracyJNeal There appears to be a gap between saying we want people to work longer, they want to work longer and employers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TracyJNeal You are kind. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting challenges ahead. My Outspoken with  @DianeMaxwellNZ  @RichardCTU &amp; @MasseyUni 's Prof Tim Bentley https://t.co/Va8GFunTox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizenBomber @dtyukich  and will there be work for those having to hang on or benefits for those who can"t ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retirement Commissioner would like more benefits and training https://t.co/KCxut9hvHM Whole discussion on Outspoken tonight @ 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM to stay away from Waitangi https://t.co/f4vH5KskD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fav was when they insisted my indentical twin sons had to have an id each to prove age, not just the one buying. https://t.co/Y30RY7YQ5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trapped in airport bus with sound track that is dissolving my brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganjwhelan @BeeFaerie I think  there is a whole subsection like that, gender aside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree, but also been surprised by negative responses. https://t.co/DESx2tz2EI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people trying to change these tragic numbers but could/should more be done? https://t.co/yU3A7BdaQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excellent way to spend the day. What is the project? https://t.co/UzheE0D7js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy to have tweets about standards. Happy New Year. https://t.co/GA8S5mp3k8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am wondering how those beauty spots are coping at the moment? https://t.co/wlNcHbK7E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An A-Z of 2016: Bennetticiaries and Teepeepees https://t.co/YtOcEzEMru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ honey producers angry Australians using word 'manuka' https://t.co/RrLGE46ftT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaths, dildoes and Donald: The big stories of 2016 https://t.co/1EjrGF50Oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some great podcasts and videos as part of this investigation. Load up https://t.co/sp0D07yOIx https://t.co/TK4RZtoIWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it from Insight for 2016.Happy Xmas from us!There are some great highlights on Mon @21.30, head to itunes or… https://t.co/yBmco38Dzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No witty bar chat then? https://t.co/XOz3NSRi9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire I grasping to  be glass half full here :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to have this attitude at his age! https://t.co/dDhmdt3kRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have just seen a BBC prog with the title: What Went Right in 2016? A definite podcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Insight by @RNZteresacowieuncovering some questionable employment practices for vulnerable workers https://t.co/wljCm6W9mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArielaZibiah Enough for this year! Hoping my ex sister in law is with her family in Frankfurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @janepatterson joins me to analyse the Cabinet reshuffle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With me ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune in @ 5 for @ rnznews special on Cabinet reshuffle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My investigation of the sex industry https://t.co/aPmamL0Hpd &amp; https://t.co/qs41L33t1n https://t.co/rIA6Lx60Bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh I hope so. Was just saying to whanau the other day it didn't exist in NZ https://t.co/aGaLs8k59Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reporting and video from Graeme Acton from trip earlier this year. https://t.co/XajZmRFwqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So pleased @InsightRNZ could give space to this material that @greyscale84 couldn't broadcast earlier..it's great! https://t.co/4m678zebnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is worrying https://t.co/OiOicccYvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously not helpful.. https://t.co/E2yzqxYkGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Wgtn virtually cut off by flooding and slips. That moon has a lot to answer for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally amazing and such a reassurance as everything rattled and rolled https://t.co/vllaxLdIl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine to Noon and https://t.co/7dmqKE7prR keeping on with updates on the quake damage. Midday special with Gyles Beckford and @nzpjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcPiercey Good to see you embracing twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a 40-hour week the answer to prisoner rehabilitation? https://t.co/6OhHJRxxU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be missed! https://t.co/GzjSxoxuCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VSAvolunteer Great to hear of @RoundSally 's work getting recognition https://t.co/SZTaa7WI6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you can sign up to get the latest from @InsightRNZ https://t.co/SZTaa7WI6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love hearing from the women themselves about their own experiences. including from the trans community. https://t.co/6wuVAgREk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stories from inside Paremoremo and the women's facility in Auckland. https://t.co/lRiUBrOu1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yes it is ..have already purchased turkey and Christmas cards on behalf of parent. https://t.co/dtp81xywXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the age of Tinder, why pay? https://t.co/VoHHdN56eR  and there are 2 other podcasts for your binge listening pleasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do wonder if people are re-evaluating what a once in 100 year flood means now? https://t.co/EpMxtLClEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On now, climate change and the homes at risk. @RNZSunday @wallacelchapman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a look; https://t.co/1N5CRK9eSp Then load up the podcasts for a good weekend listen. https://t.co/sp0D07yOIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@markcubey your farewell is an afternoon tea??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you caught Prt 2 of  "The Oldest Profession" on Night,s hear the other 2 progs: https://t.co/zsC94rrpbP or download all 3 @iTunesPodcasts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great investigation by @RNZteresacowie into long term   use of "contractors" who want to be staff and other employm… https://t.co/NiuZiT6DM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know why, but this makes me feel vaguely unwell https://t.co/lLGVuea6lQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Melbourne Cup draw not bad on performance and all go on colour- Big Orange and jockey dressed a bit like a bumble bee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is NZ's legal model over commercial sex working? Insight audio &amp; video online now. https://t.co/qs41L33t1n https://t.co/CwmHy97gVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more addition. Insight @RNZSunday then RNZ website and itunes https://t.co/PJSDJmHPuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad you enjoyed it. Do head back for the next two podcasts..and an @InsightRNZ on "The NZ Model" on Sun https://t.co/LAHDvGe7gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad stories but great resilience too https://t.co/UlgopwBG4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I think it's weird even now, the thought of have sex with a stranger," Hear Jenna's story https://t.co/lPECBitEM3 https://t.co/m0UueNOmFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Led by the nose https://t.co/Ou51kCcBJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great practical ideas to let wildlife and people co-exist safely @TCF_wildlife https://t.co/oVbD27KNpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a tough start in life, but Mimi has turned it all around. Have a listen. https://t.co/i1EJ11IdJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last part is up now! The Oldest Profession Part 3: From the Street https://t.co/lPECBitEM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are all broken china dolls" The Oldest Profession Part 2: The Business of Sex https://t.co/ZjctZ4jloo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a bit of a hiccup the podcasts are now on itunes  https://t.co/sp0D07yOIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Oldest Profession Part 2: Part 2 of the 3 part  podcast is live now. The Business of Sex https://t.co/ZjctZ4jloo @SexWorkerOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks ..I hope we achieved that. I think we did. https://t.co/H5riXVbSxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the kind words. https://t.co/EHrpY4FCFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first podcast in The Oldest Profession series goes live tomorrow. Pretty fascinating few weeks &amp; @greyscale84 took great photos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of questions still need answering on #homelessness. https://t.co/LYKK6MgFTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always great to have well reasoned input. https://t.co/8Oo1Te1oIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh..horrid weather so inside jobs loom large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there are free RNZ tea towels on offer..how can you resist? https://t.co/gJCAapkTxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just compiling this week's @InsightRNZ on NZ/ EU links and the descriptions of the conditions at the Battle of the… https://t.co/uu5LWPrNHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to be here. https://t.co/tAv1IMr87f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to declare I love the Great British Sewing New..for reality TV they are such kind generous people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland, mayors, water and turnout. It's all there. https://t.co/d1cFkqnaNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geoffsimmonz @InsightRNZ making it happen will be the thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @wallacelchapman 
for having me on this morning. Good to talk local government given their importance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counting programme for STV running faster than last time? https://t.co/yHFsVVgUW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New city mayors tell @insightrnz election special they plan engage to communities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One programme down..but wait there's more..8-9 @InsightRNZ special on Local Elections with @wallacelchapman on @RNZSunday]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>