<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a good week twitter friends, thanks for all your likes and RTs https://t.co/dJNx9wxf6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinneolhungdim And to you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Chinese New Year to all.
Gong Xi Fa Cai https://t.co/TnPrz8iPPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder that Spring is not that far away. The Loft, Haddington, East Lothian, Scotland https://t.co/Jvnz9T3gH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Window at the Loft coffee shop, Haddington, East Lothian, Scotland https://t.co/GmYHlKYQju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Straightforward' Brexit bill likely to be published on Thursday https://t.co/0QWglfBhHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Guardian view on the supreme court: a cheer for the judges https://t.co/A1u0qLbOOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rm123077 They always lighten the heart. Have a nice day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker He would be a genuine leader, speaks a lot of sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rm123077 In Scotland, just popping through the cold ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sun down at Aberlady, East Lothian, Scotland https://t.co/PKAlHbVo5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magnolias, something to look forward to.
Good weekend to all my twitter friends old and new. Thanks for all likes a… https://t.co/X46YzhiMVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker As one who has the layers of make-up every time you appear on screen, it's rather the kettle calling the pot black?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@citygirl74ever @alisonrobinso Yes, I thought you did, I just find the expression on Lincoln's face amusing.
Have a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonsnowC4 It's the Gods!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuggenheimPGC Beautiful smooth pan, always good to see this view]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wee bit nippy in Aberdeen this morning. https://t.co/YRAWasRNVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melbourne: young child among three dead after car ploughs into pedestrians in Bourke Street – live https://t.co/I35pjpOor2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what Lincoln is thinking? https://t.co/AFegStrNMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaBene7 @Biagio960 Very timely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rescuers battle to reach hotel in Italian avalanches https://t.co/xzUVGuxQUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy avalanche: 'Many dead' in hotel Rigopiano in Abruzzo       https://t.co/G9qELzxQZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the parking is non existent as here in China Town, Bangkok. Where else but in the Pharmacy! https://t.co/YfznNbRMis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheyne St, Stockbridge, Edinburgh https://t.co/4mksUEB0Jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stockbridge doors, Edinburgh 
Good morning everyone. https://t.co/K3EFvxedy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye @Biagio960 I think that a second referendum is almost certain now after the speech by Theresa May yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye Marvellous Streeton,  I love these paintings you tweet at this time. I can close my eyes and imagine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the rain. https://t.co/Dbw7VFGzRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommervillebbc Are the powers to be cutting back on expenses then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reindeer herd, Scottish Highlands.
Good Sunday to all followers, old and new. https://t.co/pOijGPMKiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJMacDSTV Just in case things don't work out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye Thanks for all your likes and RTs. Have a pleasant weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This little Angel seems to be crying because of the cold. https://t.co/sqWidhe4df]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCBreakfast Sorry I've had to switch off because of the dramatic wintry scenes from your report from Canterbury!
Warning please next time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like all the S92's are back in business today. https://t.co/q6lcwYByXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First light. https://t.co/bplrwFCkg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basil flower. https://t.co/eXfnJ8CCpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greyfriars Bobby, Edinburgh https://t.co/Pw2z4JPIk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCandrewkerr Thanks, I was looking forward to lunch!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold weather forecast for Scotland, goodnight all https://t.co/lhEaiweQe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scalpach correction, one S92 returning now https://t.co/28oahDZx5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scalpach Only one heli powered up as off 22.09 and nothing else flying at all! https://t.co/G81NR9wi4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurStramash @IainRWhite Much better perspective!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GucciPatrizia I do so like this art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommervillebbc  The P &amp; J is still reporting on supply vessels !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alex_Verbeek How sad, but that's nature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clematis 
Goodnight all, thanks for all your likes, retweets and new and old 
followers. https://t.co/EEUBYLfzMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@photographymd1 Please take care of yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cymbidium orchid https://t.co/SI20KMdJBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Temple, Ban Amphoe, Thailand https://t.co/EyyG1Ndn81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puffdude5 @theresamax Oh America, what have you done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EveningExpress And yet our marvellous council continue to grant permissions for new restaurants and hotels which will suffer the same fate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFPphoto @saidkhatib Certainly wrong image, check photographers account!
This must be shot of drone !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsBreak Who cares, no news day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommervillebbc Same when tourists come to Scotland on a dreich day, they love it, while we shelter inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern You take some beautiful images.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern But did it have " the answer"? (Dylan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern Take care! https://t.co/EOqH9m5CBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern Not so good, deep low pressure just south of you, should start to clear by midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Round House, Aberdeen Harbour https://t.co/x3KkKvIseZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new dawn, a new day and a new year.
Good fortune and health to old and new friends in 2017 https://t.co/PN035CFEgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aonghasphadraig Brilliant talent.
All the best to you and family in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merdeme67 Good evening to you also, Claudia.
Your likes and retweets mean a lot to me. Happy New Year as the hour approaches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@on_lothianbuses on board 44 around Meadowbank, ceiling falling down but carrying on! https://t.co/8jihkS2kh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye All the very best to you and Australia in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye I love the Australian landscapes, many thanks for all your retweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommervillebbc I will look forward to it's content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GucciPatrizia Buon giorno Patrizia, the old year soon to be gone, thank goodness.
Good health and fortune to you in 2017. Happy New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late afternoon glow, Victoria St, Edinburgh https://t.co/6yUNumHqa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detail from wall painting, Edinburgh, Scotland https://t.co/C3voUiVs8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colour to brighten your day! https://t.co/AtcoKB7ClO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCScotlandNews Engineers gone on holiday already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Aberdeen Library.
My thanks to all new and old followers, likes and retweets. https://t.co/IU4oLhY6Vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern Atmospheric shot, love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern I pray that it is .
Hope you are enjoying the festivities and good fortune in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern This year has seen so many great people pass away.
2016 will have left its mark with so much sadness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisavonSteijern Take care out there, snowing in parts of Scotland too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking Come on! This is hardly Breaking News! OAP still has cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CookCarluccio And to you sir, good fortune and health in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophiasstudio And to you also, enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lord_Sugar There is plenty of room for two on here, Trump and co! https://t.co/IXyykwoH30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GucciPatrizia Perfect selection!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GucciPatrizia Have a wonderful Christmas and New Year,  good fortune in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lackyliu Beautiful image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstieMAllsopp My goodness that's some cocktail!🙄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Did I really just hear your Royal Correspondent say that this was the story of the day!
Couple of OAP's with the cold?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimWonnacott Will this recording be transmitted on a particular channel or is it for in house? We are all missing you on the network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to the Cuillins, Isle of Skye, Scotland https://t.co/hXMjNYd7tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsBreak Don't worry, one will simply have to put one's Turkey in one's fridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all a Merry Christmas and Peaceful New Year.
Love and Good Health to you all! https://t.co/V7sypcTtkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussianEmbassy My thoughts are with you all at such a sad and painful time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4News We can only hope for a melt down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mido3bitte I can hear it too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duff_steven Not a lot to work on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wallyford Station, East Lothian, Scotland https://t.co/U4U4WnMbTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slipper orchid https://t.co/grH5dSQ8oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mido3bitte I have a pied wagtail comes every winter to my garden, he arrived last week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yebosfaye There was only ever one Marilyn, never to be repeated. Great memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STVNews What a sad year this has been, RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Town House, High Street, Old Aberdeen, Aberdeen.
Good weekend to all and thanks for retweets, likes and new followe… https://t.co/RJ62KPlg1p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>