<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nypost by weighing they mean they have a special app that calcs exactly how much money they will personally make off of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnTDolan @buddy_faro to be fair, he made Amy Schumer's job possible, because it wasn't talent that did that for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FERASS_FROM_NJ @artiequitter I had no problem with my drinking, other people did. #31yearsNextJuneiftheWorldDoesntBlowUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buddy_faro oh.  oh that hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buddy_faro no she used to look like this.  It's what living with him did to her. https://t.co/J3Vw3DyY1A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buddy_faro you'll lose you're appetite.  It's a picture of Chuck Schumer's wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinJacksonTBS good a licious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @buddy_faro I heard he was making a remake of "The Bitch is Back" https://t.co/sKW8lv9aTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CH Illustrations. Facebook. https://t.co/7NewIyjVmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler if people though ACA was any good, they wouldn't be bitching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler here's an EOB for one kid in my family plan.  Look at how much I'd have to be out of pocket before… https://t.co/aPkUd481Im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chelseashow @chelseahandler what's with the stupid outfit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler @IvankaTrump meanwhile you've already had plastic surgery.  You obviously find currency in the opinion of the men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze here's mine.  Here's the balance at the end of the year of what I still need to be out of pocket before… https://t.co/uTivLUklhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod here's mine. This EOB shows the balance of what I would have to pay before my $500/mo. premium covers… https://t.co/AtUA46ll7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Agreed.  Our constitution is not an international human rights doc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls your mistake was a blessing in disguise https://t.co/x98Bo8wrs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snopes Welfare Act-related entities, including research facilities that experiment on dogs and cats. True?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snopes Agriculture’s Animal Plant Health Inspection Service immediately take offline thousands and thousands of records related to Animal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snopes hey there's a group asking for money because "Today, without warning, the Trump administration ordered that the U.S. Department of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @AGOWA the Constitution is not an international human rights doc. Protection of our borders is constitutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryBrownGov while you've been focused on everything but your state... https://t.co/WM46sS1Jhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom while you have your eye on the world, here's what's happening where you are https://t.co/xZ3CIP478s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starbucks just sayin' if you have that many jobs... https://t.co/xZ3CIP478s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenjay1 @POTUS noooo.  the Constitution is not an international human rights doc.  wouldn't clap too hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGOWA So how do our laws extend to those coming into our country before they're here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski because a Clinton, who is above the law, could not...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN unless your name is Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorillaRadio_Tv @nyuniversity @Lauren_Southern @Gavin_McInnes @PrisonPlanet one reason the firm has a such a turn over rate. #dumbBells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorillaRadio_Tv @nyuniversity @Lauren_Southern @Gavin_McInnes @PrisonPlanet AP scholars we tutor, compute percentages and are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorillaRadio_Tv @nyuniversity @Lauren_Southern @Gavin_McInnes @PrisonPlanet events, can't field homework questions of the inner city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorillaRadio_Tv @nyuniversity @Lauren_Southern @Gavin_McInnes @PrisonPlanet highest honors who can't write well, can't identify historical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorillaRadio_Tv @nyuniversity @Lauren_Southern @Gavin_McInnes @PrisonPlanet this is why I work with brand new grads from best schools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Teamnguns JFK wouldn't let Sammy Davis at his inaugural ball because of his own personal racism so maybe not...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adirado29 @AnthonyCumia @TheRevBobLevy @StaceyPrussman then he'll be just like the guy who left office, ut oh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson: 01/17/1974...Robyn Hilton https://t.co/tX4vknXUsA via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@exjon and bras.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nordstrom seems you should be kinder to her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nordstrom way to go for dropping her line.  Thanks to her, her father didn't EO LGBT rights back to 1950s https://t.co/ixlVcvfaLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NorthwellHealth @jmolinet I can't afford healthcare.  look at the cash I have to put out until expensive insurance… https://t.co/njGgXYmE5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaibatsuNews @JayCaruso @ChelseaClinton Alas, if @GovernorVA "supported" the campaign of his loved one, this would have been averted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews she's can adopt them all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcpnews :( Lousy world man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton there's a misspeak and there's a lie(s).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncleSamsChild @TheRevBobLevy no caption darlin'. My hero. Love him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynusCantwell @TheRevBobLevy does NY Mayor drop her in this story, too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissLizzyNJ @POTUS these are terrorists. Nat'l guard 'em.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heminator @washingtonpost Honest mistakes happen and she copped to it unlike subject in your non-parallel https://t.co/CJxzvhI7uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer calls flight attendant who told him to turn off cell phone 'bitch' https://t.co/eY6TDW68SK via @nypost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeJorgensen5 @SenSanders Pelosi is nearly 80. Feinstein is 83. Mrs. Doubtfire and Greedy Old Men go to Washington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benshapiro wasn't the DNC candidate kicked out of the running for even questioning such things of his religious opponent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Are you serious? Do you hear yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders but the @DNC candidate was excluded for running for even questioning such things. #DoppioFacia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDCGlobal @CDCgov don't have the children of smokers have cancer markers, as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat no sh*t. Tuition is ridiculous and these schools crank out people who perform at 10th grade level, tops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat @govHowardDean they aren't about hate and violence? This group threaten children of conservative reporters in tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddow @MSNBC So Maddow can now buy a gun! Air high five!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepStevenSmith @LindaSuhler @POTUS when these guys show up torching stuff, send out National Guard and bust 'em.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @Nordstrom @IvankaTrump you used her when you needed her like elitist politicians who were glad to be associated with a Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @Nordstrom @IvankaTrump great stores like @Kmart @Sears places where the working class shop I hope welcome her stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nordstrom it makes sense that you distance yourself from @IvankaTrump because you're not the store for the working class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman the mic any more.  the twat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman two words that will make you scratch your head and wonder: Judd Apatow. Don't let him have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman I have to leave now for one of my two jobs to support my fam because I don't f*ck men to get by but here are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman or girl versions of tired movie series. It's the same every where. leftism ruins education, art and economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman they're so ordinary. They have to re-boot other people's ideas. Not a literate, artful one in the lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman she's in politics. Typical needs to be in a group to be affirmed mindset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman eh they're replaceable. She's a dependent personality. He's in comedy, she's in comedy. He's in politics,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRevBobLevy @SarahKSilverman her "boy"friend quit acting (I had no idea he was in it) to be an activist, which means loudmouth narcissist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider @CounterMoonbat @Nordstrom cuts both ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat @NFL @SuperBowl I think the same people who ran HRC's campaign, are running halftime. What a waste of money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kokomoschmoe you said name them...so I named them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat @HeyGirlGaga @ConversationEDU I am going to stir things up. https://t.co/yGl7ufu3U0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CounterMoonbat She has a face made for radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @Cernovich @JuddApatow you know we've never seen Adam Lanza and him in a room together...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvelynBeaHall @gatewaypundit @Cernovich @JuddApatow who wants to bet this guy has to explain his side of things, multiple times a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @Cernovich @JuddApatow isn't he the guy who bumps working comedians to hog the mike? #rockstarsyndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dennis Miller's rant on Hillary Clinton https://t.co/k2FDo57gnF via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch talk about little hands..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blackmare00 seriously I don't a shit who they are because I do lump you in with them. Ciao.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blackmare00 Bernie, it figures.  You're an antifa lover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blackmare00 from your reply?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blackmare00 by not sending out the cops to stop it. @UCBerkeley and @JesseArreguin condoned it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longwall26 @tedcruz you and @joss must have the creepiest secret picture stash ever. #fantasizesaboutanimalsandstrongmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blackmare00 It was condoned by the Berkeley community, the University and the town when the campus cops and cops didn't stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein who is richer - you or Pelosi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRichardLewis at least the free speech terrorists last night had the decency to hide their faces.  Sheesh, no manners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei FAKE news. kind of like Chris Suprun was a 9/11 hero - not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayCaruso @RedState she boycotted a few classes, apparently..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heritage @LindaSuhler Back in the 50s, another gay Jew was under siege for controversial writing.  https://t.co/Wp28bvLotw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtyAbsatz @JesseArreguin wonder how much he got paid, if anything, to look the other way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @benshapiro you're not by definition.  So the definition of legitimate decides that issue for all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @benshapiro except for when you publish this https://t.co/gZ0wycF7dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NFL @nflnetwork I hope so.  Let them ruin everything - the infestation. https://t.co/nUdp6F8K77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afezio1952 @FoxNews that's because @sarahksilverman is banging Michael Sheen. If he was into monster trucks, she would be too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jparkABC @WhipHoyer @POTUS @TurnbullMalcolm did Whip also call Mexico and promise we won't invade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jparkABC @WhipHoyer @POTUS @TurnbullMalcolm does he know it's true or out of school fiction? interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseArreguin  If this had happened today, we'd be waking up to City Lights destroyed https://t.co/Wp28bvtN4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseArreguin Thanks for taking us back to the 1950s where gay Jews are silenced for their controversial speech https://t.co/Wp28bvLotw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fox5sandiego sure. you guys called it fake news when they were against Hillary.  that was the other way]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>