<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kirstastrophe @AdHocFiction Yes, deadline tonight. E-book will be online tomorrow morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kirstastrophe @AdHocFiction Glad you're in again, Kirsty. Looking forward to reading the e-book tomorrow. Good luck. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop! Many congratulations Jess. @JessKiddHerself #amwriting #shortstories #flashfiction https://t.co/LkMis9OwIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPersaud @ambitmagazine @WoolfJames All the best, James. #amwriting #amreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SalnPage I'll give you two out of three for that. #Meatloaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dream job. #gamejobs #backyourself #hiltcareers https://t.co/tLTm9ks0qO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachaelDunlop @LouiseWalters12 @BaileysPrize @FMelroseWriter You'll be mesmerised by the time you're finished. Shattered my soul! Nicely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cal1 @AdHocFiction Great! Look forward to seeing it in the e-book tomorrow. #votingtoday #readingandvotingtomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lindahill50Hill All brick walls are currently occupied by others banging heads. I'll try to find you a space. #resist #frustration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseWalters12 @BaileysPrize @FMelroseWriter Yes, yes, mine too. #Midwinter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Seamus, if only your words could transcend the misery the world has been plunged into by ONE TYRANT. #resist https://t.co/jccrSK44FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharonmariej One giant hug. xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to hear it, Sharon. #GraceEllaBook2 https://t.co/U9xUCnOsGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of memories here. In the '60s we used to walk with our father from car park on Castle St. to his office on Dam… https://t.co/bL73HLL6tP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these 150-word stories. Mine's in here. #amreading https://t.co/jFjqTPXgxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HouseofSecrets by @LyndaStacey on my kindle. Let's see how long it takes for it to wriggle its way to the top of my TBR. #fittestbookwins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This
Should be
A #pyramid poem
But Twitter rules make
it difficult to build a pyramid
of left aligned text within 1… https://t.co/LBrVrxKRXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halfway through #WhiteFeathers by @susan_lanigan. Crazy about and captivated by this story and Susan's skillful writing. #amreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just read again @voimaoy's beautiful #YearsLikeSnow in @vignettereview's Winter Issue. Gorgeous! #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the characteristics of malignant narcissism is zero empathy. Will this tyrant be allowed to continue? https://t.co/psT7lWdxPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thislifegood Except then of course, as expected, she was promptly fired. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susan_lanigan Needs must. Breaking all sorts of rules here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is completely fascinating! Have a look. #talent https://t.co/WizYMbf6yU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizzy11268 So sorry, Liz. Hugs. xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impeach Impeach Impeach Impeach Impeach Impeach #sixwordstory https://t.co/k1jaNxwA7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But they don't really mean it. It's a Loganair computer glitch causing the crowd problem. https://t.co/8WPRFj4EUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanya_landman Yea, he looked in the mirror and it was the best he could come up with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malignant narcissism is an incurable condition. https://t.co/WyCyaJ9NwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mollegato You may be able to help/pass this on. xx https://t.co/EmCDH9hN3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely there is a competent medical professional out there who can certify this insanity. https://t.co/0ASSo9eNFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PM_Jordan Well, that's the $64M question isn't it, Peter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little gem from @AEWeisgerber #flashfiction https://t.co/IueJcYLMfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabesley Oh, good for you, Laura. That's quite the achievement. All the best in the competition. Rooting for you. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judehwriter @scooterwriter Congratulations, Jude! Best of luck for the next bit. #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already looking forward to getting 300 words into MC57 for @DanaFaletti to judge. #sharpenspencil #amwriting… https://t.co/ZAo8YAmi6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've signed this. #resist https://t.co/2XRqexJppd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poloconghaile Highly recommend Ristorante Rinnuccini city centre for an amazing Italian meal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanaFaletti Yours was a beautiful story. Well-deserved win. #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ewanandsmith Thanks, Ewan. #positivethinking #keepwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scooterwriter Thrilled for you, Diane. Well done for the double! I didn't make the list this time. Will try again next round. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad face. I didn't make the Flash 500 long list. Congratulations to fellow flash writers who did! I'll try again next round. #pullssocksup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @EndaKennyTD needs to go back to school to learn this. https://t.co/cX14HjsdTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jounwin They do, they do. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fuzzynick I think your title is brilliant. Not sure what another ending would be like but this one works for me. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You did, Caleb and we all enjoyed reading it on MC56 @MicrocosmsFic. Well done. Great story! #amwriting… https://t.co/MNaDzT48bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @JustinRose99 for coming in tied fourth place @FarmersInsOpen @PGATOUR. Congrats to winner @littleJRmaza.2 x eagles clinched it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic winning story by @DanaFaletti. Congrats to SM @billmelaterplea, HM @firdausp RU Angelique Pacheco. Well d… https://t.co/sAZieWEggw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling on Aaron Sorkin to rescue the world by extending 'The West Wing'  #series. Create Season 8 &amp; make it REALIT… https://t.co/ZML5ZLGvb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do take a look at this glorious piece of captivating neuroticism by @fuzzynick. Top marks, Nick. Love it.… https://t.co/LAj7AdFzP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feclarkart Fine, thanks. I always enjoy your fabulous photos. xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feclarkart You captured the light perfectly, Frances. Lovely photo. #amwriting #amtryingtofindtimetoread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may It's not a row. It's an illegal order, made against the Constitution of the USA. Tell it like it is.… https://t.co/kJRdvWHsrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The orange guy's state visit to the UK is at risk due to a row with Prince Charles over climate change. Good! #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undetected trump. Lower case t for a lower than low tyrant #horrorprompt 81 https://t.co/Nr8W8HJSsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many congratulations, Vanessa. A wonderful feeling! #amwriting #flashfiction https://t.co/QjueG2ufyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rooting for you @JustinRose99. Just 2 off the lead. Let's go. #fanstuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My words are in here alongside some wonderful flash writers. #amwriting #flashfiction https://t.co/2zomJj1e63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it affects Britons https://t.co/zbuBaicVDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zevonesque I made a decision on Nov 8th 2016 not to visit the USA again until there's a new occupant of 1600 Pennsylvania Ave. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The survivors will rummage relentlessly through the #ashes. They will find the orange evidence and hold it aloft fo… https://t.co/JykKQvKGeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankdaad Oh great! Welcome to The Angry Hourglass, Frank. See you there later. Skates on. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If HM The Queen at 90 doesn't need help stepping back down the steps of the Cenotaph, why would TM need help for fo… https://t.co/QywQMcgvQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clock is on. #amwriting https://t.co/2zomJj1e63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@val868594 @raisenutrition @EDUCOGYMGALWAY @WWIreland You GO, girl! So happy for you. DM me the date so I can diary it for sending wishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@val868594 @raisenutrition @EDUCOGYMGALWAY @WWIreland I'm truly in awe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fhayesmccoy Any tips as to how to 'unsee' this picture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@val868594 @raisenutrition @EDUCOGYMGALWAY @WWIreland WOW! Amazing stuff, Val. Well done you. Cracking job. #takeabow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 16 fab flash tales up on MC56 https://t.co/s0Emhv5CVx. Why not take a look &amp; vote for your favourites. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost all of the TSA, Customs &amp; Immig people I've met are immigrants (they told me) so what say they to implementing this illegal order?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But he's VP now. He doesn't care any more. #joinedtheturncoatarmy https://t.co/qNvx611O33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a pain so #acute as that felt while watching one person undo decades of progress? 
Yes. 
The pain of inact… https://t.co/6slzxvBUWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone could let me know the date of Impeachment Day asap so i can clear the diary, that would be great. Thanks. #ithastobedone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah but that was seven months ago. You can hardly expect him to hold the same view now. #turncoat https://t.co/4akQSdfGRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_stevie @MicrocosmsFic This one is a beauty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_stevie @MicrocosmsFic You did! and I loved it and I had to keep checking back to the start to see if that was really you! 😉#amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh, this is a mysterious little gem from Danny Farmer. #75words #flashfiction https://t.co/Lzxn2QvvKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 10% into #WhiteFeathers by @susan_lanigan and already loving Eva Downey's story. #amreading #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SalnPage And while you're at it, give Sal time to enter @MicrocosmsFic &amp; @CrackedFlashFC &amp; The Angry Hourglass. Thanks! #fromAlva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feclarkart Oh I love this. Gorgeous, Frances. #amwriting #amreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to get the polish out. #amwriting #amreading https://t.co/W0YjliAeRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaMulvey Happy new home, Lydia. Hope you make lots of lovely new memories there. #getmilk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at this dark beauty from @AEWeisgerber #flashfiction https://t.co/s4yHx008BP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop! Well done, Anne. Delighted for you. Off to read it. #amreading #amwriting https://t.co/s4yHx008BP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheAdderstane by @KreskaFiction is now on my kindle. It's in a long queue but already considering jumping. #amreading #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop! Congratulations Avalina. Looking forward to it. #amreading #amwriting https://t.co/fUReaPXyj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't call it the #graveyard shift for nothing, Fred thought as he chopped up the remains and fed them into th… https://t.co/pKwPswZqVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Friday again! Time for 300 words to @MicrocosmsFic #amwriting #flashfiction https://t.co/dEu2Aq25Rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_james1 Great! Delighted to hear that, Neil. Good luck with your submissions. #amwriting #amreading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many congratulations to the three winners here. I had a piece in this competition. Will send it out again.… https://t.co/c9m3N5h5JU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scooterwriter YAY! Delighted for you, Diane. Well done. #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinlaysonPalmer @ScribblersBlog @writers_hq @catwrote @jmgatford @fictionalsarah I feel the same way about all comps I enter. Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaureenLangloss @Wigleaf Well done, Maureen. It's always a great lift. #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinlaysonPalmer @ScribblersBlog @writers_hq @catwrote @jmgatford @fictionalsarah Many congrats! Best of luck for the next bit. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aoife_m_ @CompassionateCP @MilfordLmkCC @HiberniaCollege  Congratulations, Aoife. #compassionateeducators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@collinson26 @BathFlashAward Thanks, Christine. Even when I don't make the lists I love seeing familiar friendly names on there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fuzzynick I went all out and bought a 3 piece suite! #amwriting #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've followed @OneforIreland. Have you? https://t.co/iuZVwKZjft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoop! Wonderful news for you, Sharon. So deserved. #onwardtoBook2 https://t.co/dyokbAea74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 300-word pieces are in here. Fingers crossed for the long list. #amwriting #flashfiction https://t.co/oYOwnKsKy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may. You're a woman &amp; Prime Minister of the UK, with the power to resist &amp; insist. Instead, you do this? N… https://t.co/56QJuBUUI3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>