<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2017 Royal Rumble Match #RoyalRumble https://t.co/mecHEzNvTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Champion AJ Styles vs. John Cena #WWEChampionship #RoyalRumble https://t.co/uYI7znhFV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Cruiserweight Champion Rich Swann vs. Neville #205Live #RoyalRumble https://t.co/NJNDTXxBgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were the surprises? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is the champion coming out first? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Universal Champion Kevin Owens vs. Roman Reigns (Chris Jericho will be suspended in a shark cage above the ring… https://t.co/rfu2Mw1whx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry why is the cruiserweight title not being defended before the Universal title? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taker's gonna have to be number 1, 2 or 30 with that walkway #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_CMwalsh @paddypower @JCLayfield he's their mole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower @JCLayfield he announces the SmackDown matches, will be on later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RockBottomRadio Charlottes so bloody dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cole, the WWE Championship was literally up for grabs last year #RoyalRumble @MichaelCole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw Women's Champion Charlotte Flair vs. Bayley #RoyalRumble https://t.co/BArAMTllKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this 4 more hours? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I can remember much of the Rumbles since Cena's return #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice! short and sweet, take notes dummies in the locker room #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31 when he won that #RoyalRumble in the Alamodome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only bad thing about that is it means about 50 more Cesaro/Sheamus matches #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swiss19 really? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously they do the commercial in the middle of every match on every kickoff, get the fuck over it #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently, there were 60,477 there in 1997, surely they should have been beating that easily #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw Tag Team Champions Cesaro &amp; Sheamus vs. Luke Gallows &amp; Karl Anderson (Kickoff Match) 1 #RoyalRumble https://t.co/q3kClZRKNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know why I expected them to make some sort of effort with the stage #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is HBK still involved with NXT? #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess Rollins is back in! https://t.co/79W6j1aSeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet HBK's raging they didn't let him wear the stupid hat #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NXT Champion Shinsuke Nakamura vs. Bobby Roode #NXTTakeOver: San Antonio https://t.co/YL6vW19z9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NXT Women’s Champion Asuka vs. Nikki Cross vs. Billie Kay vs. Peyton Royce (Fatal 4-Way Match) #NXTTakeOver: San An… https://t.co/6uSE5FR60I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NXT Tag Team Champions #DIY vs. The Authors of Pain #NXTTakeOver: San Antonio https://t.co/bhna4UeKpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right time to catch up on all things #NXTTakeOver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Randy Orton favourite to win the #RoyalRumble, that makes zero fucking sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Callum some idiot what 12 year old knows what a condom is or knows how to use them? #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyUK would want to lower their price so if the Discovery channels, Eurosport, TLC etc. won't be available from February 1st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wrong housemates really have been evicted this series save for a few #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical #cbb not to show Spencer bullying Kim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@castlepalooza is there a date or a rough date even for when those offers end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stacys just mad Jess has more of a chance with Callum than her #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who does Luke Shaw have to ride to get a game at this club? #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the story behind the little man badge on the boys jackets on soccer Saturday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfromct no worse than HIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfromct not really literally it's a soap opera, its entertainment just like the apprentice she's nobody than HIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie O' Hara is nothing but a washed up adultering creepy fat fuck #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That prick José better not offload Luke Shaw #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cole contradicted himself so many times on #WWEUKCT he was awful, do like McGuinness though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKurtAngle now there's a headliner #wwehof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWE @espn @RealKurtAngle It's about damn time, close to 11 years was too long for Kurt to be away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PWCoverageNews @WWENetwork Is this just new accounts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that #WWENetwork offer only for new subscribers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still maintain that stunt was set up Friday night to get @austinarmacost out of the house #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the crack with the #WWEUKCT how long does the show last tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit reading what's happened in Austin's life since last time he was in #cbb makes me feel really sorry for him and now get why hes that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitchell Cole will hardly make it back in time to be anyway prepared for #RAW Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanHGShore @bbuk and Austin sticking his finger up James' bum is alright then is it and to call him a dickhead or dick cheese, whatever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is a fucking nonce #BBUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn Angie Best went in on the Nolan sister, dead right too #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Communism_Kills shut the fuck up! who are you to say who can and can't wear whatever the hell they want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it not made kind of obvious that Undertaker is a #SDLive guy, why is he appearing on #RAW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tomking1989 Hard work pays off. Dreams come true. Bad times don't last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go stick 4 past Chelsea now please Spurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AGH lads... Honey G flopped what the hell is that about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's Mike Goldberg going to go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cody Rhodes is such a little bitch, definitely a bottom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha fuck off they must be joking! https://t.co/QKD7muCpJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelElgin25 but its not a sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT #WrestleMania card is the biggest piece of  monkey crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also where are the Slammys? #RAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the chances of anything of note taking place on #RAW tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Mcgowan I've been looking and can't seem to find a definitive answer apparently he's a Liverpool fan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Mcgowan whys that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Universal Champion Kevin Owens vs. U.S. Champion Roman Reigns #UniversalTitle #WWERoadblock https://t.co/93VebSjUwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw Women’s Champion Sasha Banks vs. Charlotte Flair (30-Minute WWE Iron Man Match) #IronManMatch #WWERoadblock https://t.co/FmsxEgxGfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thank you Neville" if that doesn't show you how bad the cruiserweights have been handled so far I don't know what will #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE Cruiserweight Champion Rich Swann vs. TJ Perkins vs. The Brian Kendrick #205Live #WWERoadblock https://t.co/4erkpRMBOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well Rollins/Jericho was a massive let down #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Rollins vs. Chris Jericho #WWERoadblock https://t.co/aIQhV91JsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STUPID! #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can no match end properly #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the tag team champions #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw Tag Team Champions The New Day vs. Cesaro &amp; Sheamus #TagTeamTitles #WWERoadblock https://t.co/Z3p6zMky9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Cass vs. Rusev (Kickoff Match) #WWERoadblock https://t.co/Q36GyBV5zD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenArnold1984 @thewadekeller @mitchellpwtorch who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say this all the time but @WWE really needs a geography lesson #WWERoadblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darts is some joke of a racket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those are some seriously crappy matches Sky have for Boxing Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clown https://t.co/jCddyftZ6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will fight anyone who disagrees with Conor McGregor winning #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Phil Jones you absolute mug come up with your own celebration #kingfukick #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Eric Bailly on the pitch means we're probably conceding a goal #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol... Newcastle fans wont be happy, Alan Pardew just said he's never been at a big club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Klopp criticises the Nevilles for criticising Karrius, then drops Karrius and brings back Mignolet, makes him look a bit stupid no? #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho destroying Michael Owen is the best #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt and Freddie are goals #xfactorfinal #XFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kurt Angle is so going to be in this year's #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would have added Kenny to that too  but has he actually re-signed yet or offered anything? #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickie James on same brand as John Cena and Nikki Bella, really? #SDLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of that interview was disgraceful. They've made a choice to live that way says @AndreGray7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JoshMurphy_ hear the end of it? They've made a "choice" to live that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should that not be the team playing spurs on Sunday? #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CuttingEdge is better when the guests at least act as if they all hate each other]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>