<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#Breakfast is served 😊 finally tracked down a cheeky double of one of my favourite whiskies.… https://t.co/HIZ3xGHMSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selection of gorgeous spiedini from grollasydney. We've got:
- grilled citrus octopus, picked… https://t.co/Bg1g2Y3gq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories of the great @belgrovewhisky tasting at oakbarrel last week. Apart from being delicious… https://t.co/fi5I0I9UjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying like a mister to track one of these down in Australia. No luck. Have been dreaming about… https://t.co/NxtxPLPaY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to introduce you all to #maltwhisky. Hmmm remind you of anyone!? 
-
That's right, he's… https://t.co/hTY0O4iukb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The delicious smoked beef shortrib from grollasydney. Eat it in burger form or "sul piatto" and… https://t.co/qiDJBWWg9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an enjoyable evening, with the opportunity to meet the legendary Peter Bignall of… https://t.co/cn1NIKoA1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This club sandwich isn't going to eat itself, but first, a negroni.… https://t.co/Jhym5RbPaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic combination, crying out for a full bodied dram. We're stepping up our offering this year… https://t.co/qdqBHtnk0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Crew-tine" burger from @the_chew_crew_1 at their Maroubra popup today. A rich, indulgent… https://t.co/3hewvTUITC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An absolute pleasure to imbibe, "O" Gin from kispirits was featured at @mattywhisk's recent "Out… https://t.co/nkbOgtCROj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An enjoyable afternoon today, spent learning about the Berry Bros. and Rudd spirit collection… https://t.co/qYNQbBb1c2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 is shaping up to be a great year for Whisky Uncovered. We are so honoured to have met this… https://t.co/CvqpADTetr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basketcase68 hi tony, hope all is well. This was Grolla in Cremorne. Paolo and Lek have created something pretty special!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not often you see drenched lamb served as part of a degustation, much less at an Italian… https://t.co/eTt1VMDPYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Event photos are almost ready but for now another candid shot thanks to our friends at… https://t.co/F82wtGSIuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really enjoyable New Year's Eve as I squeezed in one more dego at the new grollasydney… https://t.co/gvRNYs9zfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was an honour partnering with some of the country's best specialty chefs on Saturday for… https://t.co/kfkoRNttGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exclusive a.w.a.s_ bottling, these two are too special to open right now, so I'm just going… https://t.co/EaewDeGNmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a big week for us with our most ambitious event yet fast approaching. But ambition is good,… https://t.co/xov5eJHW0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Event menus with tasting notes are back from the printers. Not baaad!! Excited to share these… https://t.co/zxApTbYgSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Whisky Uncovered, we LOVE our guests! The famous WU prize box is making a triumphant return… https://t.co/bPEkXmEyT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boys from Down and Out are doing great things out in the West - will have to make an trek… https://t.co/S8HpANSkW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast becoming @mattywhisk 's "go-to" cocktail when we're not drinking whisky, the Negroni is a… https://t.co/mcpmmazIEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollingsworth @Sydney_Kids @OmptyAustralia thanks Tony! Should be a great event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food is so often art, like this mango kulfi with pistachio and rose petals. When it comes to… https://t.co/AcFT1t5prR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're excited to announce that @mattywhisk will be continuing our partnership with sushi master… https://t.co/K212ye3PVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're thrilled to announce that our December event - "Out of Kilter" is now fully booked; in… https://t.co/rddavhCJWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experimenting with new flavour combinations. This was apple, blue cheese , caramelised onion and… https://t.co/66KW4pG8xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Whisky Uncovered, authenticity is so important; we are proud of the events we run and take… https://t.co/YuwGQxlJvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets are now on sale for Whisky Uncovered's final event for 2016 - "Out of Kilter!". 

Details: https://t.co/LpaO18jQuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When friends drop around, bearing gifts...
.
This is the @lagavulinwhisky 8 year old. Matured in… https://t.co/P4141RfmVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sliders, sliders as far as the eye can see! These beauties, rustled up by our good friends at… https://t.co/pv39IMWqmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to catch up with the.brad - manager of the Cremorne Store - today in preparation for… https://t.co/fSvZtpMjde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gorgeous sunny Spring day in Sydney today and what better way to spend it than at our iconic… https://t.co/pq6NghxXFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good times kittyhawksyd in the lead up to Sydney bar week With dd00sd and sharond999! Thanks for… https://t.co/j0Hzy4I7Tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 weeks until Whisky Uncovered: Boilermakers. We're excited to announce several local partnerships. Read more here: https://t.co/or2XnXxeqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A splash of red": our dress code for the next @mattywhisk Boilermakers event. An opportunity… https://t.co/M5kJzKYq9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whisky Uncovered's September Boilermakers event has SOLD OUT. Thank you for your support of… https://t.co/Du4UiE81q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whisky Uncovered has a new website! Check us out at:
https://t.co/3mzYB4j6A6 #whisky #events #degustation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeforWhisky I have to say the new ticket system is a little disappointing. Not that it's a bad Whisky, but a lottery? Cmon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just poured first ever "silver needle". Will be great as palate cleanser. Thanks @heartwoodtas  4the recommendation! https://t.co/wmYE0enX1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger it's pretty delicious. Liquid candy, so sweet, with air it is very bourbon-y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas what was he inspiration for the name "epiphany at the lakes"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger awesome, thank you very much :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger thanks Jonathan , sold out nation wide apparently per their call centre. If you do spot one pls shout!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To my whisky friends , does anyone know where I'd find some Habiki harmony for sale in Sydney ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whisky_nerd happy new year mate, Looking to acquire some Whisky minis to give as prizes for upcoming whisky lunch , know where I can find?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas fancy a trip to hobart Tony? Heh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas all this time I had no idea. Will do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas no worries. Is it still possible to visit the distillery during that time ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas what a pity! Was hoping to duck in for a few purchases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas hello Tim, we're down in Hobart December 9-12 for cricket,are you around? Would be good to catch up and check out operations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas great exhibit as always Tim, a highlight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great afternoon, thank you @OakBarrelSydney - best Whisky Fair yet full of interesting exhibitors. http://t.co/YtW5xPNktM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger @OakBarrelSydney looking forward to it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OakBarrelSydney reading about NZ having their own 25 yo single malt now; will they be exhibiting at this year's whisky fair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dontgiveadram haha I think they look cool! Were relegated to filling out an joint form and crossing our fingers :) hope to c u there !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dontgiveadram fancy !! Guessing only blogger Celebs get these ? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ardbeg_com received email re ardbeg day but no mention of Sydney event on your website. Where do we sign up ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta check this place out soon, hear they make an awesome G&amp;T . ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeforWhisky Actually not such a random question after all. Well spotted :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger yet to try!! Looking fwd to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBADailyLineups wade playing. ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeforWhisky great review, thanks Martin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeforWhisky yes indeed ; that could be all that's left from a 750ml allocation ;) enjoy !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heartwoodtas what did you think Tim? Cracked mine last night and loved it. Longer finish than I expected. Sat on a dram for an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dontgiveadram hopefully that actually IS whisky 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskysec @whiskyledger it came from Laph Themselves via FedEx , so I guess neither ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiskyledger awesome ! Thanks . @whiskysec ordered one bottle of laph last week and got stung . :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 that's a shame, but best of luck t you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 love your work, and the Twitter announcements are brilliant thanks will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 is that around the wrong way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 lol reading the future ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 wish I knew how to DM lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 do we have to contact you separately for tips ? I'm confused :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Will_767 thanks will, line for GCS/geelong 167.5 now within 2 min? Still take unders ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gourmantic recommendation I mean of course !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gourmantic may I ask for a nice and not too exp restaurant for dinner in Newtown/enmore? Heading 2 icehouse concert after - party of 6! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realtimeresearc I can help if you still need people !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whisky_nerd sounds fantastic!!! Very curious now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whisky_nerd just saw the exciting news re AR. Congrats mate! Can't wait to hear more and let me know if I can help with anything !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious Post-tasting BBQ delights @jazzcitydiner , pairing with some mackmyra; thanks @Whisky_nerd @OakBarrelSydney http://t.co/Vtwdv2fAaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OakBarrelSydney see you tonight ! Excited about '76 laph   #understatement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PocketPunter thoughts on France/Albania mate ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeforWhisky @OakBarrelSydney see you there ?? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of the rest masterclass @OakBarrelSydney announced. Saw '76 Laphroiag, then when I regained consciousness, bought a ticket. YEWWW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PocketPunter mate, respect your self control and focus to get back to black, but 5k turnover for $80 , wow , not sure I could do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsbetcomau going to follow example of other bookies and refund admire rakti bets from the Cup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OakBarrelSydney @Whisky_nerd best
Of the rest is where I'd like to be . Keep
Us posted :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any details on upcoming whisky tastings you mentioned at B&amp;B event? 1970's Laphroiag has me salivating :) @OakBarrelSydney @Whisky_nerd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OakBarrelSydney left my baby Bunnahabhain on the table :( guess it's "the Angels share" now :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz City diner bring it! http://t.co/wcUm9AqUHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bold and the beautiful tasting @OakBarrelSydney - bring it !! Wheres Ron Moss? http://t.co/HwR0RZeX9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the Bold and the Beautiful whisky tasting @OakBarrelSydney next week! Any chance of a Ron Moss guest appearance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsbetcomau what about a justin refund oh Whincup win bets? The guy ran out of fuel on the last lap..
CMON!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whisky_nerd what the ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whisky_nerd thank you sir !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning @Whisky_nerd at recent heartwood event you mentioned a cheese shop in the city where you source your product, what was it ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PocketPunter saved 8 match points,
Ridiculous . Could have been very messy :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>