<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Top health bureaucrat who oversees RAH &amp; TQEH ousted from @SAHealth. Expect more from CEO Vickie Kaminski soon. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious two crash at Lyndoch. Three people injured. Major crash notified. #9newscomau https://t.co/I0llA8osC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@alpsa ruling out further holiday trading reforms. Says balance is right now, changes would hurt thriving independ… https://t.co/8Z1l1lx0Ds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SALibMedia call for public holiday trading reform, call current system "crazy." Harvey Norman stores partially op… https://t.co/JUKE17bt05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Two new faces into shadow cabinet, David Speirs &amp; @stephanknoll. Out Duncan McFetridge &amp; Steven Griffiths… https://t.co/1OrYcrv4vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shadow cabinet reshuffle time for @marshall_steven. Details soon. Another piece of the 2018 election puzzle falls into place. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human error found to be the most likely cause of FMC generator failure, which caused the death of embryos. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency services blackout report released. 62 recommendations, inc CBD evacuation plan. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report into emergency services response to SA blackout released soon. @SAHealth's look into Flinders Med generator fail also due #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work continues on overpass fix this morning. But South Road remains closed to traffic. #9newscomau https://t.co/oVpu885UJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there goes the Trans-Pacific Partnership. #9newscomau #auspol  https://t.co/JPW4lL4tB7 https://t.co/Ec8vB0tarE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump. #Inauguration https://t.co/C759reRdkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Deal done. Nurses call off industrial action over ward closure @ RAH. @SAHealth reopening some beds.… https://t.co/pXXvzWBb9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: @SAHealth confirms two more two cases of Legionnaires’ disease this week. Total now six in cluster. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meetings between @ANMFSA &amp; @SAHealth have finished. Is there a deal to stave off industrial action? Update due soon. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@9NewsAdel @_SarahHancock is on the ground in Melbourne. Follow her for updates. https://t.co/TtRl0cBv6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santos confirms 580 jobs were axed in 2016. Places lost cross business &amp; not just in SA. Firm looking to "build &amp; grow" in 2017. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SAHealth vs @ANMFSA legal stoush to be heard @ 1:30pm. Dept wants to block nurses' action. All about bed changes @ RAH &amp; TQEH. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal showdown. @ANMFSA &amp; @SAHealth to square-off in Industrial Relations Commission tomorrow over RAH/TQEH bed changes. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SA's unemployment rate for Dec drops from 7% to 6.8%. But remains highest in Aust. National rate up to 0.1% to 5.8%. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior RAH docs in snap meeting. Fresh concern about ward closure. AMA demands it's reopened. Nurses talking industrial action...#9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks from all sides of politics to outgoing Heysen MP Isobel Redmond. Race on to fill her coveted Hills seat in 2… https://t.co/qCgr88iR0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdwardGodfrey9 fancy taking a toboggan flat out down this thing? https://t.co/ksRHwCmOmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial action looming over plans by @SAHealth to cut beds at RAH &amp; TQEH. Nurses "appalled." #9newscomau https://t.co/P4h91UAJkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alpsa noted. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Malinauskas well that didn't take long!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A taste of the contraband found in SA prisons by Corrections staff and the dog squad. #9newscomau https://t.co/07RzlfymIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The four-legged force hunting drugs in our prisons. More on them tonight @9NewsAdel #9newscomau https://t.co/vUFpJhqGQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moral support provided by @SMullighan...opting to watch from a safe distance. #9newscomau https://t.co/SB9eQSrqjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Segway tours of Riverbank area coming in 2017. @MartinHaese set to become the pioneer...#9newscomau https://t.co/FOpyfGD0TZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First on 9: @SAHealth new CEO Vickie Kaminski sits down with @alicemonfries. Officially got the job today. https://t.co/AIVFxuBq8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Business_SA survey estimates cost of Sept blackout at $367m. But "dodged a bullet" because of timing. Could have been worse. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill describes prospect of losing extra 450gl of Murray water flows as "utterly unacceptable" to Renmark… https://t.co/QYlblanJRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray River looking full from air. Premier  in Renmark soon to discuss basin plan with locals. Full coverage… https://t.co/SnmZBTVNTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ceremonial start of $985m Northern Connector road project with @PaulFletcherMP, @JayWeatherill &amp; @SMullighan… https://t.co/IUwL5Knajl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scene at Darlington following crash. One man fighting for life. Police involved in chase of car believed to be… https://t.co/eHjXR3y2Zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @nico_rosberg gone... https://t.co/7hH0iPoZtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AEMO_Media says SA blackout lasted about an hour &amp; was not related to September's statewide blackout. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AEMO_Media statement on blackout. Approx 200k customers effected due to problems in Victoria. https://t.co/PplbFljPyB #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: No confidence motion in Ian Hunter passes 12 votes to 5. #9newscomau #saparli https://t.co/FAXEXfpx2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Division called for Ian Hunter vote of no confidence motion. Debate had been extended. #9newscomau #saparli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@marshall_steven says government has no ability to fix child protection system. "They've had chance after chance"… https://t.co/6Wg8cFlCvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnRauMP on new children and young people laws "interest and safety of child trump all things." #9newscomau https://t.co/gL546lA2De]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foster carers and family carers also set to get more rights. Full details in @9NewsAdel tonight. #9newscomau https://t.co/1CDN5rXvvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one of the proposed law changes to child protection. Guardianship to be moved from Minister to Department CEO.… https://t.co/Z3xU5ZPCE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 of 260 Nyland Royal Commission recommendations not accepted. $432m to be spent on reforms. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill outlines child protection response. 196 Nyland recommendations accepted in full. Another 60 in prin… https://t.co/lFQRXBf1kA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More details on child protection system overhaul released today. $200m+ funding expected &amp; response to Nyland Royal Commission. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccroucher9 early days but geez, a lot to like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexhart7 @ljflannas @calferguson12 deserved a second crack.  @Chaddsayers27 a first ahead of possible Ashes duties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Justice Chris Kourakis confirms @JohnRauMP Senior Counsel application was received after deadline. #9newscomau https://t.co/CU3UuBV6AX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill addressing cabinet. Says latest Arrium paycut hit workers last week. #9newscomau https://t.co/7FSGeqyUbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TKoutsantonisMP weighs into beer price debate. Worried about everyday families having to fork out $9.20 for a drink. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whyalla cabinet meeting comes amid fresh child protection crisis &amp; ongoing fallout from the Water Minister's curse outburst. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STEEL CITY: Cabinet meeting in Whyalla shortly as potential buyers for steelworks circle. #9newscomau https://t.co/RWi3HKEpzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauren__Dailey hushed and humid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Water Minister Ian Hunter has apologised for the curse language he used at dinner on Thursday night. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unearth Whyalla. @JayWeatherill launches rebrand of SA's steel city as steelworks future remains unclear.… https://t.co/PGYZvY8rK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdwardGodfrey9 singing on all 12 cylinders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#F1 cars back on the streets of Adelaide...@EdwardGodfrey9 https://t.co/65KMkq1kuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill deeply disappointed following defeat of voluntary euthanasia bill in the early hours. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voluntary euthanasia bill fails to pass House of Assembly after marathon debate. Fallout in @9NewsAdel #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voluntary euthanasia bill passes second reading, 27 yes to 19 no. Now to committee. #saparli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#saparli sitting extended beyond 10pm for euthanasia debate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnRauMP now praising fellow MP's for the way they've handled voluntary euthanasia debate. #saparli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing quite like #F1 cars in Adelaide in November...#GloryDays https://t.co/G6fXt8dwzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkMim2 true. But it's been some sort of wait until that first question has come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOOTED! 6 opposition MP's kicked out of Question Time as debate gets thermonuclear hot. Pictures in @9NewsAdel… https://t.co/AZsXRod8xT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Government to support five @nuclearrcSA report recommendations relating to expanding uranium exploration and mining. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: @JayWeatherill says state government will support 9 out of 12 recommendations from @nuclearrcSA report. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLOSED SHOP: TV crews barred from entering nuclear waste conference as dump plan fallout continues. #9newscomau https://t.co/bM5IIceTv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nuclearrcSA Kevin Scarce on nuclear "I think it’s a lot tougher now that politics has now come into what is alrea… https://t.co/1r7KFJC2YL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill seeking to rebuild bipartisan support. @marshall_steven has previously said dump is dead. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill re nuke dump "I could have easily said it was all over." Process so far has shown trust issues with government. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill says social consent to be secured ... or not ... through a state-wide referendum. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JayWeatherill says discussion should continue into a proposed nuclear waste facility. #9newscomau https://t.co/AaIrE5zmHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Premier @JayWeatherill to update government's nuclear position at 2:30pm. #9newscomau #saparli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going well... #AUSvSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @Joe_Mennie. Cap #446, debuting with @calferguson12. A couple of @WestEndRedbacks boys to show them how it's done. #AUSvSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything crossed for @calferguson12 tonight. Deserves to be #445. #AUSvSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanWillsTiser @theTiser your Friday Night Track ... https://t.co/qXoMYV0JDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French union reps standing with ASC workers. Industrial action looming at Osborne. Details soon in @9NewsAdel… https://t.co/Nj76cUXARn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100+ shipbuilders gather for at Osborne for a stop work meeting. #9newscomau https://t.co/yERBODDtaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ANMFSA says EPAS at QEH was out for 10 hours late yesterday &amp; overnight. Paper records relied on. Extra staff called in. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening of Carrapateena mine tunnel. Will dig 5.5km underground to reach copper &amp; gold deposits. #9newscomau https://t.co/BvbAISoK3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Gillman deal collapses. Land going back out to market. #9newscomau https://t.co/bYPfOTmBs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@senatorbobday officially resigns. Joint sitting of #saparli needed to ratify replacement after @FamilyFirstAust pick candidate #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scene outside Richmond Oval ahead of @alpsa Convention. Hundreds of anti nuclear protesters filling the street.… https://t.co/FN6FJKoDbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh details on @9NewsAdel soon of a cross-government delegation headed for Korea to court a possible buyer for @Arrium. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major crash starting to piece together what happened at Midway Rd. @SAPoliceNews confirm a driver allegedly involve… https://t.co/2NX8MfEP8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key bill (#14) survives. No vote. Adjourned off until Dec 1. McFetridge bill  (#15) to be debated again on Nov 3. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lib MP David Speirs concerned about slippery slope #VE may take SA down. #9newscomau https://t.co/9AzMvB3L90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But SA has returned to having highest unemployment rate in country. Tasmania drops from 7.2% to 6.5% over same period. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: SA's unemployment rate has fallen to 6.7% for Sept from 6.8% in Aug. National rate down to 5.6% #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@stephanknoll wants a decision on #VE bill today. "Disrespectful" not to happen. #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@duncanmcfet on his #VE bill "The safeguards are there." His new bill (#15) includes amendments from Key bill (#14). #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@duncanmcfet on feet talking to HIS voluntary euthanasia bill (attempt #15 for SA.) Fate of Steph Key bill (#14 for SA) clouded #9newscomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steph Key talking with pro voluntary euthanasia supporters outside Parliament. #9newscomau https://t.co/YnPvw5n54k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going well...@DavidBevanSA @KevCorduroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@duncanmcfet confirms to @9NewsAdel euthanasia bill vote is off tomorrow. #9newscomau #saparli]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>