<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#Mexico ... a #mature country with a mature #leader  .  Good decision Mexico. From a close #neighbour (New Zealand).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration. 
For instance people who left Europe  (even in the 1600's) became immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm here in Alcatraz. Inauguration is Friday.
Everyone ready for the new world order? https://t.co/siSHZXequH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscar Kightley: NZ heads boldly into 2017 https://t.co/KsuGHBEpct #NZ grows up ...  I congratulate you #MurrayMcCully a man with #courage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone ready for more of the same old (old world order)? Read your history folks. Syria, Isreal, Mr Trump etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia backs Israel rather than the US over UN resoln https://t.co/zqpr4fxc7n. "Aussies, no surprises there." Newworld(old world)order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editorial: New Zealand takes a brave position on Israel https://t.co/v5KdS0JvHO. War? Really? Big man talk Benjamin. Come on down then.1948.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Mr Trump, were you a student of history? or ... Can't remember the 20th Century maybe? We wanted peace and ...we got ...you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsmediocrity Thank you. the best is when other people, like yourself, acknowledge it.☺☺☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsmediocrity we did have the biggest earthquake in 100 years but very little loss of human life. Our land is shaken up. We are well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsmediocrity Been a strange fortnight. Apparently you are not alone in your feeling. The whole world stops and stares in disbelief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsmediocrity ah, I feel for you. That must feel like major betrayal. I wish you the best, from New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsmediocrity Why is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand earthquake: strong aftershocks as roads and rivers blocked – live https://t.co/5h4yFqfCKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10th November 2016

What happened?

Really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any place there is #nowall ". New Zealand is such a place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Paralympics # LiamMalone #NaylandCollege #Awesome . #Legend . from a past Nayland College Student, teacher at Stoke School and dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Paralympics #sophiepascoe you are an excellent role model for us all. Andrew Thompson. Primary teacher. Nelson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Flexo - Bendable, bouncy, flexible building bricks! by Flexo on @Kickstarter https://t.co/AVvHVuELWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasHaig ha ha I didn't reread it ....schools per second is pretty funny.😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasHaig I know!?#!?@$ ....not the schools per second that bother me It's the unfairness of the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just entered to Win with Whittaker's!... https://t.co/MUO31hKNog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lies: Hekia Parata fabricates a 'Special Education Association' that she says backs her plans https://t.co/P79tcMmyrO via @Dianne_Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenkellyUnion I am a teacher since teachers college 1983. Love your work. THANK YOU. Go Marijuana for medicine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lily_Garland @JeanetteGinn psychopaths and politicians and journalists and "the media" aren't interested. Unlike you. I Congratulate you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardenasElanie @America_1st_ @craftylady55 you must be one of those ones making it feel unsafe eewwwwwww ... nasty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardenasElanie @America_1st_ @craftylady55 well she would B welcome here. we prefer people with ability 2 consider others.U inconsiderate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@America_1st_ @craftylady55 you didn't listen to her ... she said she didn't feel safe. ... she was honest, she didn't speak poorly. U R tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@America_1st_ @craftylady55  blatant scare mongering. You are not the only country in the world either. Get working on the positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about visitors?  Can they "bear arms"? Why? Why not? I don't understand you see. Just want to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... and I thought "all" American citizens had "the right to bear arms" U know .... muskets frm PaulRevere's ride... some don't? Who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is it? A keen hardworking honest person with vulnerable children at heart?? Say it is..... https://t.co/I8SkhhUjJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Thank you so much! https://t.co/q5lgSv0Y1B via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David.Wales@education.govt.nz: Keep Salisbury School open to give girls with the most needs the choic... https://t.co/OwbZXxOwxd via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NŹ #government  #NationalParty #paidparentalleave #veto #roughshod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DefendingtheUSA @realDonaldTrump  one thing missing ... how?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kotcha301  fools paradise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robdelaney  very backwoods (back woods) thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cory_1077  and if you don't give a damn why you saying it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cory_1077
seen  real videos like  rest of us?
Where was the airplane wreckage?
actually U seem like more a problem than anyone who's muslim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rollingitout @oreillyfactor 

... so why aren't you fixing the main problem 63% is committed by American citizens???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCongress 

as in your previous tweet "do you're job..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCongress 

#We #spell #"your" without an #apostrophe because it is a word in it's own right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCongress 
One #spells "you're" with an apostrophe, because the article belongs to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, many consider #MrTrump to be the largest #threat to the world right now.
#agree

or 

....

...

...

...

...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #Trump2016  a farce?
Is it #theater ?
#entertainment ?
#good for TV ?
A well thought out distraction from #realEvents ?
A #badjoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any #thinking Americans care to explain #PresidentialElection2016 to the rest of us and what you are all going to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#funny #entertaining (&amp; also a #Presidential       #race (?) ) 4 the #world right now, but hey! #Trump (#Tromp is better) is not #reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does the logo say tromp? #Tromp #PresidentialElectionUSA2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe that adult/thinking/ people would even consider letting a man like that anywhere near real power. #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of the people of Paris. Keep safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumich I understand. My work requires knowing about both halves of the "half full glass" I can't shut my eyes to the "other" students.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumich Sorry to burst your bubble:- It has been a daily truth during my 32 year career. The real issue is when people refuse to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Hekia, I don't want to be an All Black https://t.co/5LifzZw05a via @Dianne_Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#allblacks #win #WorldCup #RWC2015final #BackToBack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#congratulations #YourMajesty #QueenElizabethII #LongestReigningEnglishMonarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the Pony Express to deliver 100 letters! #GoogleDoodle
https://t.co/3Q0zZqVBte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BlackCaps even more pride for you. #true #sportsmanship. No one saying Australian team are not #sledgers. tell us about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Australia.  #WorldChampion #sledgers. #BlackCaps so proud of your huge achievement! Well done #ICC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICCWorldCup2015 #BlackCaps play your own game. play it your way. Go team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want a fool (even a good #rower) to represent me. "#Landedgentry" #StBedes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StBedes Who wants a 17 year old who does#stupid when his mates say to &amp; gets dad to get him out of trouble to represent them? boys? NZ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StBedes #Rowers #MardiCup ... Gary O'Shea, your comments show good sense as a leader in Education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government won't cater to irresponsible parenting: Paula Bennett http://t.co/7PxJUaXVKS #goodonyou #JacindaAdern #sayithowitis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NZvSA Go the #BlackCaps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was the promised punishment.  Prosecute if they compete @ #MardiCup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NZ #CHCH parents use Courts to renege on a promise to ensure their children behave.  2 boys ride luggage carousel into #secure area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#saddened to hear of the death of Celia Lashlie.  She spoke out. #RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MardiCup #stBedes. Boys allowed to compete. Who cares what they did? Daddy thinks it was #just fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roastbusters ...their faces all over the news? as if they were clever boys?? smiling at us too??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why are the media celebrating those #roastbuster child/boys on the media? get their faces #off. Are you on their side or the victims?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CWC15 #IRELAND remember #SaxtonOval]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CWC15 #NZvENG day night game? we might not see #darkness before the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the #decision that brings down the #NZ #government ... 2 #miserly #successive justice ministers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AmyAdams #mp are you copying #JudithCollins #mp over David Bain? you are voted in to make decisions for us. just make it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CWC15 #Ireland #historic #win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GibbsDeb4 enjoy! I'm missing the MST already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time-lapse video of New Zealand from space | http://t.co/CqwTUets1V http://t.co/kGxD7nUauz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hockey: Punt scores four in victory http://t.co/6WdoTgpCvV via @nzherald  &lt; #Congratulations Anita!&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little labels Key 'liar' over Sabin: http://t.co/qm76H9ybqz ** yes, and I do care about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GibbsDeb4 hi Deborah.  Good so far thanks. Needed the rain tho. How about you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Catton success illuminated nation: http://t.co/DgGmUKbjXj #madbutcher #bookerprize ?  #NZ devalues it's writers and thinkers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?  ( #Catton 'has no great insights into politics': http://t.co/XEin77o3NK  ) Maybe you should write about this Eleanor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The surprising origin of Murphy’s Law revealed http://t.co/dGBT2OuTHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrkempnz @Shareaholic you're welcome Craig.  Best of luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Edublog Awards - nominated! - http://t.co/EoojsFjYSX via @Shareaholic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So impressed with #TheHobbitTheBattleofFiveArmies . Loved #Legolas leaping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BattleOfTheFiveArmies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eldest son had his Christmas lights party this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wild day at #Wharariki beach yesterday. Wind, sand, seals and surf. Edge of the planet! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Escaped prisoner.  Excellent result. Now forget him.  Media don't mention him. Long time in Brazilian jail...good. ignore his presence all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PMJohnKey ..."at the end of the day". Chris Luxton #AirNZ Says "taking a step back..." both mean "I don't want to answer your question. "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargLBailey Hello again. I think my tweet is about being digitally connected to the entire world and how that helps Nelson.  #gigatownnsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargLBailey my wife is Irish &amp; lives with me in Nelson. My irish bro-in-law shared the news digitally Why is it off the topic? #gigatownnsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland beat South Africa in Rugby. #gigatownnsn . Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrafalgarPark #Nelson #gigatownnsn #NelsonFalcons 2-nil win. Congratulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NelsonFalcons . Your win. well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Nelson had UFB then I would tweet a photo of the moon. Big bright shiny full #gigatownnsn moon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was a great #Schoolgala at Wakefield today.  #gigatownnsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wakefield #School Twilight #Gala. This afternoon from 3:30 pm! #gigatownnsn #Nelson .]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>