<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm an irrational asshole when I'm overtired, too. Has anyone just tried putting the toddler-in-chief to bed at 10pm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few songs make me wish I could play an instrument like "I Will Possess Your Heart."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Taco Bell made a taco shell out of fried chicken.
Dan: There's hope for America after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieiscrafty [zipped mouth emoji]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're not giving ratings to those making a reality show out of the highest court in the land, The Parent Trap (LiLo) is on E!.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my kid keeps up this level of high pitched screaming, neighbors are going to think I stole Ollie the bobcat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kellyrand No alcohol yet, but definitely the other three. @EmmyA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mazzie Yeah. Only on our way back through, though. Can't believe that it's something we have to resort to, however.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mazzie We are in March. Planning to delete all social media from phones and act like luddites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandwiches at @TaylorGourmet aren't even CLOSE to being as good as Chik-fil-A's, and I easily gave those up, too. https://t.co/tjedxR3mCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This baby's racking up protests faster than teeth. https://t.co/88k3AaHSZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, looks like we have a new family hobby on the weekends. #muslimban #regufeeswelcome https://t.co/RiZLRzz9LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess protesting shit that ignorant bigots are trying to get away with is my new weekend hobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave away a bunch of blank white cardboard at the #WomensMarch because I didn't think I would need a new one every fucking week. Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was looking for this. DC, let's ðŸ‘ show ðŸ‘ the ðŸ‘ fuck ðŸ‘ up on Sunday. 1-3, WH. #resist #protest  https://t.co/wHkEMJCH4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parenthood means never getting to do anything you want or need to. Apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lsarsour Did you know "Sarsour" is an anagram of "US roars?" Thank you for your work.ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drivers and staff of @UPS are lying fuckwits and I hate them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankly, is there proof getting punched by a member of the minority ISN'T what redeemed Draco? I think it helped. https://t.co/r9rJH0CwkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetingNaoto @adamihasegawa kneW, not knee. Baby on hip. https://t.co/7bT4CFpK1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetingNaoto @adamihasegawa Have you seen @PunchedToMusic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetingNaoto @adamihasegawa I knee exactly where this was going to go and I am still cackling with tears streaming ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Snape and Dumbledore already covered this question. https://t.co/eLGcORfl1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 am and this crazy-ass wind is waking my baby up. She doesn't even have an exterior window in her room right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstharrington The pseudonym is how I recognized this while scrolling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time a viral FB post reminds you that you owe @mstharrington a DM. ðŸ˜ https://t.co/79VcqsNtw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone wrote fiction that went the way @markbaumer's story did, I would think it was too heavy handed with the symbolism. Jesus. ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicoleindc Yes, but a Getty image. I am not that tall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought a lot about Abigail Adams yesterday, so I made a thing. #WomensMarch https://t.co/bhpyc8egws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second up: that first postcard should tell your senator to give ME a senator. #DCStatehood https://t.co/sBM5BP9G9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaValenti And it took an hour and a half after the first tweet to send this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby was super chill all day at the #WomensMarch, but don't worry! She's been making up for it for over an hour. https://t.co/W1ZsUiv9hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future @ggwash contributor right here. https://t.co/ZSmvzfxNeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aviatrixt We saw that one! â™¡  @dylanmarron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hodgman @nytimes But they'll be able to reuse it pretty much every day. Work smarter, not harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSerwer Then you might appreciate this one I spotted, too. @CAwkward https://t.co/mt3mvhAVRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@70Ceeks @1followernodad @davedittell Hope you guys had fun in our fair city! Thank you for coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley if this is in DC, I definitely saw her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am in awe of the sheer numbers in this crowd. But I am crying because we all should have been here yesterday. #womensmarchonwashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @timkrepp for the sign inspiration. #WomensMarchOnWashington https://t.co/wpHUXXYkZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt DC followed your advice! Lotsa visitors to my artsy shop; we made postcards to send to mosques that have been threatened. â™¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobAkimoto Totally fair. I know lots of people have thought of others in similar situations and we march in your honor. â™¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had 10 extra envelopes, made 10 extra double-sided signs to hand out. See you tomorrow. #ImWithHer #WomensMarchDC https://t.co/peUoxllpJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I deliberately unfollowed this AM but was back to following a minute ago. Check @VP &amp; @FLOTUS too.  https://t.co/YpcHbjN9l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An RV covered in that asshole's name just parked itself blocking two lanes of K St NE traffic. Not as a protest, just because dicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've found the president has very little influence on my life so I don't care either way." -- SHOCKINGLY, a cis hetero white dude to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My toilet just clogged so my life will literally be a shitshow at noon. Seems appropriate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geekylonglegs Don't watch. Jackass only understands ratings and transcripts will be available later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to be so optimistic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilPhorward Oh yeah, I am well and fully fucked there, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilPhorward Debating what countries I can move to while teething baby fucks my nipples up while battling PPD/PPA. It's been rough. ðŸ˜• You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barnswallowkate I think I read Twitter archived them and moved them to a POTUS44 acct or somesuch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss_sequential I am so glad the march is happening on Saturday or I would have had to leave town for the weekend/rest of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw my first red hatted jackass tonight, and then five dozen more. I've been here a dozen years and never felt less safe in my city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lgstrick My fingers are crossed for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnburntWitch Goddammit, you're telling us you're NOT Chuck Tingle?! 

(Also, thank you for your brave post.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bethesdaist I have had his songs stuck in my head for two days despite not having heard them in a long time, and now I know why!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitolRomance (Though she is being pretty cute right now.) https://t.co/O1TejgJG2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitolRomance Relatedly: fuck fucking. Never again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, you could take the Uber part out and it'd still be true. https://t.co/lKGnJesTXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when my kid slept through the night for a hot minute &amp; I thought I might have a normal life again someday? 

Yeah, me either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beyonddc YOU add the gap when you say it because you don't mind being wrong, apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out @beyonddc pronounces s'mores "sa-mores" so I am now in the market for a divorce lawyer. Recs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has rush ordered the passport that he didn't fill the application out for, btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't think you'd have to tell someone to have a completed application for a passport but a guy was just in line for  an hour+ without one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone had some misplaced confidence a couple years ago. https://t.co/or6fElxLL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genehack Upstate NY here &amp; "warsh" is how my Albany-area grandpa still says it. Never heard of it as a southern thing. Hmm. @amaditalks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genehack @mazzie I mean, you're not wrong. https://t.co/IkQGHmchaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genehack Always looking on the bright side, you are. @mazzie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrrrrie ...turns out I have no Oreos. Nor do I want to put pants on to go get Oreos. So there is my answer, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrrrrie Why am I NOT eating Oreos at 2am?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthePill Dicks. THANKS A LOT, USELESS BOOK PEOPLE SELLING ALL THE WORLD'S KNOWLEDGE. https://t.co/XLaymD1ASJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthePill His sister is cool too but literally just left Denver for work yesterday. Tattered Cover is the huge pretty bookstore downtown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthePill My coolest Denver person is @brettmarshbanks but that asshole moved to Bristol on us. Hmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthePill Do you need Denver people or things?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1followernodad Sobdiscussed this with spouse for 2 hours &amp; your tweet showed up the second I opened Twitter &amp; summed it in &gt;140.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'M TRYING TO WARN YOU PEOPLE. https://t.co/eHKDe6QmB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now on my third change of clothes in three hours. Guess we're trying to set records here.

Babies are assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a service that feeds &amp; raises my child, delivers groceries, &amp; runs my business for me?

Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going through two wardrobe changes in thirty minutes is why parents look like hobos in public.

Seriously, why tf do I bother trying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikki_d Like roses as a state flower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikki_d Oh we def don't have an exclusive on it. But it is our official.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannabis: The Official Perfume of Northeast DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If y'all have friends like @LulaMaeDC &amp; @NoPants_McGee in your lives, who'll come take your screaming baby for an hour, treasure them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoPants_McGee It'll be fun, they said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoPants_McGee ðŸ˜• We could have opened it a crack if we had thought to tell you sooner. I'm sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoPants_McGee Oh, we assumed it was for leaving him but taking Lucy, since it was on the dog bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne They can't be assholes straight through or we would leave them in the woods. Good break in the middle. Smart evolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne I'm assuming toddler yrs, when she can do something/anything without me, will be more pleasant. Not sure if true, but I cling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne (I am still working on this one.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne That sounds like it blows. Be good to yourself, too. It's OK to be frustrated &amp; annoyed &amp; angry. It doesn't make you awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne It gets better in fits and spurts. I no longer want to murder her on a regular basis, for one. Just occasionally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gloriaevonne You eventually ate?! Impressive! ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ Spouse &amp; I joke/not joke that 6 week smiles have saved humanity from dying out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the birds wake the baby up in real time on the monitor, &amp; then watching her be like, "oh, just the birds," and go back to sleep. ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am home with the baby all day and I reheated two slices of pizza.

That was ambitious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mazzie Show. No. Mercy. ðŸš«ðŸ”ªðŸðŸ”ªðŸš«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mighty_pigeon I know, right? How awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg A friend's coworker DID wake up from a coma late last month. She did not take it well. @mighty_pigeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aminanotameena But you would know what a calculator was and maybe how to operate it. ;) ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aminanotameena But you're reasonable. If I said "but 30% of X should be Y," you could give me more than a blank stare.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>