<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[drinking having breakfast at The Dolphin Snack Bar, Linlithgow https://t.co/J58V1qe7yV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking like -3 this morning, gonna be a cold run to work #allyearbiker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😣 #bbcbreakfast says prime minister to take a "quake" to USA to meet trump, FFS is "quaich"..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tescobankhelp Hi, I sent a DM to get a copy of any valid offers on My Tesco card. Have you managed to look at this for me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On route to Glasgow office. Caught the 8:06, by skin of my teeth. No bike today😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FallenShadows82 god now I I have done the same drovers for herding cattle. 🤓]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FallenShadows82 drivers, you herding cattle. Sorry had to do it, not normally a grammer police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tescobankhelp Hi Ross, now done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Glasgow friends fancy this? https://t.co/sqc752H5HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tescobankhelp I have a CC and there was a couple of offers, i have deleted the email, is there any other way to see this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up – drinking beer at The Tron https://t.co/mxQTrnJxoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josshorne89 you walk passed me at Gyle today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handy app for keeping tabs on your vehicles https://t.co/PPRhOkLtRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aandpbikephoto @Oli_Rushby Was about to say Knockhill, as a joke obv. 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these sketches. https://t.co/XOD7x8wryh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carronvalley MCC Santa Run 2016
#carronvalleymcc #santa #charitymotorcycle #charitymotorcyclerun… https://t.co/49K7m9J6iU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland Hi no problem, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland thanks, also is 22a running as normal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland is the service 38 &amp; 38a running as normal after crash on B8020 last night. Reports of diversion through Broxburn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QUIZ_Help Hi, I ordered product code 00100009001 black and red floral print mesh flippy dress but was unfulfilled, why is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EzyR1der nothing at all wrong, always good to have a backup. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland it's cool no need. Can something not be added to the page as a fares guide?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstScotland Hi, can you tell me the cost of a return from Winchburgh, Opp Tippet Knowes Estate to Edinburgh Princess Street?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FallenShadows82 I'd stay Samsung, S7. Wireless maybe the future but earphones are a basic need, no adapter should be needed. SD slot too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenpaton134 Definitely don't envy the Americans though. Population that big and only 2 choices.. Process seems flawed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenpaton134 I'm not sure, think trump bad in a divisional/racist way. Think Hilary would be worse from a military point of view though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenpaton134 Who would you pick? As you say neither is good, what's worse in your opinion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atthesummitmtb @wemoto Always get a great service from Wemoto. Good bike too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grumpybill81 @STVNews Your 30 mins at least from Meadowlark. Behave 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garryscott7 Get it cheap in Aldi the now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy The people need to know what we are fighting for though, if any parts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy The government (or Tory part) must know what they want out of it though? So we can see what they will fight for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy It will still happen, but at least we will know what is happening? Has to be the right deal before triggered??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DVLAgovuk Hi, called and was told this too, thanks. Never seen this on the site, if it's not on can it be added. Regards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DVLAgovuk Hi, Sorned my vehicle last night and then you have taken tax for November by DD. Will this be refunded? Sorn immediate I thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House up for sale, make a perfect first home for someone. New Kitchen, Recent Bathroom &amp; neutral decoration. If... https://t.co/ADhXx9NJIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not often I'll share a daily mail article but this is a worthy cause. I have registered today, can you spare the... https://t.co/RbiGtAkZ2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Auto66Racing Thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Auto66Racing Hi, Taken some amateur photo's at the gold cup, link to public Album on FB is https://t.co/kl5glNGrzE, Can you retweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pals page, give it a like and see some of the shots he has taken. https://t.co/ie7vs945Ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotRail Well thanks for making me late for my class this morning in Glasgow replacement bus service was a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On way home – eating McDonald's at Mcdonalds Fortwilliam https://t.co/RPSF8z1xJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdirecthelp Thanks, possibly have to look at switching my accounts then as i'd like to know better whats coming off, other banks do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdirecthelp Hi, why do Debit Card transactions not show in the pending transactions in my account, other banks show this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trafficscotland Any Problems between Newbridge and Broxburn on the A89? Seeing information on Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineMUA oh, make sure you have the correct connections needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineMUA if only pictures it should be fine, TVs are not great for monitors/gaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GranthamAndrew @Auto66Racing Was my first visit too, I'll defo be back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy @SkyNews @HackneyAbbott Or change channel? Save the expense of a TV a day ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice That's the one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Scarbourgh tomorrow for the Gold Cup at Olivers Mount over the Weekend, cannot wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice ah no problem, do you know if Winchburgh is up and running, last time it was shut, no notice until there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice Hi, has the PO branch closed in Broxburn EH52?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamjar_1986 Ha Ha, knew you'd not fire a bet on Man Utd. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamjar_1986 Man Utd? God your a brave man to have them on a coupon for a win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PedalScotland fiancée left for class at 7:15 heading to Lithgow, not allowed left turn. Stewards clueless. Only eastbound needs shut....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PedalScotland what time to bikes leave Glasgow? Roads shut in Winchburgh from 6am. Should be rolling closures. #joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PedalScotland why are roads closed at this early? Time do bikes leave Glasgow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PedalScotland Fiancée had to leave Winchburgh this morning for a class, road closures and stewards who don't even understand English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy is that not because although we voted Leave we are actually still in for now? Until article 50 trigger it's all a guess??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotCitylink what is the earlier service? Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotCitylink Thanks, as the M8 is suffering serious congestion, are you aware of any delays to service? That only leaves 10mins spare?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotCitylink Ratho Station in Edinburgh to Glasgow bus station direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotCitylink I need to be in Glasgow for 9ish on Sunday what bus can I get? Is the M8 works causing any delays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotCitylink Hi, has the M8 works effected any of your journey times? on the 900 service? I need to be in Glasgow for 9:30 on 11/09/16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#adrenalinbuggy #knockhill #tracknight #busapower #turbo https://t.co/4ndITIhMx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/8m7UEWcCI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFromley Don't believe everything you see on social media. 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFromley Nope, you've been told lies 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/67mMHkuNBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/CuRbCRVIA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/2ZWWT3ElHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/J5V9mGHG0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/wOSOVDHl2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/TetiKVkUOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 2 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/Q8eKlaH4hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 3 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/1kk9vtKOdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 3 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/qTovO8MUl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 2 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/cIymUNqyNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 7 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/jT4UrD8XED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 3 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/mM3qBGvFTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 3 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/CLe6s7L1IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "Knockhill" https://t.co/0DsNV6CGPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a series link set up for this. https://t.co/VyfKOBG26f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia Cool, I'll check closer to renewal time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia Thanks... One of the reasons I took TiVo but hey ho, come renewal time I think Sky have it so will see what deal they can offer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia Is Spotify no longer available on TiVo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice Yes. I had to travel round to the Broxburn branch to post my parcel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostOffice Arrived at Winchburgh PO today to see a sign saying closed till further notice. I had checked the website and no note on there!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 37 photos on Facebook in the album "Annual Carronvalley MCC summer run" https://t.co/2qHgLfj79h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy It looks like labour needs to split anyway as part of it is more centre and part is left leaning. Two different parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy challengers need to be nominated but I don't think you can just wipe of incumbent.. you need the whole membership votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy @johnmcdonnellMP unfortunately Labour is in a massive heep of crap the now and this is just another part of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy @johnmcdonnellMP challenge then I agree but if you wipe of the incumbent you risk people saying it was not democratic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy @johnmcdonnellMP he has to have a chance though, if you wipe him of the ballot then it's unfair as he could  not be voted in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValentinoMossy @johnmcdonnellMP the members want him? Democracy says he should be on ballot paper I'd say. People's voice not MP's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any bikers in or around Edinburgh, try to attend. https://t.co/hBKOzq3yQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any skater pals on here? I have a set of CCM Ice Skates size 46 which I believe is a UK11. Any use to anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well had Chris round from C.R.B motorcycle repairs to sort some stuff out on the bikes. Great service and genuine guy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>