<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench ...perspective, nothing offends me more than lecherous dicks claiming to be "real men". Lowers us all to level of creeps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench @Ben_T_Johnson Know I'm part of the problem for being the spokesperson for one of the offenders, but from a personal (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eportelance @groulxsome @Ben_T_Johnson Fully agree. But when you want to be Drake of Craft Beer, this is how you build a rep as a "mogul".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eportelance @groulxsome @Ben_T_Johnson It's buying an LCBO listing, I'm sure nothing more. Gives lost craft another spot on the shelf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest Bastard is ready to roll! Next Saturday, Feb 11 at the bottle shop! https://t.co/PzmALfuLaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally checking out @GreaterGoodBar. Awesome space, awesome beer. Enjoying @NickelBrookBeer Kentucky Bastard on ta… https://t.co/6cTehE32oA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidsunlee @crystalluxmore Are you trying to tell me that Activia and Jamie Lee Curtis have been lying to me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @crystalluxmore , one thing I've never gotten a straight answer on: is sour beer pro-biotic? Can I consider it good for the gut?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench @_VictoriaBrews Must be a triple threat: able to act, sing, troubleshoot draught system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucksahoy That's awesome!  Be sure to try pretty much everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench Yup. Inspired by Hamilton, it will be a hip-hop musical on the History of craft beer. Opening track: Fritz and the Maytags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning something really cool with work right now, can't wait to tell everyone about it. Soon...not yet...but soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for two tix to #RHCBF for me and the lady. Not working the event so can't get in like usual. Any help is welcome! Will trade beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty happy with how this all came together. Live edge cribbage table with steel mid-century… https://t.co/XMmdY9YoZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayoungvoice Thanks! Can't wait to teach my first class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a sour man myself. What do you prefer? https://t.co/uAbfcgNr47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm teaching Prud'homme Lv 1 in June @NickelBrookBeer . Come learn about beer from me! Sign up here… https://t.co/CeAuNIxlAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayoungvoice @indeedemma Which documentary? Did you mean to say "The Agenda with Steve Paikin" starring Matt Gibson? You probably did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a vegan beer dinner @starbeer ? Talk to @BrewScout , he puts together some shockingly good vegan beer pairings regularly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench @NickelBrookBeer That was our thinking, and the @LCBO agreed. Could be the start of something cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Legalizing Weed Really Affect Craft Beer Sales? Maybe Not. https://t.co/2ystqGh6Ec via @munchies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench @NickelBrookBeer To clarify: it'll be in our bottle shop and https://t.co/8dNQU3cwVC only. No LCBO store distribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench Fun fact: @NickelBrookBeer Cafe Del Bastardo will be a limited https://t.co/ZxSKPr359g-only release coming soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hhoebrewery I'd love to see more breweries doing 355ml cans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poppin bottles @theshoreleave for the Beer &amp; Cheese pairing night with @pantrycheese and… https://t.co/221ixEJaOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering how perfect @FRabbits Midnight Organ Fight is as an album. Need to track down a vinyl copy ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench I just go with "Beer Sommelier" (for Prudhomme 3) and people can do with that what they will. Would do same for Cicerone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign up for the @NickelBrookBeer Mailing List to be the first to hear about new releases and bottle shop exclusives https://t.co/DbdFJycjJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indiealehouse Where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HendersonBeerCo Gotcha. I always considered the Amphitheater separate from Ontario Place proper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HendersonBeerCo wait, I thought Ontario place was closed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevepurf @TTChelps A just to be nice tweet? Purf, you are a rare gem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrunkPolkaroo You will...regret it deeply. But only one way to find out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrunkPolkaroo If you've ever eaten a hop pellet, you know the answer is definitely not. Bitter bombs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench "shadenfuckoff"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttthewGeorge Last Action Hero, hands down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Cheese! Email theshoreleave@gmail.com to reserve your spot today! https://t.co/CTPV51elUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new piece for @Prostly is now live w @NickelBrookBeer @DetourCoffee @CollectiveHam @lagershed and @Kneadpizzanow https://t.co/MjrpANScWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OntarioBevNet Damn. Hoisted by my own petard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Issue 2 comes out this week, featuring a piece by myself and photos by James MacDonald. Subscribe so you'll get it… https://t.co/J4kjDds5Hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeaumontDrinks @OntarioBevNet This is a super entertaining thread to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @starbeer for the double shout-out for New Years Beers (still worth drinking in 2017!)  https://t.co/CSHkQPG51J via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First event of the year: @NickelBrookBeer and @pantrycheese pairing @theshoreleave Jan 12. Email theshoreleave@gmail.com to get on the list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LORAKIRK2 what a sweetheart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OntarioBevNet man, Cowbell bringing the strong game before they even have a brewery built]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ringing in the new year with great people and this vintage beauty. @nickelbrookbeer Cuvée… https://t.co/QxH2HT9gqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OntarioBevNet Oh Chris. You think I actually read the things you write? Oh, poor poor Chris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OntarioBevNet Well, Trump won, so anything's fair game now I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @NickelBrookBeer Core Lineup is now available in 57 @mybeerstore locations across Ontario! Just in time for New… https://t.co/Tx0P9e2R40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full listing of cities @NickelBrookBeer is launching in through @mybeerstore this week, just in time for New Years… https://t.co/qk5n2VGQRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ring in the New Year, or grab some dinner for the big night at Forth Avenue Kitchen - In… https://t.co/rGeU1mTNbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crystalluxmore Tell Conor I just started reading Kill Shakespeare and it's awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @TheThirstyWench forecast for The Next Year in Beer. I bet @nickelbrookbeer will be doing some of these :  https://t.co/1WId3ytUSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the events over @OntarioBevNet including our cheese pairing with @theshoreleave Jan 12! https://t.co/ovEFEbuaTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer and Cheese @theshoreleave with @NickelBrookBeer and @pantrycheese https://t.co/k0BMPRlX3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OntarioBevNet @theshoreleave Thanks Chris!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You like cheese? You like beer? You wanna eat cheese and drink beer @theshoreleave ? Email theshoreleave@gmail.com… https://t.co/m5kYmYh8fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top 25 new bars in Toronto by neighbourhood, many of which feature @nickelbrookbeer . Just saying https://t.co/Zji61hBXdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @theshoreleave Beer &amp; Cheese Pairing is coming Jan 12. Full details on @blogTO https://t.co/ryTMCoiZ81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_VictoriaBrews what street dis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specifically booked a "business meeting" at @lakeinezto so I have an excuse to drop by next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @LORAKIRK2 and @RubyWatchco for an amazing food &amp; beer pairing https://t.co/BDKoXWksM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Cheese! Email theshoreleave@gmail.com to reserve your spot today! Jan 12 2017. @theshoreleave @NickelBrookBeer… https://t.co/qF6LxRiYAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer &amp; Cheese! All local, paired perfectly @theshoreleave with @pantrycheese and @NickelBrookBeer. Jan 12 2017. Tix: theshoreleave@gmail.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayoungvoice What country is that style from? America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved chatting beer and fine dining with @ChefJKennedy on @TheAgenda. Wine and beer can make a meal great. https://t.co/BDKoXWksM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved chatting about craft beer, wine, food &amp; spirits on @TheAgenda w @SpiritsCanada @grangewinery @NickelBrookBeer https://t.co/BDKoXWksM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great sum-up of the continuing growth and challenges in the Ontario craft beer industry. Thanks for this, Chris! https://t.co/Xn0YhBU42p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttthewGeorge Just a hint of blush to highlight my cheekbones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight! I'm on @TheAgenda talking beer and food and politics and money and fun stuff. And I'm wearing TV makeup which is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolshevik Bastard Sourdough bread. Substituted @nickelbrookbeer Russian Imperial Stout for some… https://t.co/9bRByjfOnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to the crew @lakeinezto for their soft opening. The place looks incredible, going to be a new favourite for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted at Rogue One: yoda-ear Santa hat. That's a very niche merchandise market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna see me on TV? Check out @TheAgenda Monday Dec 19th at 8 &amp; 11pm. I even wore a suit (jacket only, no pants).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markjsolomon Check out https://t.co/U6Nhg72WyN for the classes. I'll be teaching some level 1 courses in the New Year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer and Cheese!
Come out to @theshoreleave Jan 12 for an epic beer and cheese pairing featuring… https://t.co/l9ZCPdp2iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dark chocolatey light at the end of the tunnel https://t.co/31g0qNI4aN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta go with a Half Bastard or Bolshevik Bastard stout. How about you? https://t.co/xuBtzSnEsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Admviolin next up is giving my liver a bit of a break after the holidays. Then beer-nerding my way across the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free beer! 6-8pm tonight @dominion_to I'll be sampling @NickelBrookBeer Raspberry Uber. Come by and get your sour on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidsunlee much appreciated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officially a Beer Sommelier. Got the hangover to prove it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Event of the New Year: Jan 12 - Beer &amp; Cheese night @theshoreleave with @NickelBrookBeer and @pantrycheese. https://t.co/3qCsPQuCFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheExB @ayoungvoice This is what you were looking for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More @torontolife love for @ChefPinkerton . That kimchi pancake tho #gerrones https://t.co/Kzm7ZEH3No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrunkPolkaroo Sending a @NickelBrookBeer Kentucky Bastard out of province? That's what I call diplomacy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished shooting my spot on @TheAgenda , airing Monday Dec 19th at 8 &amp; 11pm. Talking craft beer, politics and food!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calebwhutch @LCBO Year round! All da time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Available in @LCBO stores across the province now! https://t.co/LckYkcGrLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I know any animators that can do little digital logo animations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ring in the holidays with the best Xmas music there is @TheEdmundBurke1 https://t.co/zSygJmqDiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cane_Matt I mean. ..technically https://t.co/ZxSKPr359g does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Beer!! Sampling Raspberry Uber and Naughty Neighbour @illbeseeingyou_ right now! Come say hi and drink delicious beer! Prizes too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get thee to Lloyd's! https://t.co/54EWOtofmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is a tasty sandwich!
Beef cheek Sammy with smashed taters bodegahenriette paired with… https://t.co/04Ut6bcbRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repost from ontariocraftbeer 

Our unbelievable Cuvée is in the LCBO now. Fantastic now or… https://t.co/pSIpnDXEAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer by @RainhardBrewing , sausages and dirty fries by @WVRSTbeerhall. Solid Wednesday https://t.co/WNkLFFIWGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now on tap: @NickelBrookBeer Raspberry Uber pouring @dominion_to @PourHouseTO @MurphysLawTO and @PogueMahoneTO https://t.co/857f2Yt3EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome the newest addition to #Leslieville: @lloydsonqueen, opening today! Pouring @NickelBrookBeer Naughty Neighbour and more great beers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repost from @brewscout  - I thought about storing this but curiosity (and a long, taxing week)… https://t.co/CZZ28Nv3Bw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>