<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is just the beginning.... https://t.co/MCa1nk9NIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPI_NZ @NathanGuyOtaki really need to get this sorted. Not enough was done to stop the cruelty which is still happ… https://t.co/UPDyXvCxRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how can we think this is still acceptable?@bhudson_nz @PeterDunneMP @grantrobertson1 @pauleaglenz @NathanGuyOtaki https://t.co/ltcG55ojKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our city's resilience has to be at the heart of any key decisions @WgtnCC makes this year. https://t.co/Zd7kMVpm6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that I tried it but very impressed to see swimmers at @WgtnCC Khandallah Summer pool today https://t.co/DP4KJPhkMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fascinating place on a Sunday afternoon- Onslow Historical society 😊 https://t.co/QmkyNzkOaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either way, does this mean sun is a  prerequisite?🌂 https://t.co/UqdIfKT05Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCalviFree Absolutely and let's just hope it has plants suitable for the climate and not locked ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On our anniversary day, 22nd Jan 1840 seems very similar  (weatherwise) to today here in Wellington   https://t.co/b9FDm0FHpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same sentiments for Wellington re homelessness https://t.co/gJNzXGzohe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it wasn't so warm, you swear it is Winter out there ... https://t.co/DRx0paj72K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm.....summer in Wellington. https://t.co/iodoHpSVmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you can never have too much chocolate... https://t.co/skhF162mx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a fluffy? 😉 https://t.co/oaagVIDiWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never had so many likes so quickly to a tweet! Was it because of @pauleaglenz , cycling or both? Happy holidays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ibeardslee @WgtnCC @pauleaglenz Off road with a ramp  and judder bars to add interest. Our Dep Mayor has hidden talents😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay @pauleaglenz @WgtnCC Bike has @WgtnCC branding but there was only one. Paul couldn't resist taking it for a spin🚵]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cycling around @WgtnCC carpark with @pauleaglenz . Anything's possible 😊🚵 https://t.co/pesGa8k8W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good points made here. Worth considering and discussing with CBD commercial ratepayers that fund this. https://t.co/BTLxUDjF7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice if you are thinking about your next dog https://t.co/7LJn1aeg9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A heartfelt plea for the animals this Xmas.. https://t.co/KNAGmxzfTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great place for a birthday pool party @WgtnCC Keith Spry pool https://t.co/jUE7vDJ8Nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's ensure communities of place &amp; interest are engaged with early on, even before trials. Consultation is formal… https://t.co/ei3ITPkHvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to be at the @zealandia strategy launch. One of the key projects - Kaiwharawhara stream, from sanctuary to… https://t.co/ITADo18DQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @jilldaynz @davidleeWCC @sarahfreenz @IonaPannett Andy Foster, Malcolm Sparrow &amp; Peter Gilberd https://t.co/EbVo5IjDZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee culture going well with @WgtnCC councillors. https://t.co/m5evGm3KBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes it's true, not a cloud in the Wgtn sky for now..... but this afternoon? https://t.co/lTieS6nKLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too true ... https://t.co/14uPAUdnEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With no parking worries you can also check out #buglab #Tepa . Another great callaboration  with @WetaWorkshop https://t.co/XslZlmESbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# bugland #tepapa officially open. https://t.co/kb1EEXxxZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Xmas @sub_urban2015  with @jilldaynz @caffeine_addict https://t.co/aTX3xGi4ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From logburner yesterday to this! A summer of surprises! https://t.co/6vNRkRfQt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see @WgtnCC  has a strong voice on @lgnz https://t.co/9vGx0NtM4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity to see a world class exhibition for free! https://t.co/hrpSktZCBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC Mayoral summit = real community planning &amp; engagement. https://t.co/53ydYvY8AX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC  Mayoral summit  with @justin_lester  on now. Great ideas and so much in common. https://t.co/BV9tDtfzMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd week of summer and log burner still going strong..... https://t.co/xGFPrCnCZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A city of surprises 😆 https://t.co/ggwomVIX3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congestion put into perspective... https://t.co/neMZmRznEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking tea this afternoon with @pauleaglenz this afternoon https://t.co/WiDcYM6Jnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpaaustralia Wellington event. Proud moment. Jeff Owens received 10 year membership. Yes Tax can be exciting! https://t.co/o1nzq9IWZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Rattle and Hum....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northland Community providing facilities to temp re home a city chidcare for a few mths. Great use of @WgtnCC North… https://t.co/Fd3hJAbTcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final session down at Aro Valley Community Centre today. Join in and share your thoughts for the future of the area https://t.co/qS0RCYue9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time....warm sunshine 2 days in a row https://t.co/JKWeDCqM64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee just now at Le Maquis in Wadestown with local residents. Do we need a new access from Oban St to Trelissick Park?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative community engagement, check it out. https://t.co/p9UhG0gBqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people helping to shape their community space at Aro Valley this weekend with @WgtnCC  &amp; Aro Valley community… https://t.co/Uks0GSEdkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling energized! Great community conversations happening this weekend at Aro Valley Community Centre with @WgtnCC https://t.co/Wwqnr55ptj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good turnout on a wet night for @WgtnCC  Makara-Ohariu community Board inauguration with @justin_lester &amp; Councillo… https://t.co/vsdWDctcaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't get into the city, check out Jville Mall and co-working at @sub_urban2015. A great example of social e… https://t.co/48nVrzDSZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because @CHC_Airport already has a multi-level carpark building (and free drop off/pick up without going through ba… https://t.co/fiCZihWmW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC have developed a real time emergency map which provides
information for local communities :
https://t.co/lbZ7d3SOc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With my @WgtnCC Mayor and Councillor colleagues. We are open for business and back to scheduled work. https://t.co/dG3CmggqgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for a early night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok and thanks to people like you who are doing a great job looking after your friends &amp; community https://t.co/X4YoGItOEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC Contact Centre getting calls from people home alone needing assurance. Reminder to check on your neighbours if you can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @nmjyoung &amp; Andy Foster @WREMOinfo headquarters checking out the identified CBD buildings significantly impact… https://t.co/HMtULLfV6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC  &amp; @WREMOinfo staff working well coordinating the city's response. Great team effort. https://t.co/yL1XfIGR6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City of Surprises! https://t.co/mYaJvTsvja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All fine here just not keen on the aftershocks. Hope you ok. https://t.co/Zk8FcPXEu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxleRyde Absolutely but not everyone will unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 pieces of wet unreadable advertising material from letterbox.  A lot of stuff for landfill. Must be a better way… https://t.co/8x6gU3HFBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five houses in Wellington threatened by landslips, as heavy rain sweeps North Island https://t.co/U7eX0erKt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payback for a mild winter... https://t.co/J9XneFpqFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a new Councillor, I'm keen to get a briefing on next steps and what decisions are required from Council @WgtnCC https://t.co/QPtes43xnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalENZ great place to chill after visiting  Green expo at Queens Wharf. https://t.co/R4ip3sZLZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Green expo and @WgtnCC stand with @pauleaglenz . Good place to be on a wet day outside https://t.co/JTwXyRBjhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khandallah Post Shop made it to final 5 nationwide of the Vodafone local business awards. They need your vote  https://t.co/d6FGlb2O1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First  @WgtnCC  full Council mtg about to start. Maiden speech coming up https://t.co/4xOdbEIwyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come down to Khandallah School Fair. It's all go and the rain is keeping away. https://t.co/2VxKhQLWfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fantastic firework display. Thanks @WgtnCC https://t.co/xtQpaoRTHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says Accountants can't be funny! We had to go out but my husband made sure any visitors didn't miss out! https://t.co/Zs3iVNGrc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jansen_Lambton @johnkeypm @WgtnCC The point is the govt sees Wgtn economy doing well and not dying. More incentive for govt invest in Wgtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At function tonight, @johnkeypm says "Wgtn flying" . Absolutely agree. @WgtnCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterDunneMP This could be something to consider for Khandallah Park pool?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamVoulstaker @ianapperley @AP Absolutely! Much better than the European sludge ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down at Khandallah Village collecting for @NZBCF. Come and say hi. https://t.co/NyHPgEw58x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good suggestion. Thanks for heads up.  I will be in touch soon. https://t.co/WFzsrWB8if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapperley NZ marmite much nicer than the European one. Maybe a new trade deal for NZ? https://t.co/pRQIMkFaKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the badge! Now the real work starts https://t.co/34BddXgEKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the badge! Now the real work starts https://t.co/ItSFHQg8Rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newbies bring new thinking - Meet the new Wellington city councillors https://t.co/loSKPjssOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greaterwgtn @DaranPonter No 44 bus leaving 3.30 from Willis St very full. Not first time. Need to plan for more buses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First get together for @WgtnCC #Onslow-Western councillors with Andy Foster @WoolfSimon. https://t.co/7XwaAbUMtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyMihaka You may have been the youngest candidate but you had strategic vision which is definitely a must for a governance role]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bhudson_nz @WgtnCC @justin_lester Thanks Brett. Looking forward to working well with everyone across the political spectrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to positively serving the citizens of Wellington city. Thanks to all family &amp; supporters for help i… https://t.co/JFUrryyXAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With supporters @ktradingco https://t.co/HHb3KbP6AP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow @lgnz Normal is not good enough and you can't just blame lack of online voting. So @lgnz, what are you going to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to be in the top 3 for  #WCC OnslowWestern ward candidates . Generation Zero https://t.co/vhPExrmwKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room to improve but on the right track with a 'B' Generation Zero https://t.co/wChuVG9PpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IonaPannett Is there an opportunity for WCC to also partner with @kitteninn_nz who have also been running a subsidised desexing programme?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @SPCAWgtn @WgtnCC Much more productive than a set of bylaws https://t.co/nNN9dUPsOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyMihaka Happy Birthday and may this be a succesful week for you in more ways than one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is the overall balance of the council that matters, even more than the stripes of the mayor" Good Editorial:  https://t.co/xzaSC24Qqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Vic friends stay safe -Reports of gunman in Mt Victoria https://t.co/Nwmo9MgcvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sun came out for start of Mahatma Gandhiji's birthday celebrations at Railway station. https://t.co/sgex1g3lz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyMihaka @WgtnCC "Candidates are not permitted to use council resources for
campaigning purposes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC What's the KPI and target to measure the performance of your marketing campaign?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>