<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LennoxLuxe_xxx Beets. Bears. Battlestar Galactica.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeafsLostSoul 2nd team in Vegas baby!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rayferrarotsn Fun, but my heart is just returning to resting rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I doubt this Bos/Tor game ends 4-3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyFerg @draglikepull @macdFraser You know who probably doesn't remember that fight? Matt Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realjknoxville It's Lipstick with fuzzy purple balls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wraparoundcurl That Jess girl was pretty cute though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixpotvin There's only one Texan capable of this: https://t.co/HCyACFKsGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissyXMartinez I'd take you to Bingo and a 4 pm dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyllaCustomWear At first look, the guy in the background kneeling looks like a giant bird photobombing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouStayClassy_ Orchestrated by Keyser Soze, Norman Osbourne and Gargamel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustAboutGlad Depression equals no bathing at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateBeirness I've seen that commercial at least 100 times. That is not a complaint though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pksofourlives Clockwork Orange, Trainspotting, Se7en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KailLowry I drink tonnes of water. only drawback is I have to piss every 30 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elvis was indeed alive all this time, but was unfortunately killed during the #BowlingGreenMasacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if your going to buy some Bandcamp stuff today, throw some cash here. great music and James seems like a cool dude. https://t.co/eZOkRGTSOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evan_greer @tmorello If I recall, Harambe was a one of the victims of this senseless act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lower_northcore Shit, I wish I knew who was paying people to protest. I wonder how much i could make?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metaltxt @Bandcamp Yep. I guess I should stop swearing at my computer now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and wrestling PPV's https://t.co/DjsTLiWR7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck that Orange twat in the hair. https://t.co/u8a9gMjNFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Howard Stern should look in the mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraUnderwood Wouldn't mind seeing that "bare" in the woods.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOttawa @CBCAlerts Who hasn't dreamed about shitting gold?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarcelMousineau I'm sure there is someone with a nice farm that would take old Donny C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP24 O'Leary need to go fuck himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredOfLondon I'm sending him your way. https://t.co/engM8R6BwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette @adidashockey Nice. I'm a size 10 and need new gym shoes, hint Adidas hint. I'll settle for average ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twolinepass But he's a WWE Hall Of Famer bah god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twolinepass Imagine if a country like Brazil was put on the list.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN I have almost as much a chance at getting eaten by a Dragon........oh fuck I hope Dragons are banned from America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DogGilmour He lost a match to Mean Gene Okerlund, so fuck him :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN The statue behind him looks like a dog taking a huge diarrhea shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twolinepass @YahooSports Agreed on the 4 on 4. There are so many benefits beyond on ice product as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickC1983 If you don't like the world and human decency and happiness, instead of taking countless innocent lives, remove yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickC1983 The majority of the world wants to live in a peace and freedom, yet these pieces of garbage keep fucking it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It baffles me how a person can kill a total stranger for no single reason other than fear and hatred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a shot every time Jim Hughson mentins 1 Million Dollars, like it's the be all end all of this fucking thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notsam @KarlAndersonWWE @LukeGallowsWWE Sam looks like the love child of Wallace Shawn and a ball of dust from under the couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckDontLie He probably remembered a Fatty Arbuckle skit from his teenage years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theterrirunnels I heard you and Moppy had legit heat though ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Protect_Wldlife @MailOnline Fuck him. Hope he dies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully Trump doesn't randomly see Pearl Harbour on AMC one day and decide to ban Japanese people from US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyshynski I hope you never want to buy a house in New Tecumseth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YakovMironov Hopefully he still has enough money to feed his dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejustinfisher I'm into Metal and I had the same problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyshynski @StLouisBlues Yeah, both players won multiple championships for the Bl.....for themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickyclove @littlekeish @JessyJonesxxx I don't believe that was standard Police procedure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette Hasn't Marchand been fined for Slew Footing before??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abella_Danger @KeiranLee The way he spelled it made it sound like Really Smelly Pussy is a disease in stead of a random smelly pussy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know how Polak's good? He now has as many points as super rookie phenom Lawson Crouse. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish we could clone @Jtillathekilla2 at least 3 million times. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Sports @SWhyno @AP I think he's just "Malkin" this injury to get out of the ASG ;) #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimNorton I thought you had Best Supporting in the bag for Furry Vengeance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20buckspinlabel The Ominous Circle album is A+ #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityNews Trump (hopefully) won't be in office by the time they try to build this atrocity #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PPPLeafs Auston Matthews with 10 points tonight #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Real_ESPNLeBrun Marchand has slewed more feet than....someone that likes to slewfoot #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigern10 That would be the ideal bread for a ketchup sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle @mirtle @bigern10 Whole grain or white bread?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholsOnHockey Unless it's to clone McDavid 17 times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigern10 Weren't you in the league with Cooke, Kaleta, Burrows, Lapierre, Torres, Downie ect back in the day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twolinepass The voters saw "Black" and immediately ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metalinjection I'm surprised Phil hasn't called himself a F***** over that tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philthatremains @metalinsider @ATRhq That last PL tweet was all sung (badly) in auto-tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE How much can the baby bench??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philthatremains @megans_law @JoeThrashnkill Wow, are you a fucking moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philthatremains @JoeThrashnkill @sanchokeep33 Are you looking in the mirror??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle Sending message to JT of Brooklyn, New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredOfLondon Or a good "Total Elimination" https://t.co/w4CMBTatiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouStayClassy_ Damn Lettuce pushing that calorie count up :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travisyost Aren't you a Bill's fan too??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Weirdneal That guys name is Ty Cobb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdPeriodSuits  A swamp with a dead skunk in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottcwheeler I love that idea for 2 minuters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlekeish That girl seemed like she might be a bit of an asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle @TheAthleticTO When Rielly went down, My first thought was "Who's gonna take Gardiner's spot on line 2?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lshima_model Damn, I want Indian food now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lshima_model Did you at least get to have some pizza after the shoot was over??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCToronto The TTC stinks. Can't wait to pop a $5 bill in for a single ride in the near future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope every one of these people tries to go swimming, In Winnipeg, in winter. And drowns. https://t.co/UyDk9Ow7Qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityNews @CityPamS Of course it does.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amount of times this happens to @rayferrarotsn is ridiculously funny. https://t.co/yOzwMLJBja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50_MissionCap Nothing good can come from being named Spector apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLHS_Mike I'm glad that we can finally hear Glenn Healy's thoughts....I can hear crickets for some reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckDontLie don't know, but this is the time where Matt Martin's contract will be a drag as far as what these players will want/deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaliyahLove69 Thankfully I don't have that problem.....(Not that I have a massive dong, I can't get laid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN If it's a Comedy Club, Schumer should be kicked out (she's not funny)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meh Blah Ugh Grrrr Urrrrrgh #DescribeYourselfin5words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustAboutGlad Is he The Hulk??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wraparoundcurl Especially since the tone of all the Marvel/Netflix shows are pretty dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelseyChapstick That's my kid......wanna fuck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredOfLondon Is that show funny, or is Bell just trying to shove it down our throats like CBC does with some of it's crap shows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draglikepull Spector beating the Hall for Larsson trade was good drum again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckDontLie Cabin In The Woods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle Apparently, she's a bit of an asshole though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DownGoesBrown McDavid for Masterson: Carrying team on his back/willingly lives in Edmonton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyAnneJudd I'd say no. I can't see an UC cop in vice or whatever just saying "ya got me"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrButterChicken Looks like we finally get Lena Dunham of the street as well.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>