<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Key to building wealth is buying something that is worth a $1 for 40 cents....makes sense to me #WarrenBuffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Trent Dilfer speak like he's some kinda QB guru makes me believe anyone can accomplish anything...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At National Prayer breakfast this AM The Donald asked crowd to prayer for Arnold and the ratings of Celebrity Apprentice ðŸ˜‚what a clown!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anarchy continues as The Donald fires the acting Attorney General of the US!! This is only going to get worse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the Muslim ban has begun?? Didn't realize that included those already in the United States?? I guess this is "Making us great again"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @serenawilliams 23 major titles all time record!! Congrats to @Venuseswilliams as well also a great champion! #AusOpen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sixers fans youall need to be excited entire team 1st and 2nd Year players and are ballin! How youall say it in Philly? #TrustTheProcess ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ur having drinks with ur lady and the waiter steps over u to get at her what does that say about u?? ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Edition story who knew Bobby was that crazy?? My real question is when they start being allowed to cuss on BET?? #NewEditionBET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus and Serena finals at The Australian Open! 36 and 34 years old still dominating women's tennis! Go Venus!! #australianopen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Bivins wise choice New Edition over ðŸ€ðŸ€ especially considering dude grew to 5'7 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #NewEditionBET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at that man Ralph Tresvant has loyalty at 11 years old!! ðŸ™ŒðŸ½ðŸ™ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far New Edition miniseries is good! They even got Avon Barksdale with a fake ass Jerrycurl!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In honor of The New Edition mini series tonight on @BET what's your fav NE song? For me it's 1. Candy Girl 2. Can You Stand The Rain...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me tell you what I'm watching #Hardball #msnbc and Dan Rather is on..I had to look up just age he's 85 he looks spectacular!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jay Z bought Tidal for $56 mil less than 2 years ago..today he announces $200 mil Sprint investment for 33% that's 1000% return in 2 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok proving that Hollywood will recycle anything they have actually made a movie out of that sorry 70s TV show CHIPS so much for originality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were Obama and Joe holding hands as they walk to the capital steps? I know it's all love but they may be taking it too far...ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdatcher @Morning_Joe @MichaelSteele Real question is what we gonna do about it??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me tell u what @WashWizards Otto Porter is gonna get paid this summer! He's turned himself into knockdown shooter! Hard work pays off!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think @PopeyesChicken is paying Jerry Rice in money or chicken? To be honest I'd take lifetime supply of Chicken and Cajun sparkle!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few more months Ima be eligible for all those semi pro 50 and over hoop leagues!! Time to get back on the court!! ðŸ™ŒðŸ½ðŸ™ŒðŸ½ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ’¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna pray for a windy day on the 20th I wanna see what Trumps hair does without that damn Make America Great Again truckers cap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never give up never be bitter stay hopeful and keep pushing forward" #quoteoftheday #johnlewis @MeetThePress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man it's unbelievable watching these GOP types squirm as they answer questions about obvious Russian interference #meetthepress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must see TV Congressman and Civil Rights icon @MeetThePress "i don't believe president elect is a legitimate president" those are big words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just another reason to dislike @realDonaldTrump you don't attack political/civil rights icon John Lewis and say he has accomplished nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 6 month anniversary Big Meech!!!!!!! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ’¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mooresbarber @RexTillersonHQ Lol he needs it something bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok now we are figuring out ways to lose games! #knicksnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After listening to Trump I'm convinced the key to success is speaking in 3rd person! From now on it's BC don't do this and BC don't do that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Rex Tillerson Sec of State hearings....one thing Ima urge him to do if he's confirmed or not. Get rid of the ungodly nose hair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People on my timeline are crying real tears about the Obamas leaving like ur upset that The Donald and Melania are coming? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama has been completely flooding my timeline....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's TV dilemma watch my life story/fav show "This is us" or my fav actor Tom Hardy in "Taboo" on FX...first gotta find FX..decisions ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classy speech by a classy man! Salute to a classy family!! #POTUS #FLOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charleston Church shooter Dylan Roof sentence to death!! I will lose no sleep over this one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me tell youall something some people r fine with cold weather walking around in shorts/short sleeve shirts! Im not 1 of those people!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Moonlight wins Best Picture at the Golden Globes whose seen it? Any good?? #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Glover big win for Atlanta Ima have to check this show out I guess... best actor #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denzel didn't win? To be honest I'm not surprised he was good but Viola was the one who was great in Fences! #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has seen "the crown" wanted to check it out on Netflix just won best series #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as I say that Atlanta best comedy!! Never even seen it gonna have to binge! #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[feeling after all those snubs at the Oscars gonna b a good night 4 black people ðŸ˜„ congrats @TraceeEllisRoss #GoldenGlobes2016 #blackish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some may know I love an award show...up here watching @goldenglobes Billy Bob Thornton wins and clearly he's already twisted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Giants dominated the half Beckham drops a TD pass and they fail on 3rd and 1...they should be up 2 touchdowns! It's a game of inches!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beckham 2 big drops!! Gotta make those plays if u wanna win in the NFL playoffs at @packers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soulja Boy got Money Mayweather in his corner Breezy got Iron Mike in his..don't be surprised Soulja boy may have that skinny man pop! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 degrees!! Today's high is 22 so much for being "down south" might as well still be in Massachusetts/New York...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgetownHoyas 8-8 and 0-4 in the Conference they created The Big East!! #nolongerthebeastoftheeast #jt3mustgo ðŸ€ðŸ’¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get busy living or get busy dying" #shawshank #quoteoftheday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Knicks gettin run by @Bucks in cold ass Milwaukee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dreams and ambitions have always been and will always be more powerful than anyone's doubts!! I will prevail one way or the other!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Guys don't tell on other guys that's guy code" #oldschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be clear GOP has no plan on how to replace Obamacare as flawed as it has turned out to be I personally know it has benefited many!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ApprenticeNBC the catch phrase is "you're terminated" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ awful can we bring back The Donald since Pence is gonna run the country...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for the boring ass Big Ten Penn State and James Franklin are an offensive machine!! #RoseBowl2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Celebrity Apprentice 1st impressions Lisa Leslie is a big chick and Boy George's makeup looks great!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["1st u get the money then u get the power then you get the women that's why u have to make ur own moves" #classic #scarface #pacino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ima say that these Sunday night games are hard to watch cause I cannot stand Chris Collingsworth his voice is annoying as hell!! #NFLSunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tell me nothing about Kirk Cousins being a big game player!! #deadskins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Smith classy speech after a phenomenal 16 years in the NFL!! "There is life after football" played with that chip on his shoulder!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all my friends and my family especially my girls I wish youall a #HAPPYNEWYEAR and as I always say #thebestisyettocome #2017 ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽˆðŸŽˆðŸ¾ðŸ¾ðŸ¾ðŸ·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[while youall partying I'm watching the beard James Harden kill my Knicks 50 points 15 rebounds 15 dimes! #HAPPYNEWYEAR #NBA #KnicksNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would Terry Bradshaw be calling Mike Tomlin a cheerleader not a coach if he was one of these white guys that keep getting fired and hired? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40 shot and 12 dead over the holiday weekend in Chicago!! What the hell is going on in Chi-raq??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Leia aka Carrie Fisher dead at 60 Rest in Paradise...a lot of deaths coming the end of 16!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @warriors can't beat the Lebrons without @TheRealJRSmith in December they ain't gonna beat them in NBA finals!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like the fight but we gave up 119 points! No defense no winning!! Still like how this team looks but we need a shooter at 2! #knicksnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a word to the wise! Don't ever deal with trifling people! #TheEnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carmeloanthony on fire!! My team on a roll! Love it! #knicksnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to get my miles in on this treadmill....whose gonna provide me with words of encouragement ðŸ’ªðŸ¾ðŸ’ªðŸ¾ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ima say Tony Bennett looks damn good for 90!! That Vegas lifestyle clearly does wonders!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I know my timeline is filled with Deadskin fans youall had a lot to say Monday afternoon youall silent now though!! No #HTTR today ðŸ˜‚ðŸˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama finally speaks on Russian hacking accusing Putin! should have spoken up b4 election would have seen different result! Now look!! #smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple words of the day... Never give up!! #happyweekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 degrees in the DMV that's just damn disrespectful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in paradise @craigsager you made watching sideline NBA interviews fun with your colorful outfits &amp; sunny disposition u will b missed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boo boo kitty clearly been doing crossfit!!  #EmpireWednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he just say the "burp their net worth" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ luscious funny #empire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read books not graffiti ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #empire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could Google it by why not ask youall..who won "The Voice" lastnight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's not a catch so I'm going to bed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're an NFL football team and u don't have a backup long snapper?? Smh eagles deserve to lose! #deadskins still stink though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok so got to the point where I see who Diamondback is and let me say I'm not impressed... #LukeCage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so tired of @DickieV gushing over these damn Dukies!! This team has no PG they play against a team with quality PG they get eaten!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just named CEO of Exxon Mobile as Secretary of State man who has close ties to Russia and Putin! Ponzi scheme to make Trump richer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprise surprise the Russians hacked the GOP according to US but didn't release the info to Wikileaks smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 episodes into @LukeCage and my only question is...who the hell is Diamondback? I guess I have to keep watching to find out!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#knicksnation my team not quite ready for prime time #NBAonESPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd in the East the Lebrons coming to the Garden 2morrow night..this teams not half bad! Maybe Hornacek knows what he's doing! #knicksnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is us.....who saw that one coming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Vegas betting on Boy George to win the new Celebrity Apprentice with Arnold.... those odds gotta be like 100-1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So let's get this straight they have an app for those who want to join the "mile high club" ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you gonna shoot a man in the back and walk? Judge Declares Mistrial in Walter Scott Police Shooting Case - TIME https://t.co/zXkdNQvTwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rajon Rondo unique player but how does an NBA Point Guard go 10 years in the league and never learn how to hit an open shot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching pregame for @chicagobulls Vs @cavs aka The Lebrons...saw some old clips of The Kings hairline thank God for hair club for men! #NBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fences looks like it's gonna be a classic! Denzel and Viola and August Wilson's writing on the big screen..that's gotta be a classic!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phylicia Rashad on Empire! Let me you what don't know what Ahmad Rashad was thinking cause she still fine! #blackdontcrack #Empire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is us...love this show man does it hit home for me for obvious reasons!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>