<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms @mysphoria (I just hate the myth that she DIDN'T appeal to people, because she did, pretty well.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms @mysphoria you mean, in the way she got more votes than anybody except Obama, historically...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms like I said, I get you, but every vote the left does NOT get makes NZF's chances of government better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms I understand where you're coming from, but abstaining from voting doesn't actually fix anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms you have two votes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brekekekiwi it wasn't *perfect*, but I didn't realise how good it was going to be to see a Disney movie that looked &amp; sounded like home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I cried as much as I did in Rogue One but for 100% diametrically opposite reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I'm late on this (I WAS ON A BOAT ALL JANUARY OK) but MOANA, guys, oh my god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin well, yeah, but a genuine military coup attempt - which would *not* be universal - would make it a way easier sell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin and a *failed* coup would be how good an excuse for a crackdown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having done this, for a short period of time: it FUCKING SUCKS, and I had pretty good assurance it wasn't forever. https://t.co/504Tgz6Fpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubiousStephen oh, how cool! I've sailed on the Falkor. It's a lovely ship. Didn't have SuBastian when I was on it, though - we took ROPOS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hungrymama @grumpybirb it made me mildly uncomfortable in the early 2000s but not like it would now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grumpybirb @hungrymama I really like all the Tor re-reads - they're very thoughtful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hungrymama imo it gets worse as the Dune books go on. Frank Herbet just did not like or trust women at ALL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hungrymama https://t.co/NRInhh4Uqq are doing a re-read of Dune right now and this is definitely front and centre as an item of discussion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester holy crap, glad you're ok! Hell of a way to end the week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk well, how can it be censorship when a government run by white dudes is doing it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we all spell "censorship"? Cool. https://t.co/9dlVIqU1LR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms this is why @mysphoria and I moved out on our own after three years of flatting and have never regretted it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms nah, I get it. I just wouldn't get your hopes up about it changing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms if it makes you feel better office kitchen horror stories seem to be universal, it's not just students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms I take it you've never flatted with PhD students then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not thinking about weather and equipment so much anymore. Ten months seems like a long time right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the time I was mostly thinking of weather/eqpt issues, getting samples from the deep sea is HARD and you should never count yr chickens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally last week I had a conversation saying I wasn't going to bank on getting samples from a cruise with US scientists later this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilith_grace all my sympathies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicgaston terrifyingly, yep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicgaston 'it's not that I think women shouldn't vote the world was just better when they didn't why are you making that face at me']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, everybody who was like 'maybe it won't be that bad'? IT'S BEEN LESS THAN A WEEK. https://t.co/0K2J9QFzhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That last retweet - I didn't know that about ResearchGate, but it's mostly been a source of spam-y emails for me anyway, so not surprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms there are a few US comedies I really enjoy (e.g. Brooklyn Nine-Nine, Better Off Ted) but it's a fingers of one hand thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms right, precisely, plus a lot of American-style humour (body parts are funny, etc) that just doesn't work for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms nah. I don't find the funny:hideously not funny ratio high enough to deliberately watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie @gtiso @johubris @BeeFaerie that's certainly one way to put it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie @gtiso @johubris @BeeFaerie while I was at sea this month we had salads that I swear were half raw tomato and half raw onion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case you haven't read enough about the #hydrothermadec cruise yet https://t.co/Ke9XO88jnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yinbagua never feel any shame about blocking trolls. you don't owe them your attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @mysphoria we should go here when you're back in town https://t.co/R7w80bd9bN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMack @tui_talk seems likely. Or is the favourite food of drop bears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk IDK but my money says they're poisonous, because Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, Wellington, if this is the 'summer' I missed out on, I'd like to petition to get back on the ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk also a great option, mostly meant that the key for hot climes/aircon is layering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brekekekiwi soooooo good. (Also, she's 13 now? Oh my god. I've known you forever.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brekekekiwi just about to fly back to Wgtn, huzzah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brekekekiwi 100% possible since I'm sitting in the bar/coffee place in the Akld domestic terminal as I type]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk cardigans are your friend in this environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our cruise is over, but somebody else's is just beginning...that's another ROV waiting to board the Sonne. https://t.co/gMcC1opT7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I...think that's my parents front and centre there. Go my parents! https://t.co/OTtrdsRDtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aroha and good wishes to everybody marching today in Wgtn/Akld/Chch and elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The North Island is lurking just over the edge of the world. Almost home! #hydrothermadec https://t.co/RSF3Wjla74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the ship I've been on for the last month! Come check it out next week, Aucklanders. https://t.co/GSf1vFJhJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our final science meeting &amp; Marcel from the ROV QUEST team is showing us the highlights tape. Twelve minutes of won… https://t.co/auv6ex8GaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen not in stuff I edit before sending out (e.g. pubs), at least I HOPE not. *goes back to check the grant I'm writing*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen I...totally do this a lot and I know it's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a bit bumpy as we slowly head south and the storm rolls north - glad we didn't get any of this while we were diving. #hydrothermadec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody talking about submitting their #abscicon abstracts is making me sad I can't go. :/ I hope you're all going to livetweet it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilith_grace so sorry to hear that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly everything you need to know about the NZ Herald https://t.co/xd0hl6bBFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merenbey luckily this is a problem which a) has an obvious solution and b) you are in full control of addressing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our last dive today! I'd say it feels like we just started but tbh it's been a long (and very productive) month at sea. #hydrothermadec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bonniej1 @dimsie I used to cover my eyes/ears a lot for that show before I noped out but not for embarrassment...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie cover my ears. The dialogue is usually the worst bit. Or just leave the room. I have a VERY low fictional embarrassment threshold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hot' in this case meaning &gt;&gt;100C. A source of some confusion between the biologists &amp; geologists at times -'hot' for bio is a lot lower!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at Brothers for our last couple of dives after we couldn't find any hot fluids at Rumble III. Perils of exploration! #hydrothermadec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk I think I'm going to be thrashing Beautiful Collision when I'm fifty, tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms it's all fun and games until somebody drops sulfuric acid on their bare foot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms a humanities thing that...sandals &amp; labs don't mix well, sadly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie this is one of my favourite weird facts ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen exactly. It's my first stop for info on many things, so I should make sure other people are getting the right info on my area!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen six years later, on the one hand, screw them, OTOH I probably shd find time for that now I actually know some things abt vents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen and a bunch of old white dudes immediately told me 1) it was a terrible idea and 2) I should go do it myself then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@methanoJen I once suggested at a Ridge2000 meeting a quick &amp; effective way to do vent outreach would be to fix up Wikipedia pages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secvalve it really does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secvalve I googled a bit, found it. (Took me a bit to figure out that suggestion...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secvalve nope, not that. Webpage (on phone) I need is 404ing anyway even though link is from a doc issued august 2016. Aaaaaaargh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, ok, just my laptop it seems - can access on my phone ok. On the same internet connection. Who the fuck knows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't access any .govt.nz sites right now. Admittedly am On A Boat, but internet is definitely working. Anyone else having issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These tweets brought to you by wondering if hydrothermal vents were discovered pre or post-GPS (it was post, btw, 1979.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very big and (to me) very featureless ocean, and yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to get a real feel for the scale of Māori achievement in settling NZ just spend a few days bobbing around in the Pacific]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Would have shown you a picture but the still semi-miraculous mid-ocean internet is not cooperating tonight)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status: making cooing noises at microbial mats and diffuse venting, like a real microbiologist #hydrothermadec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk aw thank you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we're exploring Rumble III, which is a very dynamic &amp; relatively unexplored volcano. Who knows what we'll find! #hydrothermadec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS I know, it's baked into the culture, it's that he doesn't get that *that's what people object to*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS amazing how the argument still so heavily relies on the basic premises of fear that drive current gun ownership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@testeeves thank you! So excited to be doing science in NZ again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secvalve hah, exactly like hackers and con shirts except mostly you only get one or two a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocking my new Sonne fleece (like most vent scientists I have a million ship &amp; ROV t-shirts, a fleece is a nice cha… https://t.co/DMzvaTLziD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cook hot seawater in ovens so I can count the bugs in it. Sometimes I do this on boats. https://t.co/ipMPWm7an0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilith_grace they're pretty neat-looking. Hopefully also scientifically interesting for my geologist colleagues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh, shiny - this is pyrite but some sulfide chimneys at Brothers do contain gold and copper, previous studies have… https://t.co/Wg38YsEmW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazyndara ugh I remember that feeling. Worst time of year to be looking. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilith_grace I think the blog has some much better official vent chimney pics, though obvs not from today: https://t.co/mtigKDFXtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilith_grace it looks way better when it's not my 3.5-year-old phone taking a picture of picture on a tv screen, I promise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn not really all the island are marine reserves and obvs we wouldn't want to interfere with reserves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn the engine workshop has pretty much everything, I'm sure we could figure something out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can make our own fresh water and catch fish or something. Turn off the internet connection. Seriously. So tempting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was told today on an engine room tour the Sonne has enough fuel to stay at sea for 2-3 months &amp; the news is making that seem a great idea]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>