<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking A!!! @cardiffdevils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 @SamDunleavy only twice down the toilet. But that's two too many in my eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 @SamDunleavy at least she released instantly this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 You can have two guesses what's under this rice? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚@SamDunleavy https://t.co/HREZW3NFb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildthingJ74 @SeanPhillips95 @dwalser38 if it was a mistake why didn't just stop skating when he saw his team were still on the blue line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElsJnr I know!! I just hope @Tacosteve10 and co don't think all us fans are all that bad! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElsJnr @SeanPhillips95 just brilliant! The bad thing is nowadays that's not the worst thing on there! ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPhillips95 I stopped reading when somebody wouldn't believe that David Clarke was a Brit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@block15blaze apparently absolutely terrible for the dressing room though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@covblazehockey mines @Stefhogarth for the blaze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sloc07 do you want to put your arm around me? Yes or no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinic @AVFTB sounds good mate. I'll buy you a beer to console you after two devils win in your own barn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinic @AVFTB oh yeah def should have got something on the play, just fishing for a response ðŸŽ£ðŸ˜‚. Yes mate I'm there. You??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steelershockey @hannahh1106 don't let Tony Smith find out! You'll be banned from home games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraeheadClan legends??Smith played 24 games for fucks sake ðŸ˜‚#walloffame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 Bristol 2:45 on Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV @cardiffdevils @covblazehockey Rejean Stringer's winning pen shot in the CC final!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielLawrenceP @cardiffdevils read our minds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finished 2016 without dying!! That is a high point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For New Years I'm giving up heroine! ðŸ’‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Year, New Me! ðŸ’xoxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andy_backhouse @brentwalton18 think most fans this year would prefer   UFC or boxing to hockey unfortunately!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SteveLawrence f you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thought of work tomorrow is killing my insides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will everyone stop dying please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SteveLawrence because your a muggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTemme @Mike_Danton so much room for activities!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Szpadtsy mate we are top of the league and one bad game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrontRunnerTV @officialEIHL any reason why your not showing up on my freeview??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones @BBCNews and now his watch has ended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTemme we're actually supposed to call it 'the service' now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simmsey @officialEIHL Nelson clearly headbutted Haddads stick!! Have you not watched the footage??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AskBordy @cardiffdevils @PBordy if you crash landed on a desert island, could you eat your own shoes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fourthlinewing didn't know you were involved in this! You should have tweeted about it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First ECHL game with the @OrlandoHockey! Still repping @cardiffdevils though! https://t.co/Aybh26uWKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 hell yeah!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pajo88 hell yeah! Can't wait mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkLoui5 well played bud! Hope your alright #warrior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fourthlinewing he hasn't got away with rape though has he. He was cleared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fourthlinewing will you stop fucking moaning about everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@covblazehockey apparently its playing one shift a period and having zero impact on the ice then #goon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrperkins send me a link to that bordy hit please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I get to power I'm going to make the 3 day weekend mandatory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noddylad1988 truly terrible. Offers nothing whatsoever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grizzly_Adams23 I don't! The guy is a total waste of an import for you. Doesn't score, doesn't hit and plays one shift a period! #Goon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PBordy Revenge will be sweet! Bring on Oct 8th!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlandoHockey already bought!! See you in November from the UK ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor from @hendrikx71 not shaking @AndrewLord17 hand tonight. Show some class!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffdevils well if you were you'd have sold one. Saved myself Â£100 though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PBordy just got a whole lot busier!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffdevils great choice! Can't wait for Sunday! Are those jerseys for sale?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlandoHockey what's the best way to buy tickets to a single game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 @SamDunleavy 4 tickets for both games please. Ha yes and not fist a toilet this time ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 two of my mates are coming as well. You ok to sort them tickets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 @SamDunleavy thanks mate. Is there a bus from the airport like last time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarmerG5 @SamDunleavy yes please G! Two for both games please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belfast booked for February! ðŸ€ðŸºðŸ’ @SamDunleavy @cardiffdevils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV any chance of any highlights of the preseason games so far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTemme no no you must have misunderstood! It's a D man blocking a shot! Only happens once every 3 years ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puckoff92 @johnscott_32 @cardiffdevils @steelershockey also don't pay their players. Just ask Fata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattc0625154 @johnscott_32 @cardiffdevils mate if you pull this one off you should become an agent ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pajo88 ha this looks awesome. So many places to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffdevils no offence but these are horrid ðŸ˜‚ Where's our logo gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pajo88 haha that's class! I genuinely can't wait @SamDunleavy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pajo88 @UniversalORL looks amazing. What ride is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPhillips95 shame it wasn't a house brick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDunleavy shit! Fucking autocorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can show your fucking nandos up your arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be proud people!! We may have lost but I've never felt more proud to be Welsh and I don't even like football that much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport @Hughesy_91 is it true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDunleavy **fingers crossed emoji**]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noddylad1988 will find out soon enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noddylad1988 I thought the same but it's a different Jarvis I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well it was my first Big Black Cock but boy was it tasty... https://t.co/HR0LreCTSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold the door]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Behind_The_Net again just can't see it. Why waste an import for 5 games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Behind_The_Net will played like 5 games? If that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Behind_The_Net even then I don't think he'd agree to that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Behind_The_Net can't see it. No way would bowns sign up to split the season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noddylad1988 you literally can't make up some of the stuff on that forum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPhillips95 @cardiffdevils from their previous tweet I'll go with Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the crime scene LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffdevils any chance of a signing to get through the rest of the week??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@block15blaze huge. Give us the chance to win every night. CC final this year he was the best player on the ice bar none!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shepherd68 @bulmanboi @Hughesy_91 haha credit to @John_pinnell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Wood, then Chyna and now Prince!! Bruce Forsyth must be shitting him self...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cardiffbus why is the number 23 scheduled at Welwyn Road at 7:44am 5-10 minutes late ever single day??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fourthlinewing yeah but G wasn't  @Simmsey best pal so it doesn't count]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV please stop using the corner camera as the angle is terrible and can't see anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simmsey @DontSayF disgusting hit! Should be banned for life ðŸŽ£ðŸŽ£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tomskii16 @tigertemme what did he do in the hand shakes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitchey16 @belfastgiantstv shout out for me and Drew Peacock watching the webcast from Cardiff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DontSayF almost like we need to win on Wednesday ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV @IceArenaWales @cardiffdevils or you could just put the highlights up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTemme were we at the same rink? Love the screens and could hear every word from block 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wait is finally over @cardiffdevils @IceTimeTV https://t.co/0tZNIfweo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV @cardiffdevils any chance of a picture of the Devils changing rooms?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lovett1993 agreed mate. Without bowns you would have done it in reg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IceTimeTV just pure passion from @AndrewLord17! The guy is Mr @cardiffdevils. #proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0nejob @FarmerG5 @cardiffdevils i lost my shit when he scored that!! Great goal]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>