<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LearnKotch true, so many ways to get free PD too. L&amp;D need to model learning outside of courses too! #walkthetalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BerylOldham ha ha, maybe I'm super early for next year ;) thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm curating video for a project I'm working on, it's great when someone else has done the work for you! #curatedcontent #curatefirst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you taking charge of your own professional development this year? Read what I'm… https://t.co/8ozTYkw2cR https://t.co/485aACodUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow I'm so lucky!! Now to unconnect with this scammer #scams on linkedin https://t.co/EnG6nBDTlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to hear my #contentcuration model has been cited in Jane Hart's new MWL book!! Thanks Jane! @C4LPT #MWL https://t.co/BYFPiStwE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to work after a month caravaning break, feeling revitalized and excited to see what's been happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a tight budget? Check out this Webinar in the NY #eLearning #video https://t.co/E3v9NgFpd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snapsynapse I'm thinking about getting a new email addy and starting over... one for junk, one for social, one for work only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with an arrogant person is assuming they are smarter than simple person not the case #xmaschallenge conversations without #no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1opter yes and it takes a lot of time investment until you figure out if you've got it wrong ;) https://t.co/Jc0v7CoXPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handy little tool for #elearning #Audio Very portable, good quality and simple to use #edtech #H1zoom https://t.co/E0lendyOS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! Reflect little and often builds greater learning over time. Writing (video or podcast) adds to commitment… https://t.co/NxUS1YgCzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that crazy time of year. Christmas deadlines for all work projects! # traffic jam #holidayscoming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a tough week influencing beyond rapid elearn product. More to do next week #elearning/learning more than one thing and way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway I like your poll how did you do that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flipchartguy ha ha I'm my boss (so mean) I read blogs as smaller. It's how I juggle work and 2 children under 5. Books for holidays for now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great list @flipchartguy if only I had time to read a book, maybe Xmas holidays https://t.co/0TbrGwrDXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great post on content #curation from @AndersPink https://t.co/YoruIS0klB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M7.8 Kaikoura Quake: Future Scenarios and Aftershock Forecasts - Earthquake - GeoNet https://t.co/Kkfpok6hjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LearnKotch @ActivateLearn thanks for the retweet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to a remote contract communicating through email, much prefer #slack or other #collaborativetools so much faster being less formal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juanblanco76 I love to have a couple of very different contracts going at a time, helps improve skills for future… https://t.co/bCxTf5ML3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BerylOldham thanks a lot, glad you enjoyed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LearnKotch sorry predictive text Con :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LearnKotch thanks Content aftershocks starting to calm down check out https://t.co/fzlwMyPnaL #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media to supercharge your professional development https://t.co/SogsoWGC7J https://t.co/ZzvjMeWBYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished my first blog post after 5 mth break, scheduled tonight, excited to be writing again # blogging about # learning &amp; #socialmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway just what I needed a reason why. Putting it on my learning plan, thanks! https://t.co/joBgfn7nps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway it was funny at first not anymore:( hope my imagination is just being overactive freaking out a bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#woltip dipping into parallel industries, IT, marketing, SoMe and comms adds richness into learning solution tool box - wide view #WOLweek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LearnKotch great practical way implementing wol in your team -spreading the joy #WOLweek #wol https://t.co/QAR0F6tzsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wolweek purpose: getting back flow after 5 mth work break #woltip SoMe supercharges flow! Going to start days with 15 mins SoMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway thanks for sharing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActivateLearn thanks for sharing your #woltip :) I'm going to join in too! https://t.co/37M0XjWYfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway awesome thanks for sharing #workingoutloud going to invest some time in those :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway not sure I've got it right on my comp, txt BadA55 link? Great reminder I must invest more time in coding... any tips? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway @criticallearner @elearningcoach I like to borrow UX/UI design from big websites then nav intuitive based on prior experiences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway @elearningcoach yes perfect timing for me have just been asked to update a very dusty looking Moodle UI :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elearningcoach @MelMilloway Great tips again, thanks for sharing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 20 Learning And Development Value Tweeters https://t.co/sBXGj21Td3 via @elearnindustry @bizlearningdude thanks for sharing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good tips!: 4 Things to Know When Using Layers in Storyline https://t.co/ib9vJ6dUKr @eLearningBros]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great video why implementing social learning is more than the technology https://t.co/cP0bbL6fTB @JeremyScrivens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monthly inspiration - Clive Sheppard reflections #blendedlearning @clivesheppard… https://t.co/NoJnAVhZo0 https://t.co/clfbxHY4zU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Webinar next Weds on Augmented Reality. I'm going are you? Check it out https://t.co/sLQ9mAOz7J @Bloomrecruit @NanasHype]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bound to be another great session Wed 18 May @NZATD @kineopacific Learning Insights https://t.co/s5KxqUXeFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to connect with someone in sales and marketing only to find they didn't have a linked in profile. #strange or #ironic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryantracey Ha the motivation to 'tick the box' is strong there, more important than wasting time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Design Blended Learning that is Engaging and Effective https://t.co/NyxEjP6eDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cliveshepherd webinar 20th April on blended learning. Get your questions in now! https://t.co/WfSzfBraWe #blendedlearning @Bloomrecruit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blended learning expert Clive Shepherd will be presenting our first Cyber Chats with Lead Learners webinar on https://t.co/QPB8rYTTqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out more about Content Curation and how it's relevant to you at the @NZATD event next Weds 13 April https://t.co/S3CsK0u73a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Content Curation in Your Skill Set? It Should Be. by David  Kelly : Learning Solutions Magazine https://t.co/OKeLVX4RCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Killer Content Curation Tools, Keep Your Blog and Social Media Rich via @pantelischio https://t.co/qebZGOp16I https://t.co/bno9f50mCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on developing flexible modern content #MWL #contentcuration #learning https://t.co/pvOVKXEQrl https://t.co/XlYYozLDT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog: The art and skill of content curation #contentcuration #mwl #elearning https://t.co/n79BJGXRrj https://t.co/Mc5B3ePswx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How content curation for learning can be extended way beyond courses https://t.co/4cDPIfb0cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content curation for courses, your role, pros and cons, process. Thoughts from @elearningcoach #contentcuration https://t.co/AeV09bDhPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great list of tools and content curation services @RobinGood via @ZEEFcom | @scoopit https://t.co/BadEBwBXts #contentcuration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Wellington NZ on 16th March make some time for our gamification interactive session https://t.co/RbMDUY74Ll @NZATD #gamification]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content curation how can it be used? https://t.co/c9UzOkBwHf https://t.co/2LJi4twZhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A framework for content curation https://t.co/H0Bqajs6MI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Makes A Great Curator Great? How To Distinguish High-Value Curation From Generic Republishing https://t.co/qyXpuENb9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scoop.it | Content Curation &amp; Content Marketing Software https://t.co/17hcxdeD7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scoop.it | Content Curation &amp; Content Marketing Software https://t.co/pk7fZ0VGpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this original idea of considerate pavement use #communitydesign #design https://t.co/AgEeRO2MNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to have a geeky husband - home office with 3 screens now #surfacepro #efficiency @BarryMinister https://t.co/OvDzxMQhkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those in Wellington: NZATD event on 17th of Feb on Instructional Design - come and join us #nzatd https://t.co/TkwsvEoPTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A – Z of my work place learning https://t.co/tI5fBDGmNt https://t.co/qydNRubQxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflecting 2015 and learning 2016 https://t.co/Sr2yPcf881 https://t.co/GjiUDiyp3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ complaint in, switched to 2degrees 6 mths ago V account not closed properly, and told can't have access to my customer notes!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ just experienced terrible customer service you even make it difficult to switch providers!! Seriously unhappy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to work smarter, how about curating content and repurposing it. Check out this example… http://t.co/JFJil8fsF1 http://t.co/J21c9koir6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattybee on back channel with you :) #learnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#learnx wish i was there. on back channel thanks for sharing eventifier @LearnKotch #learnx2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stipton thanks for great experience of my 1st twitter chat #OzLearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OzLearn get my curation tools in order old school currently using bagtheweb time to upgrade the system #ozlearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downside to twitter chat can't type on my phone fast enough, and adverse to texting. I need a better system ;) #OzLearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To learn twitter and share with others who are also passionate about learning #ozlearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience and connect, get warmed up for work after 2 week break ;) #ozlearn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lorraine minister, Wellington NZ, 1st twitter chat and 1st #OzLearn hi @LearnKotch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recapping #elearnz2015 good blog explaining the difference between NFC and iBeacon http://t.co/V7rGI0RZNo #locationlearning #elearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bone conducting headphones you can hear and listen at the same time. @LearnKotch it's surreal and cheap http://t.co/4KeN1MwUZV #audio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did an awesome VC design course, interactive small groups with elearningguild - no chance to use it @nolen_smith @kineopacific #elearnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube great for self learning @LearnKotch that's how we got a home built pizza oven - yum #elearnz #elearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome session by optimism great to see why you won the award #elearnz #elearning http://t.co/pGnvtoEc59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the virtual classrooms (not webinars) in NZ - anyone know? #elearnz #elearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free learning videos from guru Nigel Paine watch ondemand http://t.co/H0wrDwvE6H #elearnz #elearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the onboarding journey from newbies perspective and reach business goals perspectives at the right time for the newbies #elearnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love ❤ putting the people first on day 1 onboarding not technical content Tina Griffin #elearnz @kineopacific]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blogging is my professional development - reflect learn and share http://t.co/P52vFFybCV #elearnz love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[finding the back channel http://t.co/8QIChlFY0e and curating - good advice from @learnkotch #elearnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[book recom by @learnkotch for social media http://t.co/KvXLiIVdnY #elearnz #socialmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curate variety to keep a open mind and disrupt #elearnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And had to stop to milk a cow outside #elearnz http://t.co/fFJIAtJjFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be late costume requirements for #elearnz http://t.co/cJKDCX81nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting people moving and interacting great ID in you session Anna Kingston @ #elearnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise worlds from Richard Durham #elearnz give up the control with games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for 9 clubs, help me out #elearnz this is me http://t.co/bEZKOMi4WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived in Auckland excited to learn more and meet folks at #elearnz tomorrow http://t.co/oR1bq48QtR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>