<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobeChadFinn I swear I blacked out. I didn't notice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti the pats have arguably played in the 5 greatest Super Bowls ever played. 36, 38, 42, 49, and obviously 51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti he's absolutely right about that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich everything I hoped it would be and more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich I'm not a religious person, but that was a miracle if I've ever seen one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer well Bert, all records are meant to be broken, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk someone hasn't forgotten FCC v. Fox Television Studios...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_McKone he was the best player on the floor when NC State beat Duke a couple weeks back. Sucks that his team isn't all that good though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_McKone Yeah there are a lot of good point guards for sure. Fultz and Ball are obvious, but I think Dennis Smith Jr. is pretty nice too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart any prospects in mind that you like for the Celtics? Josh Jackson from Kansas seems like their kind of player to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DAonCBS you forgot Curtis Martin. But that's okay. You're not the only one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelFhurley doing his best Donald trump impression obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray is the #drivefor5bus swinging by Washington, D.C.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray @l @hardy985 @ second on the D.C. question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray the fact that orange is last is a crime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theMMQB it'll be pretty awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart death, taxes, and the patriots killing the steelers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk The Patriots and the NFL have the best relationship! There is no better relationship! #spicersays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart yeah, and if our team is fortunate enough to win today they had better be ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente yeah, only difference though is that Bill doesn't go on TV and talk about how he outworks everybody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenGriffeyRules And it's not even halftime yet! 🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottzolak I mean can he play corner? Because that's what they need right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poetic_kid @AlbertBreer god, sarcasm really doesn't work on Twitter does it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer what a throw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer I mean how do you take a personal foul penalty on 3rd and 18? How dumb is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich have you checked out Walton calling the title game in his Uncle Sam suit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer that's some of the worst secondary play you'll ever see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer Dolphins tackling execution on the other hand...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart well he should be watching the game right? Oh wait, he doesn't do regular season NBA...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenGriffeyRules that was a bold move John]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat god that was awful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CelticsHub refs missed a terrible over the back too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeGiardi what do you think the chances are for Pats-Giants III in Houston?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RapSheet maybe we should think about the fact that this guy was passed out behind the wheel of his car in the middle of the street first...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SI_PeterKing because the patriots did it Peter, c'mon!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wingoz oh c'mon, what could go wrong? Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucktodd I'm sorry all of trump's bluster on this issue should surprise no one who has been paying any attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich I only hope Brandon can avoid Fred's negativity vortex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart this take is almost as dumb as your Chris Sale trade proposal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlombardifoxtv and I have no interest in watching them have no interest in playing tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops that's an excellent question, especially when the rankings are determined by a group of "neutral" athletic directors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer put em in baby! I want to see some buckeye tears tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich if that was lebron, it would've been an and one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart got a favorite college prospect yet jimmy? Need a felger and mazz NBA draft board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport yeah, but only one plays in a dome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart @bigjimmurray Mitchell. Got two hands on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart but the jets are playing well so we can just stop casting blame in the second quarter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottzolak he sucks but at least he's better than Brian Kelly on the tool scale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer the business of college sports is literally the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SherrodbCSN this is what happens when you have a bunch of lawyers writing rules for a basketball league]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregABedard finally, someone standing up for proper grammar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart so we're going to build this thing up and then rip Danny when it doesn't happen, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SI_PeterKing he'll start that game Peter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray I heard teams in the Chinese Arena Football League may be interested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelFhurley all I can do is laugh at that. That was so bad. 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenGriffeyRules you worry too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart what a shame...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjones985 that could be the worst quarter of basketball I've ever seen in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops it's hillsborough county Seth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray who is going to win New Hampshire Murray?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti it's only three runs mazz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray Dude, they've played two innings haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports that was wet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk so if an offensive lineman in Houston was concerned about being hit, he'd meet with him too, correct?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JumboHart I thought he was kidding but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray dude, in those conditions, from 51, that's a great kick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marc_Bertrand it's called a draw Beetle 🇬🇧]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray anyone want to ask mazz how many times he's watched Julius Randle play basketball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HallieJackson #trumpthepuppet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJamesStewart just keep swinging jimmy. You'll be right on something eventually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes @nytopinion still holding my breath for that student loan question...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jheil still waiting for that first student loan question. I won't hold my breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnston985 look at him standing there menacingly behind her. Did anyone talk to him about body language at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HallieJackson what's with trump's breathing problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpriceNFL that's not much of a claim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardy985 excellent decision sir. I've been doing that all afternoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich poor Donald just getting taken apart in front of 100 million people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitlockJason I think you need to listen and stop tweeting for a bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelFhurley did bill o'brien wait until we got back from commercial to challenge just for laughs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti "they cheeped out Mike!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamMKaufman @CelticsHub absolute steal in the mid second round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franfraschilla horrible for the league and you know it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorTwellman easily wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredToucher haha tell us how you really feel Fred!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richeisen sucks I had to waste 5 minutes of my life listening to that clown talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleChris4204 @ColinCowherd then you're almost as relevant as the Boston Celtics. Almost...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd why don't we stick to these playoffs first before talking about that irrelevant has been franchise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray pretty sure those are tears of joy...but you tried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESPNAndyKatz is he sure??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops that's why they pay you the big bucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBilas that's really profound. Thanks for sharing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostSports eh don't think that's quite right but you tried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richeisen is that what you're calling this atrocity of a football game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyMassarotti my pillow is tougher than both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell can't wait....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @foxnewspolitics @realDonaldTrump how can you bomb and take the oil?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMikeWilbon alright coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer dude with the double negative?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenVolin alright coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keefe21 he's the only one]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>