<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of time to sit at home and think on the couch! #loser https://t.co/l4N3UOFGUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tear up the worst deal in the history of all deals! #IranDeal https://t.co/ITaeQYuS2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the immigration ban so far. My only criticism of it would be not enough countries on the list. 7 not enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS has been #winning since Inauguration Day. Keep up the good work Mr. President!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the stupid zombie you mindless rube. Barry O accumulated more debt than all previous presidents COMBINED! https://t.co/LbqaUgjnzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dishonest media! https://t.co/gC1Gc2GtAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear liberal psycho, she lost. Get over it https://t.co/96DtLjGbfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glory, glory, hallelujah ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸ https://t.co/xvYhtHFBMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum is a loser!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MyPresidentIsPatriotic #MyPresidentIsTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @JoyTaylorTalks were wise, she'd take up a career @ crooked @CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps if @JoyTaylorTalks would cover sports more than politics, FS1's ratings would go up! Can't rely on Skip forever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbvy435 you better worry about paying rent on time, broke boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sptguy33 you're a rube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StillAKilla85 not true at all. Hence why I don't like speech that divides us, the American people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfollowing @JoyTaylorTalks because she can't help but promote her grossly liberal views that divide us. Stick to the day job sweetieðŸ‘‹ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realJeffreyLord does an excellent job representing common sense on crooked @CNN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for romo  https://t.co/zCuAT6OzPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Redskins Nation" on at the bar, what a sad and sorry program. Attempts to make skins look good when in fact very bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fakenews @cnn would of course point out Barry O's fake tears! https://t.co/1qse8oPM6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course we're all happy to see Barry O go, but I'm also very excited to never see/hear dumb @PressSec Josh Earnest ever again after 1/20!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washed up @KeithOlbermann is a total hack. No real fan base. The guy is a total dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LmaoðŸ‘‡ðŸ» this guys so lame https://t.co/sCmnpLDjEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Romo is better  https://t.co/L6Ss35BYL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump please #LockHerUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shame https://t.co/U3dFRTFEjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I fly, I will choose to ONLY fly @Delta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for @realDonaldTrump to take office. People like @omgAdamSaleh will think twice before pulling these terror stunts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No playoffs for the soft @Redskins  - But with players like @_willcompton, @cbaker92redskin, and @KirkCousins8 what more can you expect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurgerzBusty @TAOShinaishin @SkinsGM_ well said, Mr. Burger. These redskins fans are fickle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must be smart &amp; vigilant. We cannot afford another catastrophe due to political correctness. I applaud @Delta  https://t.co/CgrWBsEAcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao, remember that time Mediocre Kirk Cousins compared the "redskins" to the @spurs ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/FJsjmKzctr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald is totally unhinged and a complete left wing tool. Another lunatic lefty that can't back up his claims with facts. Dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, @kurteichenwald is a real lunatic! Totally unhinged and spreading false reports w/ no credible source! Sad! Total dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald shut up loser you had forever to answer the question &amp; you kept dodging/filibustering. You're a liberal clown - A true dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing he did more of for the economy was add more debt - by double the amount! Sad! https://t.co/lGuAH5rKzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very pleased The Donald chose a world class businessman, and not another #PoliticalHack https://t.co/wsJmARQUaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for #maddogmattis to run the @DeptofDefense #MakeAmericaSafeAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for Tony to return https://t.co/WCATYBA09i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need tony romo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to college footballs best player, @Lj_era8 on winning the @HeismanTrophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of hating, take notes ðŸ“ https://t.co/l4GJn5JDme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, @RepMikeCapuano is a true clown! Another liberal lunatic that thinks he understands the intricacies of banking! He is a real dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaddukes LMAO ðŸ˜‚ good luck ever beating the #DallasCowboys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No but he could run for President if he were a woman named Clinton! @CNN should be ashamed! Bias and totally wrong! https://t.co/Rd42sM1U2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be nice if we could waterboard @tariqnasheed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton, who is a sore loser, is now flirting with being prosecuted for her e-mails thanks to her campaign's sorry recount efforts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, @timkaine is a loser - what else would you expect! https://t.co/ucInybAov0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dckeith @chaddukes lmao you skins fans are pathetic. I PRAY you give cousins that max contract ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao my mans talkin bout LAST YEAR ðŸ˜‚ #TypicalSorryAssDeadskinsFan https://t.co/DvvgIqXX3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao my cowboys will take the sorry "redskins" any time, any where. #GamesWonOnTheFieldNotOnTwitter ðŸ˜‚  https://t.co/aKHSOi9t5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and no https://t.co/mQgkl9UxuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorReid, also known as Broken Harry, isn't aware that WE elected Trump! His party tries to divide Americans! https://t.co/Bw1Ssb96t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine is a LOSER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, @KeithOlbermann is a real nasty guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol clearly zeek is the MVP ðŸ™„ https://t.co/HpXtngG4iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm almost certain that @JoyTaylorTalks voted for @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clementefan87 nowhere in the second amendment does it discuss regulations. It's a right to bear arms, not a privilege.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, crazy liberals like @WeNeedHillary are comparing the American people's Election Day to 9/11. Lunatics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to:
1. #BuildTheWall 2. #repealobamacare 3. #BanMuslims from entering the U.S. 4. Cancel global warming payments to UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought you said you'd rather lose every cent than see Donald in the Oval Office?ðŸ¤” https://t.co/QmeCsIVJzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMFAO!!! ðŸ‘‡ðŸ»ðŸ˜‚ at least you concede Trump is a 2 term president ðŸ‘ŒðŸ» https://t.co/IdOoew366a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AD_Strider how's your degree in sociology working out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic, now your fans of the 2nd amendment ðŸ¤” https://t.co/kNGtvnhsMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, thanks to the Trump victory you'll still be allowed to partake in your 2nd amendment rightðŸ˜‰ https://t.co/T93rVynuwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's deport this guy with the Muslims  https://t.co/VytrzVVrdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oxminaox oh yes he is lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Real change starts with immediately repealing and replacing Obamacare!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr GOD bless you both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump we love you Mr. President!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianefallon is truly one of the nastiest, most disgusting people on earth #filth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they know our policy will finally be #AmericaFirst  https://t.co/kb8KHsPFGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @HillaryClinton Jay-Z's lyrics certainly preach a message of women's rights and respect toward women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, the failing @nytimes reported a profit loss of over 95% this past quarter! Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the US continues to lose our jobs.  @realDonaldTrump SOS https://t.co/RXO5wv3tEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially with a guy like Kirk Cousins at QB lmao ðŸ˜‚ #clown https://t.co/fPVi7CRHhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DebatePoll who won the third and final #PresidentialDebate #StrongerTogether #MakeAmericaGreatAgain #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PresidentialElection #Poll #DonaldTrump #HillaryClinton #MakeAmericaGreatAgain #StrongerTogether who has your vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyTaylorTalks @adamcald11 way to use dishonest video editing to twist reality. You could have a long career at crooked @CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNBCi funny because Barry O is a shitty public speaker. Dude lives off the TelePrompTer lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan is an undercover liberal! Loves raising the budget for his master and overseer, Barack Hussein!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zjensen6 @CNN funny she just laughs lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Poll - Who won tonight's #PresedentialDebate #Debate #DonaldTrump #HillaryVsTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CowboysNation  - join me in cheering on the #RavensFlock today against the LAME redskins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to bring @CLewandowski_ back to the campaign, @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally never doubted.  https://t.co/YvP4wsQ3JG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericsshadow is a nasty liberal! He loves his candidate who lies under oath, loses to ISIS, fails in foreign policy &amp; leaks Top Secret data!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly a missed holding call. Anyways, who won the game?ðŸ¤”#DallasCowboys  https://t.co/z05KFEttXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe to say biased @brianstelter will be voting for Crooked/Unhealthy Hillary. Like his masters, he is a surrogate of the Clinton campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaddukes @chiefofdc Kirk cousins needs help he has no playmakers around him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaddukes @blackberrysmoke @KyleCoroneos @MusicBoad great Chiefin' music ðŸ’¨ðŸ”¥ðŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News: @KirkCousins8 again receives NO criticism from nasty DC media after another terrible performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just now realize this? Skins won't win til 8 is gone. So many weapons, his water gun arm is holding team back! https://t.co/NXmJ7NRLUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Track_King21 @radsam_ @SJJ_ATC @localblactivist lol were really gonna dispute if the nat'l debt has doubled or not since 09? Ur all idiots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeLo216 my homies wages ain't gone up in 8 years, MY PEOPLE still struggling - Barack let US down!âœŠðŸ¿âœŠðŸ¿âœŠðŸ¿âœŠðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeLo216 has everything to do with what you said. Explains why he gets no respect from our ppl. I'm a brother and Barack let OUR ppl down âœŠðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJJ_ATC are you literally that stupid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeLo216 what happened to that $10 trillion he spent over the last 8 years? Or 33,000 emails?ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@localblactivist ya probably because he doubled our national debt and has failed miserably in foreign affairs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HOFMaddenCoach oh ok thanks for the insight]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>