<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just bought a new lipstick. Don't even care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do I buy myself for Valentine's Day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're doing your best to stay engrossed in your daily routine... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I joined the gym. Tomorrow I cancel my first session at the gym #fitfam #firspiration #strongnotskinny #GirlBoss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hadid sisters aren't as stunning as everyone makes them out to be ðŸ¤” especially Bella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lewismccann16 I'll ignore that spelling mistake since it's your birthday ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lewismccann16 happy birthday Lewis. Have the best day x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually can't take a piss in peace in this place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently I was shaking some girl on the bus coming home on Friday asking if it was @louisecee_xox its wasn't ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a natural tendency to run yourself into the ground, b... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to make everything worse. My bus is 10 mins late ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And get in trouble for being late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope one of them slips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are children so excited by a puddle that's iced over? Stop screaming and get to school ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the scoreboard at motherwell ever worked properly ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't understand why people enter competitions to "win a wedding" fucking save up or don't get married at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is anything but real #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is the worst housemate. Her swearing is horrific #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly don't think it's fair that at 21 I'm getting made to share a room with a 9 year old ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long before I fuck this one up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callum_Warren thanks! Need to look good at the wedding eh d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callum_Warren putting it all back on, on cheat day ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ate half a jar of onion chutney on garlic crackers and that sums up why I'm single]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to go back to Belfast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've avoided wearing bras at all costs the past few days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're ready to dive headfirst into a passion project, feeling... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sick of this Trump shite as well. Why do these people encourage him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who does Theresa May actually think she is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't understand why people feel the need to gossip about my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danny Boyle talking about Bowie on Graham norton had me in tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officially lost half a stone ðŸ’ªðŸ¼ skinny in no time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're reluctant to show your hand just yet, preferring to wat... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When can I go to bed without crying over a boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet to meet a boy who doesn't lie constantly. Fucking sick of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I get the jersey turnpike out tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it's a good day at work when you break out the jersey turnpike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole again by atomic kitten is still a jam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A casual conversation with your partner or a close friend may ... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually hate Nicola. Is there any need to say "fucking" and "fuck" so much #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate people who park in the bus stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love a 20 min wait in the cold for a bus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OfficialSteps tragedy has just come on in work. So buzzin. Faves for life ðŸ‘°ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting enough rest should be top priority now, whether or not... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love doing morning entry and seeing dead bodies on gurneys just left outside ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ what a great start to the morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So in love with my tattoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's done! So in love. Thank you so much miss_froo ðŸ’•ðŸ° https://t.co/ekFvy9qljz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just u followed Liam Payne because he said something was poppin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You take it personally when something doesn't go your way now.... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhSPMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never seen a top so me #BoyBye https://t.co/Z86rHhfp9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gives me the fear when people don't use mascara to blend their real lashes and false lashes together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In such a bad mood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may be inspired or overwhelmed by irrepressible waves of c... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caitlinmcnabx thanks gal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want a huge bowl of pasta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel so free in a sports bra ðŸ’ðŸ¼ what a great decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When David just realises now that I can be a wee snake ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Soz not Soz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may be inspired or overwhelmed by irrepressible waves of c... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay I take back what I said. Ed sheerans new songs are v good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People need to grow up and learn to take banter ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may act as if everything is copacetic today, but you're li... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I pay my taxes for it to go to scroungers like this??? @Number10gov ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a job then Hun ðŸ™‚ https://t.co/EX8yzaT8Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6lbs off in 2 weeks ðŸ’ªðŸ¼ skinny in no time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationship dynamics grab your attention today, requiring tha... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ken it's bad when ur 15 year old cousin rips you for being single]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I slept in this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Beckycunningx @themaine hope they come here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of concentration and effort are necessary now to make a... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I question if I'm the fuckboy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As from tomorrow I've officially given up wearing a bra unless I'm going out ðŸ•ºðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chloe ferry is absolutely disgusting #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kirstyf27 so nice ðŸ˜ 8-10 weeks of fleeky lashes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have I never had my lashes lifted sooner? They look amaze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Beckycunningx ðŸ¤”I'll go myself then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When predictive text gets u ðŸ™ˆ https://t.co/shlGw8N8wF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirBroxiBear comedian as well I see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirBroxiBear I assume you are qualified in that area so I'd be in capable hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirBroxiBear time and place babes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best place for maximum support sports bras??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offered to pay for my mum and dads flights to Rome and they said "we'll see" it's like they don't want to go on holiday with me ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnabelleTayl0r to be fair that makes you question if she's telling the truth or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you fix today seems to create new problems, like th... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen someone flush their hamster down the toilet. Wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do boys get offended when you tell them their dogs are cuter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the bouncer tries to chuck you out https://t.co/4wp1nv8DqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting beyond a joke with the alarm at work ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a fine as well??? Disgusting. There should be a prison sentence there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has David Goodwillie just being charged for rape now? Absolute joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels good to boldly state your needs without much of a fil... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhSPMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst part of Christmas being over is @emmas7573 can't listen to me sing all I want for Christmas twice a day ðŸ™„ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieEdmond turned it off. Can't stand Bella Thorne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone watched the DUFF?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remembered I don't start till 10:30 tomorrow. What a time to be alive ðŸ•ºðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished Brooklyn nine-nine. What to watch now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many neurofen would it take to finish me off ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels good to boldly state your needs without much of a fil... More for Leo https://t.co/8QBHrhBenY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The death penalty should be brought back for people like him ðŸ˜¡ two poor innocent girls robbed of their life. Disgusting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually makes my blood boil that Ian Huntley wants a sex change. Clearly only doing it to get an easier time in prison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if Calum Best would ever go with Chloe #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chloe's glasses are just offensive. Not even slightly cool #CBB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>