<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnquietDreams @Kitsgirl1 We use Patrick for the export market and keep Brigid for ourselves. That'll work, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman I really should sleep at some point. It's next month already! Goodnight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kitsgirl1 Are we allowed two patron saints? Brigid and Patrick? @UnquietDreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman I will of course. And I have to keep getting things done. One small step at a time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman But for now, getting things done is a good start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman I'm alive. I'm happy. I'm getting things done. I would be getting things done faster if the courts service was quicker (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman Hopefully! I'll put it on my to do list now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datbeardyman I'm still torn between whether the cover for this, or for Death and Duty is my favourite! Two years though... Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahO_Connell acceptance, but there will be support from sources you never thought of. It will be difficult, but it will be worth it (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahO_Connell It's a very well put together piece, and so true. Be positive going into it, be confident, don't expect universal... (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahO_Connell The first thing. I am still the same person. THIS. A MILLION TIMES THIS! And being trans* doesn't define you as a person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianMcCarthy @RebelLipstick In test 2 I... never did the reverse. Was about to when someone took the space. Examiner signed it off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelLipstick A nice examiner will put your mind at ease. Then you can concentrate solely on the task at hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelLipstick My first was a pr*ck too. Failed. Asked where it went wrong. "I  can't tell you". But how can I learn? "I can't tell you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelLipstick It helps if the examiner is really nice (my 2nd was), but take it easy, and do the basics really well (observation++)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelLipstick Calmness helps. I was pulled up on progress (grade 2), but examiner said that I was making sure I didn't fuck up. (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickoshea I would have thought at this stage, anyone old enough to regularly use the word "dude" would be too old to rush anywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ I agree completely with the good Captain! Congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kitsgirl1 'Tis far from stained glass windows ye were reared! Oh, wait. It's Ireland. Ye were reared under one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Queen_UK I hope, Ma'am, that you stand ready to offer to move in, set up a Governor, and pretend Independence never happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixiephoeynicks @ClaireByReverie @wildechicblog It would just be me in a corner with a bottle of champagne not tweeting about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixiephoeynicks @ClaireByReverie @wildechicblog Exactly! But there wouldn't ab any actual awards, because it just creates problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByReverie @wildechicblog We need awards for bloggers who don't do awards. You'd both win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lornajaneduffy There is just something special about Copenhagen. An amazing place to be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unakavanagh Probably the most random tweet I've seen today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EimearMcCormack I can think of worse ways to spend a weekend! Congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByReverie Signed. Though by March, the only people who can get visas will be white American males #ImNotReallyJoking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe If that is what being an "influencer" means, then frankly I'd tell people where to shove that title. Disgusting behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue I'm not allowed to discuss my contractual arrangements :-P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsCherrySue You can't replace him, so... Have fun furniture shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jim_Sheridan More and more Orwellian. As I see it, Trump is BB. American people are Eurasia, Eastasia &amp; The Party, part bringing their doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlamityJane1 Your point being? You don't need to have a cat for one to suddenly appear claiming rights over your couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlamityJane1 That's about right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquidgeMundo @ChirpsLilRedHen Virgin have gotten a bit better since they started on the new separate modems. The one in the TV box... :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lovelygirlybits Must you post these things when you know my bank balance can't cope with the cuteness! @TooFaced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @lidl_ireland for letting us know a #Valentines outfit should be bra, knickers and hold-up's. I prefer cl… https://t.co/6O7smZy4fY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blacknight Fair play for trying so hard to get things sorted. Guess it proves technology is great when working, but hell when it isn't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByReverie @totalmakeupadd There is that benefit of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireByReverie @totalmakeupadd Though the couple of quid to enter may be worth it for the few hours of hope it gives you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd @ClaireByReverie You know what they say... If you're not in, you can't lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeauttruth Sometimes it does! I agree completely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeauttruth Good choice! Enjoy the vino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patcourtenay Say Pat, while you're there retweeting me. Could you give it 30 mins and play Blondie - Maria for me? Will be in the car then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickoshea @instagram @facebook That is very true. I hope someone can some up with an option that helps you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickoshea @instagram being a Facebook brand, maybe you could try with them too? Might be able to point you in the right direction @facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patcourtenay That's impressively cool. Without the pickups, it looks kinda like a Nordic concert hall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Could you make it sound any more Orwellian? It's scary enough as it is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Creativeyoke Hmmm very tempting! That's definitely not the worst that could happen! @RyanGosling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redlips_redhair Was trying to remember if it was arm or shoulder, but yay for being able to do something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redlips_redhair Woohoo! Hope the arm feels good after!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ There's a Lemon gif for anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fluffanella We just have to wait and see I guess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fluffanella Not in those exact words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fluffanella Would they say yes to a trans* person with more baggage than a package holiday flight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must be insane. I've just applied for a ticket to the Late Late Show... Valentine's Singles show. What's the worst that could happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kitsgirl1 Glad to hear it. Enjoy the nap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kitsgirl1 Looks nice. Horse it into ya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiamhieMc I love the sentiment, but my bank balance doesn't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PopsyDaisyCorn Beer... Caramel... Popcorn? Now you have me interested! @galwaybeer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaroadwatch @LiveDrive Something is backing up traffic on R118 Wyattville Rd heading to Cherrywood/M50.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive Excellent, thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiveDrive Any issues on M50 this morning? About to do an airport run from Bray. Tried yesterday and got stuck in that traffic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cr15b Indeed! You could see the looks in other passengers eyes of "does someone say something, or do we all move"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cr15b Busaras to Abbey St. @Luas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of the @Luas Red Line. This afternoon: Woman brushing her teeth, while smoking a joint. Proceeds to spit on floor &amp; throw t'brush 😰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatkhdid Some things are allowed to be said over and over. I think this counts as one ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EffiMai Isn't it on your list of requirements for an appearance - lights turned down and mirrors covered? It's on mine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemaryMacCabe I see there is a lot of furore online, yet I don't want to see the article referred, lest my click is seen as support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redlips_redhair I'm only about here for a few minutes today running errands, but yes, coffee is required soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lloyds Pharmacy Blackrock replace Christmas display with weight loss one, because guilt and New Years resolutions are great marketing tools!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1980's @hornby #trainset instructions were surprisingly #PoliticallyCorrect #ThomasAndFriends #FatController… https://t.co/nMHp4NrRrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd I think we have all done that last bit at one point or another!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd Wow! That's really bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd I will! They can look great when properly done, but they are a lot more hassle than people think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd Oh dear. Neither option sounds pleasant. I can only offer hugs and sympathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@totalmakeupadd I'm wincing in pain just thinking about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people feel the need to start commenting on tweets from 2 and a half years ago... And they deign to call me a… https://t.co/YPIs6IuG6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CormacCor You win the internet! #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it over? Have the singers gone home? #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosesandRockets Exactly! And the licencepayers are footing the bill 😡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I have €10 in cash, Ray? #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibly appearing on tonight's #raydarcyshow are my sister and brother in law. They were on the radio with him during the week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HappyBubbleGal Did he find the droid he was looking for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Musings The feeling is very much mutual x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_Musings Awww. That is really the nicest thing that has been said about me. You're a wonderful friend #WomenWhoInspireMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Ryan, making the poor kid think he had eaten his pet lamb. You're a feckin' monster #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParcelMotel I hope so, and that things are sorted out soon, or a second package will have to be declared missing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea for @parcelmotel - Put, in BIG LETTERS on your website, what date you are processing parcels from. That, or start responding to people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scarie @InTheseHeels I've lost sound of the number of great people I've met via Twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InTheseHeels I'm surprised at the number of no votes. It's almost like some people don't realise there's people behind these words (mostly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParcelMotel Ticket raised 166085]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParcelMotel Can I get an answer please? Is the parcel in a queue to be checked in, or is it missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ParcelMotel Hi. If an item was delivered to Newtonabbey on Saturday (via Hermes) when should it be checked in? Not on account yet (802652)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cat tried to seize control, and everyone panicked, until we realised she doesn't know how to work the remote.… https://t.co/Ru4OvAVinV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsgrainnet I'm still surviving. Doing little bits and pieces as much as possible. Hope you're well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Rory, you'll have the stadium in tears #IRLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 wins and one hell of a loss. Great month's work by Ireland! #IRLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mumm yellow: Difficult call, but if you were to trust anyone to make it, it would be Nigel &amp; Jerome. Great teamwork @Nigelrefowens #IRLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaFeatures70 Alas that seems to be the case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. I have to say this. To all making hideous comments about Rudd. It's none of your fucking business. Fuck off! #UniversityChallenge]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>