<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's classical, anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how, Bert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't be sure whether you're stepping on glass or crunchy nut clusters, something has gone horribly, horribly wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a recurring dream, and it's quite stressful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is full of it, but some are more full of it than others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I do not want to be taken seriously in some quarters until it is too late."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's damp, cold and misty, so it looks like Blackwater Park is on repeat all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should've taken the BEng and fucked off rather than deal with this bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thall is life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is what being a web dev feels like then fucking kill me now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, please, please let me get what I want -- a connection to SQL Server.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All hail the beauty queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I was my dad, because then I'd have the guts to shut the door on cold callers instead of silently wishing they'd go away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always sad when you see a guy who used to have a ponytail has got a haircut. It's OK dude, you're still metal on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MonstroCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losing your keys for a couple of hours is a great way to ruin all your plans for the day and still feel like you've accomplished something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This still exist en aye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feel when you're about to go ride, but you've got a flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something something switch something bait something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about leaving first; it's about sending a message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I've accidentally attended an Interaction Design lecture. I've only got myself to blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you watch 'Skint' and get mad, you're completely missing the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bows + Arrows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feel when you break the display on the specially designed microcontroller you were given at the start of the semester... FUCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's almost Emacs-like." - probably the nicest thing anyone has ever said about Visual Studio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently picnicking in the crunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically all my feelings are currently "gooby pls" in one tone or another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those deadline hacking feels... it's a fight for survival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 10 minutes and already Eclipse is fucking me off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm surrounded by wankers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about OCaml is, is that it's close enough to Scheme and Haskell that I understand it, but it sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone wants to be a waster deep down... just a little bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've lead a charmed life this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for a nice little picnic round the crunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theory of computation in 8 hours. I am woefully under prepared, and I've already had my share of luck in these exams. I am sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The downside to arriving early to his exam is that I now have to listen to everyone badmouth Scheme.  Except Dragos, he's cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me right now: https://t.co/yjL3aXbFt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take it easy mate; you start to think you're a state, you definitely are a state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do feel a bit guilty for nay saying on a tab article but fuck it, they should have done some research. Nutrition has enough bullshit already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have you been gym today?" "No." "Have you been lectures?" "Not yet." "Have you done anything?" "I went Aldi.." "Awwh you pagan."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It can be frustrating, it can be difficult, and you can spend a long time getting nowhere. But god damn, I love functional programming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I wrote 40 lines... but I did learn Windowpane and the intro to Through The Looking Glass, so I guess I've got that going for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week is really going to suck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, coming up with an admissible heuristic is a lot like hard work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Committing to Git gives me that warm fuzzy feeling like I've done something of worth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, At The Drive-In are unbelievable..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how clever Alan Turing was, he was really clever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davesgym ...swift? ...the cause of continental drift? (oh dear...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, maybe I'll be OK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theory of computing is loads of fun until, you know, you have to answer questions. Please, not again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the ocean, I am the sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up for... 36 hours? I've had Skepta bars stuck in my head the whole time; these days man would murder a guy for a box of grade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get me started on CSS and jQuery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having to learn JavaScript in ~4 hours has been somewhat painful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think my idea of a Nobel Laureate edition of Punch Out! went down as well as I had hoped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since '95 my momma been working 9 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should have thought about how I recorded my results; filtering 45k lines of non-uniform text has been ugly as sin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I already told you, if I catch you using another one of my plates again I'll kill you." -- things are getting heated at 77.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Christmas while I'm working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every 2 months I have the same revelation; I should never stop listening to Symphony X... (coincides with expensive guitar drooling week)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just did a test on context free grammars but neglected to learn what context free meant. Fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I have to be ill now and not in the three months I spent doing precisely fuck all in summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, the brain, right? Crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to grades, I keep it three hunna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just applied for an internship in 10 minutes. I might actually be a bit disappointed if I get it, though I doubt that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling this day is going to go from 0 to a hunna in the blink of an eye when I get my test paper back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 day scheme hackathon scheduled for tonight onwards; perhaps by Monday I'll know how to write scheme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who you are, but I'm going to kill you you obnoxious bastard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That wasn't on the agenda. 0 to a hunna real quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It actually only took an afternoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rome wasn't built in a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a hunch, but I think the secret to success may be getting up at the same time everyday, regardless of if is a weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First years are filthy casuals; can't touch this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Spaceape; truly a great loss. Listening to Black Sun in remembrance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't learn maths at school, you learn instructions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all filler no thriller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Switch is bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I fackin know you cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyNameIsDave_ you have to eat your own poo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure I have enough clothes for bestival then center parcs... too many holes in my jeans. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you critique Tempa T's form; are you dizzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something something Bestival something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dat accidental touchscreen hype #goobypls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On some third eye shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...it's not like athletes will do anythig to win. People are just getting better, that's why records increase. Not better "supplementation".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To awake and avenge the dead. @Hattybones https://t.co/1Uicw0eptw FUCKING YES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind, body, technique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "law" makes me sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['COS IT'S THE END OF SOMETHING I DID NOT WANT TO END https://t.co/kFuFiyBE7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you mean, "you people"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing people drinking cans at 9am was almost funny at first, but the shocking regularity of it is nothing less than truly bleak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On some 3rd eye shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So fresh and so clean, clean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A race in mid-August heat will be a whole different level of exhaustion; things need done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday long run "hype". #TM14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something something elbows something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dance with the Devil was real as fuck back there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also... seeing @ImmortalTech at the Globe tonight; oh yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to stop being so evangelical about fitness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenRMoon What are you laughin' at? Ain't a damn thing funny.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>