<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is old news. He had been using campaign funds to get his businesses out of hock. He paid rent to himself with… https://t.co/RQEDUUhC62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong I wonder how many kids got that reference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder @washingtonpost has Flynn said anything yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sal1948 what is Iran on notice for? Oh yeah that's right, oil!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMartinR @zeebap2 And Moscow Mitch is a opportunistic worm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grendl64 @MJMcKean Russian hacks, FBI, hate rhetoric, false promises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WN... The new SS, I'm sure. https://t.co/YnfJW4Q8T2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnLeguizamo @mike_pence @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @seanspicer I am more worried about what they're trying to cover up now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnLeguizamo @mike_pence @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @seanspicer it's just another distraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably felt that he was so important his membership should be free. https://t.co/SGz0We81PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notgilt @SassandClass33 @SAmericanMonkey @funder Defensive much? Just trying to get answers and you feel the need to be a dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notgilt @SassandClass33 @SAmericanMonkey @funder If I'm mistaken, I'll own it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieJordanACN I'm confident that ban and mass disapproval is a big smoke screen. Is anything going on worldwide,that @POTUS tried 2 hide?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notgilt @SassandClass33 @SAmericanMonkey @funder Podesta Emails, also spear-phished by Russians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LatestAnonNews I'm more worried about White nationalists who randomly kill innocent people without answering to any hierarchy Or handlers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarHatSH Just wash it down with a bottle of soy sauce and you'll be jerky by the month's out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man of the people, right @POTUS? How is Flint's drinking water? https://t.co/benqAxAEYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyjlm @LucyLiu good God, I wish elementary was on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost A sob story about sexual harassment in politics,so she becomes the mouthpiece of a serial philanderer.Psych Eval, now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you kidding? @POTUS bedroom is going to have a revolving door. Keep the tributes coming, my knuckle dragging mi… https://t.co/mTRKSqHFUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJusticeDept what about the army secretary buying stock in an aerospace company which holds government contracts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the more you master the human psyche, the more of a goofball you become. https://t.co/z1k8dCjJma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder @Isikoff @YahooNews i'm sure that all of @POTUS Fuck ups are part of a big elaborate distraction from Russia. Ideas for Russia plan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BAM__MARGERA doesn't look like they got much. Maybe some spare parts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notgilt @SassandClass33 @SAmericanMonkey @funder were those hacked also? Law term fruit of the poison tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjferraresi @sentientist @SamHarrisOrg I hear surgeons develop a God complex. Short on empathy, but I don't know many surgeons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarHatSH she always loves you like a son, Mr. Holmes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LatestAnonNews Trump won't do it. Without ISIS he has no scare tactics to force citizens into submission. ISIS is @POTUS greatest ally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susannecraig @nytimes six months to a year and we will be at war. Which means death for dollars. First things first, I'm a capitalist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Offerman YUGE conflict of interest!!!!!! Holy shit! Where is the integrity? He's practically pandering for a bribe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody likes him!!!! Yes, I got the reference. HA HA HA! 😂🤣😂🤣😂 https://t.co/W2p69chVwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the hell did you squeeze all that in the 140 characters? https://t.co/fmpp6AHnhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is going to crush the record for most vacation days taken by President. https://t.co/gmLHcfgyi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP are fucking idiots to believe they could control a pathological narcissist. You can only kiss his ass and d… https://t.co/dt02Usljpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, is that bc The Muslim states that had more American deaths but have Trump businesses in them are not on the ba… https://t.co/T3idKAakki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JMoriarty @Betterw05759703 What is that old saying, Mr. Moriarty. "Enemy of my enemy..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WithoutaTRACE Rich fucks are so entitled they truly believe they should be given everything just bc of status. Paying would be an insult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WithoutaTRACE because they obviously don't have accountants working for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling I thought only nazis burned books? Oh wait....Klan did too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sentientist @Betterw05759703 Or instructions from others, but who am I to judge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sentientist @Betterw05759703 it's simple, Democrats are more creative and more relatable to other people. Whereas GOP only follow routine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjferraresi @sentientist @SamHarrisOrg correction, abstract thinking. We are all free, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjferraresi @sentientist @SamHarrisOrg probably because it requires creativity and freethinking. As opposed to following instructions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayandSteve @Juan_Abbe @HPLifestyle --&gt;"You insult me on my show and you insult the American People by lying to all of us." I bet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayandSteve @Juan_Abbe @HPLifestyle I wish to God, instead calling her bs falsehoods, he should said."These are lies, you are lying--&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joekeene @LisaZucker3 That knuckle dragging, uncle-fucker is as Christian as a shit slinging chimpanzee. @DrDavidDuke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelly_Herself @GOP It's true, frothing mouths like hyenas. They force their ideology to dictate reality. Or they shoot up a mosque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foomper @fdwilkinson @aasif @washingtonpost Fact, unfortunately. Like the Cold War.People were scared and paranoid, they gave up everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MINAtheMYNX @fdwilkinson @Fahrenthold Even Cheney says this Admin is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kelly_Herself @GOP That's rather sociopathic to say the least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SassandClass33 @notgilt @SAmericanMonkey @funder They don't anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a brighter future than the shooter, he reacts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EWDolan @PsyPost Is there an element of jealousy and resentment from recently unemployed active shooters toward students? Perceived to---&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@funder The only way trumpers will learn is if they do a job for @POTUS and gets stiffed on the invoice like every other small business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SassandClass33 @notgilt @SAmericanMonkey @funder Same argument was said over emails a while back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PsyPost Would this be evidence of building reflexes? Through practice, the neurons build themselves up from visual to the brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the Dems are forced to be the parents of politics and GOP are spoiled children. Who are the snowflakes now? https://t.co/Mbs9Vw18xS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusC22973194 @dawnstotlar Picking that jury will be fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EW Tom Hardy is such a crazy badass!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess the fruit doesn't fall far from the FUCKING IDIOT tree. https://t.co/13j91XuG9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morgfair No surprise there. Why appear on a network that won't sell your kool-aid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janis_wilds Of course he is. @POTUS is running like his businesses, have other people run it while he takes credit. At failure, hung to dry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antfarmer @LRBitisnot Oh don't worry, they are. Bottom feeders bc anyone with a brain knows they're fucking idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo!!!! Lovers' Quarrel!!!! https://t.co/u3UPjZPGtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As inspiring as it is adorable. https://t.co/WL0CtHbsoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what we think of you @POTUS. How far does #PresidentBannon shove his hand up your ass before you sing "I'm… https://t.co/SSdRa0Ganq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So block them too? Roger that, Senator Chicken Shit. https://t.co/QemYNV4MBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical White Nationalists are Terrorists. https://t.co/FbiEBH9vz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitch #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frown #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pissing #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House of Nards #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake off #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hooter #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Gay #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BoneRs #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBE's #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bunted #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Gang Theory#OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stream: the series #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatman #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dick #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bed #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cosby blow #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaved by the bell.... fuck you guys, I'm trying. #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star bars #OneLetterOffTvShows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@komonews I hope the little twerp is put away for life. If possible, death penalty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BjayukCat Thank you, Sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that a start. By the way, that was #PresidentBannon order. He wrote it and saw it through. @POTUS is a joke to… https://t.co/VzqjjXpSrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man wiser than myself once said, "What would McConnell do to Obama?" Fucking snowflakes. Yes, GOP are whiney, man… https://t.co/4bWXu41k0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's what it means to have balls! A bully is nothing but empty threats. Not get his way, he'll be sobbing lik… https://t.co/TYc6jhQwC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @POTUS Is sure biting these knuckle dragging hicks in the ass now. https://t.co/kF8eVDorZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to be safe until we find out what the hell is going on. https://t.co/haAk58zv0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American citizens come in all races (including Muslims), so do terrorists (including whites). https://t.co/Jof0ESl0lY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Yup. Bullies generally are. https://t.co/RGzOTSH7oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man of the people, right @POTUS . When you're face to face, you buckle like a belt. Just like in Mexico. https://t.co/sSnDeARfZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMFG!!! Bible thumpers are retarded. You're not in the bedroom or the stall with them. Let them live with the same… https://t.co/yzDzhbPYYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieJordanACN @NPCA There is nothing sacred with these assholes until it's pounding down their front door with s gun on their families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God doesn't bless murderers, HE BURNS THEM!!!!!!!! https://t.co/SpzTRv7FnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig @TheRealDaniYell Radical Christian Terrorist.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>