<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually an ex of mine broke up with me on Valentine's Day. #WorstCooks #WorstCooksInAmerica @rachaelray @chefanneburrell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rock Ford Files #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Patty Dukes of Hazzard #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Thin White Dukes of Hazzard #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The David Dukes of Hazzard #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Scarecrow and Mrs. Coretta Scott King #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All in the Manson Family #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West Wing #CelebrityATVShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeannieG40 How old are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise I loved the props. "He will not be de turd." "Moose lambs."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise @ScribblingSandy Apparently the Canadian history curriculum is much more like the European one than the USian one, thank heavens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise This is really interesting too. #LongReads https://t.co/TvLWlyA7ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise Watch it fast before they make it private. https://t.co/3Xipg28qfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise Hahahahahahaha that is sooooo too bad! It was literally AMAZING. Lemme find a vine of part of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise Did you watch the video?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KIRKPATRlCK Smart, since I'm really not trustworthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baradar85 Yes!! It gets a funky fermented taste if it's not refrigerated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legalizetasiaa @alexiabailey97 Proud member of the #GiantRackNotSoSneakAttack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Ginch Stole Christmas #UndergarmentAnything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @eveegdmann Impossible. The only inventors who didn't inadvertently help the Axis powers in WWII were being protected by gov'ts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Crying. @melissamccarthy #SNL @H2OWise https://t.co/dWoVEFq9p3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindogg88 @Maher48Hours @48hours @sylvianyc  I'm also out West.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindogg88 @Maher48Hours @48hours @sylvianyc  Well there were 5 of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maher48Hours @48hours @sylvianyc So who WAS responsible? Did the DNA results get any hits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@48hours $1MM for every year of incarceration! #48Hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@48hours $1MM for every year of incarceration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope it doesn't turn out to be something stupid like her dad has a 2nd family or something. #Ransom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm playing chess while watching The Queen of Katwe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCSharkTank YASSSSS! Legit one of the best deals - for everyone! - I've ever seen on the tank. @LoriGreiner @mcuban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TS_Lambert @MackLamoureux Hey @NancyAPainter check out this editing gig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoulCunting Yeah I dunno. I think some people are incapable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuteOverloads That's a person in a bear suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoulCunting The same reason everyone gets a customer service job... it's the only job available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I encountered Marmalade within the walls of yon Gallic city. The poxy street walker was no lady. #ShakespeareSingsInTheShower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweeps, please donate to support my walk in The Coldest Night of the Year! If you can't give, join my walk!… https://t.co/8GEqbF00uY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday at my work @FirstUnitedDTES. #Ganja #Youcantmakethisstuffup #DTES https://t.co/A7MJpTzFnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/xdK19SGhqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 44 new followers from USA, Canada, Nigeria, and more last week. See https://t.co/MgwNku6xDN https://t.co/X3UvrdVwFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He's my son-in-law." #TheBlacklist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2day I introduced 2 friends at a girls' lunch. Turns out 1 is from Kurdistan. The other is American, but LIVED in Kurdistan! #WhatAreTheOdds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would literally watch MasterChef, Project Runway and Ellen's Design Challenge every single day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wakeup call. #CatTweet #CatsofTwitter https://t.co/8DhQQJ5iKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink No. When are you going to start letting riders submit complaints &amp; commendations via Twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to the driver of bus No. B8106; he gets passengers to move back at every stop. @translink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomservo10 His Klout score is THROUGH THE ROOF, and he's super-excited about it. #BlackHistoryMonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There'll be #HellToupe #Trump #TeamTrump https://t.co/QM7L4mxAz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 Rocks #OneLetterOffTVShows @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise @Twitter This is also funny. @peterlouwe https://t.co/DaBMTj1nfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dozens of people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/xdK19SGhqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a Creative Writing prof who's spent the past 35 years screwing his students and plagiarising their work. #RoastofSteveBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is spectacular. https://t.co/O5KzbS3Fs2 @h2owise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maccytimeless Sorry to hear that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilw @GreatDismal Retweeted. Anything for William Gibson!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Serpentine202 @JimmyColema1060 @Salon It's called #DeMENSA. It's when you think you're a genius but you're actually just the #POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig @MarcVegan Meh. It's been coming since the Reagan years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maccytimeless So you do think it'll bring back the guy Wyatt murdered? Or you don't want to watch any more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode of #Gotham is depressingly like Trump's America. #TeamTrump #POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maccytimeless It won't bring back the guy Wyatt murdered. #Timeless Don't know if I want to watch any more. #CancelTimeless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dgct2 He murdered someone. I'm glad she didn't come back, serves him right. #Timeless #RenewTimeless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs @BEARPAPABEAR Then the fact that the #POTUS can fire that person is a notable flaw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Ed would just shut up already. #Gotham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkdaisies18 Maybe Quinn told him. #Timeless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ORRCHIDRAIN @hopedowdlist @SURJColumbusOH @ylianova @OhioLatinx It does. I don't know if it works better than other suggestions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder who's going to be the Acting Attorney General after Dana Boente. https://t.co/bmITyDzAXp @froomkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopedowdlist @ORRCHIDRAIN @SURJColumbusOH @ylianova @OhioLatinx In the homeless shelter where I work we use baby shampoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H2OWise And this made me smile: https://t.co/EImxnK7a7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes one to know one, I guess. @AP https://t.co/v0j7W1NQ0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling TY. The soft landing the lone wolf ref gives white terrorists is not only racist, it's also chauvinistic. Fonzie was a lone wolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump is suffering from #DeMENSA - a delusional condition where one thinks they're a genius, but they're just the #POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoraReed America has the best Celebrity Center though, or so I recently learned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MisterPhisto @1MorWMN @lisaboban @saletan Typical Capricorn. That's the same deal you gave Nixon, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM Yeah it was nice to chat. Twitter is great for news! Sleep tight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM Fucking fascism for fuck's sake. How is it that 70 years later we have to RE-CONVINCE the world that Nazis are bad????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM He could destroy the global economy with an ill-advised tweet. Nevermind singlehandedly reviving FASCISM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM I'm scared too. He could pretty much do anything... invade Canada, nuclear war with N. Korea, conventional war with China...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM It's like a horrible pastiche of The Handmaid's Tale, V for Vengeance &amp; Mad Max, but with the dystopia 1st, nuclear war 2nd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM It goes to show how fragile the republic actually is. At this rate, it'll be completely dismantled by Easter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't take the analogy too far, Hayes. He's not you! #Conviction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strawberryJAMM Thanks for the RTs and faves. One woman I chatted with called Kellyanne a 'bowl-circling turd' LOL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DeMensa: The disorder where you think you're "Really a smart guy, the smartest ever, amazing!" but you're actually the #POTUS #Portmanteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTM33TN @Kaled1974 I'm not debating the reason, I'm stating the existence of contempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTM33TN @Kaled1974 Katalin, please don't include me when you reply to Kaled. Kaled, ditto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what I learnt this weekend? People really really hate Kellyanne Conway. #TeamTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTM33TN @Kaled1974 If you're referring to the EO, it absolutely does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTM33TN @Kaled1974 No. It's inevitable when people treat each other with contempt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@good4politics That's my plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So heartbroken to hear of the #QuebecCity mosque shooting. #JesuisQuebecCity #JesuisSanteFoy #Resist #NotMyCanada https://t.co/8oRk7o6E1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndiciaObscure @saletan INORITE?? And I missed the Jesus inference, pointed out here: https://t.co/AKDaCW6yoy That makes it even creepier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darn you @coffeemateph for making me tear up at a commercial for edible oil products! https://t.co/w03DDTf7ct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leacohodas Me too. See you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reddcurlz @saletan My hero!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMegaparsec Well that's a relief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HockeyHangout It's like it's your first time acting in a porno and your mom's on the sound stage encouraging you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbiBrkovich @saletan And she's clearly too darned busy (seeking braaaaaaiiiinnnnsssss) to watch her clips.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And again, another of my most popular tweets is a reply. https://t.co/NryeyQdLre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, who is 'you guys'? https://t.co/ofNBrMBqhj @brylo103102]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I understand hard work. I don't think you understand humour tho. https://t.co/ofNBrMBqhj #TeamTrump @brylo103102]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full of gaping, seeping wounds and no sleep in months?

IOW, #TeamTrump is made of actual zombies. 

https://t.co/nm8Z2l9sTA @saletan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@good4politics I think that's exactly what Carlos is suggesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter made him and Twitter will destroy him. #Trump #MuslimBan https://t.co/gjJygfDdVH https://t.co/yrjDVHhKWt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>