<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan really you interviewed Alex Jones not too long ago?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@intolerantsteve if you like listening to tv in the bathroom,would highly recommend wireless headphones,I can walk around the house wit them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnellyStephen @drivetimerte was it alternative language?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani did @Rampage4real and Mariah meet up in the end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackAEustace @fiannafailparty @fiannafail  @activedan is this you again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnellyStephen moving to FF goes to show why you should never have faith in any Irish party or politician]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kahlout @thejournal_ie It'll be hard to identify altrightuser73534 in real life though, probably some 40 year old virgin living with mammy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well thats the BBCs end of questions for the next 4 years #fakenews #maytrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Theresa May just call out @realDonaldTrump bullshit on Nato? Says one thing in public another in private #maytrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec @theresa_may @POTUS first and probably last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iresimpsonsfans @Glinner @divinecomedyhq post the original meme https://t.co/wVxOWETQph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNews is it these guys https://t.co/noETLXOTIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whats the point of @Shane_RossTD being transport minister if he doesn't want to get involved in matters that affect transport? #dail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump should we be impressed that you can get out of bed before 9am?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan The Washington elites? Hes now the President FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its started raining #TrumpInauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hes already said great #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be interesting to see @labour kotow to Trump if they get back into government, Gilmore met Netanyahu FFS https://t.co/wropE3bSCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanefolan I guess its worth putting things into perspective. Imagine in a few years if a former Isis commander became a politician]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colette_sexton who's we though? Do we not include the 6000+ homeless as equals?  #generationfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage Shes being mocked now too believe me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloysmail from my numerous trips to Germany peoples attitudes would suggest differently, depends on what people you ask I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNews @realDonaldTrump FFS they aren't illegals if she legally let them into the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp new layout is awful, anyway to switch back? Poor performance and static interface, bad UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything about the BDO is worse compared to the PDC. The players, fans and even commentators #bdoworlddarts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure that was a foul, never mind a yellow. Can you not slide tackle anymore? #MUNLIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaundraHamilt16 @CNN well if its written on a mug it must be true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman genuinely was a few inches away today from a fractured skull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If youre a #NewYearNewMe person in the gym, quick tip, dont lie down on a mat in the weights area where people may drop weights on your face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MMA fans need to take a chill pill about Meryl Streeps comments, they really can be the worst sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iresimpsonsfans @JOEdotie Is it possible to build up a list of contributors so you can credit them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanefolan Its grand, John Delaney has plenty of money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time! https://t.co/tTVxqzus9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FineGael continue to tell us there is a recovery, but for who? 

https://t.co/4U7UtHKnYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stars who left us in 2016 playlist has to be the best/most depressing @Spotify playlist of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simoncoveney literally heard a story of a colleagues rent going up 225 over night. Your strategy for Dublin and Cork is going well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia @VirginMediaIE Ireland dont work Sundays can you let them know internet is down again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE no internet second morning in a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE internet seems to be down again. 3rd time this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GAA,an org which claims to be ran by the community for the community but also has a multi million euro deal with Rupert Murdoch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia is the latest price increase going ahead? Can we expect better service or regular issues as usual?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump but you still got them small hands bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtenews fascinating news there lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GardaTraffic squad car parked on a double line at a junction on the wrong side of the road. If Guards dont bother… https://t.co/OnS3qZ1HQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving a tax rebate to first time buyers to help them buy houses, instead of you know, actually building some houses to buy #Budget2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[them 0.5% USC cuts will really help first time buyers try and save 20% deposit whilst paying €1200+ a month in rent #Budget2017 #joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man City away kit looks like a can of coke left out in the sun for too long #celticvcity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26 year old IT worker from Wexford living in Dublin. #knowyourrepealers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas whoever made that decision should has explaining to do. Any real company that had downtime to a major app would be out of business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas are you serious? You chose a week when there are multiple bus strikes which means more demand to do a 6 day maintenance job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woudlnt of thought someone as smart as CJ de Mooi would publish a book with details on how he secretly killed someone but there you go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTE_PrimeTime @downesr the insurance companies will need a new excuse then to overcharge us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions league nights have gone to shit with @VirginMediaIE not having setanta. Please raise prices again so we can cancel contract]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luas where/when/why/how long?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanTheMusician what a feckin ejit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskKBCIreland Ill probably apply online over the weekend, Ill let you know though. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI 1 wk later still no reply. Cant get through on phone. Going to try @AskKBCIreland instead, savings rates are higher too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI once a month. Don't mind waiting till next month so long as I can alter the amount]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI it was paid in today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI yeah did that a few days ago. Havent heard back yet. Is there an SLA on lead time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI  how do I change amount going into monthly savings account online? Doesn't seem to be any option to do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bankofireland emailed using online service desk days ago yet no reply. Spent 10 mins on hold just there too (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bankofireland how do I change amount going into monthly savings account online? Doesn't seem to be any option to do this. (1\2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsungHelpUK why would that be? some of the pictures I only took last week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsungHelpUK clearing the cache seems to have helped a bit. Still some pictures in my gallery with a blank thumbnail and exclamation mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No water in Castleforbes since I got home from work. Notice said it would be off from 9am-6pm, whats going on? Not good enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsungHelpUK my samsung a5 is driving me crazy. cant open the gallery without it crashing. Whats the length of manufacturer warranty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus what was that. #UFC202]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear the Irish crowd in full voice already #ConorMcGregor #TeamMcGregor #UFC202]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time @VirginMediaIE raise the price I am cancelling the contract. Serious scramble today to find somewhere to watch UFC202]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The42_ie you seriously need to improve your app. Full time Leicester score 0 0 ? Really? https://t.co/IzybwCtWw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YearOfFestivals Wear suncream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinamarashow @DubCityCouncil Still there 6 weeks later. Someone will either sue, get hurt, or worst case scenario, do both. Sort it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seatwave_Help cool once you follow me I will be able to DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seatwave Hi, sold tickets on 27th May, still not have received payment can you follow up on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sterling goes down again. Also Sterling went over easy there #ENGICE #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whats next? Referee blocks a shot off the line with his hand #COYBIG #IRLITA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE love it when my horizon box decides to randomly stall during two euro 2016 matches #shite https://t.co/0UTKZQdunu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rte player randomnly switching to analysis of the England Wales match. Good to get values worth out of that 160 euro a year license fee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goong to the 3arena ? Probably not a good idea to drive. About 7 cars in a row clamped https://t.co/CzNJY05mLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEplayer Thank you thats helped a lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEplayer quality atm is pretty poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrahamF watching it in work !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see strongest lineup picked, Long Walters and Hoolahan all starting  #IRL #IREvSWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting nervous about #IREvSWE COYBIG #IRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Andrews doing an Apres Match impressiom by the sounds of it #tv3 #ENGRUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else get an MMS from a number saying "Justin" with a link to download]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubCityCouncil @mannixflynn can you  remove this ad stand at 4 courts. Pedestrians cant see  cars and vice versa https://t.co/21jsf5JPhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I will not have any dealings with Michael Lowry, or any other Independent,” the Taoiseach said.
https://t.co/xzHumvxIZQ

#Dáil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen a @VirginMediaIE ad on tv for 360 mb broadband. Speed at the moment? 0. Because it isnt actually working...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well thats one way to get a clamp off #Dublin https://t.co/PhPXg0kFMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Allen comes on = Liverpool score 3 goals #BVBLFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Part is the Michael Owen of darts. Talented player, brutal commentator #lovethedarts #skysportsdarts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Hart just found out why you dont pass on a goalkick in Fifa #PSGMCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But anyway theyve hold on and gained 2 points over Spurs. Surely in the bag now #LeiSou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats at least the third time Danny Drinkwater needlessly lost possession #LeiSou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy hasn't seen Paul McShane #IRLSLO  https://t.co/FZG933aUQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed for Rob Elliot. He deserved his chance as NUFC and IRL no.1 #IRLSLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI seems like theres still an issue with viewing statements online? Is this being looked into currently?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>