<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateFloor @HouseFloor @Reince @Scotus YOU are creating a civil war in this country kissing Trump's ass. Republicans will own this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan At the expense of clean air, water. Coal is NOT clean. YOU will own this like all republicans will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @RiencePreibus @GOP ALL republicans own this destruction of America. We will not forget. Your allowing Russian ties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateFloor @HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems Most administration have russian ties. Shame for America. Republicans own this. Marches!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateFloor @HouseFloor @GOPLeader Remove filibuster and we will remove you. It will bite you back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @SenateGOP @SenateDems @HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats @HouseFloor @SenateFloor Change the rules and we will r… https://t.co/W4iAfIIMtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP @SenateGOP @SenateFloor Remember your rule change. This republican will register Democrat with millions of others. Election coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @GOP @SpeakerRyan I am Republican, but your values tell me I can never vote republican again.Tillerson/Russian ties is wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my new 12 followers and goodbye to 5 unfollowers (FREE stats by https://t.co/e6MEi6wen4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory @KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump That is a true nazi/ kgb tactic. Bigoted pigs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are planning for a war. Probably to take oil as they stated https://t.co/du9r1VOEkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicenteFoxQue Us Americans agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs I think you meant SCROTUM pick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReutersWorld Didn't they get the 'alternate facts' memo? @foxnewspolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this https://t.co/iWWWj3DhaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @WhiteHouse So what. OUR scotus seat should have been filled long ago. Elections coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign leaders need to stand up against @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/h1JOectGLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DNC @SenateDems @HouseDemocrats @christinawilkie Don't stoop to republican level on SCOTUS. Show we are better than them and lets rebuild]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@igorbobic He will ask his daddy Bannon what to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS screwing more workers we see #shutdownmaralago https://t.co/wT7xf9APWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @PressSec The republicans blocked SCOTIS on the opposite pronciple. Fucking liars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was Nixon's lawyer speaking out https://t.co/awCWdctNUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smencimer @SAI @AnonPress maybe someone needs to embarrass them..........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Followed, 1 Unfollowed me (monitored by https://t.co/YoSI1bq5s7)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jawja100 @Newsweek Done illegally without the required Senate vote. here is the law https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban This law states Bannon in NSC was done illegally. A Senate vote is a requirement. Please share https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Politisphere1 This law states Bannon is illegally in NSC as clearly states a Senate vote required by law https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi Can you explain how Bannon is in NSC? This law states a Senate vote is required. Trump forgets laws https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Am I right in that this law states Bannon cannot be put in NSC without Senate vote? https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madonna please help share this. Love you Madonna https://t.co/b7Ts4h2iTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiencePreibus  @SenJohnMcCain Bannon was not approved by Senate for NSC as the law dictates! Uphold the law https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraBoxer @nytimes Bannon is in NSC illegally. A Senate vote is a must. Trump bypasses laws https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraBoxer Law states Trump illegally placed Bannon in NSC without a Senate vote. How can it happen? https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosieperezbklyn This law states that Bannon is illegally in the NSC without required Senate Approval. Please share https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ Maybe you should cover how Bannon is in the NSC illegally. Law states a Senate vote is required. https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters Explain how Bannon was placed in NSC without Senate approval. Law states it a must https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME @nytimes @latimes Can someone explain this law? Bannon should not be in NSC without Senate approval! https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OurAmercnRights can you assist in spreading this law. Bannon was illegally placed in NSC without Senate voting https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheWhoVotes She upheld the law as her oath dictates. The President is NOT her boss. Her only duty is to our country's laws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA Read this law and tell me how Bannon was illegally placed in NSC without a Senate vote. Get him out! https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSAGov Read this law and tell me how Bannon was placed with NSC without a Senate vote. https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo Sir, this law states Bannon was illegally placed in NSC without Senate voting. Why is it not upheld? https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Law states Bannon needed Senate approval to be placed in NSC. Trump ignored the law again https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredKushner_ @IvankaTrump @POTUS This law states Bannon was illegally placed in NSC without Senate approval https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DNC @dncpress @keithellison Law states Trump putting Bannon in NSC illegal without a Senate vote. Get him out https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomsThoughts @TheSpringChickn @StopTrump2020 @realDenaldTrump @RealClearNews Read this and spread it everywhere pl… https://t.co/jcylcv4N1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilRights This law states Trump illegally placed Bannon in NSC without Senate approval. Do your job  https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @cnnbrk @NBCPolitics Read this law and tell me how Bannon is in NSC without Senate voting. https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @DebraMessing Could you read this law and tell me how Bannon is in NSC without Senate vote. Please share https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queenelizabeth As an American I implore you to wait and see what kind of President Trump is. He is showing us to be a facist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotus @POTUS @DHSgov Bannon in the NSC is illegal under this law without a Senate vote. Do your duty https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejointstaff @OfficeGovEthics  Read this law and tell me why Bannon is in NSC without Senate approval? NOT LEGAL https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren This law states Bannon cannot be placed in NSC without senate approval. Why is he? https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama How can Bannon be put in NSC without Senate vote sir? We miss you https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Am I right that this law states Trump illegally put Bannon in the NSC without Senate voting? https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders @SenFranken @SenateFloor Law states Senate has to approve Bannon before placing him in NSC https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @SenSchumer This law states that Trump does not have power to place Bannon in NSC without Senate https://t.co/3NtarZL0Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Feel your facts slipping away? https://t.co/w1Hz7k23Hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eessenmacher @peterdaou @christinawilkie Senator Schumer lost his grandmother and most of her children due to nazi's doing the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban Absolutely correct. People need to research their candidates more in this country and not just rely on media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good place for the next protest https://t.co/sHWazVZoRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLU @SenFranken @SenSchumer If people die because of this ban, can Trump be held accountable for crimes against humanity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinawilkie Obama well informed the people and government departments of the 'why' and 'when']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 9 followers and lost 2 (stats by https://t.co/YoSI1bq5s7)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @HouseGOP @McConnellPress @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerRyan Your decision on muslim ban caused this.… https://t.co/FDh3w2kRgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC @SenateMajLdr Yet McConnell remained silent and did not speak up. Two faced liar. Here is proof https://t.co/bHox2HyNox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing Propaganda Barbie. Alternate facts sold separately https://t.co/8D4OaYelK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse America is watching and elections coming https://t.co/bHox2HyNox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing @Rosie @GOPLeader No wall, no ban or protests will continue daily https://t.co/GrUvMMMhNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reince @SpeakerRyan @SenJohnMcCain This muslim ban is a crime against humanity and we will seek to remove all in support, or silent of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @SenateDems @HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats @SpeakerRyan Those who supported, or stayed silent will be removed https://t.co/bHox2HyNox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Then protests continue for 90 days getting bigger and bigger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SpeakerRyan @McConnellPress @GOP YOU put all their lives at risk and WE will hold you responsible… https://t.co/mzXQcVkLAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They are working for us, you only care about yourself and money. #impeachtrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOP @SpeakerRyan Come out to Penn Ave in Washington to celebrate you coward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @SenateGOP @GOPLeader list of Senators and governors against, for, and silent on muslim ban. Shameful https://t.co/bHox2HyNox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our POS POTUS is a PIG, BTW, WTF the GOP does nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fINALLY SOMEONE IS REPORTING THIS https://t.co/rAPUDlExkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @SenateDems Muslim ban is a violation of the Geneva Convention.This is a crime against humanity, we will hold those responsible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME It is NOT confusion! It is against American values that we will NOT let them undermine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpHotels It was trump Hotel. Seeing all the fine chinese products in the rooms and lobby, bars, a building built by immigrants, A dump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boycottuber https://t.co/9kDueWBvu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @PRyan @mike_pence Here is a list of those supporting/ and against the muslim ban https://t.co/bHox2HyNox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing Please spread the info https://t.co/gerlQDQXbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NRSC Seriously? Look at the protests in the world, in our country. This is caused by republican values. See you at election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SenFranken detainees at #Dulles just told me CPB is saying they can't let lawyers in bc HQ won't let them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers @Dulles_Airport #Dulles Then protestors need to shut down the airport....PEACEFULLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must remember those who are silent, and remove them from office permanently. https://t.co/zRgHnrhEo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Your a puke and habitual liar. That makes you truly an ugly person https://t.co/evNoJgX7ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbggrg @SpeakerRyan We will remember those who are too coward to stand up at elections soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump Your Putin's bitch, and now Bannon's also. PeePee party's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flood NYT with followers, Spicer is Fake news https://t.co/ACIgqf7CRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @SenateGOP @SenateDems @HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats The change in the NSC is insanely dangerous. Bannon needs to be removed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS @MomsThoughts Trump, you must have a incredible IQ? High 20's maybe. Your an idiots idiot and illegitiment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP @SenateGOP @SenateDems @HouseDemocrats Trump is beyond incompetent and his destruction is YOUR legacy. Impeach him now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinawilkie @AnonPress @funder @HuffingtonPost @NBCNews Where is Trump's immigrant workers from, and what has been done with them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @KellyannePolls @SpeakerRyan @POTUS !%? Seriously? Then we will shut the airports down 100%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my new 1 followers and goodbye to 1 unfollowers (FREE stats by https://t.co/e6MEi6wen4)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban and a movement can remove him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent I bet her people feel differently. Was she vetted yet? Keep her out then]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>