<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Me trying to sleep vs existential dread be like https://t.co/Hx8QDuhtMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: guess it's time to go to bed...
Mind: what happens when you die? 
Me: in two years. I'll go to bed in two years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyways, lads, the Arad Goch production of Titus is pretty good. Y'all should go see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merteuiI looks like Idris isn't gonna be Bond so LET'S MAKE HIM DOCTOR WHO INSTEAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMcd28 because he's an agent of chaos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am suave. Where's my peshwari naan gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvyNapp that looks great!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe this person has stolen my hugh Owen library seat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there a Tesco man in the English foyer and why is he talking to us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I threw a post-it note at leanne and it hit her book and I can't stop laughing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COME TO THE BOOK SALE I AM BORED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's on again https://t.co/Y2hN8ZnLTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't sleep but at least the Hamilton soundtrack is dank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Never ever' by the all saints is the greatest artistic exploration of the loss of meaning in modern, secular life since waiting for godot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all know the real words... https://t.co/BiXpQPSCit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks holy shit we both had the same idea with different songs I love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks ironically, it's 'I don't want no mediocre' by dj lil dweeby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks this song is legit so mediocre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this song so long? We get it, life's a highway and you're rascal flatts; can we just get to the coda?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks this song is gonna be stuck in my head 5 ever now so thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks NO ITS FUCKING NOT THAT SONG CAN FUCK OFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks I want that tweet on my gravestone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks I got news for you kid. Life is also a https://t.co/eRjSyBH0fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks oh I'm sorry! I ate it too fast, you say? You know what else moves fast, Dan? Life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks I can't believe you took four pictures of meg sitting on a fucking chair BUT NONE OF MY BBQ WRAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget I'm a comic genius and then I look at my snapchat story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AledTheRed @hypothetiks I can't believe you both replied with iconic memes, you are true servants of the meme-gods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks @AledTheRed he's even doing the cross pose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AledTheRed @hypothetiks wholesome, beautiful, insightful towards the human experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaniceBirch1 @BBCNewsnight or are you saying I'm not allowed to be irked by someone sneering at the idea of identity politics unrebutted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaniceBirch1 @BBCNewsnight I've sneered at identity politics to newsnight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you trust anyone who only eats once a day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back, I should've known to have never liked Lionel Shriver. In the first interview I saw of her, she said she only eats once a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatAnstice too right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight ok now please get on Nesrine Malik on she literally already debunked Shriver once #viewsnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I spent the evening running a poetry event just to come home to play with lightsabers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This book sale is lit, get ye over there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignore the botched hashtag and focus on the fact that the lib dems are dick head https://t.co/hyeFIK6Axp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so transparent, you can see right through it https://t.co/9TGxAIR4rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO YOU BELIEVE IN THE DREAM?!
ITS ALREADY BECOMING A REALITY!!
CHECK THE PROFILE PIC https://t.co/8uuIRfvBsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AberEnglishDept it's following me https://t.co/5gdePviDge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight also, can you tell Rod Liddle that alliteration is not as clever as he thinks it is #viewsnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight thanks for the reply though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight can you get Nesrine Malik/ someone who talks sense about identity politics? Always white old people who sneer at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarieHeleneTho2 @BBCNewsnight when newsnight segments sound more like super villain victory speeches, something is seriously wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight I think I just threw up in my mouth #viewsnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone who said get rid of the dog made a smart decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenJKFeeney CAN WE HAVE DUELS?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which one do I get rid off? https://t.co/BiFa2O13t7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks too many for a single tweet my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks I'll add it to the sitcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks Accrington Stanley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks who are they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['And all I had was twenty chicken nuggets' - Dan Davies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AberEnglishDept the duck is back https://t.co/fWLtK99m5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BangorUniPAPERS I've got Tesco receipts that flow better than Bangor's poetry #provemewrong2K17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in London, please go! https://t.co/XPAbZ1Qtwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneRose__x for a minute I thought I was donald Trump there and everything got weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneRose__x that doesn't help things in the slightest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks Stephen Colbert as a confused imperial admiral because we all know he wants to be in a Star Wars film https://t.co/o3jerkGJjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks grey-haired Robbie Williams as Palps himself (amazing what a little makeup will do) https://t.co/4mwPLugiof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks Ewan McGregor as Obi Wan BECAUSE HOW ELSE ARE WE FINALLY GONNA SEE HIM IN ANYTHING https://t.co/jgYyY6PrcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks bumbling imperial soldier who just wants to impress Palps https://t.co/LDHtKaREOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks do you think it could be a musical?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks that palpatine comedy is a great idea isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks what's the name? Just between you and me. No one else will know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks hey, Davies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks I can't wait to go to sleep and get woken up by my new alarm clock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rylan and I are both in our bedrooms and we sneezed at the same time and it was great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks You don't happen to have a 9am for lit since 45 tomorrow do you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypothetiks when are you back in Aber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merteuiI 'why do you suppose I just threw a chair at your head?' is still one of the great lines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I wish good morning Britain would just go away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Anne Widdecombe would just go away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But also nowhere near as cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Furthermore: touch by Little Mix = also a tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also I can't believe Sutton United beat leads this is great take that dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris by the chainsmokers = tune]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_bone_x tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessToLetYuKnow not as much as I appreciated the tweet 😂😂 Hope all's ok!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessToLetYuKnow this is surely one of the great tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need to be harsh on England. Great game of cricket between two fantastic teams. Shame we lost but well done India #TMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BestIsYetToCom_ Jacob, I tweeted that yesterday 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how it ends up, this England performance has been for the most part well-planned and clinical. Jordan's been fantastic #TMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatAnstice I'm so hyped to re-listen tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatAnstice it was an emotional rollercoaster to say the least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibly the worst moment of my life https://t.co/whps5cv0Bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry @StevenJKFeeney bit harsh on me and, to be honest, a bit harsh on my friend, Chris Pratt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry @StevenJKFeeney come on don't turn kanye against me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry @StevenJKFeeney I'm just gonna say that using Chris Pratt gifs totally breaks the rules of the cheese pun game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenJKFeeney @toastteapoetry ah yeah, that chris Pratt guy is so... so... RED LEICESTER *runs into the night*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry (thank god im running out of ideas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry pigs will fly Wensleydale that you make a better pun than me comes along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry don't you think you're being a Brie bit hopefully with that pun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenJKFeeney @toastteapoetry these puns are getting out of hand, we cheddar watch ourselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry this is too much. I feta get going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toastteapoetry that was cheesy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turned up to mock a debate about cheese and now I'm in the debate about cheese and out of my depth help]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>