<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMiglio if you don't pay your taxes, then you're not paying for the wall #justsayin #VivaLaRevolucion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_Towl however, after a wee bit of research, I found this response: https://t.co/sPSzv8lRQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_Towl I didn't see that question on our NZ residency application... (Which we finally submitted yesterday)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 1 of Trump Administration: ACLU filed a FOIA request. Let's hold the president accountable - take action now: https://t.co/yQ7N01BeRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from the world's best @MasterClass: https://t.co/K6zMzD3MJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[live streaming Barack from NZ, but the audio and video aren't sync'd #expatlife #ObamaFarewell @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thesis is submitted for examination. Pictured is the "interim… https://t.co/JJILQ2zOk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm one of the fruity-est of all the loops... my loops have loops #PhDBrain https://t.co/esuC3zobGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMiglio we must see this.... #notime #ermagerd #rogueone #starwars #childhoodmemories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that time you lost an IMPORTANT piece of paper, moments after you scanned it (assuming you'd lose it...) #planningahead #blackhole #phdbrain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_Towl Do your hands hurt from clapping so much yet? :) So great to see you up on stage last night!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is so key to #PhDLife I'm lucky mine have been tough, but fair, this time around. Last time I got backstabbing… https://t.co/Gxcbr8d8ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things start getting more real when you've finished gathering your bridesmaids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if a psychologist has done a long-term EEG of a PhD student to see just how crazy we get throughout the journey... #PhDLife #crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got my page count down to 256 #PhDLife #journeytosubmission #nerdalert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that moment when you're simultaneously moving house, moving jobs (essentially), and planning a wedding #overwhelmed #phdlife #toomanychanges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What Has To Happen In The Next 14 Days https://t.co/YXSlcLpp1c via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh Rory... #GilmoreGirlsRevival #CircleOfLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about 2 wks from submitting my thesis (finally!). This marks month #42 since I began it #PhDLife #answertolifeuniverseeverything #yay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#truestory #massivedebt #expensivecollege https://t.co/nq3yOMCu0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how my top "skill" on LinkedIn is Sound. I guess I am pretty noisy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[other tweet got erased... The soundtrack to #westworld is amazing, but reminiscent of #BSGtheme? https://t.co/KhFIS7GqEq via @pitchfork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris worked on this, and it's finally coming out! "Netflix Just Picked Up the Hi-Tech Ghostbusting Movie Spectral" https://t.co/PXdSnWNMXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had a dollar for every conference badge I've acquired over the years, then I'd still have a lot of conference badges #PhDLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take Action:Urge the U.S. Senate to Pass the Amateur Radio Parity Act  https://t.co/YXJMDl90xP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of New Zealand:
"Hey, Sanka, you dead yet?"
"ya, man" 
#coolrunnings #beingfunny #notmakinglightofdeath #90smoviequotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@floisawilson yes us either... pretty bad one, eh?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Earthquake update: Chris and I OK. we're exhausted. we did feel… https://t.co/2L14Ho78I1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love you @SenWarren @elizabethforma https://t.co/Brgtu2BESC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article re: election things. #DontPanic https://t.co/HOGHULnvw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope to see this fervour and passion in 4 yrs, when stakes are back on the line. Don't forget, we can change things in 2 yrs too #congress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I couldn't get health ins. &amp; needed blood tests and Rxs for diabetes, the full-service clinics at Planned Pare… https://t.co/q0Hl7Ze4Bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rMuBV8QCOT here's why we grieve today #DividedNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart hurts. I'm dizzy. I can't breathe. #StillWithHer #LoveTrumpsHate #HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm proud to have voted for @HillaryClinton in the #Florida race as an expat studying in New Zealand. I also feel safer living in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's Immigration Site Keeps Crashing For Some Reason https://t.co/IqCuSm9UPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you FL, for legalizing medical marijuana. Save prosecution for the REAL drugs. #Florida]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh Broward County, always causing issues in presidential elections. #homestate #homecounty #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me. Right now. #Florida #imwithher #StrongerTogether #StrongWomen #GoHillary2016 https://t.co/bqLOKxZLjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrowardVotes My mail-in ballot was "received" on 26 October 2016, however it has not yet been "tabulated". Will this be updated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad my vote was finally counted in FL ;) https://t.co/bdD695ShJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwis are hilarious :) https://t.co/rrS1ZQJd3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#imwithher https://t.co/LwgfbFphU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great day to stay inside an edit a thesis #phdlife https://t.co/wNZ5bZNd9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 10-16-2016, Chris asked me to be his wife and I said yes… https://t.co/56HTglbZXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FiveThirtyEight's polls-plus forecast gives Trump 53% chance of winning Florida https://t.co/cxhzjVgAwh #unhappyvoter #votedinFL #imwithher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand tops world prosperity index again https://t.co/FwmgbD67GP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having travelled from USA, I'm up at 5am local time now. Amazing how much one can get done so early in the morning #nightperson #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This wouldn't be a family trip if there weren't drama #sigh #mitigatingmode #needaREALvaca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FatimahAl_Attas @Lizzie_Towl #PhDLifeMentor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lying down on the couch (getting over sinusitis) and flipped the channel to the last seconds of the NC St v. Clemson game #wideright #wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @MichelleObama She is the best thing to happen to this country. She makes me proud to call myself an America… https://t.co/ZjRTVDoShz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go ahead Trump supporters, vote on Nov 28! https://t.co/xMCctAbw9I via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlowlyUnbending my family has been with T-Mobile since 2001, welcome back :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also, It takes time... heaps of time... to do it right the first go https://t.co/8HsJa08JxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHwang A friend wrote the inspectors a letter and left it unfolded in checked luggage "I'm a computer musician. please be kind to my dmi"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHwang I'm very open with the TSA agents. I treat it like a computer, out in the open. #nosecrets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[these games are always nailbiters #MIAvsFSU #fourthquartermayhem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so thankful to have all the content written for the thesis. now it's just editeditedit! #phdlife #journeytosubmission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be a week too late to koin Hillary Clinton in Coral Springs! Fri, Sep 30, 2016, 3:30 – 5:00pm EDT https://t.co/nIburXA96N #Hillary2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so true #PhDLife #neverending #justfinish https://t.co/BmcRxiHdZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 2 3 4 6 #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's hard to let someone see an unfinished product, but it's the only way for a supervisor to know your progress an… https://t.co/MwaKTvLnBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when your partner sends you random uplifting notes of support #PhDLife https://t.co/h5nkuPqkzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is what I'm talkin' about...!! #win #FTW #allthewin https://t.co/rXU38anW8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love winning things! Thank you spark Very excited to be part of… https://t.co/ZRnt3WT64i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmcerqueira it's quite frightening... I'm voting absentee in FL. Hopefully our county doesn't pull a 2000-hanging-chad-type issue again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my brother is one of the many who got scammed by @ITTTech and had to take out many loans for his degree #loanscam https://t.co/F0ByOpQUE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ah yes, winter is still here... jk, spring https://t.co/ivJB1bwpTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But @Lizzie_Towl should know I am resting! I am taking care of myself! :) #PhDLifeMentor #almostthere https://t.co/A7yxFQa8hC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several people remarked how tired, sad, or concerned I look, but I think I'm suffering from #restingbitchyface #PhDLife #SleepisOverrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pun-based poetry: "Mei is bae!" https://t.co/Sc1Ov5Gkqi via @reddit from my MATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew these 7 years ago, but I can whole-heartedly agree now #phdlife #liveandlearn #bethechange https://t.co/fKFblOefAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that my hometown shows up on maps. Hurricanes in FL. Earthquakes in NZ. Still gonna finish my phd #phdlife https://t.co/MWee98blbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @Newsies soundtrack for providing the pump-up necessary for finishing this data analysis! @Spotify #phdlife #journeytosubmission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All day writing session in the library with my mates @FatimahAl_Attas @ReneetaMogan and #kameronchristopher #journeytosubmission #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get this alllllll the time.... https://t.co/hkMgyj6Ar3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you https://t.co/W6EmzT6Fmv for maintaining my sanity these final few weeks of thesis'ng #PhDLife #helpfultools #journeytosubmission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love kiwi-coverage of the USA elections #expat  https://t.co/5oHIYLRCKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna need reconstructive surgery for all my facepalms from watching this election drama #expatlife #sayswho https://t.co/jndgt8d3z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to thank the 90s Spotify radio playlist for helping me figure out a problem #ThrowbackThursday #PhDLife #highschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of Data Analysis for PhD: it doesn't work, until it finally does. #breakthru #phdlife #journeytosubmission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advisor is great! He had me parrot back what we discussed once. Turns out I misunderstood one thing! #greatadvise https://t.co/DfbW9NTKVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris sure got to benefit from this program! https://t.co/T1R5Mwbcuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey artists and artist-wanna-bes... Check out this fabulous unique course by my friend @spencersalazar #GetYourArtOn https://t.co/bnfdzNigjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tad cold this morning... https://t.co/9uteuBvhSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biphenyl I'm a crazy woman... Lived there 25 yrs... Also, the beach... I lived at the beach... but I got skin cancer #FLproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChorusNZ No tech came by. I did get a call 2 hrs after the scheduled appt that it's reskd to tomorrow. #unhappycustomer #stillnointernet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprised the technician is late. Classic kiwi "customer service". Still waiting. No word. @ChorusNZ #lateforwork #hopingtwitterwillhelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two simple ways to be happy at work https://t.co/73585Gy9GV via @nzherald https://t.co/pWpGp0yFsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yay! Thank you @SparkNZ for the extra mobile data for the weekend, since a Chorus tech can't come out until Monday. #greatcustomerservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[home internet is out. mobile data almost gone (#pogo). can't do much of anything except wait for @SparkNZ to call back #sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, New Zealand news #noguns #notrump https://t.co/GNsnZL4Q7F via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm over-explanatory in emails and under-explanatory in my thesis, so I've been writing my chapters as gmail drafts #whateverworks #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acknowledgements section: I would like to thank chocolate, coffee/tea/espresso, and alcohol for helping me through this thesis #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[funnily enough, I have a remarkably unique name #onlyoneintheworld #anonymityimpossible #cannothide https://t.co/xFPMMzLwXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@floisawilson pokevision is a great site, if you haven't already heard! :) I kept meaning to tell you.. ha. #phdlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I definitely agree #welly https://t.co/RGXcSoYJKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when other people get buzzed/drunk, then I can just be myself #naturallyexcitable #bigpersonality #seeminglyforeverdrunk #uptomylevel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DianaSMuzyka However, now I also have the problem that my advisor's name is Jim :) So "I'm going to the gym/jim" is ambiguous. #TheJim]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>