<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We love our free range life so much that we laid an egg with a heart on it. https://t.co/rIdoEQexqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart, empathic and good at maths - yep, that's me: https://t.co/DQyl8EkSGP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #nationalbirdday today in the USA. I'm a bird. Yay me! https://t.co/9bdec4cmWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yvonne found a baby bird that had fallen out of its nest. Swallowed it in one piece, with the tiny legs dangling out of her beak for a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovered the new neighbours' bird feeder, I'm now a regular visitor over there. In return I let them take selfies with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle A sheltered spot, cool, long grass, maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I was allowed to go into the house and check what's under the tree for us. Sigh. https://t.co/2iwHAsqb3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greeted a human in the driveway today, got asked how I got there, picked up and plonked back near the run. Don't know why I try really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the treats and the little foxy egg cup, but the toy is the best! Love playing ball!!! #nzsecretsanta Thank you… https://t.co/HpSx1TtQW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #nzsecretsanta presents are amazing! There were even chocolates for the humans (not pictured due to sun) &amp; a don… https://t.co/wHSGCPh47L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went for a wander down the street - just walked up the driveway now only to see that I missed our #nzsecretsanta gift opening ceremony!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So relieved to see my #nzsecretsanta giftee loves her present! I still have to wait until the whole whānau can unwrap together tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly! https://t.co/dtuxuKKKcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's how angry I was about being told off for escaping from the run and hanging out in the veggie beds. https://t.co/dD9vSkMKYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escaped from the run super early today to wait for the #nzsecretsanta sleigh. Then I remembered that I'll have to wait until Tue to unwrap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time we really nailed that whole game of hiding our eggs. The humans have no idea where we lay and are now out of eggs. #freerange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learnt that everyone in this family has to be present for #nzsecretsanta gift unwrapping. First opportunity: Tuesday. Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good reason not to eat my sisters. https://t.co/dsXe02DVSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donkeys on the paddock next door! We got quite upset and alerted the humans as loud as we could. https://t.co/fakZEUaMIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh-oh, the human found Birgit's secret nest. 17 eggs, 2 of them broken. #busted https://t.co/1UusLzBY6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #nzsecretsanta gift is at the storehouse! I'm so excited!  And the present for my giftee has also been received.… https://t.co/aAo2jhha6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just accused of escaping. picked up and carried back to the run. When the other two were seen out too, popped back down with an apology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's coffee time! https://t.co/i0PixxwPct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q9 #nzsecretsanta Same answer as Q1 (I think?): I've n ver watched a movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q10 #nzsecretsanta Parrot food, a couple of hens for a family in need (by Oxfam), a Christmas tree, a heroine egg cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q8 #nzsecretsanta I love Karori and would never want to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q7 All my #nzsecretsanta memories are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibookgirl I do!!! And mealworms! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q6 #nzsecretsanta  I'd lay better eggs. Lately I've been laying a few without shell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q5 #nzsecretsanta Anything animal welfare. My previous companions Sonja and Eva were rescued by HuHa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta That last one was for #Q4 #nzsecretsanta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta Elegant, tidy, clean. I preen several times a day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q3 #nzsecretsanta  I wanted to continue laying awesome eggs, but as I'm getting older the quality varies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q2 #nzsecretsanta I'd buy a larger house for me and the kids (Yvonne &amp; Birgit) and eat only mealworms and buttermilk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzsecretsanta #Q1 #nzsecretsanta I've never watched TV. We don't have power in our coop and the human's house is off limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foot is looking much better now. If I was allowed to cross the road I'd go shopping for my #nzsecretsanta myself. Will send human instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoah, last night's storm blew our water bucket and feeder over! #hungry #thirsty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small piece of wood got stuck in my wound. The female human got it out with tweezers, while the male human almost fainted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news! It's not bumblefoot! It was 'just' an abscess, now we only need to keep the hole clean and hope it close… https://t.co/hPoWBGa0kM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the human was hugging me after the dog incident, she checked my feet. She suspects I have bumblefoot. Have to see the vet today. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got chased by a dog! A small one, but it was still scary. Lots of humans ran outside when they heard me getting upset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may or may not be guilty of some of these too... https://t.co/wH6ExpksUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human said my feet were too dirty (after scratching in the mud) to come inside and sign up for #nzsecretsanta. I hope she did it for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@litchfieldhens this seems like a very good idea! Wonder if we'd get treats to go if we try this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a damp start to the day. Lots of wriggling things above ground just waiting to say hello... ... to our stomachs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fireworks night (week) isn't our favourite time of year. Loud explosions and high pitched whizzing noises can be scary. #animalsafety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@W_Rigs Give it to your chooks, give it to your chooks!!! It looks so much fun, they'll love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a xylophone!!! Look what other talented chooks can do: https://t.co/pmKGfVLYWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoseTheChicken Yep. I had ALL the silverbeet! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get that tomato plants have to be kept safe from nasty bugs and caterpillars - but does that have to mean 'chicke… https://t.co/awehRGZspO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gail_nz Will do! They're rather proud of their beautiful eggs. My eggs are much bigger though (sorry, just had to point that out).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lettuce has been chicken proofed - that's a disaster! https://t.co/K7N9KKDexy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesss!!! It's a gardening day and I can help with the compost! https://t.co/Ru4tidt8bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busted. They found me in the veggie patch. https://t.co/Okt0NrSN0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're really enjoying this nicer weather! https://t.co/Q0J6fcQ5yI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out on the deck, watching what's going on inside. https://t.co/pFu5n1bBQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain. Hiding under the flower cart. https://t.co/q2UsUwF41L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free chicken in New York: https://t.co/O2cIlExuu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ut5Uv9ucEd This is so weird... a yodelling Japanese guy is making fun of hens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proving that we're tree birds. That's Yvonne in the front, me in the back. https://t.co/SuTPUmBgvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a cool new door opener! Works automatically based on day light. No more hedgehog intruders! #fancychickens https://t.co/Pw2RBqqtKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be in the Chicken-Wing for the day because I'm moulting, it's cold and raining. Need to stay warm. https://t.co/kUqoXceK2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to make a chicken wrap: https://t.co/sDxzXtAEZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a new water bucket. Not convinced yet. https://t.co/XP2ODXbSHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're not impressed with the weather. https://t.co/dzd2yuNAG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating a chicken habitat - sounds a bit like my home: https://t.co/FYNKlDLDSI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so glad my life doesn't look like this: https://t.co/uOmVV9Jk9x.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thing has been installed in our run. We're not interested yet, but might be once we find a body underneath. https://t.co/Vi9GsMcusT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escaped the run to sleep in a tunnel I built during the day. I'm too far in for the humans too reach me, hehehe. #sleepingunderthestars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting chicken research: https://t.co/oIBKl29JsV - we prefer pretty humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birgit is sick and has to sleep in the rumpus room tonight. Hope she gets better soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karoricat That's why the water tasted fishy!!! https://t.co/MUe1gMPD0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I laid the tiniest egg (eggs from the others for comparison). https://t.co/Q4dobzYja1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The beer brewing neighbour brought us some treats! #yum https://t.co/Rn2FT7Tl2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating some of the yummy mealworms we got for Christmas! https://t.co/jZlIOXRG06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a shortcut to the veggie garden via the deck, but the cat saw me and told the humans. Got turned around. https://t.co/THcKcWRHDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what @bexquilliam and @Christ_Monkey got me (and Yvonne &amp; Birgit) for Christmas!!! #yum https://t.co/guVxyDa9QR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're very welcome. Merry Christmas! https://t.co/weFazdOGhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birgit was attacked by something *inside* our run at 1am. The humans are no longer wondering why I prefer to hide in the woods at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have vanished into the woods again. Why would I sleep in the coop with two others if I can have peaceful solitude?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked out of the forest behind the sheep paddock, where I spent the night. Not sure why the humans worried about me. #borntobewild]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that I've got my #nzsecretsanta present I can be a bit naughty again - haven't returned to the coop, will sleep outside tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aigantighe Thank you so much, I feel like a super heroine! Love the card too, especially since we're not allowed to cross the road at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally I have an appropriate way of presenting my eggs to the humans!!! Thank you, my #nzsecretsanta @aigantighe! https://t.co/Sj8bgWE7rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we've worked out that if we all run in different directions, at least two of us get a longer roam. Silly humans can only grab one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? I thought I could open it on deliverey day! How am I supposed to wait for 2 more days, knowing it's so close! https://t.co/vcfYm16JV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wake up earlier than the kids. Why shouldn't I hop the fence and go for an early morning wander? I tried to keep quiet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Too hot to go out And too hot to play ball. So we sat in the run. We did nothing at all. #chickeninthehat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sun only shone. It was too hot to play. So we sat in the run all that hot, sunny day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason to quit eating chicken: https://t.co/0mPyI1qRLi (apart from obvious one that we're really smart friends, not food).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we all agreed to behave ourselves. We came when called, even if Birgit was a few minutes behind. We all got treats too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and Yvonne watched, from the run, as Birgit kept hiding under trees and bushes from @Christ_Monkey. She missed out on treats too!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... I hid 20mins longer than the kids, but 1 snuck out again while I was being found! We found it more entertaining than the humans though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We invented a new game. We all go to different corners of the property, then stay still and eat, waiting to be found and returned home...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't beat treats eaten straight from a hand. Makes you feel personally served. Must be what eating at a restaurant is like for humans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoohoo, my #nzsecretsanta present is at the storehouse! Already figured out the way to the mailbox (at the end of driveway), can't wait...!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took years to learn how to overcome the fence. Now that we're good at it they've raised the fence to 2.40m! #unfair https://t.co/VJJaEz2rCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle Neighbours' chooks sleep outside on top of their hen house. Only go inside if it's really cold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wings clipped, fence raised, but I'm unstoppable. Still manage to throw myself across fence. Result: we're locked in the hen house tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't get back into run for bedtime. Made humans search for our hiding spots when they got home late. https://t.co/AvROKIscbJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>