<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat yup midnight tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakedslob @dayzdevteam I wouldn't say fps is great. Still get drops into the low 30s on a i7 6700k at 4.5ghz and gtx 1070]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightwlf @nzBrowncoat @MightyApe you think with the amount of stuff they stock they could spare a few things for Banana points. Let down!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @Steep_Game I'm not into snow sports so maybe my opinion is moot, but the demo did not grab me, played it for a hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mafiagame @IGN I didn't get far, the game was a technical disaster and made it unbearable to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlefield yes but at different dates and what about every map pack after this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlefield why must you split the community like this? Maps should be free! Find other stuff to charge for, like you done with Titinfall 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamejunkieNZ @HPomen wow that is impressive! Do you get to keep it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamejunkieNZ @HPomen specs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamejunkieNZ @HPomen are you reviewing it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DMC_Ryan IGN ignite the console wars by putting up click bait titles all the time so don't try take the moral high ground Ryan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForzaMotorsport @thegameawards this is a insult to all the people who can't play it on pc dues to issues. Core 0 at 100%!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hangar13Games @YouTube "the award for most unoptimized pc GOTY goes too" at least there are heaps of nominees! Shit year for pc ports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@netflix will netflix release a Windows 10 update so we can use laptops?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@netflix thank you so much! I am a Seafarer and don't have a connection at sea, so this makes me so happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@survivetheark is this game 60 fps yet with high settings? Gtx 1070 I7 4770]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoMansSky I have tried refunding twice. I honestly felt betrayed and scammed after reaching 10 hours. Then the radio silence, low blow man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhhh Yeahhhhh https://t.co/1wQuvRZZLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BishopTamaki you are the scum around my toilet seat, and it's time to clean that scum. Get lost you con!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlefield operations desperately needs quick match option, always empty servers! It's this being worked on? Also medals system is flawed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CallofDuty @SamLndn I'm not buying it until it's separate from that stupid space shooter. COD was once great :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat so that leads into another question... press review? Who you reviewing for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZSO that game is a pretty big deal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat who did you order it from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyGeorge @RobertDowneyJr Boohoo criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightwlf @GamejunkieNZ nice nice nice! I'm on a gtx 1070 myself paired with a i7 4770 and 16gb ram with 2x 240gb SSD on a 144Hz G Sync]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightwlf @GamejunkieNZ specs? Same case as me! Build it yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat started watching this last night due to your recommendation. Very good so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RockstarGames you must be kidding me!? No PC version!? Why rockstar why!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Berduu I wish the HUD was not so cluttered but unfortunately you need most of it to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SgtRoss_Squad @RoyAwesome @JoinSquad pretty sure I ran into a bug of it in v6, head would rotate but not my body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommandrAwesome @RoyAwesome @JoinSquad would be great, but I suspect its just a staged shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyAwesome @JoinSquad how is that guy aiming away from where he is walking? New feature!? Free look? Gun moves with head?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlefield cash grab much! Way to go, exploiting the passion of your fanbase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForzaMotorsport and still get major fps hitches with a i7 4770 and GTX 1070 and 16 ram on medium/high settings. Where's the communication?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForzaMotorsport I should not have to disable a cpu core, lock my 144hz G-sync screen at 60hz, and enable V-sync just to get stutter free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForzaMotorsport I disappointed in the complete lack of communication from the team regarding all the issues with the PC version.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mafiagame I'm scared about performance now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForzaMotorsport pc performance on FH3 is a joke. My rig should be getting at least 60fps on ultra settings. Stutters and low fps instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have stopped playing Forza Horizon 3 on PC until the performance improves. 30fps on a i7 4770 and GTX 1070 is unacceptable @ForzaMotorsport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Berduu what about the performance? I have had to do a lot of trickery just to get rid of the stutter! Surely performance over photo mode?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeelingLogical @bohemiainteract @Hicks_206 @eurogamer I don't want either of those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @NoMansSky I got bored and have not played again the second day from release]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HorizonForza where's pc? It's the pc platform where you need to prove yourself, not xbox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xema25 @NVIDIAGeForce Open the overlay in-game, go to options, overlays, FPS counter, and tell it what corner to go in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xema25 @NVIDIAGeForce there always has been that option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@creationz89 @Battlefield confirmed, I cannot join Conquest, and rush is dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickBach 32 players on the opposite team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickBach just counted snipers using the scoreboard, out of 32 players, 16 were snipers. Only 3 medics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickBach my one criticism are snipers, too easy, and far, far too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Demize99 BF1 is so far the best BF game I have played, and I have played every release. The beta is truly stunning on PC. Good job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EA_DICE BF1 is so far the best BF game I have played, and I have played every release. The beta is truly stunning on PC. Good job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickBach BF1 is so far the best BF game I have played, and I have played every release. The beta is truly stunning on PC. Good job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlefield BF1 is a absolutely excellent game, stunning. How you get it to look so pretty and still perform as well as it does is amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport @paulconner33 thats happening on Chrome for me also on Win10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport @lpkdanny its happening on PC's too on all browsers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@True_ACGHD @AskEASupport I will do anything for your PC code!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport @Burent_obama the chat is not working for most being and when it does it says there is a 200min wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport its 31st August and I still don't have my BF1 Insider Beta key and your support page says "No support channels..." What gives?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EA @Battlefield @EA_DICE @AskEASupport really - Wait Time: between 85 - 90 minutes. Did you guys not put extra staff on for BF1?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirPunk619 @AskEASupport he never would of been as good of a friend as me :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirPunk619 @AskEASupport can I have your PC code please!? We will be best friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskEASupport your support page and chat seems to be done and I still don't have my PC BF1 code and its 11.15pm on the 30th, what gives!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @DeusEx it's 5.30am and I just got to bed thanks to that game. Luckily I have no work today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @NetflixANZ @netflix I loved netflix a year ago, but it's already old and stale, the only New content is Indian &amp; Japanese stuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XboxAustralia unless there is some sought of steam integration, this will be wildly untrue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeusEx typical pc screw over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gamespot typical click bait from GameSpot. I'm done and unfollowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Lounge &amp; Steelseries Ultimate Peripheral Bundle https://t.co/fPIs9Sok5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @vodafoneNZ @Ookla is this Vodafone cable by any chance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can win 10 games in the @GreenManGaming Summer Sale! #GMGSummer16 https://t.co/nnMZqpX0IS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've entered @Gambitiousinc &amp; @GreenManGaming's Giveaway for NVIDIA GTX 1070 &amp; 1 of 10 copies of Zombie Night Terror https://t.co/V2pBWJLIa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreigChris still no anti-aliasing by the looks of thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoinSquad please work on the anti aliasing because it's terrible in its current state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DMC_Ryan voice acting and writing was terrible! Looked same same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Computerlounge no new card is affordable in NZ after we get gouged at retail! Just look at the GTX 1080!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bohemiainteract "another week starts, another week of no experimental server's. 15fps on stable is not playable." Really worth a block?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bohemiainteract I was just blocked from the dayz twitter for my 1st ever dayz tweet, all it said was....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiteFraven @dayzdevteam they just blocked me because of my tweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got blocked frm @dayzdevteam for my last tweet. That was my 1st eva tweet about DayZ. No insults, no swearing, no trolling. But blocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dayzdevteam You ban me for this? First tweet ever about DayZ and you ban me? Wow, this is what I get for giving you my money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dayzdevteam another week starts, another week of no experimental server's. 15fps on stable is not playable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GameJunkieNZ @2degreesmobile in crappy low definition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@turtlebeach Your new site does not have links to the drivers! I cant download the Stealth 450 drivers for Surround Sound!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I entered to win a AAA game from @GreenManGaming! You should enter too!  https://t.co/GSOPACI77p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SgtRoss_Squad @JoinSquad overdue on some updates I think, game is getting a tad stale with slow content drops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CallofDuty so incredibly bored of COD. Please, go back to WWII or current day and back to basics. COD4, still the best by far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BattleRoyaleMod please leave it like that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuantumBreak @XboxAustralia is the fun just starting for the pc version? Remedy, you let yourselves down. Shocking work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majornelson @QuantumBreak @SamLakeRMD @remedygames shame the pc version is such a wreck, guess I won't get to enjoy QB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KokaKolaA3 @Arma3official looks great, but at 23 fps is not fun to play. All I want, over everything else, is more fps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyAwesome Congrats, when is it going to be implemented into the retail build?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyAwesome you tease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BattleRoyaleMod you look a little like the guy from Freddy Got Fingered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Unblock_Us Netflix is down again, unblocker error. Not sure what I'm paying for at this stage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steam_Support would think you guys would mention something before planned outages here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat poor thing :( hope it's doing alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @majornelson @MadMaxGame @XboxNZ_Official haha it's been $20 on steam!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nvidia can the shield DNS be changed manually? Need a device that can use my smart DNS settings. Also, Are they available in New Zealand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NVIDIAGeForce @DyingLightGame I prefer sharp shadows, I know its not realistic, but I think it looks better.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>