<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots not sure I understand what you mean by the west end being toxic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#weareallcanucks first time here! https://t.co/dDhX247jYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots without liberal values you would not be able to happily live as an openly gay man ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump so classy with your husbands hand on your ass.  Just like your daddy #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshallscanada You lost me as a customer until you stop selling @IvankaTrump brand in your stores #NoBanNoWall #votewithyourwallet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau truly disheartening that extreme Christian terrorists have felt empowered by the actions of our neighbours to the south]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieLeitch extreme Christian terrorists...sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bob_crowe come to beautiful BC! We're spending all our vacation in Canada this year.  Lots to see &amp; explore :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booked a few nights at an apartment in DT #victoria over Canada day weekend #staylocal #explorecanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can you do to #protest #trump in #canada? Write to companies that carry their brands.   https://t.co/Bof5GoX0Wv #votewithyourwallet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hudsonsbay why do you keep selling @IvankaTrump brand at your CDN stores? She's now a political figure and ethically opposed to CDN values!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump your father is a disgusting human. Stay on the evil train with him &amp; u will be remembered in history for all the wrong reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @KellyannePolls @JudgeJeanine @POTUS the world is watching the disgusting behaviour of #potus and #gop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's sad watching America go to sh*t because the minority, led by an orange anus, are ruling and ruining things for the majority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone we can work something out of you want another Dale vancouver original hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone yeah love doing paintings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone lol..too southern?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like #jethros restaurant on Bute didn't last long!  Already closed.  What happened? #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you get rid of tiny moths? #vancouver #advice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriendsRH have you checked out @zombie_housewives on Instagram?  Super funny.  Especially Eileen and Plump Brandi xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super excited we booked a lakeside cottage on #saltspringisland for a week in June.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having fun text debating trump with my drunk  brother In law in Winnipeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump how does it feel to have over a million people march against the disgusting views of your father?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: don't buy the "fresh" #kirkland shepherds pie @Costco - grey peas, foul sour taste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro sad that's all she's valued for...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_wingrove @RonaAmbrose she doesn't represent Canada or the vast majority of its people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow...I will not watch. #blackfriday #fucktrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a msg on FB from an old classmate apologizing for bullying me 25 years ago...I have hope for the world  today, even if short lived]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christyclarkbc you didn't put me first, and I won't be putting you first come election time #disgraceful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah!  Loving #merylstreep for ripping #donaldtrump a new asshole!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone @Communism_Kills I don't understand...a nice pearl choker can really pull an outfit together! :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[according to #AncientAliens tv show, my genetic skin condition may mean I'm descended from Reptilian aliens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #cocoonthereturn like a boss...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly...I can't wait for a quiet and boring January]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots Happy New Year by the way :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots I hope 2017 will be filled with less news stories like this :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nandos_Canada slowest service ever in my life at the Davie St location in van just now!  1/2 hour for take out order nobody ahead of me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiggybubba merry Christmas to you and yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a good Christmas cry earlier thinking of family far away &amp; departed, pets &amp; friends we can't be with,  and those who are lonely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots lol that's ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contemplating researching #Wicca.  Anyone familiar who can point me in the right direction for a crash course?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched the movie "other people" on #netflix it was heartbreaking, real, and amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mark_musing thx.  Yeah they're taking $150.  Rip off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious how much you think is reasonable for my building management to charge me to fix a 2" ding in the wall I caused accidentally?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pantone just announced its colour of the year for #2017 is Greenery! https://t.co/MWSuKaoMaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRaymondMc indeed it should be.  I have to learn to not give in so much to unrealistic societal pressures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Christmas season I freak out about buying the perfect gifts and not having enough money to do so. I know it's wrong priorities #lesigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking ahead...I'd like to see a Winfrey / Warren democratic ticket for 2020 US election. Just putting it out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynneux @colinjones so frustrating.  I can't believe people are so blind to the rising of Hitler 2.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this Remembrance Day more than ever I'm grateful to our service people for our freedoms and security of the greatest country, #Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I'm watching a horror movie #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NakedBoyNews @PiranhaVegas @charliesvegas @PhoenixLasVegas @FreeZoneLV thanks...coming tomorrow for 5 nights :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my #USElections2016 #predictionmap we'll see if it's a little optimistic, but regardless #imwithher https://t.co/jK8RY5irLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which #gaybar in #lasvegas is good to check out?  For dancing or for the bear crowd?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for our new chair to arrive and also packing for a 5 day trip to Vegas tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That #awkward moment when as part of upper management you're not included in the lunch out invite w/ rest of coworkers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slice_tv will do.  It was actually my favourite of all the housewives series (Beverly hills and New York close behind)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realize when we booked, but we'll be in Vegas for the election #gongshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slice_tv will you be bringing us RHOMbourne seasons 2&amp;3 soon?? Please??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our upstairs neighbour has had "the sound of silence" on repeat very loudly for the last 2 hours #annoying #ironic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westelm even with exchange &amp; shipping, why would the same sofa cost $2400 in US but over $4400 to bring into Canada? #frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver now that they've woken up everyone in a 4 block radius, the protesters ran away like dirty little rats,  @BlueHorizonVan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone oh oh that's not good.  A quick cheap trip to vegas may be in order? :) we're going in 2 weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone @BlueHorizonVan @CityofVancouver union workers from hotel staff I assume.  Way too loud. I called the police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Loving the super load banging at 7:45am in front of @BlueHorizonVan @CityofVancouver this is not a peaceful protest.  Way too loud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trump and #clinton sitting and laughing at a fundraiser dinner separated only by a cardinal.  My eyes don't understand #cnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany wow that's the most delusional thing I've read all night.  So embarrassed for you and your candidate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I think we can safely assume we'll be saying hello to Madam president in 2017!  #ImWithHer #debate #hillarywon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany not going bankrupt and playing the blame game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far #hillaryclinton is slaying #trump intellectually #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottienhughes U keep saying there's no evidence Donald walked into pageant change rooms even though he said it. Are U saying he's a liar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmBanafsheh @KellyannePolls @MELANIATRUMP @CNN @JamilSmith he should have been arrested immediately #deplorable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyAnnPolls @bigrope_store @realDenaldTrump @NYDailyNews that's the smartest thing I've heard from your campaign!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our prime minister in #canada is a proud #feminist will yours be #usa ? #werewithhillary… https://t.co/OquTr4Hf9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very telling that #democrats poll higher among college educated voters than #republicans #justsaying #canadiansforhillary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @AC360 @scottienhughes Ana you're the smartest woman on tv.  Thanks for keeping it real.  Canada loves you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany @ABCPolitics I pray to your god that child doesn't learn anything about ethics from your candidate! #pussygate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBC @TheGoodsCBC sorry I gave you a full week but just can't deal with one very annoying personality :( #seriesrecordingdelete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FemalesForTrump then I hope you get fingered in so many ways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankSchwab71 @kayleighmcenany  "when you're a star you can do anything.  Grab them by the pussy." -Donald Trump still defending him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany "when you're a star you can do anything.  Grab them by the pussy.  You can do anything" -Donald Trump still defending him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany "when you're a star you can do anything.  Grab them by the pussy.  You can do anything" -Donald Trump. Still defending him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@postmarkone yeah.  It got me really down for a few minutes but I'm over it. My bf loves me the way I am so I should too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A client of mine I haven't seen in 3 months and bumped into asked me if I gained weight and told me I should work out :/  #lifelongstruggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRaymondMc my employer is offering free flu shots.  I've never gotten them before.  Is this something you'd recommend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch so it's ok when trump does it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren so it's ok when trump does it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davingreenwell I don't know for sure but sounded like worker rights and demands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite the loud #union #protest outside of #bluehorizon #hotel on #robsonstreet #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaiGeddes hello!  Happy Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I'm 60 years late, but I just discovered Ella Fitzgeralds music.  Great at work listening.  But I need a martini to go with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized the oranges I bought from #urbanfare are imported from S. Africa.  That can't be good for the environment ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm living for Real housewives of Melbourne! #awesometv #guiltypleasures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#quntisential awesome #saturdaynight watching #StrangerThings and eating #popcorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling dizzy all morning.  Weirdest thing is that on my FB notifications it said 7 years ago today my status was "felt dizzy all day"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiggybubba you are a good person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancityhotshots do you believe in reincarnation ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally started watching #StrangerThings on -#netflix after finishing #OITNB and super love it so far! #80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched #meangirls for the 100th time.  It's still pretty #fetch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autocorrect on my phone for my first initial and last name is Deodorant...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>