<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Freer Remember how we were chatting about how much forgotten protein shakers reek? Guess what I forgot... D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tfw you've just had the best extraction ever from the coffee machine at work and no one cares. FINE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Yeah man for sure, lets sort it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris because you always had a very visible boner whenever you said it to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a related note, my stomach feels oddly warm right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that @Peter_Freer keeps destroying souls at work with his spicy sauces and related food items]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone talking shit about this crappy NZ summer but I'm just happy it lets me get some sleep at night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DraskylDotaTwo Hope you keep streaming something man, I love chilling watching your streams!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Are they legit or grey market?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day up at the bach feelsbadman https://t.co/SYpmor7tBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to switch off the brain https://t.co/i2YU7HUCLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris "I prefer PC gaming" still never thought I'd see the day =')]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight of the fucking year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarioSeags 100% Nothing can touch eggs benedict.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris @polg @olafquintessa You're picking up new series' constantly ;o This one is one of the best though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMonoChroma You picked a pretty good day for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the new grinder, the set is complete. Coffee heaven. #Profitec700 #ProfitecT64 https://t.co/PVoRrhkHGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmmmm new coffee grinder on its way! The full set up is nearly complete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@incognateo Yeah totally. Bit of a slap in the face tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That UFC Melbourne card is truly atrocious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange @TheReaganMorris You know what, you're right, it's a terrible idea. Sorry guys =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Haha yeah you could pretty much just throw everything there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Your new section is 200m from your current house?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The magical time of year is nearly upon us! Xmas? Nah, fibre is being installed on my street!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington folk, are buses still running to/from the airport?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Happy birthday Reagan from your friends at Simons Cheap Cars! We hope you have a fantastic day. DM dick pics to unsubscribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garage_Project Perfect, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garage_Project Hey guys, do you know when I'll be able to get my mitts on some Red Rocks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day in the new office down! 3 crashes and one guy kicking the power out. Got heaps done. Heaps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last week of working from home. Cherish your time with your espresso machine, guys. You never know how long it will last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange Home grown lemons!? They should be so lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh NZ, where you're not quite sure if trick or treaters will come so you have to buy candy and none ever show up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I miss the memo about indicating becoming optional or something? There are some deadset munters on the roads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody black birds flicking the garden mulch everywhere!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange Lunch of champions. PSA do not try the spiced whatever one. It will only make you sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange I was dubious because most iced coffee type stuff sucks, but man that shit is goooooood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garage_Project My favorite time of the year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Solid choice man =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty stoked with how my peach tree is coming along this spring. In related news I'm definitely over 30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange @Peter_Freer @Daffyflyer Bandwagoning is at new heights and gamers have always been notorious for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow really, McGregor gets ANOTHER fight outside of FW? That's some bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited about the Foran signing, but at the same time it feels similar to the RTS/Luke stuff last year, and that didn't work out so well....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's only so many ways you can dress up chicken and rice before you become a serial killer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point I assume you can just stitch all the FFXV trailers together and watch the whole game. There's one for every 10min of gameplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris Never say Melly Gibby again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWiLeague @iHeartRadio Unlike the Warriors you guys are going from strength to strength!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter It's pretty easy to find, and Twisted Fork is nearby for good brunch. OH also Nero belgian waffles in West End.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter You need to go to Twisted Fork for good food and Fritz European Fry House for good junk food poutine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris @Playdead Easily my GOTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyHarman1 @TheReaganMorris Thanks! We're all family really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris lol! Thanks bruh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least this should be the end of Cappy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris I've had years to get used to how annoying you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it annoying peoples fault for being annoying on social media or is it my fault for following them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nztigerinoz Onya bro, hope you guys win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris ahhh things are a bit muddy atm. For 1080p gaming it probably is. Or the RX470/80....depends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupid NZ pricing. Oh well, new PC gear is always fun https://t.co/rpuQnJok5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrecklessEating https://t.co/87KgAl5gHi Instantly thought of you guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't often have milk coffees but it's nice to know I can make this whenever https://t.co/BY0DuNFHnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes indeed Suicide Squad was legitimately awful. Barely functioned as a film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside is one of the best games I've played in a long time. Do yourself a favor and get on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheReaganMorris potentially, I gotta get this thing running first haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is going to be an interesting day https://t.co/rpVCl62M2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greeniecg We can arrange that. https://t.co/LbiqMeBGrD It looks more like a penalty there, but 5-7 weeks? 2 tops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greeniecg https://t.co/Fg7v9WioQs here it is. No really, that's it. 5-7 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty typical really, but that one will come back to haunt us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really quite hard to have any sympathy for Jon Jones given his rap sheet. Such a shame too cause he is by far and a way the best LHW ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smaughstein Yeah man it sucks =( dampened the excitement for 200 considerably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha they start playing a 200 promo with Jones in it, then cut it straight away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I thought we'd get through to UFC 200 without a fight being pulled =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnWarrior @NZWarriors Would love to get a big prop, or maybe have a go at Foran ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Ricky Stuart things #NRLRaidersKnights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should have another coffee or breakfast? Trick question! Coffee IS breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy I'm bad with street names but I believe they're on Dixon. Rather far away from where you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy If you're after a good place to try, I recommend Flight Hangar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy I mean, it's good that you're getting into coffee and all, but Reagan....no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP @RyanJimmo =( Will always remember the robot after his UFC debut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy Fair enough then. Hope you enjoy your first not MMO but MMO experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy have fun feeling like you're not doing something everyone has already done =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy wow welcome to what everyone was doing years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsure if it's exciting or scary watching the GBP tank. #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNewsboy Hmm? I was just out your ways, thought I saw you too but didn't want to disturb you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gromange Had the Manly and KBbq, both were amaze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have Umami Burger withdrawals. Send help asap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lN8O4ZKlgw First 12 win arena run!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought a massive bag of Twizzlers while in the states and they're awful but I can't stop eating them. I am everything I hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tomchoucrew @aurora44games We attended rather quietly. Feel free to check out our interview with Epic for updates! https://t.co/aLad1Ynd4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greeniecg Interfering with the Roosters player in a try scoring situation. Not penalty try because of other Warriors player proximity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hectic first #E32016 is now done! Met a lot of cool people, though barely see the show floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys I need to find some Nike Romaleos in LA. Pls help D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lippykid @aurora44games Hell yeah, good times mate :D Hope you're doing well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter nah not this year, we'll try find you after and say hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter oh you have purple hair, we saw you in line haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's do this #E32016 https://t.co/jwKp4DShrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to #E3 tomorrow o_O Days getting pretty packed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stoked the Warriors went out and played some positive footy. Looks like they found their identity again. Win is just a bonus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inzer belt is on its way! Right before I leave to E3. First world problems &gt;_&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always fun watching how feral Aussies get to each other come Origin time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From fielding a side well over the cap to fielding a side worth less than a quarter pack. Well played Eels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter Yep, I'm sure we can work something out, our schedule is still comin together]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>