<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn can't complain with a secret rare on day 1 tho I hope you get some great pulls in yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn yessir! No hyper rares tho :( I was hoping for a lapras one it looks great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn awesome! Looking forward to it, I wanted to post my box pulls in case you didn't have an idea of pull rate yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn extremely happy with the pulls https://t.co/rhkMnUuIvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho do you still keep up with the NHL in your downtime? If so curious to know if you are a rangers fan or another team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketk33 @dominickevans @pjackson_nl @gliverpool9966 @thirstleigh @JustinTrudeau prob bcuz of health care, still should be a non issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself is it too cliche to say your the greatest Joker ever? Tip of the hat sir and looking forward to The Last Jedi!! â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandyOrton @xXSound_WavexX met you a ton during your initial run always a stand up guy thnx for takin the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKurtAngle I think it's a crime you never won the Rumble, excellent time to come back and win it. #BringAngleBack @WWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho Leafs destroyed the Rangers last night you stupid idiot, put them on the list #GoLeafsGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme @survivorcbs @JeffProbst guess what week it is...it's #SurvivorMillennialsVsGenXFinale week ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keys_cory @thegamechasers your portrait above your tv is amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Messineo @Stabby_McTaco @Pokemon most people breed to get their shinys easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pokemon Sun/Moon is the greatest Pokemon game, Go was fun but not the same as the main games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn @TrollAndToad and I pulled a mega v venusaur ex in the salamence box needed it as well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn @TrollAndToad thanks for the recommend! I found a store close to home picked up 8 needed ones today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 it will work for your iPod but unless you go thru the work they won't show up on your phones itunes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 good luck bud it's a nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn ps I didn't buy booster boxes I opened about 100 or so packs in general but yea what you recommend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn I'm hesitant to buy single cards cuz for the most part I have good pack pulls thanks ptp :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn quick question I'm like 20 cards off completing evolutions pretty much 8 full arts do you recommend buying singles or packs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @DanSlott wow is it actually? Damn I gotta keep an eye out for it..the baywatch one comes out tomorrow too ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @JayBauman1 @Billythechode check this out Billy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegamechasers @YouTube get your shit together YouTube what's going on Billy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieevamarie the black and white brings the sleek, you bring the sexy to my screensaver ðŸ˜› https://t.co/famI9fxzx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme ahem there was a 2 hour episode tonight and you haven't even been watching ðŸ¤”ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn no worries, love the videos I got watching them with my family :) thanks for the reply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimePkmn do you happen to need an articuno full art from generations? I have a spare I can send]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadyJay1908 especially that maple shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis @YouTube your Display name is jokes! #HappyHalloween buddy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HulkHogan try dealing with a Toronto fall/winter creeps up on you fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassiraptor enjoy! Lots of subtle ties to the original make it a fun watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho have you had the chance to catch any Jays postseason games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme hope to see ya soon hope all is well as well as well as well as well as..you get the idea :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme @survivorcbs ma lady I watched, I'm gonna have to pick Michelle, she knows the numbers game #SurvivorMillennialsVsGenX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@people what have you done to contribute to society @KimKardashian ? Why would anyone care about your beliefs and opinions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme @survivorcbs watching delayed starting soon ðŸ™ƒ #ButFirst #TribalCouncil #premiereFinale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk Best of luck tonight boss! Side note Larry needs an account, he's hilarious. Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 Goldberg is gonna be there randomly this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 well that's the main one every year it runs Thursday to Sunday this weekend you should look it up and see what's good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 you should get your jabroni ass to fan expo on Saturday would be cool to say hi shoot the shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 I picked up the BvS extended cut it was long as shit but it was good tho I actually enjoyed that movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 @BenAffleck who is that dead shot? And from JL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ #AskJr #Fav7Movies one or two if you don't wanna think I know you like John Wayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fav7Films The Dark Knight, Rocky 2, Stand By Me, Jurassic Park, Wolf Of Wall Street, Scream, Planes Trains and AutoMobiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcourteisme lol fashun Sarah! Hope your summer is going good. We shall chill soon again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcCartney Kristy, would there be any chance if I could get a happy birthday card sent you were very helpful last night thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcCartney Hi Shelley, I'm using my sons account. I'm the peace girl that you gave water to in Hamilton I didn't hear if he said my name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassiraptor I wanted to wait for the Canada release and now we got it this afternoon yesss! #TeamBlue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 DT has some good places too on Spadina! Take care boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 my buddy's obsessed with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 I had some sexy pho when I was in New York it was really good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik perfect bubba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRock finally got to see #CentralIntelligence just now. You and @KevinHart4real killed it! The clappings had me laughing so hard ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadyJay1908 @thegamechasers what do you guys think of the bespin map pack if you guys have it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis lmao yea I did. I wanna play that No Mans Sky game if they ever release it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis tell them Niko, it's brown costume logic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogerrdunn @TheRealXPac @GoodMicWork @ShawnMichaels @TripleH I was running your theme and the original yesterday. Sorry for your loss guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealKurtAngle met you a couple times back in 03 stand up guy and one the best wrestlers ever. Hope to see you finish up in WWE eventually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet hello was wondering what time the NHL draft starts on June 24th? Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSNBobMcKenzie Hello Sir was wondering what time the draft starts Friday the 24th? Wanna make sure I'm off to watch it. Thanks, cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegamechasers dots all over like they aged but didn't cuz they time travelled? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@survivorcbs first time viewing party! #SurvivorKaohRong https://t.co/1fpv9PICam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst finally got together for a viewing party! #SurvivorKaohRong https://t.co/ya2y3rdtDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst are you live tweeting tonight for the East coast? #SurvivorKaohRong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk the shambling around saying Dallas I guess had me laughing hysterically out loud everyone thinks I'm crazy now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk same. Luckily we got to register 3 and one of mine is doing well but not the one with my friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk go Leafs go! #2018StanleyCupPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassiraptor @totalfilm ahh thank you for the link! Keep up the great work again I enjoy reading your tweets and post on Instagram. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassiraptor @totalfilm wait Keaton turned down a role for a solo spidey film?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho I'd like to see you win the World Title again but I dunno if that strap would fit around your fat ass #AssClown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biggest pet peeve is listening to ppl chew with their mouth open like who raised you to eat like a donkey I don't get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk I dunno man Sharks lookin good this year. Beards on point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ I find it very in genuine and sickening especially In regards to Stephanie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ I know you prob won't wanna say but don't you think it's wrong that WWE promotes Chyna only after she has passed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon @ChynaJoanLaurer your insecurities died last night with a woman who should have been recognized years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregCapullo and now Prince too! ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk that was neat reading your picks for the playoffs on https://t.co/2moqhvU6lU ..caught me off guard. Go Hawks! #StanleyCupPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegamechasers @YouTube thanks for bringing this to our attention I was randomly unsubbed from @PatTheNESpunk and didn't know why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho once your done pretending to be heel, you can acknowledge me for saying you stole the show yet again #GummyBears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho Rangers or Blackhawks Assclown? #StanleyCupPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho good luck Sunday #AssClown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 other than that it was good I can deal with the Lois stuff comes with the rom superman gimmick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 yea I agree about Lex he did a decent job but to me it was just Eisenberg playing himself. The Flash costume looked weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 movie was dope bro. Same feels here. I was marking out when they showed the team on the computer and the score was good too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregCapullo Harry and the Hendersons?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon @WWE loved that attire, nicest legs. 'Twas my 9th Mania as well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregCapullo I'm lovin it Greg, not too sure about early reviews for BvS tho.. Gonna have to watch for myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegamechasers hey Billy have you come across and or collect Jurassic Park toys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho you goin to see GnR at Coachella?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst few friends havent seen in forever are gettin together for future episode of #SurvivorKaohRong plz send @sarahcourteisme a buff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HockeyWebCast love your vids. Do you still post or know anyone that still posts the HNIC opening videos? Miss those ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk Austins bout to whoop your ass son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk good luck on your first official match. Long time fan. If Batman can take Supes you can take the UFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMPunk who you got facing Chi-Town in the finals this year? Also what do you think of the new/old Leafs logo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith I really enjoy your show Comic Book Men. My mother and I watch it together lol she likes all the Celeb guests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnMichaels at Daytona a couple days before your big match with Flair at Wrestlemania 24 ðŸ˜Š https://t.co/afNv2fkwTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho hey boss you going to coachella this year to take in the GnR reunion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadyJay1908 you and me alike bud. When I think x-files I think mr.burns causing chaos in the woods #Die-T lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWEBigE @WWE y'all are jokes. Finally some fresh material in the stale product. Keep up the good work sir fans got your back now]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>