<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy at the very beginning she sang a few lines from "This Land Is Your Land"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy I actually think that Lady Gaga's performance is more political than Beyonce's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy I know. And that makes me upset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did Lady Gaga nail the half time show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraveyDice singing "Born this way" too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy @etnow singing "Born this way" is huge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy @etnow she didn't need to speak about politics. she let her songs do the talking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta wants the Thrashers back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeCanuck @glovesaveluongo Atlanta is choking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xNikki_B I know but that is rediculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT.THE.FUCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMN @huffpostqueer she was probably told not to be political]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Lady Gaga do every half time show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["no matter gay, straight or bi. Lesbian or transgender life" YAAAAAAY. I love this woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could someone please link me videos of #SuperBowl #commercials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could see American #Superbowl commercials 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying great. I'll think about checking it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying I'm not going to support apps/dating sites that aren't inclusive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying how LGBT+ inclusive is Tinder? Are you allowed to say "transphobes go fuck yourselves"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying how affective is it? I mean is it worth the time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying I've never used Tinder and don't understand how it works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying seriously though, isn't it a good thing that person unmatched you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying you're awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celyying good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaJustice @themadisongrace @RebeccaMinkoff how did you do your hair Vic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when will the Canucks be mathematically eliminated from playoff contention?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I hope he'll decide to do a Vancouver meet up with fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo lmao I know it's Avan's b-day in 5 days :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo is it you?🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks who's cutting onions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo @AvanJogia I've always wondered-what do the rings on his hands represent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks holy shit dude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sanga8 @realDonaldTrump please educate yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sanga8 @realDonaldTrump you don't know how the Constitution works, do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I love being from the same city as him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo Avan and I are both from Vancouver. It's a great city :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I wonder if he's enjoying snowcouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so who's enjoying snowcouver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glovesaveluongo @CityofVancouver not any better in Surrey 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvrwx lots of snow falling in Whalley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit https://t.co/hNF6QZw04y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glovesaveluongo I hope it was loud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GirouxTheGOAT @BrettClaudio I miss him too. Brett tell him we miss him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrettClaudio is he okay? I haven't heard from him in what feels like forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I'm crazy about him no matter what he wears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeks_2016 jeans and a blouse will be fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeks_2016 how formal is the restaurant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lolrenaynay @ThatBShar damn I was hoping you were coming to Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Umm_kbye nah it was an accident. You could tell by her reaction. I don't know where to find the video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSedig trust me I've searched YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSedig I don't know where to find the video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I saw the behind the scenes video. Vic accidentally grabbed Avan's crotch and that is everyone's reactions 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo most people don't know why they are laughing. I do :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo Vic's facial expression gets me every time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo pls keep tweeting #vavan and #elavan pics. I will love you forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo #friendship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I miss seeing them hang out and posting videos. #friendship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo I really need my #vavan fix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsAvanUpTo have you heard anything more about Cool Girls/the outskirts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJHeerMusic oreos, mcnuggets and cha?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DAVIDsTEA will you consider bringing it back as a seasonal tea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SevenSixTwo_ @Ghostayami_ I agree with Cody :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrettClaudio sounds good to me 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are some healthy but delicious snacks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DAVIDsTEA I heard that Chocolate covered almond might be discontinued. please don't stop selling it! I love that tea :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @DAVIDsTEA needs a mobile app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrettClaudio the cutest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glovesaveluongo @TransLink what did they do this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSedig SEATH sentence??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikegmale @boldandworthy don't say this isn't an act of terrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy also Quebec has a history of Islamophobia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anybody know how the rest of the country can support the people affected by this terror attack?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[poor people in Quebec city 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy Donald Trump needs to accept his share of the blame for what's happened in Quebec city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy why do I have the feeling that Donald Trump's rhetoric is responsible for this act of terrorism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boldandworthy this makes me sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thoughts are with the people in Quebec city. The rest of the country will support you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avanheartlight can you tweet more #vavan moments too? #bffsforever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscolfer your facial expressions in this scene makes me burst out laughing every time https://t.co/lvh57ZNXOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avanheartlight @avvjogia I really miss their friendship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StealthLAX next time you decide the half time event is bubble soccer could I play? That looks like a lot of fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StealthLAX @Duchee10 WHAT A GREAT QUARTER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud to be Canadian https://t.co/H1DVXXxpDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_Blogger if only I could smuggle you across the border somehow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_Blogger I feel so bad for you and your family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_Blogger I love being Canadian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW 350 followers! three hundred and fifty of you are willing to put up with my shit. I feel loved! y'all are amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonofSoH Handsome as FUCK*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBrotatoe "nerd actor"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone help me estimate how much it will cost to go to Twitchcon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlinaJkrs @AvanJogia did he mean to zoom in on his crotch? 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glovesaveluongo @HEELCanuck what? where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sweetfacefergie psst I have a really important question to ask you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transitapp this is awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transitapp I'm in Metro Vancouver if that helps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transitapp I just installed the app on my phone. I'm just wondering if there's a feature that lets people see where a bus actually is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1stWarriorsage I found the option that says to transfer apps to SD card, but the app's aren't transferring :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1stWarriorsage it's a Moto e 6.0 second generation. Google is confusing me. I need someone to explain to me like I'm five]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also how the heck do you transfer apps from internal storage to SD card?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally bought a micro SD card for my phone. What are some decent apps to install?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>