<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpet solo truly sets the mood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moonlight In Vermont- The soundtrack..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok because chatime refuses to use milk subs I have resorted to making my own milk tea we are over chatime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart breaks every time I see this trending. Prayers. #QuebecCityMosqueShooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChatimeCanada Please start using milk subs! I love milk tea but I'm lactose intolerant ðŸ˜© We neeeed soy milk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible to find a non biased trump article on anything im just trying to get educated :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what the hell I miss #wastehistime2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna be this unbothered https://t.co/y2UYqfV3iQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where can i watch adult swim online 4 free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesssicahu only when i choose a lower earning field that allows me to earn 75% of my average male competitor! ðŸ™‚ its about job choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she think the trap is romantic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[perfect timingðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u r not worth time/effort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papiiirayy @Raphael_manzo01 oh shit what the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenasylvan I'm lacking so much sleep I saw the word xan in this tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what mood I'm in whenever I wanna listen to Kid Cudi but it's so relevant wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papiiirayy @Raphael_manzo01 The update looks great Raph just has a weird phone hahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really goes to show how much you cared lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenasylvan September is my birth month :-(my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Far Gone and Thank Me Later were so fucking consistent man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright on the other hand I'm going to try and teach myself french after this semester ends lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[advancement, it is perfectly okay to point out flaws or to renew a system that decides your moral code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who had been indoctrinated to do so. Almost every prejudiced bias or belief stems from raw, traditional religion itself. In a time of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But you know who's not contributing and and advocating for LGBT rights? Women's rights? Children's rights?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I will forever encourage what helps you, help others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We, in the first world, have the freedom to pick and choose which values we enforce in our daily lives. Some may utilize religion peacefully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[have disappeared from the religious narrative because a few have publicly ignored what the majority of your religion practices at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not understand the fear in pointing out the flaws of a religion. We act like extremism is a third world rarity and traditional ethics-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papiiirayy I'll throw one for spring break â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only like u when ur high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reinforce abortion &amp; lgbt rights ðŸ’#WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How hard is it to find some consensual-looking bondage because now I feel bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mdme Crawshaw changed my french life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She wants to erase me mmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there such thing as sad trap music because I love grey and first take lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to travel to places like New York but I am afraid I might want to stay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to bind all my poetry in a notebook but I think my handwriting is too ugly for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenasylvan tease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow you are so cute I wish you had a sense of humour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papiiirayy i didnt even realize until i looked at your photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressin about this tat so hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Differentiate feelings from intention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The myth of sustainable happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this isnt me https://t.co/Uo4nJBjC2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do i get these https://t.co/DLmKS5RPHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dont know if i want her or if i wanna look like her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Competing with your team feels so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 outcomes and neither are in my favour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember 4chan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever send me a playlist to listen to if it has White Iverson in it ever dont do it you suck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then we flourish... in all seriousness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow imagine being in love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My reply game is fast when I want it to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot fathom how one does not like Earl Sweatshirt or in the least appreciate his lyricism :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancelotignacio burnaby is home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss Burnaby tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to start using synonyms for "creative" and "vision" because I'm starting to sound like Ian Connor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My yellow fever is not a phase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xhazelv Ok but Colby refuses to be Romeo because he doesn't want to kiss my hand in English what the hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck I am actually so clingy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me &amp; my girl got matching bling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people even find my vsco my link is literally nowhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going 2 take my chances &amp; hope for the best https://t.co/slld0KgmAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you really open minded if you refuse to jerk to gay male porn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it okay not to want anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[days before the rodeo&gt; birds.. lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a little too nice for my taste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancelotignacio change your methods...happiness is a choice, its a mindset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rebooting my computer and it feels so new and clean. My new onenote setup is beautiful as well. Bless this new year momentum :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancelotignacio help yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENTERING THE NEW YEAR WITH PRIORITIZED HAPPINESS, STABLE RELATIONSHIPS AND HELLA SELF DISCIPLINE. IM FUCKIN EXCITED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenasylvan when im on drugs yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A daunting yet liberating thought: we create ourselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of these newfound revelations that seem self contradictory are crucial for my self growth and improvement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess the only definite character of mine is that I am a blank canvas,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallahi @peta @RickyMandac read the thread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordynaranja now we both recognize the two as counter-productive, an accomplishment indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what the fuck https://t.co/cPoInApSse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so tired I started quoting Ian Connor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sean leon put me in ixxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he who provokes thought and controversy, a creative sacrifice to the masses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmseileen what does he mean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmseileen literally who hates asians. my ass took a poll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe @JohnnyRainOD has a song called "Isis" and it's a fucking banger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get asked if i'm latina about 26 times a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenchy_ shot you a dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenchy_ @smokingdick johnny rain and sean leon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not appealing https://t.co/z2job1kEKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently so inspired to create I am so excited for 2017 and what is going to become of me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country music makes me mildly uncomfortable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordynaranja too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlvsmsn i thought you said crystal meth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lontayaomarc But I lost sleep just thinking of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Connor must have been so annoying in highschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bd_VIII Lowkey softie https://t.co/h47c50x2ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallahi @peta @bd_VIII read this thread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TooDopeWithHope @bd_VIII this kills me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bd_VIII @chulomang Me on the aux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I don't finish learning code by the end of winter break I am the laziest piece of shit ever and u all get $10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjFrancisco_ do you even go to church]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>