<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski "You have to take out their families" - Terrorist Don https://t.co/bwuUWoNl1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its plenty fucked anyway https://t.co/BFSLqLzxPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski I thought this wasnt worth the finger swiping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy @HiLauraaa try throwing against wall then buy non apple non trash no need to thank just wire the $$ to my acct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump started his campaign with a bogus paid crowd and became President with a much smaller crowd than Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont do that https://t.co/qJMgUJ56xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier look at me im markiplier I dont even politic bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im slowly building a conclusion on Piers Morgan https://t.co/R4rMSE7KRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob has zero concern for the underlying causes of poverty, just laments the tragedy of having to interact with mino… https://t.co/J5RMxHGH4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck https://t.co/sSadI1u8a5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to bite Meryl Streeps ass? https://t.co/kH5i4AMZ71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMank77 I will BE having a general NEWS CONFERENCE on January Eleventh IN N.Y.C. Thank YOU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski TURN OFF YOUR BLUETOOTH JESUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grooming... *shivers* https://t.co/KfeN1LFKw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alex Jones reporting live from inside his integrity https://t.co/8AWy34r6lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matchity Theres squirrel guys on craigslist but you should steer clear of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy would be a bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy thats bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy what does it mean for you to get dropped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hasanthehun at least he had the courage to @ everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too pathetic for words https://t.co/1PThfmYQuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fred_Delicious @pixieheaIy whats your toilet name?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier how does santa deliver gifts to houses that don't have chimneys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy no its bc of the acid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy my eyes hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Misread as a bake sale that involved steroids. https://t.co/pGgzYIPDpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good grief dude, focus on running the fucking United States yeah?? https://t.co/Pgk0VZl55C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski North Korea got a serious fake news problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump will be the least popular President in modern U.S history https://t.co/iduu9XLCj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punishing free speech with stripping of citizenship. Orange Hitler everybody. https://t.co/Em5l58zMWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a pundit that do you both https://t.co/98mn99DSra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude, you're the next President and you're always tweeting. Not a big enough platform for you? https://t.co/7F3D0wFaoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is this tweet https://t.co/tgPvLQ2Vn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SJW Trump needs a safe space. Mikey was triggered by some actors at a musical. SAD! https://t.co/rP585nB6ZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Key: Strip Destiny Church from TAX free status - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/DWtksYwjDu via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest outside the NZDIA conference, Police have assumed the "stalled conga line" formation. https://t.co/goJ45TqlBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjohnsonNYC was the election a vote for Putin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Hillary Clinton of an alternate Universe would have beaten Donald Trump" https://t.co/pi52hmVgVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski best thing to come out of 2016 https://t.co/JLjKhVGDvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have tremendous chemistry, you know, ask anybody about my chemistry, they'll tell you my chemistry is terrific.… https://t.co/zHGs5LOsj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still whining after winning an election. #LoserDonald https://t.co/Y8y2e3luNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im sure scones with Bashar Al-Asads wife is fucking lovely too but... https://t.co/28PpkxQwrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only she was more condescending, maybe then she would win over Trump voters. https://t.co/F7iTAvQWHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her talents include losing to the most unliked candidate in history. https://t.co/i2DLOvDyR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alot of young faces here https://t.co/qXRJmwRuIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck happened to Dave Rubin https://t.co/zQg6fvSy3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jvgraz @ElefanteEd now is not the time to be polite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im going to need this today https://t.co/pLSxOuZOx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hasanthehun I see you preppin for the deportation task force Mr Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pewdiepie fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats Alex. https://t.co/vaKUSqW93x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with the added bonus of not being this person https://t.co/TF1iitGFXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can provide this same service for free and will give a more accurate take https://t.co/m4NirG5wPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One grifter capitalising on the success of another grifter https://t.co/2XWlkPeO3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is into kinky shit https://t.co/SEbUeLGuLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems about right https://t.co/g41mpjWdZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jvgraz @GaloreVida Use the dick morris technique]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur I like how Cenk was vague but @WesClarkjr threw @BenMank77 right under that bus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait for the end https://t.co/LckjoFFwro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski @RealAlexJones oh shit alex watch out, your horse is a shapeshifting bilderberg reptilian illuminati. EXPOSED!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski @GovMikeHuckabee This will really push his book sales past the 23 mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DescribeYourselfIn3FictionalCharacters https://t.co/KsOXHSyt69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski @Slate health-conscious teens, all 17 of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy doctors hate her! See how she cured her self hate in 1 easy step!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Hillary cant get enough votes to beat a candidate like Trump then she doesnt deserve to win https://t.co/VbrsA4t8j3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski BRICK #1 IS LOW ENERGY AND A MESS. NO ORIGINALITY. SAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski BRICK #2 IS TREMENDOUS. BELIEVE ME. #2 WILL MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afrer dispensing with the obvious David Brock and MM in the tank for Hillary, this graph is interesting https://t.co/dEdoQpRFo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You share company with idiotic bigots, unhinged lunatics and trolls, what the fuck is there to be proud of? https://t.co/YXmORtpoN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The request for Police to reel in Police Brutality is "divisive"? https://t.co/8PUBLxQHF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hasanthehun @AP a humourous tweet on this thread from me is upcoming. Follow @TheAlphaRanga for updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicBergerIV @RobertJohnDavi @realDonaldTrump @BreitbartNews please hush that deplorable dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: I'm proud to be part of a white supremacist hate group. https://t.co/LtUEQffBBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski they're already there are'nt they? Special Forces are in Syria correct me if Im mistaken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenMank77 interesting part about post 9-11 switch much like Dan Rather https://t.co/mXtrVs51TR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski @AmirOtagh watch out @hasanthehun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we go further inside I think we will achieve inception]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is about an insider versus an insider who is denying their insider status https://t.co/o8tgc1Ji6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being born into privelege means we can relate to the struggles of young people and students. Vote Trump." https://t.co/BYFbXdYV4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Much like our own Father, daddy gave us everything in life. We earned 0 of it. Vote Trump" wtf? https://t.co/BYFbXdYV4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOOVER 2016: A chicken in every pot and a #TacoTrucksOnEveryCorner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Trump used the word crime as a verb #tytlive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The danger is that you'll have a good time https://t.co/fVqFUAAhgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur EXPOSED! BILDERBERG ILLUMINATI HAVE ASSUMED CONTROL OF UYGURS LIPS! WAKE UP SHEEPLE!      https://t.co/PNqOBobvHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may not be porn, but Id put money on Trump having whacked off to it. #tytlive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isnt real. This is a parody. Got to be #tytlive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that hes single, the Weiner has been unleashed. Everyone is in danger. Carlos Danger. #tytlive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The long wait is finally over https://t.co/ss2hmgfZCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALEX JONES NEEDS TO SIT ON CHAIR, A CRUTCH PERHAPS? ALSO SWEATING UNCONTROLLABLY. EXPOSED! #PickleGate https://t.co/tnrrH6o9t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXPOSED! Alex Jones is not fit to host a show! Supplement pills did not help either! Fraud! Sad! #PickleGate https://t.co/tnrrH6o9t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a zinger. https://t.co/sBNtv9HaZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But then this. https://t.co/ClZGfdJdIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, so this.... https://t.co/sePJAgtmg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur To compare TYT to Alex Jones is the 7th greatest false equivalency of our time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surgesoda @dtkennedy @cenkuygur If this is who you prefer to watch then Im glad you dont watch TYT  https://t.co/umZseLYm9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur Cenk is literally laughing while you trolls fire off your hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixieheaIy choo choo all aboard the hype train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelshure @BenMank77 I see they passed on 'forkstick' for obvious reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski Just like what Daddy Trump would do https://t.co/ryb2QEoV1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleKulinski DUDE LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT THE MAYAN CALANDER]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>