<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacobCoplenas @SenSanders hey retard, weather is not climate, if you don't understand that you opinion is worthless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kkcfly1 @DamonPettit @SenSanders Out of fear many think the S word would kill Sanders, if we stop fearing one word he can and will win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Criticizes Trump's Immigration Ban, Is 'Heartened' By Protests https://t.co/bONdL7cSam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump Reboots Pipeline Expansion, An Unexpected Delay Emerges https://t.co/6sk8UkcCuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's A Big One': Iowa Pipeline Leaks Nearly 140,000 Gallons Of Diesel https://t.co/zBhwx5YbJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@66Mariann human caused climate change is real and driving change faster than what is normal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeLewisATX @cenkuygur Fuck, really!? I hate all that Alex Jones stands for and sheeple ignorant enough to believe him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mutt1960 @SSsheaden @Fusion there was a period at the end so the sentence was finished. Stop using alternative facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnalSystemist @LeoDiCaprio your wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Str8Killa99 @LeoDiCaprio @guardian people who live on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddavenport213 fool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaKasparian I agree, talking to an imagery cloud man is childish, it is taking to long for people to realize it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirPatStew I agree with you. Most people do. Don't feed the trolls Ignore them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Trump's First Press Conference As President-Elect, Annotated https://t.co/zp5DPWQpn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeofyourLyme @mattMLGx that shut his ass up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson I am sad to hear about your father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Announces Sanctions Against Russia In Response To Cyberattacks https://t.co/LcdOkMSIp3
On a scale from productive to war what is this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greg has given you a FREE Uber ride (up to $20). To claim your free gift, sign up using this link: https://t.co/WsTdqGkqM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Ashley I warned you about that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Krissy_Caster @USATODAY @SenSanders @BernieSanders 99 percent of the scientific community agrees that human caused climate change is fact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cams__thoughts @AnaKasparian Cameron sounds like another briegtbart troll zombie flying monkey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of my brothers and sisters 

2,000 veterans to give protesters a break at Standing Rock https://t.co/Lw0qwb0KXZ via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh he is guilty, but nothing will happen 

Former South Carolina Police Officer Takes The Stand At His Murder Trial https://t.co/o2L8x99bfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nooooooooo! 
You will be missed. 

Ron Glass, Emmy-Nominated Actor Best Known For 'Barney Miller,' Has Died At 71 https://t.co/Ugx7idpwhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes sense, 

People Knowingly Donated $100,000 To Dig A Big, Pointless Hole In The Ground  https://t.co/7BBPYfeGts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_petrie @PrisonPlanet they thought the civil war would be over quickly too, that turned out terribly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thewolfhoof @pattonoswalt I was just kidding works for PROFESSIONAL COMEDIANS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geniodalampida @SamHarrisOrg If the thing keeping you from immoral acts is fear of a god, than you are not moral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg  yes it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregroa @davidsirota agreed, we need voting to be made even more easy for more people, that would help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, this is fucking terrifying. 

Students Have 'Dismaying' Inability To Tell Fake News From Real, Study Finds https://t.co/y0bfS2P9fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabeAppleton @myearthfriend @BuxySays @BI_Science I hope this is true but who knows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTylt yes as needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is a thing now. https://t.co/dKWVU5z1CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is Pence's views, not that the  people voice their disapproval of your vice president… https://t.co/ewEf5PcV8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficerPhepe @BBCWorld being gay is not a disorder of any kind Phepe. There is gay gene.  Proven fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buckle up, it will only get worse! 

Racially Charged Remarks Derailed Trump's Attorney General Nominee 30 Years Ago https://t.co/glTRAX7Qjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Parents Have Unanswered Questions About School Vaccination Rates  https://t.co/eA6Y3PBFlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickJunkins @exxonmobil cow's gas is a huge problem releasing massive amounts of green house gasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samphireisland @UltimateTennis_  man is making it worse and the changes are happening faster than nature alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @realDonaldTrump Release the Kraken!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickJunkins @exxonmobil oil and gas are the passed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfranken fighting is nice but we need you to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelshure can someone spoon feed this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbgirl19 thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Is What Donald Trump Wants To Do In His First 100 Days https://t.co/EKl2XepKVY
It gets worse around number 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbgirl19 @BBC @YouTube keep calm and carry on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuakarla what ever you say chump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuakarla @StephenAtH @derekahunter whatever you say chump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuakarla @StephenAtH @derekahunter it is funny you are just butt hurt that Donald is a racist bigot who feels entitled to assault women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BDorr @StephenAtHome the joke is funny. you calling it flat does not make it so. Donald is a #whinylittlebitch and so are you BDorr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrioticpepe @realDonaldTrump Donald is a #whinylittlebitch who will not win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamQueenAri @realDonaldTrump oh honey give up Donald is done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump like if Donald sounds like a #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALavagnino @johniadarola what genocide is denied and who by name is denying it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJTknowsbest @CNN @john_walsh @realDonaldTrump Trump is not fighting anything. Outside of what is trending, he has no plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliensinsocks @DONJONvote2016 by who and when?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lehimesa @TheYoungTurks @YouTube @DWStweets what a load of BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@candace_ave @Roger5y @realDonaldTrump #loserdonald is hiding something... Get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJTknowsbest @CNN @john_walsh yeah I mean look at George Bush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump shut up #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilTurner_ @BarackObama don't waste time watching. Just video clips cut up and repeated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Oil Is Seeping From A North Dakota Hillside” by @ADavilaFragoso https://t.co/dUrHCk0zgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdCJohnson @TheYoungTurks @shailenewoodley enlighten me. What is the technical difference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanTbernard @realDonaldTrump @vine #whinylittlebitch #loserdonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrioticpepe @realDonaldTrump unless they where captured. #loserdonald #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump would be, but your not. #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffreyForrest8 @nathanTbernard @realDonaldTrump @vine and he won't because his is a scared #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump 
#loserdonald, are they letting you tweet now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump @johniadarola yes! And how about those tax returns? #loserdonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Istillwantapony @CDCgov that is up to the mother and her doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenland Shark Is At Least 272 Years Old https://t.co/BShy1qZJAz
Fascinating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cenkuygur, I would propose a law that compels police to immediately perform first aid to anyone they shoot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan's Emperor Akihito hints at wish to abdicate!? I confess, I did not know they still had an Emperor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution4077 @BuxySays what about two women?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuxySays i don't get my morals from am iron age book, written by men who though the earth went around the sun and sickness was demons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revolution4077 @BuxySays do you know? How do you know there is a hell let alone who is in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuxySays @Revolution4077 Christianity has more blood on its hands historically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump fear mongering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastB0yScout @cenkuygur @RealAlexJones Wtf are you talking about? Look at the numbers TYT destroys that conspiracy loveing nut case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_HunterSanders @OrmondDerrick @CNN amen brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dragoon215 @cenkuygur #LoserDonald #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWright1968, we have more incarcerated citizens than China, some people are guilty, and still victims of draconian sentences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinpetac and Trump will not fuck up plus not fuck up cleaning the fuck ups, breading super fuck ups! #whinylittlebitch #LoserDonald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtinfo @WhiteHouse @POTUS appropriate considering we have more incarcerated citizens than China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
#whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
#CROOKEDDON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MakeAmericaGreatAgain:

Step 1: Read the constitution

Step 2: Release your tax returns

Step 3: Drop out of the race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeedySpriggs  if someone invaded your space and was an over the top ass hole, let us see how well you would react #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankPikula @TheYoungTurks but look at how those 5 failed and how partners and employees where screwed. #loserdonald #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MakeAmericaGreatAgain:

Step 1: Read the constitution

Step 2: Release your tax returns

Step 3: Drop out of the race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ha ha ha. Me laughing at you #loserdonald #whinylittlebitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newskye @TheYoungTurks I hear you. What about #whinylittlebitch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheYoungTurks #whinylittlebitch #loserdonald wants to run this country like his failed businesses Zeus help us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Parker9_  @Tuan Steel @realDonaldTrump #losertrump #whinylittlebitch 
 Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #losertrump #whinylittlebitch 
 Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #losertrump #whinylittlebitch 
 Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #losertrump #whinylittlebitch 
 Who cares ?
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS
TAX RETURNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump yeah SHE is the liar. You and your supporters are so profoundly stupid]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>