<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s an immigrant nation and we thought immigrants are welcome here.” https://t.co/h2UjvkJDSo #MuslimBan #Immigration #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellyannePolls This was actually a FBI sting operation which put weapons in the hands of suspects. https://t.co/BsFbXrXRk9 #BowlingGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please check your facts. This was actually another example of a manufactured terrorism case by the FBI.… https://t.co/tD1jFK7Q5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KellyannePolls. Check your facts. This case was another in a long line of manufactured terrorism cases by the FBI. https://t.co/BsFbXrXRk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don’t think there’s one person on our team that thinks a ban... is right.” Guess he didn't speak w/ @GeoffCameron https://t.co/aWDhoAIvaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump can "banish U.S. lawful permanent residents, then he can do anything." https://t.co/rgoTwQtIP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yemen raid approved "...without sufficient intelligence, ground support or adequate backup preparations."
https://t.co/UhRERt3pV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. They're not illegal. 2. Australia is a friend. 3. Where's Melania? https://t.co/GmZlnRpfPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @MerriamWebster I would think that "feckless" will soon be in contention as the #WordOfTheDay, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Running for office as an outsider is one thing. inviting Wall Street into that office once you arrive is another." https://t.co/ZbRuhcIWUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI... "These tweets by Fox News dishonour the memory of the 6 victims &amp; their families..." - Canadian PM Trudeau  https://t.co/1tjeNW87kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmadmzaghal Maybe you should launch an investigation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmadmzaghal Doesn't that depend upon the office?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This op-ed is by the man who some call a "conservative apologist." https://t.co/7rF940VKwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My remix for @citiesandmemory This is for all the immigrants looking for a place to call home. https://t.co/8GvLLQrucc • #RefugeesWelcome •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...the level of secrecy and exclusion involved here was obviously vastly excessive and dangerous." https://t.co/7bl4qBvyBv #ImmigrationBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Sessions during Yates Confirmation: "You have to watch out because people be asking you to do things you just… https://t.co/FRazXLvTIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...the final straw for people who were already knowingly ignoring a lot of the abuses" of @Uber - https://t.co/q4cBtd2kUD • #RideShare •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I didn’t fight to bring the rule of law to other countries to see it ignored here.” https://t.co/eONkfQgFUe #TrumpProtest #ImmigrationBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's policies were "brushed off as 'campaign rhetoric' but he is following through." https://t.co/3tmASPiq5Y • #Economy • #Dollar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump LOL. A friend just said. "There he goes again. What a crazy old cracker"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More pictures from protest today at the White House. • #RefugeesWelcome • #WashingtonDC • https://t.co/pW7nP7WIkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["New DC Sunday Routine: Shower. Brunch. Protest." • #RefugeesWelcome • #WashingtonDC • https://t.co/6SQj0OaImk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pictures from the protest today at the White House. • #RefugeesWelcome • #WashingtonDC • https://t.co/NgA2q98Mlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Power does not corrupt. Fear corrupts... perhaps the fear of a loss of power." - John Steinbeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entertaining the protestors w/ the National Anthem. #RefugeesWelcome https://t.co/vgTJg7VYYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No Hate. No Fear. Refugees are Welcome Here." #RefugeesWelcome #WhiteHouse #WashingtonDC https://t.co/0fGec23RKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend just said, "I'm scared that @realDonaldTrump &amp; Co. will make Richard Nixon &amp; J. Edgar Hoover look like amateurs." #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more you can increase fear of drugs &amp; crime, welfare mothers, immigrants &amp; aliens, the more you control all the people." - Noam Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Courage is knowing what not to fear." - Plato • #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've deleted @Uber from my cellphone. Meanwhile, @Lyft is donating $1,000,000 over the next 4 years to the @ACLU to defend our constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindingMusic Actually, @Uber was trying to profit from the NYC taxi strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGDCphotos I can give you the details if you follow &amp; DM me. I don't want to publicly share that disinformation again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGDCphotos The tweet linked to a story from 2013. Nowhere in the story was there a mention that the case was another FBI sting operation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dan_hoyt ABC News finally deleted that tweet but only after it got over 100 retweets. Bad journalism pisses me off. I'm still pissed-off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC ....on the day that thousands of people are protesting around the country the Executive Orders of @realDonaldTrump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC That tweet got about 120 retweets. Why would your employees spread disinformation especially...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ABC Thank you for deleting the tweet from your account. Did your overnight staff go rogue? It certainly was irresponsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC But if you prefer to keep the tweet... that's fine. Thanks for Keeping Fear Alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC I am asking you to delete that tweet and do some responsible journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC I thought you were a respected news organization but you seem to have hired people who exacerbate the problem we have with Fake News.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC So, would you please suggest to your employees that they delete that tweet or shall I go on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC ...involving people suspected of supporting the Islamic State, a sharp rise in the span of just two years."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC "Undercover operations, once seen as a last resort, are now used in about 2 of every 3 prosecutions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC Do your employees know that the FBI manufactures terrorism cases?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC Do you employees know that the individuals involved were caught in an FBI sting operation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ABC Have you vetted your overnight crew? Are some of your workers happily spreading fear? I captured this tweet for further investigation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why tweet a story from 2013? This is unprofessional. Do you have an update? Or are some of your employees trying to… https://t.co/7Ba21rOLZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miracalix I believe he's only modified his libertarian views due to the moral outrage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a number of friends who have deleted @uber from their smartphones since the CEO said he's happy to work w/ @realDonaldTrump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Google has told the BBC it is concerned about the order &amp; any measures which could block great talent from the US." https://t.co/iUu4BBe7k4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The anti-abortion bill is "...among the most restrictive abortion legislation in the United States." https://t.co/sX3ZgE5SPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["London-based film-maker John Akomfrah won the Artes Mundi award for his "substantial body of outstanding work." https://t.co/lSBKqqh198]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dan_hoyt Hope for the best, prepare for the worst, as they say. Personally, I think the pendulum will swing back but only if we survive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let us be clear: This is not a peaceful transition of power. It’s a corporate takeover." https://t.co/oTASJUxqyq • #Trump • #WhiteHouse •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Meanwhile, a media blackout has been introduced at the US's Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)" https://t.co/JGtT5YIeao #ClimateChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time might be ripe for whistleblowers "who for reasons of policy or pique might be ready to leak to the press." https://t.co/2zvLPoKWV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI... Staff of @realDonaldTrump have to “control information that may infuriate him.” https://t.co/sJcrvuIoHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to sign order to limit the flow of refugees from Iraq, Iran, Libya, Somalia, Sudan, Syria &amp; Yemen into the US. https://t.co/HXVQB0Eyjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmadmzaghal Yes, I did my usual Irish Goodbye. I was wiped out. We should catch up so you can tell me all about your obsession w/ pickles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmadmzaghal Just thought I would echo a previous convo, Enjoy your piquant ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Think on your feet. Communicate with your neighbors. Dream of the future; stay alive." - @K_ALICEGREER https://t.co/UVq80kuSza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gag rule has been shown to increase abortion rates esp. unsafe abortion rates in places that depend on NGOs. https://t.co/qnJEHypoKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I’ve never been in more despair about who we are and where we’re going.” https://t.co/8SPpKdP01H • #Novelist • #Literature • #USPolitics •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I rode a bus all night' https://t.co/MvHoiKn9gG via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sec. John Kerry walked through the crowd with his dog &amp; people started cheering &amp; then chanting, "John Kerry. John… https://t.co/6nghW6PEsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@womensmarch • #WomensMarchOnWashington • #WomensMarch • #Inauguration • #TrumpPresident • #Trump • https://t.co/59RyP5witW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennifer Todd, her daughter and her partner, John Philbeck at the #WomensMarchOnWashington • @womensmarch • https://t.co/OqRjXU7H8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colleen Siochain w/ coexist flag,"The #WomensMarch is restoring my faith in humanity. We still have a lot of work t… https://t.co/n63iwE295x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larisa Thomason from New Market, Alabama. "I rode a bus all night. I'm excited but really exhausted." @womensmarch… https://t.co/RB3V5aPM2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was great to see @marcribotmusic last night at the @BlackCatDC for the No Thanks benefitfor @CasaRubyDC. Now? It… https://t.co/VK8jWHHWqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It was a moment rich in irony." https://t.co/VER3d6uaA1 • #Inauguration • #TrumpInauguration • #Trump • #TrumpPresident •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This "MAGA" float rolled through my friend's neighborhood in Washington DC. She took a photo and then heard someone… https://t.co/aB0Pm8kTo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my local bookstore here in Washington DC is trying to communicate something.. #Inauguration… https://t.co/NouYCXxeXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have to cut a montage for @BBCNewsUS of Donald J. Trump's #Inauguration as #POTUS45. What would be the best music to use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MerriamWebster I would've bet on the word apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmadmzaghal Sweet or sour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK. Okay. We'll get through this. We will. I'm sure we will. But ya got to get busy because I'm not going to wake you up when it's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Trump going to take credit for this too? https://t.co/i1o6JET3Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man, I think the people down the hall can hear me laughing. Thanks. Of course, the sad reality is that he's stil… https://t.co/eSCHLdt0SV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at this @WSJ cover &amp; I can't help but wonder... how much have I aged over the last 8 years? And how much wil… https://t.co/oBWSBN2cIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DDDrewDaniel True but I just wish that those millions voted in the last election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I forgot... if life made any sense then there wouldn't be any need to be creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitlinKellyNYC I understand but I'm sure you fight the good fight in whatever way you can. We all should. We all will. I'm sure of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...it will become evident that, for everyone, life is a preexisting condition waiting to happen." https://t.co/dDeJZkXCf8 • #HealthCare •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitlinKellyNYC Thanks for making me laugh. But truthfully, I don't want to be marching the next day with a massive hangover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@theQuietus "Low" is still my favorite Bowie album and I could go so far as to say that it actually changed my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the right beer to drink the day of Trump's inauguration? https://t.co/PTlLNJFSny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gbullard Your mom looks much happier than Grant Wood's sister in American Gothic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...still plenty of dorky-as-all-get-out wedding band dudes performing" in Washington DC for Trump's Balls. https://t.co/TuuVSPOLf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump doesn’t have a philosophy. He has an algorithm. He sees no heroes, mentors, or bonds of moral aff… https://t.co/wcXsuJQBJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There was nothing especially Christian about his efforts, Mr. Harris admits..." https://t.co/bP8m8Jaurm • #FakeNewsMedia • #FakeNews •]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mohamed Aboutrika "one of the most successful African footballers of his generation", is now on Egypt's terror list. https://t.co/PYDqo9bIzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[William Onyeabor - March 29 1946 – January 16 2017 • RIP https://t.co/fXqsl27BRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...nothing would piss The Donald off more than having to throw away a bunch of Trump merchandise." https://t.co/tTCTzqXI8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, that's true but polls can't predict voter suppression efforts. https://t.co/H1OKq0eUcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Director "went ahead and made some weird AF lemonade." https://t.co/EPLQU7VRwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There is a link between America’s flawed interventionist policy, especially the Iraq war, &amp; the refugee crisis,..." https://t.co/MoC2SHAy69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TheMagFields It looks like Stephin &amp; @AskDrRuth have something in common. https://t.co/fJfuA0mYRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fan Fiction: 3 Doors Down do the most amazing anti-Trump tirade @ the Inauguration &amp; become instant heroes. Also, who is 3 Doors Down?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>