<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CVFry @mark_bonnar What a tremendous series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Prommer1 My trouble with Adriana is that it comes down about two hours too late!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richmond Theatre; Round The Horne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning Had to have the grass cut in Christmas week last year, it was growing so rapidly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirTuftonBufton Yes! Frightening isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @WestMonster_UK Making lists of opponents for their supporters to attack is a typical Nazi tactic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking back control. https://t.co/Pi2EXkCtzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamths1973 @KellyannePolls I suppose when you spend your time lying and distorting facts fantasy and reality become indistinguishable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaroldItz @ManyaZuba And it would be more terrible still if it had happened!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgecovengard @jsdhenderson @DavidCloke There was also an incredibly crass line immediately after. 'Nobody should have to do that'????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgecovengard @jsdhenderson @DavidCloke I mean she had just very conspicuously shot herself and spent a fair time in death convulsions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgecovengard @jsdhenderson @DavidCloke One would have thought so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @DavidCloke Think the delivery of it was partially to blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @DavidCloke Me bringing down the tone of the audience I expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @DavidCloke Particulary in the last scene inviting audience laughter just when least wanted. She's dead!!!! Provoked giggles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @DavidCloke Thanks. Found it very powerful at times, though not entirely convinced by the updating and some classic bad lines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @DavidCloke What did you think of the NT Hedda Gabler?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EveWinters @BonaTweetette @RichmondTheatre Booked tickets ages ago. Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKIPNFKN @Independent Yet another triumph for the Wrexiteers and their plan to totally ruin the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grey_Wolfcub @acgrayling @TomLondon6 @OliverKamm AngieMeader @dontbrexitfixit As Ken Clarke said,membership has turned around the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grey_Wolfcub @acgrayling @AmnestyUK @AngieMeader @BritsfortheEU @TomLondon6 Perhaps you can ask Jeremy Corbyn,he enjoys going on marches;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jake_Kanter @nickreeves9876 @AdamBienkov How very sensible of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PGilluley @RuthElleson @SydneySoprano @E_N_O Are you not giving your Sparafucile tonight then Paul? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Now if you don't behave yourself today, you'll be sent to bed early without your tea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyttleton Theatre - Hedda Gabler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a bit early to start out on my trip to Vauxhall on 24th August, but thanks. https://t.co/J4xDS2iI4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FulhamFanTalk Less than confident. Now if we could play with any consistency.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManyaZuba @dailykos Could they come to a similar arrangement with all the other channels as well please. Mind you CNN and MSNBC are dire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulnuttallukip As you have now broken the law, I'm sure you do the decent thing and resign as party leader and electoral candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverKamm @mvonschantz What a sad decline for a once great party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDunt @Independent Taken unexpectedly drunk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bangorballetboy BTW what terrific music in Death Takes A Holiday! That trio for the three girls in the second act was especially fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuidoFawkes @jsdhenderson @shamichakrabar1 @EmilyThornberry Just the sort of hypocrisy you expect from this apology for an MP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's awful when you have politicians like Corbyn who flip-flop https://t.co/8aJA7NPEkc never know where they stand from one day to the next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UKIP News. Nuttall found falsifying information on his electoral forms. Farage accused of misappropriating EU funds. Let's take back control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So interesting to read that most trade agreements worldwide involve freedom of movement between the contracting parties.Taking back control?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@schnuckster Ashamed to admit I have started it four or five times, but not had the intellectual rigour to reach the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimAshAsh And we all remember her sending her children to private school while condemning non-state education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimAshAsh She is a hypocrite and waste of space. Sadly symptomatic of a failing Party with a disfunctional leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With slight reservations about the book &amp; some clunky dialogue, really enjoyed Death Takes A Holiday. Some lovely music,very well performed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whousedallnames @cheekylatte @LBC @Nigel_Farage Pretty unlikely that we BOTH did I think.Anyway we both voted according to what we believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whousedallnames @cheekylatte @LBC @Nigel_Farage  It rather depends on your idea of success. We shall see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheekylatte @whousedallnames @LBC @Nigel_Farage Ah the one where the economy tanks and poorer people loose their jobs. No thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whousedallnames @LBC @Nigel_Farage He can't do much harm in that job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whousedallnames @LBC @Nigel_Farage If you like him so much in the States why don't you have him over there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LBC @Nigel_Farage And if anyone is an expert on rank hypocrisy it's our Nigel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Strewthieruthie @jsdhenderson @JohnVecchio @DavidCloke Yes I believe tickets are £35 at the booth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @JohnVecchio @DavidCloke Yes it seems to be on most of the ticket agent's lists. @bangorballetboy thoroughly enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charing Cross Theatre: Death Takes A Holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsdhenderson @JohnVecchio @DavidCloke Thanks Jamie Sounds good. I'll have a look when I get back from Death Takes A Holiday later tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnVecchio @DavidCloke Thanks I'll have a look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCloke @JohnVecchio I've been put off the plays by the ridiculously high ticket prices. Much greater than at Stratford or Barbican.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are any  whinging Wrexiteers who don't understand this, try reading it again and again. https://t.co/cfExCQFVbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andree_frieze @nickreeves9876 @JamesBerryMP @tania_mathias Sadly that fool Cameron told voters that it was binding. What a mess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gavinplumley @AbbottandHolder Not even sure that's so! Kleiber certainly conducted both ROH productions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gavinplumley @AbbottandHolder Yes you're right. Don't know what made me think it might have been Neher!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gavinplumley @AbbottandHolder The answer is that he didn't!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gavinplumley @AbbottandHolder Didn't he also design the old Covent Garden Elektra that was stil in use in the seventies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could you not love her???? Lucia Popp: Die Zauberflöte:Ach, ich fühl's https://t.co/IT9uofRrSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gtltornt @Spotify I must total up the roles I heard her sing. Not dissimilar to your list I would imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gtltornt @Spotify It was a most memorable night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gtltornt @Spotify I was even at the Coli on the night she stood in as Ilia with ENO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gtltornt @Spotify She was adorable and like you I was enormously lucky to see her so often both in the UK and abroad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @gtltornt @Spotify Probably the only singer that I could truly say I loved! Such warmth and personality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickFerrariLBC Typical Sun accuracy. Callaghan never said 'Crisis? What Crisis?'. The quote is incorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mezzocheryl Just didn't get on with it at all for some reason. Never mind. Glad you enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mezzocheryl While Buckley was good, I thought the film was so dreadful I fled from the cinema with 30 minutes left. Each to their own!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarodSm @TheRoyalOpera Certainly better than the performance I saw in December with the other cast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbffc A combination of incompetence and lack of ambition at board level. Sickening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It says something about politics in the U.K. that Corbyn became a party leader, but none of Ken Clarke, Dennis Healey or Tony Crossland did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FulhamFC @frankieptaylor Kahn's ambition encapsulated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hariclea Very impressive and musical. Heard him sing a lot of Rossini over twenty odd years without enjoying it much. This was excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning You're a sort of operatic Eric and Ernie then?;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning Rather dreading it in advance. Maybe I'll be pleasantly surprised. Hmm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoying Gregory Kunde's Manrico. An excellent piece of work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning Hear you're adding a bit of gravitas to Putney on Monday night. Sadly I can't be there as I'm at the NT for Amadeus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCQCMP Highly appropriate having listened to some of your colleagues today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andydillon70 @WhiteNoise1879 That'll fit well on the back of the shirt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything Goes female chorus.Where are the men, is this a nunnery?Where are the men?We want some funnery. Great Porter!Gilbert would be proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gts11 Love Curzon. Such a large area behind stalls I could fit my entire office into it three times over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to McGlinn Anything Goes while on the bus. Wonderful Hans Spialek orchestrations so redolent of the thirties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curzon King's Road, Chelsea for #ROHtrovatore HD relay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably my all-time favourite football clip.  Dimitar Berbatov - Fulham v Aston Villa. Quite incredible control. https://t.co/TnagXY2zxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OperaCabbie I always enjoyed Franz Schubert and Don Estelle's recording of Whispering Grass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1966MJG @FulhamFC If you put Smithy's attitude together with Berbatov's skill you'd have the greatest player in the history of the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NTSonline @dukeofyorksLDN Thanks I was just going to post the same thing.  I misread the original email. Can't wait to see it again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiteNoise1879 Hope they can understand what Slav's talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1troggy_FFC @WhiteNoise1879 Loved Heitinga. Great competitor and tough attitude. Shame we didn't try to keep him on relegation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlameDraymond We certainly saw them coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iromg Porky's a bit of a 'penicular structure' himself if you ask me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1966MJG Such a good player and only a manager as maladroit as Magath could have played him out of position then marginalised him as he did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larkingrumple @RoyalAcadMusic @YouTube That's two Offenbach pieces I'll have missed in a couple of months. Most unlike me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adrie_vdLuijt It was everything singing should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adrie_vdLuijt Quite something isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamths1973 We're very good on the ball, not so much at making possession count. Regularly have between 60&amp;70% possession in games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamths1973 I'm just going to watch it on the FFC website so will see what I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamths1973 Oh really? Thanks! Just been on a long phone call so missed the draw. That should see the end of our cup run, but a good house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_McCreesh @MarkValencia @hugh_canning @TimAshAsh @YouTube Have heard her sing it, but can't recall where or when. Old age!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_McCreesh @MarkValencia @hugh_canning @TimAshAsh @YouTube You're building up interest in it;-) Must have a listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hugh_canning @MarkValencia @simonspenceQC @JOHNMARKAINSLEY There is so much I'd love to be able to enjoy her singing on record. Piau is A1.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>