<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelWilsonCo me too. I first thought it was a transformer exploding until I heard the thunder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCholly @HaneyInkslinger @bobmackin just one lightning strike in Vancouver followed by a boom of thunder and more heavy snow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50ShadesofVan @ensembleator and moments before, intense graupel/snow pellets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50ShadesofVan @ensembleator I was outside with the dog. Big flash and immediate boom. Strike couldn't have been that far away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile here's some reading on it: https://t.co/NXeICEBqDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lailayuile rare phenomenon (not so rare on south coast!) as cold and warm air duke it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THUNDERSNOW #yvr #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moderate snowfall resuming in central Vancouver. #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130Weather I believe we broke the snowfall record at YVR for yesterday's date, did we not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50ShadesofVan @weathernetwork Daschunds aren't great in the snow 😉 but Jagger found some interest in this tree tha… https://t.co/sMPMeojRk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's official. The snow is now too deep for my dog to go to the bathroom. #daschundproblems #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50ShadesofVan where does this one rank on your snowmometer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a couple hours' lull, moderate snow now falling again outside @NEWS1130 studios at Broadway and Ash in #Vancouver. @NEWS1130weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why on Earth is @MayorGregor having a snowfall update news conference at a restaurant in Chinatown at 11:30? Are we interrupting lunch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22nd and Oak. @NEWS1130Weather https://t.co/vdNb89FPFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ensembleator seeing some very light flurries now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ensembleator seems like EC standing down on Sunday storm now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christy Clark gov't to spend $35-mil on BC Parks, a few years after budget left so bleak campers were asked to bring their own toilet paper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BCFerries has a heads-up for passengers travelling between Comox and Powell River, and Earls Bay - Saltery Cove -… https://t.co/OxTkIpyTyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanMacDonaldAPD @WoodfordCHNL I get daily emails letting me know I can get highway cable from China at a really cheap price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green pleaded guilty to second degree murder of Surrey realtor Colin Hill in 2015. @NEWS1130 https://t.co/gs3uTSsJwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillFDrews you'll always be verified to me, Jill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's one thing we can agree on in these divided times, it's that the flu sucks. If you need me I'll be in bed for the next 36 hours. 🤧]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh... we have a rubber ducky recall from @HealthCanada -- @NEWS1130
https://t.co/32aNvyGTjn https://t.co/U1Mtege1Em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of George Orwell's "1984" have soared into @amazon's top five, according to the company. @NEWS1130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AirCanada flight from Toronto to Cozumel is making unscheduled stop in Orlando. @680NEWS @NEWS1130 https://t.co/I2AxtqClHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS Trump wants to keep manufacturing in the US, keep US jobs -- his "Make America Great Again" campaign hats were produced in China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BCUtilitiesCom decision means you'll continue to pay two-tier residential rates for @BCHydro; low income folks will not get a special rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver @ParkBoard to reopen Fraserview, Langara and McCleery golf courses Monday, Jan 23rd. They were closed due to snow and ice hazards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's only been president for a couple of hours, and already the US Climate Action website is gone: https://t.co/HbaGymaSnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First chance we'll have to ask @Christyclarkbc about Wild West New York Times article. Event supposed to be re: Tim… https://t.co/OLkUoST1Ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: when the Alex Fraser Bridge opened in 1986 it was four lanes. By the early 90s it was expanded to six. In 2018: 7 w/counterflow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No arrests made in shots fired at Knight and E 54th Ave. @VancouverPD believes it was targeted and no risk to the public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update from @VancouverPD on shots fired at Knight and E54th Ave: "No one was injured, and the occupants of the home are not cooperating."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 this includes dealing with traffic congestion, highway improvements, port access, and cycling connections, according to @TranBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Minister @toddstonebc appoints MLA @scott4delta to "develop vision for transportation priorities south of the Fraser" 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This should have been @yvrairport -- apologies! I've made this mistake before... https://t.co/le5DaUm78s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPENING NOW: @YVR announces Terminal expansion plans including extending US terminal areas, larger Int'l area, expanded parkade @NEWS1130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotcrew2004 @NEWS1130 Todd Stone told us last year they were also looking to improve Nordel/Hwy17. Wonder if they're redoing whole area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotcrew2004 @NEWS1130 You might be thinking Hwy 91 and 72nd Interchange. Not sure what this one might be. New Nordel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed &amp; BC transportation ministers call news conference tomorrow morning at Alex Fraser Bridge/Nordel Interchange - @NEWS1130 will be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Rainfall warning dropped for Metro Vancouver. Continue to expect showers. @NEWS1130weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will @CityofVancouver (in part) consult you on the future of the Arbutus Greenway corridor? "A pop-up hot chocolate kiosk on February 1"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News you can use... report starting w/ "It's called Trump Singles Dot Com, make dating great again" -- all you need to hear @astoneabcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniferB_ctv and 90% of it will end up in your trash folder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans, let me know how your @U2 ticket buying experience in #Vancouver goes today. #yvr -- on sale at 10AM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver's Trout Lake closed to skaters as of noon today, says @ParkBoard -- preparing for warmer temperatures and rain. @NEWS1130weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CanBorder (Border Guards) say they seized 17 bricks of cocaine during search of woman's car at Pacific Hwy crossi… https://t.co/lRayETnByK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arctic Outflow Warning ENDED for Chilliwack and Eastern Fraser Valley, according to @ECCCWeatherBC #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 contracts are up for bidding on preliminary widening work. One to be awarded on Richmond side, another to be awarded for Delta side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like @TranBC still expects preliminary pre-load work for Highway 99 expansion &amp; new Massey Bridge to begin late/summer fall 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Government says it spent $613,363.93 on the 2016 Royal Visit (Will, Kate, and the two children) - on accommodation, tours, transportation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in a home built or renovated in the 90s, you'll want to check your gas fireplace. @HealthCanada issues wa… https://t.co/n2FV4qPFln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(And per photo in last tweet, Northern Gateway was not approved by Ottawa)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The project (Kinder Morgan #TransMountain) has met the five conditions." says @christyclarkbc @NEWS1130 https://t.co/pV7PJt6wnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When asked about risks to southern resident killer whales, @christyclarkbc responds #TransMountain "approval came from Ottawa, not us"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Liberals approve environmental assessment 4 Trans Mountain pipeline expansion thru Lower Mainland, but hold news conference in Victoria?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@richard680news reports McDonald's all-day-breakfast will begin rolling out across Canada in late summer/early fall. Already in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Queen of the Skies" isn't so royal anymore it seems. @united to fast-track retirement of 747s. Only handful left a… https://t.co/mu0UeY4nMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.#VanRE again showing how much it's set apart when compared to the rest of Canada... @NEWS1130 https://t.co/I88UGqCUEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are applauding some of Trump's comments in the background of the Q&amp;A at his news conference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump still refuses to release tax returns, again says "still under audit" - "The only people who care about my tax returns are reporters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Over the weekend I was offered $2-billion to do a deal in Dubai 'with a very very amazing man' and I turned it down" - Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have no deals in Russia. I have no deals that could happen in Russia, and I have no loans with Russia." - Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: I tell people all the time to be aware 'tiny cameras' could be watching what they're doing, "You could end up on the nightly news"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If Putin likes Donald Trump, I consider that an asset, not a liability." Trump, "Do you honestly believe Hillary would be tougher on Putin"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hackings are bad and hacking shouldn't be done. But look at the things that were found in that hacking!" - Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The DNC was totally open to be hacked. They did a very poor job. They could have had hacking defense like we had." - Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Probably China," Trump adds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "I think it was Russia, but I think we also got hacked by other countries." @NEWS1130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will be the greatest jobs producer that God ever created" .. says @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statement from @vickihuntington; who has announced she will not run for re-election in May. @NEWS1130 https://t.co/edJdysbzCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you need to go to City Hall @CityofVancouver -- make alternate parking plans. Upper lot closed effective today, intermittently thru Feb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowfall warning issued for East Vancouver Island, but specifically #Nanaimo. 10cm possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind warning issued for #Abbotsford #yxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@50ShadesofVan @ensembleator pouring cold, occasionally chunky rain at my location.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Health Minister @janephilpott won't say if marijuana will be legalized before next election, @cmaconthehill reports @NEWS1130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most accurate thing I've seen yet. https://t.co/CGuwW7R7EP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ensembleator "Gone with the Outflow Breeze"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ensembleator very light. Kinda just blowing around in the air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnowSock_Canada good thing you told me! But I also haven't read the instructions yet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peteronKGMI sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TreenaWood thanks Treena!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwilson1130 thanks Ben! I started with you on the evening show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DixonTam haha yes there are four pieces included. The "pair" just a play on words :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marking 8 years with @NEWS1130 today. It's been great! Looking forward to more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikehellinger12 @SnowSock_Canada looking forward to trying it. Considering snow tires anyway but these may be great for shorter snow events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawzepe they supposedly work like chains but use strong fabric instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DixonTam apparently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my pair-- thanks @SnowSock_Canada! Will be trying these puppies out tomorrow... https://t.co/7PCmw6E93n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoltSafeCANADA Interesting but haven't heard anyone having trouble starting their car. No one has block heaters here. Never goes below -10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PerfectTrev perhaps you could help out some people who don't have any! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PerfectTrev @NEWS1130 It's literally sold out everywhere, unless you're willing to pay someone $50 for a bag on craigslist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way people acting at fire halls where free salt is being given away in @CityofVancouver is a total embarrassment. Shocking behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinmacmahon just called from @VanFireRescue Fire Hall King Edward / Prince Albert -truck arrived w/salt -people CHEERING in background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go again, #YVR! https://t.co/UVxiPdb5pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that is funny. https://t.co/08YlYxkuAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: @CityofVancouver now says there WILL be another salt shipment to 10 fire halls this PM but will only offer 1 bucket per household.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CityofVancouver is your website not accurate, then? @TaraJeanFM @NEWS1130 @krmason7 https://t.co/aBRfSbt3ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@deltapolice say no foul play after human remains found in wooded area off Nordel Way on December 29th @NEWS1130]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>