<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nopoweradeinusa Delet this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla I got some iron tabs if u want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*hans moleman voice* I need the biggest salt lamp u have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new lunar year new me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves does your throat look swollen at all? Last time I had that painful swallow feeling it was tonsillitis ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla bb priscilly!!! ðŸ’•ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla whats up bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollie_arnett would i mayhaps be able to borrow this? its been on my list for a while!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i dont really like vitamins but i bought mens jeans yesterday and this ring belt is a big mood https://t.co/PW30jR1aUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how im trying to look in 2017 tbh https://t.co/zVUADIm8TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss one of our old managers who would blast nothing but Samoan rnb and savage from 10pm onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wanna work somewhere that'll let me on the aux cord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reid_duncan not a dog but she's a Scorpio ðŸ¦‚ðŸ± https://t.co/zm0W6oBeG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reid_duncan honestly texting mum now to ask when our dogs were born]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one of those describe yourself in 4 fictional characters things but literally every character is Livia Soprano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archivequality one soy froggucino pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have this great frog stencil for dusting Cappucinos but no one uses it? Gonna start using it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla no one has 2 know about my shit pours if they're dusted with chocolate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johannesbay ordering 200 sheets rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@comradewest tha fucking maze game thoooooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[finally having my Slowdive moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ive been on 4 (four!) outdoor runs now so im allowed to say taht im a runner and im into running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla full offence i think that landlord should be fkn ashamed of that property... burn the whole thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla i wanna buy tha t clock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[send yourself an email to be delivered next year every time you come home drunk in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u would think that $180/week could get u a reasonably sized room w/ windows in a mostly dry house b ut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single strawberry floating in the pigeon park water feature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing big pants, flapping in th breeze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very cool and fun how the price of living has risen and my income has decreased since finishing uni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unsubscribe from every newsletter in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[catalogue everything in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching couples quietly break up in public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[other flat activities: red cards, loud music, never do the dishes. my flat: give the shower a good run thru with the exit mould]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where the best place to buy houseplants in wellington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your mcm doesn't let the grinds bloom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyZee_ free socks tho ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archivequality snatched... https://t.co/bZ98y6JRtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did not expect Marcus Aurelius to come for me like this on this day... https://t.co/f69ChexYgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stopped mid-run to take a Welly On A Good Dayâ„¢ pic for my insta story but my phone died immediately... the price we pay for our hubris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla run away with me ultimate jogging anthem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love when utube lines up dissociation anthem after anthem https://t.co/3WAcIUNCQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla https://t.co/jcMbLjP0db this fuk me up during uni lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why half of my insta discover feed is bad powerlifting memes but also not asking for it to change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla im afraid of all sea creatures - no exceptions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is my hope and prayer that we can stop Documenting Youth Culture in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tugaem yah bo. robert harris rly spruced itself up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spent so much time reading and rereading my friends' writing this year i hope they keep writing and i hope i start writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in love with this one ASOS model]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyZee_ middle left not playing around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the mall smoky red eye, face lit to the gawds, ordering soy. Forget this is an advanced look for the suburbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla iconic night https://t.co/eC0LwtrSST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla can't wait 2 c what u make x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salviapalth this is just... the most daniel thing  tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sola__mas what's ur fav song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomaslebas @NickKapica @jo_bailey Cat on a Hot Tin Roof &gt;^.^&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla current strategy: unsuccessfully attempt to isolate self, impulsively delete social media, indulge feeelings of guilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla wish i was there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen what do you use? Kind of half heartedly doing one but hard when monthly income isn't consistent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels Unreasonable 2 ask that my last name start with lowercase on my degree but also hate the uppercase d it looks wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new year, new moodboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla me as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eamonnmarra I'm giving my mum a little 'put ur feet up' gift bag with a nice leaf tea, some fancy bikkies and a candle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but brands need to stop using the word 'chuffed'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my worst quality is that i never remember to switch things off at the wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla cant wait to share my performance piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not tht keen on a catholic pm hey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilosophyTube u coming to wellington at all lol?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[having a bevvy at the cinema, great in theory but always have to piss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla where have all the latte bowls gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nocturnal animals fucked me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla I have the chorus of touch my body on loop and I'm living]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maria carey singing "i will hunt you down" in touch my body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[canvas tote but it has the issey miyake bao bao pattern printed on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[solemn ankle pants guy with awkward dufflebag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drakesgurl420 love this wholesome tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[would be nice to be out of wellington before the next influx of vic students lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aceghd cant wait for this think piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK, forever New Zealand's highly problematic uncle. https://t.co/QBpEtGRRSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in other news, I Left My Charger In The Break Room Yesterday and It Will Most Definitely Not Be There When I Get Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no Key low key drinks and crackers at my place tn ðŸ”‘ðŸ”‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were u when John Key resigned?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[make a pledge not to talk about 2017 in meta during 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This entire year has just been talking about this year and I'm as guilty as anybody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[feel bad for anyone who served me coffee during 2nd semester bc I was almost always sweaty and panicking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big fan of anyone who brings their dog to the cafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aceghd it trash. better saving inspo pics/bookmarks or making a pinterest/are.na board. source: have saved many pics of garms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really wanted to like The Neon Demon but u get 1 free pass to make a film with absolutely wooden characters- Drive, Only God Forgives...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every hour of work: 1 hour of Civ V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also don't get why kowtow gave up marketing the unisex thing? still better than any 'gender neutral' line I've seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had to physically remove myself from wellington to avoid spending money @ kowtow sale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the bachelor is nothing without mike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tfw u been hyping a new fragrance but it doesn't fit your skin chemistry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no offence but fuck christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[know you've gone full boug. when the krishnas on manners street don't even try converting you anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wrx_club tbh I'd go 4 the pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aceghd chur chur, what's ur un!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aceghd a.quality im still figuring it out tbh tho!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[soulseek giving me the limewire experience I never had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HowePriscilla when u back babe? Wanna support u x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this democratic system seems a bit broken https://t.co/16YJtd9H1A]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>