<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bigotry That Armed the Quebec Mosque Attacker https://t.co/ZXIMVfnMCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A morally bankrupt, inept executive order on immigration https://t.co/aU6ly3GGnZ via @seattletimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revealed: Conway, Bannon Members of Secretive Group - Southern Poverty Law Center https://t.co/JY25ofEVPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Anne Frank Center Just Responded To Trump’s Wall Order - https://t.co/ujAJa3Dmg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing leaker goes dark after pulling back the curtain: Trump "irrational", staff "demoralized" https://t.co/DcivlJDuNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defector: North Korea wants to blackmail Trump administration with threat of building more nuclear weapons - Hot Air https://t.co/4EneWSD0cb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inquirer Editorial: Trump's first days resemble those of a dictator https://t.co/zsehQ7RlJv via @phillydotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was such an inspiration. She made the world a better place. https://t.co/JCsW0SRrUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret Service agent: I won’t ‘take bullet’ for Trump https://t.co/trcfIKrvjp via @worldnetdaily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I know you have “alternative facts".  I live in “reality” and follow “facts”.  Please turn off the right wing radio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | Donald Trump has assembled the worst Cabinet in American history https://t.co/Io7HQngV3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos embarrassed herself and should be rejected by the Senate https://t.co/b6kh699i3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refuse to accept the new normal https://t.co/Q9rP9QSQVf via @seattletimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is already disappointing his supporters https://t.co/kNh2laVPrV via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama says voting barriers are directly linked to Jim Crow and slavery https://t.co/WmmUeTgQwU via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Grants Commutation to Chelsea Manning  https://t.co/F8AhXoc5g9 via @aclu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. agrees to pay billions of dollars to Marines affected by toxic water https://t.co/EBhVIWkcDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe This emIs/em How Democracy Ends https://t.co/QKvxHDsDU8 via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A veteran spy has given the FBI information alleging a Russian operation to cultivate Donald Trump https://t.co/AgV8NnxCCB via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren calls Trump's treasury pick 'Forrest Gump of the financial crisis' https://t.co/Y9apZSR3me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans start the new Congress with an assault on federal lands https://t.co/mzibms3T5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who the heck is Jackie Evancho?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican lawmakers dramatically expand powers of committee staff to grill witnesses https://t.co/4zLinp0nqR via @bpolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letter: Trump Pulled Con Job on U.S. Citizens https://t.co/MnJHmgavy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Pentagon Shelves Blast Gauges Meant To Detect Battlefield Brain Injuries https://t.co/mz3Sv70qHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Driscoll: Should Tacoma follow Olympia and become a sanctuary city? https://t.co/U0p9yaGad4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters put out blaze at Italian restaurant in Tacoma https://t.co/BGmvjDnWgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...High wind watch in effect from late tonight  through Tuesday afternoon
   in Seattle 20 to 35 mph with local gusts to around 50 mph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storm hits North Bay with heavy rain and moving south to SF https://t.co/tfAbDz9UZt via @SFGate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will stand up to Donald Trump? https://t.co/2qs3pCCK2L via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump transition team for Energy Department seeks names of employees involved in climate meetings https://t.co/ABSNaARJ8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chehalis school district will be having holiday early release tommorrow 11:05 a due to the predicted storm that is supposed to hit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exxon Mobil Accuses the Rockefellers of a Climate Conspiracy https://t.co/jjBctjlZ68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rockefeller Family Fund vs. Exxon https://t.co/eUEDqZYuHQ via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vox First Person: I’m a therapist. Here’s how I help patients traumatized by the election. https://t.co/btySptpTv1 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trader Joe's Hummus Voluntarily Recalled for Listeria Concerns https://t.co/MmeDWDJXJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interstate 5 southbound closed at milepost 78 in Chehalis due to crash; expect long delay https://t.co/St2BQgQGsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A collision on I-5 sb at mp 78.4 near West Street (Chehalis) has all lanes blocked.  You may want to take alt routes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Knick Bradley on ‘White Skin Privilege’ relevant as ever https://t.co/vUfjWbklcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman Busted For Cocaine Voted For Drug Testing Food Stamp Recipients https://t.co/oCGy7VHbdP via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I-5 Southbound - Collision on I-5 southbound at milepost 76 near 13th Street has the left lane blocked beginning at 2:53 pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend report: Rain, I-90, I-5 slowdowns and Monday Night Football https://t.co/uBpVHtCSFs via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's election has unleashed the hate https://t.co/iZ8KQQkGfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A look at Rudy Giuliani before 9/11 terror attacks https://t.co/d5nSS3KNMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kahlil Gibran On Joy and Sorrow https://t.co/TiG3lnnGg0 via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ana Navarro explains why it's hard for marginalized groups to give Trump a chance https://t.co/m2io8qqfCs via @LatinoVoices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pink Floyd - Dark Side Of The Moon https://t.co/jkud0wKAwi via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Hard Rain's A-Gonna Fall - Tom Russell (Calexico, Lucinda Williams) https://t.co/1H858mdZvU via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walk the streets of a Trump town in Washington state https://t.co/BcmLwy0RMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds flock to Susan B. Anthony's grave on Election Day @CNNPolitics https://t.co/FhjdNHVqxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@StephensWSJ: Trump is a demagogue. Period. The right’s failure to see it is a disgrace. https://t.co/CHSDEo7hSy via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Coup Against the Supreme Court https://t.co/EWk71xIaCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 1M state voters have voted as last-minute campaign donations come in https://t.co/aWbB9wFjHf via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocket stolen from Fort Lewis armory turned in by soldier’s ex https://t.co/3RGXaStNGC via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog Lake Washington State https://t.co/WhXe3WcwgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A letter to my daughter about Trump @CNN https://t.co/aDvYMEzKzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amy Schumer Mocks Tampa Trump Supporters in Open Letter https://t.co/hESsh8hC56 via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navy Admits to Having Released Chemicals Known to Injure Infants' Brains https://t.co/YFlikzZzqt via @truthout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump claims without evidence that the election is rigged, but officials say that's not how voting works https://t.co/0ga3fexhyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fans boo, walk out on Amy Schumer show in Tampa (w/video) https://t.co/H9pdzAEuPs via @TB_Times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie Knew About Bridgegate Scheme, 'Smiled' About It, Ex-Ally Says In Testimony https://t.co/zLStXffozH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWJD? Fire Archbishop Myers, not gay Catholic school staffer | Editorial https://t.co/BDL0NcAPQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why big ships are being turned away from ports of Los Angeles and Long Beach https://t.co/QKiJ7n7Jfa via @presstelegram]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's it like to live here? https://t.co/g7wemTE02F via @ptleader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A range fire that started a few days ago continues to burn on the south side of the JBLM artillery impact area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aetna pulled out of Obamacare because CEO was angry his big merger got denied https://t.co/ruFDuT2Y5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's bold vision: Make America Hide Under the Bed Again https://t.co/iyX6nK6egN via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharing with Gigya: https://t.co/tAsFvy79z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mercury News editorial: Enjoy safer, saner Fourth of July: https://t.co/X8zM8PLtRg via @MercNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What 31 science orgs just told Congress about climate change https://t.co/O5pOoyFQaB via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seattle is crowded; here's where everyone is coming from https://t.co/IFLjUNxNtR via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Myth of the Filibuster-Proof Democratic Senate - San Diego Free Press: https://t.co/CmNT0k79SQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crews Battle 1,200-Acre Brush Fire Burning In Santa Barbara's Refugio Canyon https://t.co/KXGYfowWBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles Weather https://t.co/uE9rJt0xKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Globe editorial on gun control: Ban assault weapons. https://t.co/fOziJqzhiI via @BostonGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romano: Why Gov. Rick Scott never talks about Obamacare anymore https://t.co/gs1ACrJ40O via @TB_Times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romano: The one question we've never answered about mass shootings https://t.co/SIscYvCnGN via @TB_Times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed the acting in "The Night Manager" Thank you. Looks like it was an enjoyable performance for all the actors.
Like · Reply · Just now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray, Cantwell move to block copper mine in upper Methow Valley https://t.co/JopA2vBPEl via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax cuts may tell a scary tale - The West Australian https://t.co/D12DkICJjo via @Yahoo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel defense chief quits, cites lack of trust in Netanyahu https://t.co/Wqof6fB6tO via @Yakima_Herald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Native Americans Were the Victims of Genocide https://t.co/tF0WE9sS21 via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. tribes mobilize against giant proposed Canadian pipeline, oil export terminal https://t.co/CWGRiXguYy via @seattlepi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oregon county says no to Nestle water-bottling plant https://t.co/UCtMQ11vxZ via @seattletimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cherry Point coal terminal rejection affirms tribal rights and treaties https://t.co/p1YeJ1x2Yx via @seattletimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford, Spielberg reteaming for fifth 'Indiana Jones' movie https://t.co/IY8LjKo3LA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pfizer rules on lethal injection drugs may limit death penalty executions https://t.co/SS7b73QyXI via @AsburyParkPress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postal service ‘doing well,’ loss of $2 billion a congressional ‘hoax’ –... https://t.co/vvCzm3L17k via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News certainly has had its share of controversies surrounding on-camera personnel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds deny permit for Washington coal-export terminal https://t.co/LRwhlfo5Dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: Miami Beach waging a battle against sea level rise https://t.co/WdFlF6qPUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American healthcare is ... often about selling you things you probably don't need at a ridiculous price. https://t.co/iF2u0TnLYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrifty Thurston – 5 Hikes Under and 5 Hikes Over 5 Miles Near Olympia https://t.co/MTOr5yrLo3 via @ThurstonTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALERT: Massive Food Recall Expands To 50 States After Several People Hospitalized - Breaking911 https://t.co/wZdGyzaQ3l via @Breaking911]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Benefits of Real Cinnamon vs. Fake Cinnamon? https://t.co/S0h5SYnvH4 via @livestrong_com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE https://t.co/ukrgpp089G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election: Trump reveals America's dark side https://t.co/RFK9T1s3BY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo “Solitude” by Norman Lathrop #500px https://t.co/ErKRDoOZ0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask A Vet: Why Does My Dog Stare At Me When He Poops? https://t.co/jvxIL0QGrk #iHeartDogs via @ILoveDogsSite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False start: Army postpones rocket test at JBLM https://t.co/6p4lcpzyj0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>