<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ametonym lets see. He may be a WS. Heck 
He might be atheist. On his fb he liked athiest authors but who knows?? Could be anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbgiovanardi eh I like calling out on both sides. Stop dissing and start loving. Work together. Unity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brooks_rosa news source is newsweek, nytimes and prolly AP... I am not surprised. #YouBeingLiedTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ametonym @MLxHobbes @TayoChas right now we dont know if hes a trump supporter or a feminist. Theres a vid of him talking about climate idk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ametonym @MLxHobbes @TayoChas I dont too. I read all news. Try to see their agenda. Do a little digging and accept the results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont like spreading fake news but if it is true that the shooter is a muslim convert, I'll be out of this site.
 https://t.co/6QNeSO8P3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E2NZ @Delo_Taylor lol go to Trudeau if u r that hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLxHobbes @TayoChas @ametonym so you believe what your news feed says? No one knows the kids motives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmatullahCm @Delo_Taylor just because hes white does not mean he is christian lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E2NZ @Delo_Taylor @colettebrowne @POTUS @realDonaldTrump and he is a femenist and democratic? Uhm dont define him based on his likes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Delo_Taylor you cant call him a white supremist until you have proof that his motive was that he thinks white ppl are better than muslims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whitewizard6mi2 @stanleyrogouski @Rideskii @Delo_Taylor I swear if this is real. This will make them scream. Something is fishy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Delo_Taylor @FoxNews stop spreading fake news. This is what gets people mad. I do it to the right I do it to the left too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Delo_Taylor why do you support the rebels? We need the Syrian government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eemanabbasi I hope you know many indians here believe All lives matter sweetie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fvizs Leviticus in the OT, Corinthians is in the NT. Your point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed buzzfeed I swear if this is fake and you do this to push propaganda. First act on civil war is hack your site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eemanabbasi @TomiLahren wheres your outrage that vets here are homeless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_walaaaaaaa and what about christian churches? It all sucks but we should never grow hatred to one another. Ppl got demons. Lord im praying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eemanabbasi he created the order in 2011. Its not even a Muslim ban. Its a ban of refugees from countries Obama deems as a concern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shoshweeetx @eemanabbasi WAIT WAIT... where was your outrage ans protest with Iraqi refugees ban in 2011 and thousands droned by Obama??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passionvii he bombed millions of ppl in the middle east and you guys miss him? Yall nuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrahhhhhh they may switch now but the democrats think they know what's best for the ppl... they dont.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billyeichner when your sources are CNN and NYTimes then yes duh you are right. Lost respects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eemanabbasi ah just another way for the liberal outlets to keep targeting Trump. Gotta love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bckybrnesjpg you believe anything negative about Trump? Hb you do some research, hear both sides and look at facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eemanabbasi this is the left. I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yamuva_ read a history book, then come back here and tweet a correction. You wouldn't be on this if white ppl came here lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Afg_zainab white ppl were opressed. The irish and atm white ppl are starting to get it if there are more riots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkKent2215 reverse racism doesnt exist, its just racism. Caucasian, african american, middle eastern, far eastern, yup u can hate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Afg_zainab I think the devil is the one who reminds a person of their past mistakes. He never told ppl to kill. But Ik some extremist :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Afg_zainab that happens in Saudi and Africa, you gonna go and tell em that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Afg_zainab thats what you wanna believe, go ahead. The intention was but hey say hi to legend MLK who changed that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlesassytaco you might get hurt then. #BuildTheWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smugjitsu @Delo_Taylor so you care about the ME now? What about when Obama droned them and killed millions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeeVee @xlaurenstephens you know, just because you dont understand what immigration is, does not mean its bad if u wanna know what it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@etambascio @realDonaldTrump where was your outrage when Obama killed the Bengazzi soldiers,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules ah being the bigger person. I wonder how u guys do it there. I wish I can show my defense to Trump here in Toronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RocksAnnaa @TheCut dont believe everything the media tells you love. Look at facts and hear both sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNICEF and did you tell Obama that during his 8 years of him bombing their areas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules i think this might be her grandmother or someone related.. gotta respect others. https://t.co/CtlUuOmyFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anon19821902 really this girl? She looks like she's about to poop in this photo. https://t.co/0hkaJm89nL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah these ppl assaulting the crowd and the guests were terrorist. That is all. Those far lefties were babies and terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHECK THIS OUT! https://t.co/3gh83mT2CR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah well there were other races within that white crowd who was terrorizing the place.. oh wait, I got it. Terrorism lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah yeah he has many and associates with Muslims, Sikhs and Latinos so its not a suprise. This is 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah no.. white kids who are torturing and burning and assaulting others... what is that called??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah question is: have you ever been to a Milo event? Have you seen the diversity he has in his audience?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah actual white supremist hate Milo. They hate him for dating black guys. He loves black dick he says in his speeches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah girl you are contradicting yourself. I am surprised you have not blocked me for calling you out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah do you equate white people as Nazis? That is something I want to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad these millineral kids here in Twitter don't care about this.. well many smh https://t.co/sqQWoaXOrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CopperCab bro just relax. Just because you had a hard time finding love does not mean you should be mean to someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbn566 @Trumptbird @POTUS there can be some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah Webster dictionary. The belief that a caucasians person believes they are better and superior to another race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah not my words, yours. https://t.co/djibOGpn4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLoeding @JessieJaneDuff @POTUS @vicky_palazzo it could have if the Clintons won.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moby_dickhead Racism: someone who believes someones race is lesser than theirs thus discriminate against them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBloom451 I think that is her friend who filmed it but didn't get to see the attacker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeygak @YouTube someone needs to run a good database to get this person's identity. https://t.co/IX3ogtARIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good for him https://t.co/hZ4a3i3N3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moby_dickhead well I can see how you need to educate yourself on what a racist is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah you mean those white kids who attack people and destroy city and school property last night at the campus? Well, I guess u right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah do you just takes what the news tell you? Oh honey please I beg you to do some research on what white supremacy is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[liberals going crazy with this https://t.co/l1uOH4kl7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyatikah uhm, you don't even know if he is a trump supporter or not. How about you do some facts instead of believing the MSM love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfullerNYT you need to grow up. Take responsibility with your articles next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malonebarry @rosabraico honey I hope u know this media outlet have been accused of false propaganda &amp; sends money for rebels 2 kill Syrians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomBrian21 @Lexialex well I believe the right are better and that is not to attack them with fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich  serious *]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich I don't know how to take an account serious when they used spelling mistakes but still, report them to police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@undergradwoman then you need to grow up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek ARE YOU THAT STUPID? Are you applauding on the assaults? Damn please find your dad. @alexnazaryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek TALKING ABOUT YOURSELF YES ROBERT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek lol stop praising him you donuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek that is your opinion Robert. Stop making crap up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek don't talk about fake news since you are fake news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AvenidaDe1aPaz @Lexialex correction: socialist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ava_rice_ 2 years ago? Or is it because of Trump, everyone is going crazy? wow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@comedyandtruth @julialxbello This was deemed fake. Just image if someone said that about Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people love Obama but hate Trump? I did a survey and the reactions from ppl were different than I expected.
https://t.co/IxSRJ56xe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there are 8K RTs of a video of protestors assaulting a girl but 50K RTs of fake news about Trump? Wow Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cleovpatra @KurroroZ @TTaRblog well it is very unfortunate. In Europe, it is sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neganthot instead of criticizing, how about you pray for the girl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurroroZ @Cleovpatra @TTaRblog my ex wore it when she was heading to the mosque.. I live in Canada so it's chill here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neganthot are you just gonna believe anything you read online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taymanffb @WeirOnlyHuman @Heritage beating people up is still not right. And who shot in Quebec? Well he liked a feminist page on fb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cleovpatra @glumkid @TTaRblog there are other rules unfort lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't you glad these people didn't come to the states? https://t.co/7oE1lnzOPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metamemette @ABCPolitics doesn't matter with me. I think you should just forgive those who offended you and that means even authoritarians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cleovpatra @glumkid @TTaRblog Ever traveled to Saudia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillianNBC WHO IS THE LADY? GIVE HER AN AWARD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisRGun @LRyanV if you are talking about Quebec, you are wrong. The shooter may not have been right wing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metamemette @ABCPolitics @Pontifex no, but the bible says we are all Saints and are priests. I'm Christian so yeah lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cleovpatra @TTaRblog @glumkid be surprise on the consequences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0ncampbell @realJamesAllsup did they arrest the one who threw something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nypd did their job https://t.co/JWecAQIyc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBlaireWhite you should contact @broderick. Can't you sue them for libel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m96gran @Lexialex I feel like Trump supporters are like the Jews.. boycotting Starbucks and whatnot lol. Then the Nazis are the far left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billieraegrant @rosesandwaves thats my bby.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>