<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheReal85 @impishhern5 @JoyAnnReid  I mostly blame those who accepted his hateful rhetoric. No real American should have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Any criticism of the right is attributed to media bias against the right. It is just an immature game of deflection, adult version.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX  I know. But they see opportunity to repeat the rape of our economy by those who profit from recession. That was my point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheReal85 @impishhern5 @JoyAnnReid That blame rest squarely on the deplorables shoulders. I blame the reckless GOP base who voted for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @TeaPainUSA As long as they do it while searching for a new job, I'm down with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Sorta like "alternative facts" were called LIES?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @five15design @BCAppelbaum @Russell_Andrews I'd lay low until this ass is impeached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProgressWeekly @ddiamond How can this be? The GOP SWORE the ACA would cause massive job losses. I remember them saying so, do you? A LIE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @ProgressWeekly Must be either bad credit risk or mob connections. Might be Putin cronies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If we were smart, you wld already be a fading footnote in our history. Don't worry, we the ppl will fix that mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBendu1 @billprady @chrislhayes Might not BOTH sides need to think about that, or is the right blameless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBendu1 @chrislhayes @billprady I wld be proud to riot against white supremacists! What they say is poison, unamerican.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @ProgressWeekly If you are a white Christian, you get a pass from Trump and the GOP. I hope they pay at the mid-terms, BIGLY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aerik_bjornsson @donaldpoopoo @RealJamesWoods As baby boomers retire, that will happen brainiac.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @woodrose300 James Woods is the stain on America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX I'm afraid that isn't so. Setting conditions for deliberate repeat so big money can scoop up assets at bargain prices, AGAIN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Strange how the "Liberal Media" did that, don't you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@physguy2 @FoxNews @MSNBC @CNN @AC360 Dumbasses get confused quickly if you stray off the script. Hard to keep the hate focused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunKing @margaretresin @realDonaldTrump @washingtonpost Trump and the GOP lied?  But they both SWEAR they don't lie to the ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@physguy2 @FoxNews @MSNBC @CNN @AC360 They didn't get permission to air it from the GOP yet. Kinda tough to spin it as a Trump/GOP win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaroldWNelson Many of those who voted for him now know they screwed the pooch. I can't wait for the mid-terms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimberrens Wld not increase coal jobs. AUTOMATION.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkJDoran @VABVOX @Catniptwoshoes If nothing, would that make Trump better?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX GOP will soon be relying on "alternative reality" to justify supporting this idiot. Good thing lying is second nature for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Trump isn't qualified for strategic thinking outside a business setting. Hope he will leave foreign policy to the professionals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX Expect silence from the same GOP asses who raised hell about timing of PBO actions in 2012. Remember?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX He won't care. She didn't vote for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bcs you will find legal means to steal doesn't mean the USA should steal. Ever heard of being ethical?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blickdaddy @TouchMyTweets @cathie_lagrange @andreastonez Don't remember him EVER threatening to take away their WH access, do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathie_lagrange @andreastonez @TouchMyTweets I remember when we had majority rule, you know, like he with most votes wins. NOT MY POTUS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andreastonez  In all fairness, the man who knows more than all the generals, isn't smart enough to help anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artzthings I fear MANY more. And he who won't admit fault, won't learn anything, and repeat mistakes. Costing MORE lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ed_Demolay @GPaulRacer @BraddJaffy @KattyKayBBC @PhilipRucker Trump being what he is, IS the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SidneyTucker666 @BraddJaffy @PhilipRucker @washingtonpost They are mentally equipped for the job, unlike Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yadira1357 @KellyannePolls Back home, us simple folk use to call it LYING. It is a strange new world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SidneyTucker666 @BraddJaffy @PhilipRucker @washingtonpost The world knows he is a dumbass, so our allies will work around Trump. I HOPE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ed_Demolay @GPaulRacer @BraddJaffy @KattyKayBBC @PhilipRucker Bcs Trump is a dumbass who is incapable of admitting he is a dumbass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @yadira1357 @PhilipRucker @washingtonpost Trump is so clueless, he thinks he can bully other leaders. DUMBASS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longwall26 @earthriseset That's the damn truth too, and I frikkin dare deplorables to deny it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisrockyoz @earthriseset If it touched her, she would melt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset @LeonardRaymundo @DrDrunken @LaceyAnne34 @nytimes Sounds like a GREAT place to be! Bet the Ave IQ is higher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PandaPolitico16 @nytimes Makes me Blv they want a Banana Republic, since only the wealthy deserve to rule the poor masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissMarciaC Maybe having someone of Dan Rather's stature stand up and say what must be said, will make the GOP start acting like Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissMarciaC @nytimes It would serve them right. POTUS is an office that must be taken seriously, unlike a clown like Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TylerHanley @nytimes @realDonaldTrump His GOP friends in congress will get rich, and will protect him if we don't win back congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phouse123 @nytimes That is probably the plan. Let taxpayer bail out banks while the wealthy buy the assets on pennies on the dollar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeradf741 @mudslidematt @nytimes The wealthy profit big on reccesion. They love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset @LaceyAnne34 @nytimes I would be very happy living in Oregon. Beautiful place with great ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killermuses @nytimes They will blame liberals and minorities somehow. Perfect scapegoat to avoid admitting Trump and GOP are responsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes @tgruka That's Bcs we can trust banks not to throw caution to the wind for quick profits. Oh wait, no we can't!   Another bailout?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgruka @KrisSanchez @KTVALE080  Just made up manure his voters love to swallow. He said he loves stupid voters, remember? He meant it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeploarableDan @DrCraigMalkin @realDonaldTrump You should be pissed about what Trump does, not at your fellow Americans anger about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're either a lying, decietful POC, or the biggest dumbass there ever was. Are you formenting division on purpose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. Another responsible gun owner got mad and shot his daughter, here in Atlanta. Good thing he had a gun when he got pissed, RIGHT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frazier_annik @ReutersBiz The swamp is alive and thriving under the lizard king Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReutersBiz What possible excuse did they make up for that move? You gotta love slick talking folks who pass this nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllanMargolin @itspossibly @dailykos @JupiterHydro @ohiomail Protestors need to be aware of their crazy nut job sherrif. The guy's deranged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio We aren't radicals dumbass. Was GOP radical when McConnell said block everything? You must be speaking to your moronic base.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeddMcc @politicalmiller Nah, the GOP already showed us the way to do it, remember? They screwed USA for 8 yrs, our turn now. HAHAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_magic_m @buckydentist @SheriffClarke @Julie4Trump You forget, when GOP protests, they're Patriots. When others protest, lazy bums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kharyp @realDonaldTrump Idiot in Chief will say it never happened, despite vid proof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When you said your Mike didn't work, it was a conspiracy against you, remember? You are an embarrassment! GO HOME!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordMacey Have you seen the vid of what GOP voters see with those glasses on? HILARIOUS! Sadly, it is also true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FurForceFive @Reuters That's just about how many morons we have. COINCIDENCE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordMacey Gee, you mean Fox lied, what a shock! Main info source for GOP folks are either stupid or liars. Sounds like their viewers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriBerman @sivavaid But McConnell said the ppl shld decide, and HRC got 3 million more votes. By that logic, HRC gets to choose next SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeddMcc @politicalmiller Why can't Dems just refuse and obstruct like GOP did? 游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind @NikitaKitty Anyone wonder if Russia said that to sow discord and weaken our democracy. Putin is certainly not a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This results of this election CLD very well be the catalyst for a cycle of Dem dominance. This shld motivate Dems to vote as never before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @globeandmail These damn RW nuts are a frikkin menace to society. Can we set up a registry for these sick turds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariellaMadrid @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass Branding yourself a gullible fool friend. Trump is the sex offender, but that's OK by you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NastyNana16 Well stated. We are America and we shall persevere as long as we cherish our freedom, and protect it. No Trump, EVER!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pharris830 @AddInfoOrg I wonder how many GOP voters will switch to Dem, since they look out for EVERYONE, regardless of race or religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariellaMadrid @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass Back to Killary nonsense? Bet you fell for Pizzagate nonsense also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joycesurprenant @Visitkarte @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass Judicial branch not going anywhere. We will remain America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariellaMadrid @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass With Russian ties, and Flynn choice, it looks mighty suspicious to non Trump cult ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@painter_nancy @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass CLD be Flynn, W/o Trump knowing. Who knows really. But if Trump knew, life W/o parole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaylesJon @Visitkarte @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass We have lost direction before, but always find our way back. That's what DEMS are for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dem_happy Just a glimpse to remind us of who we really are, and what we stand for. We will be alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuadabeauty @PRETTYGIRLGG11 Dems are the majority, will stop the madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaylesJon @Visitkarte @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass No, SCOTUS will only go so far. They know President's and congress change,they stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PRETTYGIRLGG11 Sure will make them look like a bunch of fools, and rightly so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra Maybe, maybe not. I doubt this crap will last long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @JayColton3 They really are too stupid to care. They want war with ALL of Islam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @JayColton3 @businessinsider GOP knows stock price means more than ppl's lives. ACA saves lives, lots of lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra And Congress's duty is to protect us from the likes of Trump, Bannon and Flynn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra We protest Trump, as he is a HUGE problem. We protest GOP, who harm Americans,including vets, every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra Immigrants rarely cause problems. They are grateful to be here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcspocky @PRETTYGIRLGG11 If he tries, so many millions of us will register it will make it useless. Make him look really foolish.游때游때游때游때游때游때游때游때游때游때]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing most Americans agree about, is freedom of the press. PBO, like most Dems,know of lying Fox, but never tried to silence them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighFiv49807762 @edgeoforever @JonathanTamari @danpfeiffer They know better, but recognize value of misleading very stupid, paranoid ppl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra A bit different when invasion and war are the tools for change, don't you agree?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjsanto9458 @USARedOrchestra That precaution CLD include many who are here now, and kill a lot of us. But they are not Muslim, so no worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidYankovich @blaha_b  There hasn't been for 20 yrs. When Gingrich became speaker, the GOP changed the political process for the worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coopah @ubervaper @dailykos He only did it to make the idiots who voted for him happy. They truly are idiots. Hateful idiots at that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Americans have our share of deplorable ppl, like every nation. But we won't allow basic decency to be discarded. We are good at heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agathaagitates @tkdmike History shall record Trump as the biggest fool in our history, of that there is NO DOUBT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewbridges @TearsInHeaven09 I agree, wholeheartedly. The GOP will milk it for agenda's sake, then dump Trump to mitigate losses at polls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PRETTYGIRLGG11 The world's leaders are hopefully too smart to let a dumbass like Trump start a hugely destructive world war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Visitkarte @JeffersonObama @pnwrunnerlass I still have faith that America is too strong for that. We fight and argue, but won't be beaten.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>