<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So how do I thread tweets? https://t.co/ZtYNmfwGIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@driverminnie happy birthday! Congratulations on the year you made show about disability that disabled people actually like!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTonyCoffey Hi Tony. Would like to talk to you about your show. email your number to emma.tracey@bbc.co.uk. Ta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheila700Scott Possibly didn't express myself well. I don't love social media accounts run by humans on behalf of animals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheila700Scott sorry to hear that. I have an incredible guy dog Varona who I love to bits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This boy talks with his eyes. https://t.co/vcyrhx8vge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ju90artist Popped in to Twitter for procrastination purposes and am now sorry didn't say Graham Norton's mammy on the NTAs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knight_millie Congratulations Milly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliakite Hi Julia. But I'm in Scotland now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if someone will be at your house for 15 minutes at 6pm to help you to the loo, you’d better not be late." https://t.co/TBZnCI7lIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writerlyderv Hi. Let me know how it goes. All good here. Yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westport residents plagued by calls to X-rated Babestation https://t.co/J0Hkmfw0Cu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeFielding1 Oooh thanks. I totally have a girl crush on that fabulous woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't even know DMs could be open. https://t.co/t6JcxuFT5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmavogelmann Good for you Emma. It takes energy and massive will to complain each time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikScarlet What a shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikScarlet What on earth prompted that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisybabe Oh god I totally missed this story. Thanks Lisa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes Oh, Just putting it out there, Shelley Atkinson who read The Glorious Heresies is an exceptional narrator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes Lovely! I could listen to you all day. Can't wait for the new book. unabridged Audio at same time as hardback pleeeeeease!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaraLG84 yes. I think you are right. And I don't think it tells you if a video or audio is attached anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry Some of that is singing instructions and digs at your partner in a lullaby tone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doug Paulley's blog is well worth a read. https://t.co/rIfdq8FBoE @kingqueen3065]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrnaMulcahy @IrishTimesLife subs need another glance over this f ttypos and repeated words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BendyGirl all good here. Hopefully there is no need to be anxious and they can easily see you're a great mum and d… https://t.co/5QmFK7ryNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good on epilepsy, pregnancy and love. https://t.co/cfm4HMTaje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamkremer gives you the rage doesn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BendyGirl oh my God that's so exciting! Well done you. I'm so pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairplay Mandy. https://t.co/Db8WYMeX6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doug Paulley is a bit of a legend and it's nice to see Nikki Fox on the 10. #disability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shannonemurray amazing! Thanks for sharing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheilaoflanagan because you have to constantly wash cloth's, which is a pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something in my eye https://t.co/btYnaYSKdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howardhardiman Cool. Just let me know when the alt tags are ready.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howardhardiman Hi Howard. Did I see you have created a new game for people with chronic pain? If so, tell me more please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest Untold from @BBCRadio4 has epilepsy, pregnancy and a gorgeous love story. https://t.co/lRppS9A58e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a fellow blind person, this woman's description of sexual asault is so upsetting. https://t.co/gnGbkAExkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonMHall that's going to be in my head all afternoon now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep hearing #CBB  as #CBeebies. #screenreaderproblems #dontevicttumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimesNews Central Mental Hospital? Seriously? Is that what it is called?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selinalitt Good point but I thought snow held the title because it has a blanketing effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully with more accessibility for blind users. Just because it's very visual doesn't mean we don't want a shot. https://t.co/fzW2ipSvO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting that Nintendo's new hardware is called the Switch. Switches make games consoles accessible for disabled people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your least fav weather as a disabled person and why? We're talking about blind man's fog, or snow,  on the podcast today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BendyGirl we had children's services in but were comfortable and happy to prove we had everything in hand in that… https://t.co/ni803bP5Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I produced this but the guests and presenters make it really awesome! Take a listen if you get a chance. https://t.co/cIJYp9NQ75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ms_molly_vog Fav foods. Bing Bunny, stickers, paper and colouring in stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All about the audio. As it should be. https://t.co/fw4hAqRP9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very exciting. https://t.co/JdRUZYt5ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogsawyer Everywhere I came upon it online showed a photo of the text, which I can't access. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogsawyer Thanks! Maria B read your reply out in a voice message to me. It's perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byrnemaria Thanks X.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GidsG @guardian Love this Gids. Thanks for sharing. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rogsawyer Thank you very much. I'll share it with the original post so other blind people can read it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdiscopop My husband @robinspinks knows every word of the song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdiscopop Oh god. 19 months and Tadhg has it as an earworm. "Go, Jettas go. dee dee dee."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdiscopop Haha. Are you in the same boat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBeebiesHQ Our 19-month-old wants Go Jetters Christmas ep on repeat. Only acceptable alternative is the Komodo dragon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadio4 is Phoebe's letter printed in full anywhere? Blind people can't  read photos of text. #missingout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clive_gardiner Absolutely loving AD on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamareedom And they aren't  even blind. But I actually am. What was the pic you sent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamareedom Blind as a bat I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crazyhelen09 I give up. Losing at Twitter today. that tweet was clearly not meant for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImaanStandup The @RNIBShop website is actually tricky to use with Jaws and Windows. #wheresthesearch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitzpatrickd Right. And is that better than one of those eg moulds or have you tried them? Very cheap and with a handle thing sticking up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitaldarragh I'm not naturally patient but being a parent is different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitaldarragh @fitzpatrickd Not sure how to take that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fitzpatrickd What skill would you show me or what would you teach me to cook if I popped by with a recorder?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyBainz Katherine and Joe in Last Chance Saloon was the first sex scene I ever read and I still love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damonrose No. In the microwave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickykealy @digitaldarragh @barkingbabs1971 @muzobazz #proudofyoounicholas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitaldarragh Next time I'm over, we should record you teaching me how to fry an egg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitaldarragh @muzobazz @barkingbabs1971 It can stick to the rim and burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@digitaldarragh @barkingbabs1971 @muzobazz @nickykealy Did Nicholas actually use it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barkingbabs1971 @muzobazz No Barbara, I can't . Never order them in front of people I don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzobazz @barkingbabs1971 Yep. I'm a bit afraid of frying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0ekenny The response to my tweet suggests there's ann apetite. Get it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzobazz @barkingbabs1971 I'm not a massive fan either but think that's because I'm so slow and it is exhausting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0ekenny Hahaha. So Irish. It's all about the work-arounds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barkingbabs1971 Interesting. I'm wondering if mmaybe it'd be presenter led with lots of different cooks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barkingbabs1971 I hear ya barking. Did you ever hear Janet Tuggy's AudioBooms? Straightforward recipes for cheesecake, brownies, curry etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barkingbabs1971 Totally. I sometimes feel like there are absolute basics I don't know because I've not seen others do them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FVSensoryCentre Hi. Would he talk to me about it do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blind people, if there was a cookery show made for you, would you listen? And what would you want it to sound like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crossantravels I think these tweets are what the kids call a meem. Sue Purkins tweeted one about New York.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNIBRadio But I'd love an actual cookery show with talking equipment and tips on the basics from blind cooks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNIBRadio Please serve me up a blind-friendly cookery podcast. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetry helps the Reids cope with Paul's MS. Meet them on Facebook at 3 PM. https://t.co/gwh1tTRqkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyMcNib @Coach_Kelvin @RTEdoconone @boreenbroadcast It is audio and it is accessible from everywhere so get listening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boreenbroadcast could you follow me for a DM about your brilliant documentary please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Time to Lose is a superb radio doc about epilepsy, running and being a teenager. @RTEdoconone @boreenbroadcast https://t.co/YDuRjzPOuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it great that Gilmore Girls is just immediately there on #Netflix with #audiodescription ? So easy to access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen: The lovely @Stuarthypnotist on how hypnosis helps him and others live with chronic pain https://t.co/vme9IPDgE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcSettle Let us know how you get on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJdoherty Good for you. Hope you had a meat feast for dinner last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vibeke_Venema That's a clicker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese And blind people. And severely dyslexic people or anyone with a print disability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcSettle I tried it on the phone but will give the watch a go this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcSettle Haven't tried sharing options or the transcription feature yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcSettle Definitely. Simple interface. Gesture for recording from anywhere. Beeps when you record and stop.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>