<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to get business cards done, FAST - anyone have recommendations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freelance graphic designers, please message me ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theweprojectca third strategy meeting. Again, I am so grateful for the women at this round table who are bringing my/this vision to life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday is the perfect day to refuel your soul and be grateful for each and every one of your blessings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in #Toronto for 2 weeks now, I can't even begin to explain how much I miss #kwawesome. My home is still #Waterloo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#womeninleadership https://t.co/xmjfZtkk02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more empowering than women supporting each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a firm believer of thoughts become reality. What you think you will become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot begin to express how grateful I am for all the opportunities I have had and have been given.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be grateful for what you have and what you have will be enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@consult_Aziz yes I am actually - email me please nisa@remaxcommunity.ca , thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a freelance graphic designer, please tweet me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average price of Toronto home expected to increase by $100K this year https://t.co/kRPijDQ8A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average price of Toronto home expected to increase by $100K this year https://t.co/cL1zKoaLSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OREAinfo I've been on hold for over an hour now. Why are the phones not being tended to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a busy day ahead of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you do - be the best at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success doesn't wait for anyone. Rise &amp; Grind early birds. #5amclub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often I wake up early &amp; want to sleep in. Then I remember, there are others that already have a head start by waking up way before me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge others, make sure you are perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nilaniSays @mandadooks I need an accountability partner to force me to get to the gym. Please say I do? Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anybody go to the fit4less regularly by morningside and Milner? Please DM me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a #freelancegraphicdesigner - please get into touch w/ rates! Nisa@remaxcommunity.ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lack of boundaries invites a lack of respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I had a buyer ask me "How old are you? You look too young to be in real estate".

I have good genes my friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I had like one tenth of the kind of work ethic my parents have. Tireless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a ton of work to do, instead I am sitting here googling how celebrity couples met. #PRIORITIES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you're in a relationship doesn't make you non-independent. You can be fully committed to someone and still be independent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HornesECS thanks for reaching out none the less!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krishnavms I need a helicopter, even in emergencies I need to land in style. 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There could be nothing worse than this paper cut I have in the palm of my hand right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate form of sophistication.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constantly reminding myself that all these unaccounted working hours will pay off one day, some day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a residential cleaner - email me your rates ASAP, required for a condo appx 650 sq feet.... https://t.co/appCPblsa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of you Salman D. ! https://t.co/rGj56uq5bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those of you who have already liked - thank you so much! 
For those who have not, this is my Facebook page... https://t.co/KncN7URfCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mayilirage I really forced myself not to buy a coffee at 530 am this morning. So far I am going strong. Still on for our meeting tom, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rise &amp; Grind! I heard 10am is the most optimal time to have a coffee - is this true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Luxury Home Sales Soar Almost 100% In A Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in learning more about real estate? https://t.co/1cIJojLVYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4 Words You Need To Repeat To Yourself When You're Stressed At Work https://t.co/fMbsWoJVAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Have to Teach Girls Not to Fear Failure via @forbes https://t.co/yo3uGdccsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our scientific power has outrun our spiritual power. We have guided missiles and misguided men. -Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minimalism Has Made Me Mindful Of My Hoarder's Mentality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect your efforts, respect yourself. Self-respect leads to self-discipline. When you have both firmly under your belt, that's real power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The older you get, the smaller your circle becomes. Its because you grow wiser &amp; you are more aware of what surroundings are good for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't even begin to explain how grateful I am for this life and the people in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a website designer with real estate experience - call me ASAP 416 836 3283]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to buy or sell? As manager at a firm that houses many of Toronto's top agents, believe… https://t.co/U9nSuH3qIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychopaths Are More Likely To Order This Drink https://t.co/Is6JXyXzpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no force more powerful than a woman determined to rise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I aspire to live a life that I love. Im not chasing money. Im chasing power and freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear all I follow is pregnant people on Instagram.

I have baby fever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success means nothing if your home is broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am looking for a make up artist, novice is okay. DM your rates please and some sample work on people with my skin tone. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThushanthSeev it's actually so helpful isn't it! Setting intentions is so so so important!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Me. I laugh like this. https://t.co/KF0L8FAyEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Shark Tank' For Black Female Founders Inspires Next Generation Of Entrepreneurs https://t.co/NWahlIYbM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a habit of waking up early morning and tweeting a series of quotes. It's my way of setting daily intentions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the first thing you do when you wake up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look back, you're not going that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being happy doesn't mean everything's perfect. It means you've decided to look past the imperfections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[78 years ago, a journalist who studied 500 millionaires realized something about relationships that is just as... https://t.co/YfSK7V56m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing! https://t.co/UbyN9cBkKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cfs_matt thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shharine @lovemmitt what in the world is going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But one of my goals living the entrepreneurial lifestyle is to live a disciplined one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow, day 1 of my life as a FT entrepreneur. Nervous yet excited. Setting my alarm thinking I don't really need to wake up at this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite what happens, always count your blessings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing out @gsuite this morning before it goes live for my staff. 

It is unbelievable how much technology has changed everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeBrownE46 my earache is gone! And I had a beauty of a presentation! Thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty of a meeting this morning with a client in Toronto, time for a nap and then off to Cambridge. Thank you universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeBrownE46 having a mini-stroke and tomorrow I have to do a major presentation. I cannot have this ear ache destroy me. LOL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeBrownE46 thank you. I'm desperate for something right now. I can't even carry on a conversation right now without appearing like I'm ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are plenty of options to make home-ownership accessible. So don't fear, if unsure just ask one of us friendly Realtors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many many many people about how panick stricken they are about the new mortgage rules. It is just miscommunicated/misinterpreted info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want to go on a rant, but those are the main points. If it's unclear, please don't hesitate to connect bc I've heard from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So here is my peice of clarification. 1. Don't be alarmed, 2. The 5% still applies so long as the home below 500k.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That the 5% for first time home buyers isn't applicable anymore and he was unsure how he'd ever in his lifetime own a home....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a conversation with a friend and client today about down payments on a home. He was panicking because a friend of his told him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any of you hear of the olden day traditional remedy of sticking a clove of garlic in the ear for a ear-ache? ..yes, I have garlic in my ear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to know something about everything. Knowledge is power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosh_vr oh nice! Congratulations! Yes I'm still in the KW, moving back to the 416 in a week though. Will miss it here :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosh_vr haha, how is Queens girl, that university is so beautiful, especially that Harry Potter library.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more attractive than a confident person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosh_vr you look so good! So good that I almost want to copy you(I wont),maybe I'll do a lie flat on my belly like a beached whale version.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosh_vr you're twit pic is LIFE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much Rosshanee. That means so much to me. https://t.co/AXB8Hej2M4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOT ALL WOUNDS ARE VISIBLE. 

https://t.co/VYuMsBLcsi

#domesticviolence #domesticabuse https://t.co/5GVL6GjORb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipping Homes: Tips On How To Sell Up https://t.co/MB9eRHXVEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipping Homes: Tips On How To Sell Up | #realestate #Toronto #torontorealestate  https://t.co/uMFUxQIycl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's To The Ladies Who Cuss (Aren't They A Blast?) https://t.co/WidHGUH5B2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why 2016 Wasn’t All Bad: Looking Back At The Breakthroughs For Women In Politics https://t.co/c9Nzrryxnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Easy New Year's Resolutions Every Entrepreneur Should Make || #Entrepreneur #businessintelligence #motivation https://t.co/oHngaKmFYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing In Affordable Housing Will Tame Anti-Globalization Fears: PM https://t.co/nKF2A3zLer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways To Boost Brain Power And Finally Concentrate At Work || #WomeninBusiness #womenempowerment #Focus #s https://t.co/PCdCKGeZ5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto's Supply Of New Homes Hits Record Lows As Prices Soar https://t.co/Bl9UvH5vus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you love and do it with all your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying doesn't take away tomorrow's troubles. It takes away today's peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love and be loved. Unapologetically.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>