<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece in Time: History's famous walls have almost always come tumbling down https://t.co/LNjIyGgmPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Charles warns lessons of WWII may be forgotten https://t.co/MPNtNdpr7v via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Australian scientists use soybean oil to create graphene https://t.co/9MNPHSWEIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hottest places in hell' reserved for those remaining neutral: Former US Ambassador unleashes on Trump https://t.co/Qnzzk2bFjw via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Nobel First: Tagore, not Dylan://lareviewofbooks.org/article/rabindranath-tagore-first-songwriter-nobel/ via @lareviewofbooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dutton: Allow the pregnant refugee on Nauru into Australia for urgent medical treatment https://t.co/K2pvOGjAwM via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump's executive order: Amateur hour at the White House? https://t.co/N9NPNIckRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we have a #nationalstorytellingweek too? C'mon Oz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paper artist's flocks of winged wildlife are cut from vintage maps: https://t.co/3yl0rHyMzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A Plastic Tide" film depicts shocking plastic pollution worldwide: https://t.co/L4rD8yNIzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI watchdog needed to regulate automated decision-making, say experts https://t.co/4lWIY6pGTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump's Vanity Fair Mexico cover draws ire: 'It's a lack of sensitivity' https://t.co/auNiiqRVus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - In pictures: Photographing Australia's tallest trees https://t.co/AhpngBo4GM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Netherlands 'counters' Trump with international abortion fund | SBS News https://t.co/8V47QMqdbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orwellian Newspeak enters the White House. That's worth protesting.
https://t.co/Qp1OJfmbYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait @SimonNRicketts https://t.co/agxjGJb7LL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve reported on Putin – here are my tips for journalists dealing with Trump | Alexey Kovalev https://t.co/SntTQLWfhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Fire of Australia: The return of the world's finest uncut opal https://t.co/G4QHAZf3Ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Project aims to grow a 'city of trees' https://t.co/msXxb7SxTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Why Bill Clinton helped a 33-year-old build a $1bn firm https://t.co/7OPWWKCFPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every baby boomer needs to know this - Meditation rebuilds your brain. https://t.co/5PGC3nAgis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Trump Vows Policy Vision Of  'America First,' Recalling Phrase's Controversial Past https://t.co/pyFR0tg2zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latvia too - how wonderful! https://t.co/BylGhGAeZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Jerry Seinfeld, decades on, still loving my TM meditation! (Although never stopped the morning one!) https://t.co/zmaAdX4kC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real joy in unity ... https://t.co/OW3EYU8GBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Language is the first and last contest of the post-truth era - Eureka Street https://t.co/8zwVXffdPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Assange confirms he is willing to travel to US after Manning decision https://t.co/hPcUks7Hmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a 23-year-old made $1300-an-hour for a fake news masterpiece https://t.co/Hcs6YupQ3E via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Babies remember their birth language - scientists https://t.co/gfbYmbLqBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days before Trump's inauguration, State Dept. sends $500 million to United Nations climate fund https://t.co/ig2MmkmU70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Invisible Influence of Others  https://t.co/LNbFT8Wsof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walter Shaub’s Desperate Attempts to Make Trump Adhere to Government Ethics https://t.co/xuK82qywTO via @RyanLizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapping the Freshwater Ocean Under the Sea @hakaimagazine https://t.co/lVMfUsNS3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Russian journalist wrote an open letter to the media and everyone should read what they have to say https://t.co/yR7UApZfIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A majority of the public support Corbyn’s most controversial idea, poll suggests https://t.co/NOjYcIy9zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preaching to the Converted and the Path to Unlearning: this week’s random conversations https://t.co/gtrj9yH7sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SF library book returned, 100 years overdue https://t.co/czwvw008QR via @SFGate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Melbourne, a Thriving (and Mostly Free) Art Scene https://t.co/JDpdPL7wu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China-US trade war the single biggest economic threat to Australia https://t.co/7eBlLlASIv via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A monument to storytelling - the proposed Lucas Museum looks great. Lucky L.A.
https://t.co/7Zf9aenhqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Clare Hollingworth: British war correspondent dies aged 105 https://t.co/axlG84Ou1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Luther King Day with Trump https://t.co/LUbdEjZJMP via @jelani9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Tighter koala protection rules for Australian loggers https://t.co/Fit7pLBYEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most commonly misused word in English - and what it really means https://t.co/mjPjHyVTeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking In Berlin by Franz Hessel, book review: An epic book https://t.co/wKtDuwIUuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I am a storyteller it's because I listen" Postscript: John Berger, 1926-2017 https://t.co/EafTpJhgIR via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump v Spies: A very public row which could damage both https://t.co/gSsR3nLXZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storytellers make the most influential scientific researchers https://t.co/N3vGH4Ir41 via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Lewis and the Narrative Nonfiction Formula - Los Angeles Review of Books https://t.co/4jTDIDFgKd via @lareviewofbooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WALTER HAMILTON. ‘Fighting Monsters’ | John Menadue – Pearls and Irritations https://t.co/JqI7CS5998 via @EMAILiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Greenland, a once doubtful scientist witnesses climate change's troubling toll https://t.co/P5DfpAZCu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin, the world is closer to banning nuclear weapons https://t.co/9vZE5JUj3f via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singer puts condition on acceptance of Trump inauguration invitation https://t.co/5h20Eus4Wo via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic letter personally delivered from France to National Library https://t.co/Cl6BIfLdub via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - French workers get 'right to disconnect' from emails out of hours https://t.co/o3M3l4VHVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The biggest problem of #marine animals is they are free for the taking." - #Valerie Taylor. @protectcoralsea #GreatBarrierReef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - China announces ban on ivory trade by end of 2017 https://t.co/ogFCNzysQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jibbon beach installation #beach #Bundeena #life https://t.co/do0AgqukOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Baird: How to reclaim the true meaning of Christmas https://t.co/u3ywpaK9L4 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colvinius @michellec_smith And for an armchair traveller there's even more action in the tumultuous events you covered in yr memoir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great holiday reading: Light &amp; Shadow - memoir of a Spy's Son by Mark Colvin @Colvinius #books #spies #history #journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One in five Pacific Islanders would move to Australia under new migration proposal | SBS News https://t.co/cDl4bNoa5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Arctic heatwave could break records https://t.co/FoiMsG9hBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama bans oil drilling in large areas of Atlantic and Arctic oceans https://t.co/gkH0SJ0SLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estonia's citizen army gears up to deter Putin's war machine  https://t.co/HHEUxtsxB7 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's Ban The Bag https://t.co/55ArSDvJOH via @AustMarConsSoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreaming of a frugal Christmas? Meet the people who’ve stopped shopping https://t.co/7drx2YctbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists confirm that warm ocean water is melting the biggest glacier in East Antarctica https://t.co/WbUGmfyk67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indoor Plants Could Work As Cheap Air Filters For Offices https://t.co/SLFCuNPlJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate war on Christmas: Global warming is causing reindeer to shrink https://t.co/oT1VldscWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Mick Fanning enjoys magical surf beneath the Northern Lights https://t.co/OrE7T4kvxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could US Mayors, Governors, and CEOs stop Trump from wrecking our climate?? Find out:  https://t.co/tlfqGsXCjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia leads way in fossil fuel divestment https://t.co/dSnjLcqK7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do Demonstrations Matter" We Are Many Director and Producer Amir Amirani chats with Phyllis Bennis the The Laura... https://t.co/FQZX21D6Bc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now available on iTunes and Amazon - We Are Many is a feature documentary about the worldwide protest which took... https://t.co/gN5v8pOURb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the end of the road for arts, writing, features and music on our ABC Radio National? https://t.co/jQXJmb8L31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was the thinking behind the global protest of Feb 15, 2003 to stop the Iraq war &amp; the story of @WeAreManyMovie https://t.co/vODf08LdWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norfolk mutiny brewing against island's Australian administrator https://t.co/JauCCpkVWa via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How climate change is contributing to violence against women https://t.co/JmmgVEombz via @HuffPostImpact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 lessons activists can learn from Florida’s successful ballot fight to defend solar https://t.co/JvirPQXDha via @grist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news from Standing Rock. https://t.co/GxiSXFoFOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, democracy and the truth about internet search https://t.co/d8JLEapbg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts are dead, long live facts: there's no simple solution for how to dissolve the fog of lies https://t.co/rQwNJbIpyL via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Most Powerful Algorithm in the World” by @cognitivepolicy https://t.co/48knk0DGwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists Hang Tough in Face of Backlash Against Panama Papers Reporting #panamapapers https://t.co/eoJZhWpR2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Putting a fence around it is putting a noose around it': Architects slam Parliament House security upgrade https://t.co/ecwPpW0tlj via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee Protesters Unfurl Banner On Parliament House https://t.co/4CWJuuBOFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel better after being outside? There’s a scientific reason for that. #PromotedPost https://t.co/k3HYDQhLwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rethinking care work key to closing gender pay gap - Eureka Street https://t.co/SIM9wwXnvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/3rd of wild animals gone by 2020!? Here's how we stop the next great extinction. Sign &amp; RT: https://t.co/NCSAMhTGQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antarctic expedition battles barriers for women in science https://t.co/Tbn7lkmCD4 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Brave' NSW Planning Minister breaks ranks on negative gearing https://t.co/FfPU3gezKj via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish broadcaster Alexandra Pascalidou describes online threats of torture and graphic abuse  https://t.co/iU2tQabDPl via @DailyLifeAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - World's poorest countries to aim for 100% green energy https://t.co/hzzCE9mhd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Trump's election, critical climate efforts likely fall to the states https://t.co/h6b2d3tvHR via @Publici]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia cannot have a healthy Great Barrier Reef and an expanding coal industry. Join the campaign: https://t.co/pxMhrhXBeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new role in journalism: the digital fixer https://t.co/xahWw4rumO via @cjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Reading Make You Happier? https://t.co/3cI5yHl7mv via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens could learn a thing or two from larrikin Nationals - Eureka Street https://t.co/rPul2yYcmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aeon Row strives to close the loop on fashion: https://t.co/o2qO0R6jrj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>