<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Devilsmerch hi! Have you got any green tops? In small? Cheers :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffdevils I reaaaaly want to get a green shirt! Any ideas how to get 2 x in small?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ewwww. I didn't follow @realDonaldTrump via POTUS #unfollow https://t.co/qS5wjGRj1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I can't get angry about @jeremycorbyn Corbyn's LGBT blunder - #hearhear he is an ally. Everyone slips up!  https://t.co/ueHiVtu3DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coney Island, baby! The romance of mid-century New York – in pictures @archi_twit :) https://t.co/dU1PRjTCq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CubeSocial hop you guys are well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arghghhhghhhh! - frustrated noise marketers make when launching a new site]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing time watching @cardiffdevils last night. Great result, especially as it was the first time I've watched 'em! https://t.co/pRHeky3S6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynFoot @YayAmyPay i'm partial to a glass or two! I'm loving the Kath Foot appreciation society. #iwillmakebadges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SerenLasCopy @CM_Cardiff you rocked the Lund-esque chiq this morning! I'm gutted I didn't wear mine...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was also going to venture into knitwear too, but didn't want to seem to nerdy. ❤️ Brod! ❤️ https://t.co/u7Kt7lFng6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Brod day! #creativemornings @CM_Cardiff @thedanishbakery #thisiswhywemovedtocardiff https://t.co/nOFK7VYxkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedanishbakery @CM_Cardiff looking forward to Creative Mornings at Brod #danish #sarahlund #creativemornings… https://t.co/kZoiU188Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great new course for @CareercakeTV subscribers! https://t.co/bLIh7PKYO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to watching @Aimee_Bateman of @CareercakeTV talking about her love of video SEO https://t.co/MSM79Jpq1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your blog contributing to E-commerce sales? https://t.co/8fewVGjLPh via @SmartInsights #blog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is this even happening? #InaugurationDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, hey Canton @craftydevilbrew #yum https://t.co/iNWVCpdDBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamaican bobsleigh team involved in unusual recruitment process for next coach https://t.co/FQuFzvxDkc via @RecruitmentGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab speech by @cvthompson #GoDoEntAwards :) https://t.co/fNBnQv8Ed5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hangfirebbq looking forward to eating allllll the meat tonight with @archi_twit #hangfire #bbq #yummm #moonshine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Consumers Are Abandoning their Shopping Carts and the Power of Retargeting https://t.co/nHSonxliRx - love this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 LinkedIn Tips That Helped me Grow My Business - @Aimee_Bateman's blog for budding startups! https://t.co/HXeLsyiSXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teapigs I certainly will! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have an assessment centre day coming up? You need @KathrynFoot's top tips! https://t.co/WirDML7EEV #careers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Reasons Why Customer Surveys Are Still Relevant for Your Business https://t.co/SavFqbZ6EC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 trends Email marketers need to stay on top of in 2017 and a couple of things you can safely ignore… https://t.co/vfSUoUsTIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study of UK comedy panel shows finds just one all-female episode  https://t.co/S1xne5dwX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a #marketing #xmas tomorow with  the fabulous @hollyrwatson @kimberlystartup and Michelle :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 ways NOT to use Google Analytics https://t.co/BFV7HTJQti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT bods... can anyone recommend someone who can help me why my emails are being rejected? #email #itsupport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dealing with job rejection is tough. Here, @Aimee_Bateman shows you how to deal with it gracefully. #jobs #careers https://t.co/6fC5vzYGGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that's all levels of sexy. https://t.co/2IOMnfh8rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We’re now spending more than 28% of our online time on social media with a whopping fifty minutes on Facebook alone every day.' @MelCarson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Quit Social Media. Your Career Will Thank You For It. https://t.co/AvdXWQItqC - great article from @MelCarson #personalbranding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any recommendations to get rid of concussion symptoms? Bored now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eager 89-year-old seeks job: cafe snaps him up #jobs  https://t.co/1bOmHiTFol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Nurtured leads makes 47% larger purchases than non-nurtured leads' @_ANNUITAS -&gt; there's your case for marketing automation @SmartInsights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Analytics + Marketing Automation: How to Get Better Insights About Your Audience https://t.co/kV0eLPP5Oy #marketingautomation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just asked to take part in a customer survey by @adwords ...but it was in Spanish? #huh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook and Twitter audiences are in decline, Instagram and LinkedIn are growing (UK, ONS) @SmartInsights #digital #marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[79 Countries That Have Had Female Leadera #girlpower https://t.co/VGMD1w7eyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is actually amazing. ...Amazon is surprising everyone with its powerful Christmas ad https://t.co/kVCfsDTzFT via @HuffPostUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good tips here: How speed affects your site’s performance [infographic]  https://t.co/GVgs6d8JPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atotaltwit @JessGlynne cheeky bugger! Naw; but come on... £80 a ticket. Missed out on Exeter too :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know where I can get @JessGlynne tickets for Cardiff. Without having to pay 3x face value? #fairpricesplease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You seen this @archi_twit https://t.co/bHM7HhEXJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... Trump appeared in my Google analytics today. #getout #Clintoncomeback #marketingproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Google and Facebook are capturing upwards of 80% of every new dollar spent on digital advertising https://t.co/dI57IYaRMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c56% of the traffic now comes from mobile devices - How Google’s Mobile-Only Index Will Change SEO in 2017 - https://t.co/TXKRn8y9T6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One benefit of Trump winning - Have I Got News for YOu has enough content to go on for another 125 years #hignfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Google look for when it comes to backlinks? https://t.co/CW7F4r9YEj #seo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about the west wing?! https://t.co/uNggOEBTIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brightonseo tickets secured... sweeeeeeeet #brightonseo #seo :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Fuel Your Content Marketing Strategy with AdWords https://t.co/a9IxLwSI5c via @mention #contentmarketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AppleTaxiExeter hi I want to book a taxi for tomorrow AM... but the automated system isn't letting me... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Things That Are Only OK Because You're From Cardiff @archi_twit look at number 5. ;)  https://t.co/NFmSui1Wkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 French Bulldog Puppies Who Are So Cute That You Might Actually Cry @Aimee_Bateman #justsaying  https://t.co/DiXys6bhNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating a Digital Marketing Campaign for an e-commerce Startup: 6 Things You Need to Know https://t.co/50WJLCONZI via @smartinsights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate @CareercakeTV's investment with us! All #careercourses just £9.99 this month #jobsearch #jobhunt… https://t.co/YX83VkiHTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So tried @Kupp_Exeter yesterday - food great; service... not so. #secondchance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The All-New MacBook Pro Has A Tiny Touchscreen #nice https://t.co/PM4H7SlzDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I work for a pretty awesome company :) https://t.co/ZRnDdF31yJ #edtech #startup #wales #tech @CareercakeTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Factoring customer lifetime value into ecommerce marketing planning https://t.co/yvZMp38mES #marketing #ecommerce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, mine is Moving on Up by @MPeopleHeatherS :)   #jobsearch #TuesdayMotivation #Motivation https://t.co/4IJnDfoUAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so shameful. #TuringLaw #turing https://t.co/RzOQqzjYrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aimee_Bateman @TheNextWeb good news the penny has finally dropped &amp; LI are actually developing it so it is useful...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know of where to get @twitter advertising voucher? Interested in trialling... #twitterads #marketing #freestuff #digital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Establish an Instagram Aesthetic: 10 Brands Doing It Right https://t.co/gPiSFVdFOJ - I Heart @squarespace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's Do DIY, Yeah? #BeRomanticIn4Words @archi_twit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #internationalginandtonicday #justsaying https://t.co/vEjoNpqNeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “What's this here 'Moment'?”

https://t.co/H4KtXho9M9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 marketing metrics to master for first-time startup owners https://t.co/Is2bJNiqDo via @ClickZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile dominates traffic but desktop dominates revenue - I'm seeing this a lot. https://t.co/eVMJo3PPfa @SmartInsights #mobile #ecommerce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Secretaries are women, that's how it's always been' – how I call out 'acceptable' sexism  https://t.co/wssRx4lUSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestExeSchool perfect, thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog written, seo plan competed, conversion path analysis in progress... today is s good day #marketing #homeworking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please! @archi_twit :) https://t.co/kJPzc99Tmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestExeSchool hi - what is the best email to send a letter for attention of headteacher? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 in 4 millennials chose to spend money on an experience or event, rather than purchasing a desired object @HarrisCorp @OMD_EMEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 of the Best Product Page Design Examples We've Ever Seen https://t.co/mLYeO5Ld8p via @hubspot @lkolow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn will now let you discreetly signal when you’re jobhunting https://t.co/okfHsuhdkq #whataboutthebusinessthatcantaffordthefeature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was really useful - esp. @LibertyOnlineUK presentation :) https://t.co/m2fZES8pfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #digitalmarketing tips here especially tip #1 making marketing automation at the top of the list https://t.co/GQ1INYUttu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to @_businesswales @google training tomorrow #gettingoutandaboot #digital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really?!? Government bars foreign academics from advising on Brexit  https://t.co/nKOYIudipl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[75% of users have purchased something because they saw it on social #socialmedia  via @ClickZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of this isn't surprising, but it's good to reinforce. What makes people follow or unfollow a brand? https://t.co/jtf0V3WY4h @clickz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Instagram At 6: Kevin Systrom On Moments, Mission, Ads, And Stories https://t.co/RDiYk2nXQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this train atm. Sad news, but the @CrossCountryUK staff have been communicative and professional all the way thr… https://t.co/4GH7JMDF9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloggers are the third most trustworthy source of information, following only friends and family. Accord to https://t.co/3lH5tgTTRa #blog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What @BuzzFeed teaches us about marketing https://t.co/gP5NUDfcjy via @Pure360]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby robot unveiled in #Japan as number of childless couples grows  https://t.co/z5vaEM2CtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's train drama: cancelled trains in southwest, replacement bus and ticket man's bum lodged into my face #trainlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Vogue ditches models in favour of 'real' women – for one issue  https://t.co/4lt50AaESo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bestselfco hey!! So I signed up for the PDF and got nothing :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You there! Any good at learning and dev? Join our great great team https://t.co/TeFQiomwob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely excited about the Severn Tunnel junction opening #trains #nomoregoingtoworkviagloucester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Asos Warehouse Workers Are Paying The True Price Of Your Order :O #waaaa #asos  https://t.co/uXVxsAnjFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool talk going on with @FanDuel co-founder @robuk @VentureCymru today https://t.co/rxYtajHrUh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>