<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@clay_vaughn I wonder if bitches know they're bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a bag of skittles, one lskittle is poisoned, you gonna take the chance and eat one?That's the refugee situation #travelban #Trump45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's always a good day when #Duke loses #GoHeels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So for now on when I don't get my way, is it acceptable to go protest and destroy other people's property?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please explain to me what rights women or minorities don't have in today's society?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either into someone or your not. Don't play like you're in between]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why's everything gotta be so complicated?ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like some people's goal in life is to be as confusing as possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wanted for us to be a thingðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need in feeling bad if you did all you could, and still didnt get what you wanted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it really the holidays without a heated political debate with your cousins? #trump2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If everyone would just say how they truly feel,  the world would be a better place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If its meant to be,  it will be ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really need to learn when to give up and when to shut up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wish I could get out what I put in for once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moee_bg17  no sign of em yetðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just want this to workoutðŸ™ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else remember when we rioted because obama got elected?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My prediction for the election,Trump wins by landslide #TrumpTrain #LockHerUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DrainTheSwamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wolf of Wall Street is one of the greatest movies of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just told @nbcwashington who I think is winning. Cast your vote now! #Debates #NBC4DC https://t.co/4wqX95UWzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This debate is honestly like seeing a man and a child argue #VPDebate  #TrumpPence16 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snapchat if you're gonna have a news section. You should make it unbiased.  Instead of trying to push your political agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@codesforguys it still hurts ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cam what are you doing?!#MINvsCAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't this always happen and then the cop is proved to be in the right by a jury?  #BackTheBlue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't anyone understand that all cops are nice if you simply show them respect and do as they ask. Regardless of color #BackTheBlue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cop was completely right to kill him!  The guy had a gun and there are witnesses to prove it!  #BackTheBlue #blacklivesmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clay_vaughn hell yea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clay_vaughn i got stickers if you want one bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously another polls page?  How originalðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossboy28 dont worry, you got that extra tank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want someone who wants something real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life currently https://t.co/Itxx8Rjthz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was out of work a total of 20 hours and already got another job. And some of yall out of work for months ðŸ‘€ #moneyhungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These refs are trash! #CARvsDEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its always too good to be trueðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump rally's got me excited for this wall! #BuildTheWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer reading project is due monday. And i havent startedðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An idle mind is a dangerous thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@savannahshae22 Coach K = the only reason Duke basketball is anything ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late night thoughts ðŸ’­ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she goes back to her ex once, might as well not even try because she's gonna keep goin back. No matter what shit he pulls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if #PokemonGO is just a new way for the government to track us without is knowing?ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clay_vaughn and he already blames gun control for this. Obama is such a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my eyes killing a cop is like killing a soldier.   And the sad thing is. The left will use this to push for gun control #BlueLivesMatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect our law officials and you they wont harm you. Imagine if someone attacks you at your job? #bluelivesmatter #alllivesmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DlSSED yea because Hillary Clinton is getting handed the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its amazing how people always blame racism for the cops killing someone. Everyone of these criminals have fought back!  #Alllivesmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump2016 our only hope to save us from the disaster that is #HillaryClinton  wether you like it or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I voted for @CameronNewton to win #BestMaleAthlete at the @ESPYS. Visit https://t.co/uHHE9dPB6y for all categories. https://t.co/BfDEEzAXa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#buildthewall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are finally goin right for once ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we're just gonna jump straight to throwing it all away?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is life going?  One minute we're picking our classes for freshman year, the next we're looking at colleges ðŸ˜¶ #life #feels #gettingold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@24HourPolls no because the constitution says the right to bear arms shall not be infringed. Notice these attacks are in "gun free zones"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders please explain to me how Donald Trump has insulted women, african americans, mexicans or muslims??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody wants to act mature anymoreðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossboy28 just not strong enough to break em loose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swear all I ever do is waste my time and money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to graduate, leave all this shit behind and see this town in the rear view for the last time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clay_vaughn all while holding a mexican flag tooðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls should always listen to a guy friend about other guys, most of the time we're right about their motives and what they'll do.Just sayin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBumgardner4 @Hi_im_noah i got a 100 on my auto exam. Thank you very much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never studied for an exam in my life. Never got below a 85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all so busy seeking others approval, We lose who we really are and what we really think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl who lift&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Society never fails to let me down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just so yall know, Mr Poppo is part indianðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its ridiculous how biased @GMA  is towards Trump, they'd never report about Hillary in the same way. Nothing but negative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewObOnline so they come to our country illegally, destroy our stuff and take our jobs, then hold signs up about how they're welcome here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, family and good friends are all that matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like letting it all out at the gymðŸ’ªðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of running a marathon for someone who wouldn't walk across the street for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genophilia holy shitðŸ˜‚ @rossboy28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just pray it all works out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays we got a criminal taking the place of our founding father on the $20 solely because she's black #HarrietTubman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly hate how society's become]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not about to fall for this shit again. Wasted enough time already #fuckthefriendzone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people ain't even out of high school and you can already tell they'll go nowhere in life ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly am considering deleting #Snapchat on account of their filters and live stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people post shit thinking other people care. And now thanks to snapchat. We get to see all of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is great. Beer is good. Women are crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lowkey want a street bike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna go 4x4 at the #uwharries #fullsizeoffroad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did i stay with her so long. I can do SO much betterðŸ˜‚ #wth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You made it where its not my problem anymore. So i sit back and watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back at the past only takes your eyes off the futureðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Carolinas are easily the center for sports right now. 3 teams in championships in one year?  Can we get a 4th?#GoHeels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duke fans gonna hate. When they didn't even make the final four ðŸ˜‚.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did all i could and it still wasn't enough. Oh well. Guess it wasn't meant to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm picking UNC to take the #NationalChampionship! #HeelsLockIn @MarchMadness https://t.co/WV5BiLnOpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Havent missed this place one bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna know how it feels to throw away someone who'd give it all. Even when given so little in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: #Schlongbed
Dad: Thats gross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you really matter. Then you don't always have to be the one to text first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always treated like shit. Always taken for granted. Always too stupid to let go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm picking UNC to move on from the #FinalFour! #HeelsLockIn @MarchMadness https://t.co/4pAbwcF5CQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>