<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to @IRA_INAF tomorrow where I will attempt to answer the question of can I finish another paper this week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great visit to @RUastro this week, lots of interesting astrophysics discussions &amp; good science. Many thanks @Astro_Jamie for the invite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got no words. I hope the EU takes appropriate action. https://t.co/if97WQxBTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you come from the antipodes you don't often see your name associated with an institution that dates to 1088 :) https://t.co/I5TeScHh4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeronikaMeduna @drsciman, @VicUniWgtn Engineering also has 3D printing, but the ones in the design school are v. high quality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matisidro thanks. I think this one on the same topic, given two weeks later also in Christchurch, is better: https://t.co/9vHsfxDR67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stingay @realscientists Well, the overall funding rates are still low, though it is true my group did exceptionally well in 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein @novp - this was SCPS too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein @novp there are such people closer than you think. The bring your sick kids to work to infect my kids episode was interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @theartofnight love your image in day 8 of the Wellington Advent Calendar - absolutely stunning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have arrived at Berkeley, have my desk for the week, have my talk mostly written. Now to get through this massive amount of work...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigData2017IAS @piccolomud to many women has helped for other fields. Best of luck to improve in the future. 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigData2017IAS @piccolomud male-dominated field you often get invitations with too little notice, or you get too many. Invite early &amp;...2/n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigData2017IAS @piccolomud Perhaps next time you could try more women, earlier for both the org. comm. and speakers. As a woman in a ...1/n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigData2017IAS @piccolomud 27 speakers and all men, I'm pretty sure that's statistically very unlikely to be representative of researchers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje Indeed you are! So all topics on the table? Cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje *you're* - I really need type better lest autocorrect make me illiterate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje guess it depends on why your talking to them :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje given the lack of postdoc funding in NZ, few of these ppl will get permanent jobs in unis, but that this isn't their only option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in Christchurch has been so nice, the weather is great, the public art &amp; gardens fantastic and they do a mean coffee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje that not all research careers need universities? U can do meaningful stuff outside the feudal uni structure &amp; some of them will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NJRattenbury @astro_jje @REasther Thanks for coming! It did indeed go well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh yes, have encountered many people in denial recently; it's incredibly frustrating. Publishing data would help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh Thanks for posting this, but what are we going to do about it? I'm sick to death of this, it is soul destroying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very nice paper by @cjriseley, all aspects of the work are done well. https://t.co/MjY7hUNhnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje @MarsdenFund and Pauline Harris has an astro related social science project on Maori calendars 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje @MarsdenFund There are actually 3 traditional astro projects. Cathie Zheng, my postdoc, got a fast start which I'm on also. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein @MarsdenFund Thanks :) Also Cathie Zheng, my postdoc, got a fast start which I'm on also, for a related project, which is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein ok, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein do you know if the Science Dean is around atm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein they are embargoed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theartofnight glad you liked the talk. FWIW I love your images of the sky at night :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @TEDxChCh what a great day! https://t.co/Jy1jX6Pu4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me talking about MWA, SKA and radio astronomy with @JMulliganRNZ ahead of today's @TEDxChCh https://t.co/JsiebhmmTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you there :) https://t.co/TAS4OVJnIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone involved in hiring/promotion pls read this: https://t.co/L3YRRekHYK @CEWAus's how to avoid gender &amp; other bias in meritocracies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NJRattenbury Well I hope @RayPNorris said something good :) I really wanted to be at IAU 325 but couldn't due to prep for @TEDxChCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrPaulHancock @Cosmic_Horizons So I think it very much depends on what the talk is for as to if there should be a speaking fee 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrPaulHancock @Cosmic_Horizons While science promotion is v. important, if ppl are making $ off your talk, I think you should be paid. 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrPaulHancock @Cosmic_Horizons the vast majority of my public talks were unpaid, but I have been paid in the past too. 1/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_Pratley giving my talk at CALIM on CLEANing polarisation data properly: see our paper: https://t.co/CuGaKCakst https://t.co/a40miIHX2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_Pratley's paper on testing image reconstruction algorithms motivated by compressive sensing on real data. https://t.co/ArBgipjwhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein Ah! Congrats! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendonbrewer you can't answer that correctly without more context; with the information at hand, both options could be correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein Yeah, I saw that, it's pretty accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stingay @SKA_telescope yep. Also should update the values for MWA and add HERA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stingay @SKA_telescope good point, should have a footnote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKA_telescope Were the areas of the circles supposed to be proportional to collecting area? If so, FAST needs to be much bigger...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein No worries, it would have been a shame to waste such a good cake :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made a storify record of #RonFest  : https://t.co/yYIYKERO2S I can add photos, video etc to it from all public social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroJoeC You've been quoted in my #Storify story "RonFest" https://t.co/yYIYKEAdbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pleasure. Happy Birthday Ron! https://t.co/DhT5yJX9m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroJoeC That's a cool photo. I have no photos of Ron and I, so I'm pinching this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elenchically It was a good meeting, thanks for coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKA_telescope session today at #RonFest in Queenstown with presentations from Richard Schilizzi, @SKA_Australia and @SKA_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd put my hand in the fire, for Ron" - Mark Walker quoting an anonymous CSIRO staff member #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroJoeC "The spectral revolution has occurred!" #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timcornwell says Ron's management genius was mandating free coffee and Mexican food 3 days a week! #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timcornwell says the VLA was a happy innovative place in the 80's largely due to Ron #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eggs on Legs! Douglas Bock reminds us of Luneburg Lens as originally considered for SKA #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Douglas Bock now discussing Ron's impact and changes at ATNF - huge impact! #RonFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cosmicpudding @ron_ekers Yes, that is a surprise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZScienceLearn @MaisonValentino Very, cool :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@REasther @VeronikaMeduna pity about the bit where they feel the need to mention her personal life so people can judge her choices :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is cool! https://t.co/0ryPXaEOBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, for inviting me to join your cult and allow me the opportunity to be subject to your will. Think I'll pass. #CollaborationFail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JossBlandHawtho Cherokee peace flag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @mwatelescope is a finalist for the #Eureka16 Prize for Excellence in International Scientific Collaboration https://t.co/vFWGPQW30Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoshMccool Yep. Of course NDAs are not just used in SH settlements, other settled discrimination issues often have NDAs applied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SciBry shame because you don't know these words or you do? I got 9/10 - still an Aussie :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff Wow! That is an awesome example!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh @hendysh Ok. The article should say that. Plus, still not convinced 'AU looks to UK' is a fair statement from those data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh AU equidist to UK and Japan/China. @AucklandUni seems to look to US to me. Not clear what NZ overall does since only Auck. on plot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh precisely the comment I just left on the blog. Only 7/40 AU unis included in those data. AU seems closer to Canada than UK. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hendysh @AucklandUni I'm not actually seeing any evidence to back that statement up in the linked article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One exam to set and then I'm done with teaching. This makes me very happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear of the passing of Bruce. His 70-year career in radio astronomy was remarkable. He will be missed. https://t.co/Er0FH9orIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@franco_vazza congratulations to both you and Annalisa for your ERC grants!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the airport after the amazingly good #BruceSlee meeting. Have been told the bar is high for #RonFest, but I think we can make it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piccolomud @brendonbrewer they are huge, but not bigger then having to pack 4 different ones. No issues re fit - mine not an input overlay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendonbrewer @piccolomud get an all purpose one. I have one and it's awesome - I never have to think about this anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@REasther What?! You don't want to demonstrate your immense contribution to the field of Nanotechnology?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@REasther ha! me too - and pretty much exactly at the same time (got mine 50min ago).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah sexism is alive and well in NZ. Apparently a woman with some stats is "combative", "divisive" and a source of fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah hmm... other theme on twitter tonight is how overloaded academics are. When should we get out and engage? Can't really sleep less!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why postdocs think work conditions improve with a permanent job. They don't for many people. https://t.co/m0AXTolcqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein sorry, to* (hate appearing illiterate)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_onlein No, not at all. It's only cheesy when the Editor forces you too (which recently happened to me).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff @taraxmurphy @lisaharveysmith Board were not asked about the locations. We were informed after 1st announcements were out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroJoeC @lindaunobel Good to know the AAS weren't the issue. Overall, what is the gender balance of the delegates like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroJoeC @lindaunobel Joe, mate, please tell me the Australian delegation has some women...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff They haven't been on enough telecons... might be that they can't hear, I look then. Actually you are hard to hear on this one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matisidro never picked you as an Aussie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greece might be my new favourite country! Swam in the sea, drank lots of raki, met interesting ppl, ate divine food... awesome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to a new country today: Greece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RKPriestley @m_onlein I track my hours. So I can answer that numerically. So far this year on a 'good' week it's 67hrs, last week was 81.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff @ausnetman also apparently too full /tired to spell! *your. Must go write a schedule file and have a nap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff @ausnetman absolutely! You're karma is all balanced. Also same problem: too much to juggle, brain is full.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomimcgriff @ausnetman thanks to this tweet you've reminded me I have to observe on Monday which I had totally forgotten!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matisidro @PolarMediaUK @SKA_telescope Great photo of Maria!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>