<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad this is going ahead.
https://t.co/ceMcyYd6BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates Sorry to hear what has happened. You did the absolute right thing and stood up to tyranny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yonatanzunger thank you for your amazing article. A scary but v compelling synopsis https://t.co/aosHYXqMwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to show some love to @SallyQYates for her courage in standing up to Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing job! You showed great courage and are an inspiration to us all! #Resist https://t.co/dFvhNhWwBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very proud to see this published. What clever brother I have. X https://t.co/NQt6iIDn3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for 2nd session to start #MakeItAPAC https://t.co/lmWQSaGzLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaslittle great presentation! Love your work. #MakeItAPAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meadea yes very! Woke up to seeing charges dropped but then read they were charged prior. Just want them to be able to leave asap. 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meadea just heard. Sitting tight and hoping they don't change their mind again so my brother Linton can come home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So relieved my brother can come home now!!! https://t.co/xpkfeOQGXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HalinaLee1228 No they are free to leave and will not be charged!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Prince3EG What a beautiful thing to see this today in Sydney!!! I will climb hell and high-water to catch you live here. YAY!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely love Palm Springs architecture and this home was beautifully designed by the famous mid-century... http://t.co/HbopLR6qaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely awesome speech #DylanAlcott #TEDxSydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to #TEDxSydney this week! Who else is going??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexisWilson Hi! I'm going and can't wait! First time ever. What about you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argh. Mail server down and can't receive email. Tech support off-shore and not available. Happy Friday to me. : /]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Thanks Tris, there's a local outage. : /]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Hi got really really bad reception this afternoon in Sydney. What's going on please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Art Series: Emily Besser - (my amazingly talented SIL!) http://t.co/F2GHOp3yPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FastWebHoster  Lost emails, server hanging and nobody stopping the problem, I have been online talking to technical support every week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FastWebHoster I have been with Ehostpros for 10 years and when they changed to Fastwebhost is when ALL my problems began.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have had several new clients email me today (on a Saturday??) regarding new projects. Both are large companies... http://t.co/M5QU065Gmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great free photo. Check out http://t.co/a4QgX9SU7Q #photography via @PexelsPhotos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free photos that don't suck! http://t.co/F2xKPReY5c #photography via @PexelsPhotos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to be nominated as a volunteer designer for the Children's Cancer Centre Foundation. They do such... http://t.co/muu8Wh2Slo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus via WiFi thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Hi, my internet is ridiculously slow. Can you help please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXTEL_Help Hi, can someone help me with watching movies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Can someone help me with my email please? It's been hacked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Hi, My email has been hacked. Can someone help me please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare Hi, I'm having issues with Indesign 2014...seems to have issues with some features??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@37signals Hi I'm having issues with my account. Can someone help me asap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice monthly alcohol catalogue now added to the mix! Cheers! http://t.co/SH3Z8cyXT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SugarSync I'm having numerous/endless problems since I upgraded and support is taking forever to get back to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MackandGeorgeUK Hi sorry my email addie was incorrect: studio@dzgraphicdesign.com. Look forward to hearing more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Fissenden Hi Kate, I'd be happy to help you! studio@dzgraphicdesign.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MackandGeorgeUK Hi! I'd be happy to assist you with whatever you require. studio@dzgraphiccesign.com : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great tool for sourcing inspiration and imagery for projects:
https://t.co/nhjxv3zqMk http://t.co/aSJWtGKHCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leighlo Ah but only with great patience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't been here a while! WHATSUP???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gunshotdigital Awww thanks! So sorry for late response!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful gallery wall.  Designed by Urban Grace Interiors: http://t.co/JXt6dKj5Af http://t.co/TPO1T6Qyc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! This is an amazing sculpture:
http://t.co/fSxGxgV3jq http://t.co/3bYkTIcQzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great end to a fab week after winning 3 big jobs! Rebranding 2 mining companies and a high end apartment complex... http://t.co/GErMmNQMUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@37signals Hi, the delays still seem to be occuring as I'm not receiving notifications?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous resource for inspiration
http://t.co/S69WfE2wna http://t.co/FRptM4vKXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus just called customer service and got disconnected! UGH!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Hi Esther I'm at home using cable modem. No internet since 20min ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting waiting. #nointernet #optusfail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus hi Esther thanks. So it's across internet AND mobile?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus hey what about postpaid internet? I have no service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus hi my internet is postpaid not prepaid. What's going on? I have zero connection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus hey I have no internet and your customer number hangs up on me! What's going on???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp Hi, if I order today Sydney time express delivery will I get it tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% proven method to achieve success http://t.co/jfkCSLXRo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigcartel Hi, how do I add a page to the TOP nav bar not the bottom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save @JimmyBrings! PLEASE sign the petition against new alcohol laws that will affect their biz: http://t.co/aBMIaGMLjJ]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to work and ready for the year ahead. Looking forward to what lies ahead biz-wise and am excited to welcome... http://t.co/NVDQ9jhbww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@37signals Thanks I just did. How long will it take to get a reply please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@37signals I only have 1 credit card &amp; due to Christmas etc I forgot my acc was overdue. I tried to pay it now but it won't accept my card!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BehanceSupport Hi my site is down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE this. Santa's brand book:

http://t.co/lM39waOzmt http://t.co/KntYGOqSBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous day #happyfriday http://t.co/cImHaZUMwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous day #happyfriday http://t.co/1y1T44CMWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always on the lookout for inspiration when it comes to biz cards. Love the ideas here:... http://t.co/MOPHuxaaYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen Tequila in a bullet? Me either but I'll be photographing this next week and will try not to... http://t.co/f3jWlarIkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital takeover for Research Now on B&amp;T's home page today:
http://t.co/LoIQTG6dUR http://t.co/SC7Kpq8EWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirsty_gilfo Yep. It's set up so the more ppl tweet the more it unlocks stuff on the interactive map. SIGH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirsty_gilfo YES. And it is taking F O R E V E R  to unlock the damn thing. All just for a vid. : D  #TAKEBACKTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirsty_gilfo Sorry for the spam! I'm trying unlock Justin's new video and have to tweet to do so. Hehehe. I've given up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtimberlake Nothing's happening even after about 20 tweets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet #TAKEBACKTN to reveal exclusive content &amp; @jtimberlake's new video for 'Take Back The Night' http://t.co/n5gWhYGFNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet #TAKEBACKTN to reveal exclusive content &amp; @jtimberlake's new video for 'Take Back The Night' http://t.co/sWqdeHCQQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet #TAKEBACKTN to reveal exclusive content &amp; @jtimberlake's new video for 'Take Back The Night' http://t.co/4a0GBFqMqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet #TAKEBACKTN to reveal exclusive content &amp; @jtimberlake's new video for 'Take Back The Night' http://t.co/wo3R18FckH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@37signals Hi, I don't seem to be getting notifications from projects in my email client? They suddenly stopped working last week...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a site tour at the airport and great to see my artwork on these ticket machines! http://t.co/WFMHqGoe9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on a fab new campaign for
http://t.co/73TkgwGbE3 http://t.co/gwLkutISBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to have an ad in the NY Post and NY Observer this week! http://t.co/0qRuuGZh5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to have an ad in the NY Post &amp; NY Observer this week! http://t.co/bjzphdbUoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really cool idea:
http://t.co/RBkuC81jUr http://t.co/EavgHOg757]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited that I now have another real estate client in the US in Venice Beach California!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing my clever brother @lb_online today @SydWritersFest Press Freedom and the Public’s Right to Know #swf2013 http://t.co/0cI9K2y1k9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you can purchase effects through Photoshop! Now that's awesome.... http://t.co/mSiXjub38t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is an awesome idea:... http://t.co/1n6TNpMnhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! WHAT a week its been, rushed but great. #wineoclock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this photographers work.
http://t.co/ombd43CCR3 http://t.co/k0wywNjHjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this and that all new tools are immediately available to subscribers like me!... http://t.co/IYQFapKasn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday and here's a funny Star Wars infographic:
http://t.co/fADyHZPfO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday and here's funny Star Wars infographic:... http://t.co/5V7ACRgEvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_LaCasa Hi! Is it too late to make a booking for this eve @7pm for 9ppl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASOS_HeretoHelp Hi, are you guys around now? Have a prob with an item...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gunshotdigital Hi thank you! : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK so I've now officially gone international. First a client in NY and this morning a phone meeting with a new ad... http://t.co/t0rKOKoZlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press Freedom In Australia discussion #walkleys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening now to a VIP conversation re freedom of speech in Australia. #walkleys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a massive week and am stoked to be commissioned to design a banner for outside a huge building in Times... http://t.co/ijNdZmTQJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just voted for the Best Startup Pitch in the @SydneyGA #pitchavc competition. Vote now for EVENTYAK PLEASE! http://t.co/bTYkgb6g7S]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>