<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mainmanNas I'm holding you to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a journey, to live is to worry
To love is to lose your damn mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a nice girl in my life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed the leaseðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FilthyFrank the fact that the new album is on iTunesðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad I got out of that mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenickcolletti are you the viner of the month?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I already told you, but happy birthday @_Preston_16 ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anytime you're pissed off just blast metal music and go lift... it works wonders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought another guitarðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did I fall for it again?ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrison_r47 @RealTenaciousD all of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have no past to those we haven't met."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't have the time or energy to put into these girls that want to play games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kara_Pirko this is great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinko30 haha yeah I remember when you first showed me it you couldn't stop laughing ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you raise your kids with the "everyone is a winner" mentality they can't function if they don't get what they want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can whine on twitter and do your little marches but DO NOT burn our flag! Too many men and women have stood and died for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRhinehart20 and plus neither him nor his goals are setting out to harm women, the LGBT community, minorities, or anyone for that matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRhinehart20 there's checks and balances to stop whatever evil you have yourselves convinced he will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRhinehart20 bunch of crybabies today... suck it up I don't know why everyone is so scared all of a sudden you had an idea he could win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people that are shaming the men and women that voted for Trump are doing exactly what they're apparently "fighting" against #hypocrites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We did it! Congratulations @realDonaldTrump let's #MakeAmericaGreatAgain ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyreyynolds that quote has been proven fake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Train isn't stopping at Ohio let's keep it going and #MakeAmericaGreatAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killary has ads on tinder now... she's really pushing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for the #HillaryIndictment hopefully all her supporters will wake up and see the corruption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I can't sleep..I can't tell if it's cause I'm so pissed or still anxious from the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton is so corrupt it's unreal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found out @TheOfficialA7X just released a new album today and I can't handle myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killary needs to keep her ads out of the Tribe game commercials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what happens when you let your guard down...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One down, three to go! #WorldSeries #RallyTogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a fucking maze just to get to hot heads on campus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to the World Series!!!!#RallyTogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homework or Gears of WarðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FedericoAxel8 @_Preston_16 oh shit sorry I don't want to mess with anyone that drives a scooter, they're too badassðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FedericoAxel8 @_Preston_16 says the guy that drives a FiatðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FedericoAxel8 @_Preston_16 @classifiedfact illegal or not, you still have no balls Fed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@channell_3 haha true! Same with youðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I so stressed all the time?ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what I'm talking about!!#RallyTogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When they go low, you go high"
*immediately starts insulting Trump*
#Debates #MAGA #hillaryforprison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the world's greatest Air Force @ImKovie ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @HillaryClinton too many people feel they deserve everything handed to them... you have to work for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @HillaryClinton college already is affordable you just have to work hard, get scholarships, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't realize I still had that much stuff left on my phone to delete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yeah! https://t.co/HTNQRYtdZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well at least if Hillary wins, then us "unprepared/uneducated" Trump voters can get that free college education lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump killed it and the Indians are the AL Central champs... what a good night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta put the guard back up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carly_Pirko thank you Carly!ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the Air Force!ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd surfing at avengedðŸ„ðŸ¼ https://t.co/XeQqR7G7Z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things do get better, trust me I've been thereðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still unsure about this protein shake/coffee mix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're forced to spend over $100 for a folded piece of paper with a code on it for class https://t.co/ZlMBdEblH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRhinehart20 just another example of the media twisting everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpHasAPlan They cut out a big part of this video which is just making more people misinformed https://t.co/YmH9UoeW93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kara is officially my new barber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your ex keeps trying to talk to you but you've moved on https://t.co/Rno3NIkhIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tryna live my life over here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wish I was at the fair right now for the @realDonaldTrumpðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ADTR's new album though https://t.co/7cFwy0munQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey thereðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my professors actually think I'm going to study 2-4 hours outside of class for every hour I'm in class they're crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mainmanNas you need that if it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason I know I'm a Rhinehart is because I love alcohol and hoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sure get a lot of bs phone calls and messages from someone who said they don't want to talk anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already volunteering for deploymentsðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should have just left it on read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed and I are definitely Belleria's best drunk pizza chefs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never washing this shirt lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now your true colors show...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick and tired of being labeled something I'm not..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad the cat is sickðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kind of dark that haunts a hundred year old house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going fishing for something bigger today #PokemonGO https://t.co/g3CYJufhHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the Air Forceâ¤ï¸ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @cavs will win it for Cleveland! #ALLin216 https://t.co/5TRjyL9JeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STRUBzzz I'm not sure yet I'm debating between 2 of them so we'll see hopefully by tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully getting my motorcycle tomorrowðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell yes! https://t.co/wSBTcZ6mkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to make things right as a better man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open house todayâœŒðŸ»ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just need one chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't help falling in love with youðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas seeing you in thatðŸ’“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas @OITNB wait... It didn't come out on the 4th???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please watch this https://t.co/YMXtT89MaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to songs from the CD Tessa made for me always makes me feel like everything is going to be okayðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas yeah I'm pretty sure you love her more than me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas @TheAnimalVines yeah it is!ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only at my job can you witness people argue over who has less money...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas @CauseWereComedy I'd throw it back at them if they out one on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas @CauseWereComedy I would make sure there was no cherryðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas @LifeWithAlcohol that would have been great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_tessathomas oh my gosh delete this you redneck]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>