<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Or orange is the new alternative facts. https://t.co/EEZHgr9Zvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh LOL LOL LOf..nLOL https://t.co/VybjnlKq00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia deserves an Australian Head of State - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/N3GkZs0HW9 via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ScottMorrisonMP we support a Google tax. Don't let big business water it down. https://t.co/eD16HA232F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Turnbull Government's debt-letter threats has to stop now https://t.co/HkNrEUkIW3 via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Making sure your voice is heard in Canberra https://t.co/mZ3xEQfrHd via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pass the popcorn. https://t.co/BPJbyqDNGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's now Guthrie's I mean Rupert's ABC, https://t.co/sn9tQU8sU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously not a good idea to use @rupertmurdoch paper for your private bits, even if you get ist for free, because… https://t.co/s5u6BkfLdz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@interUNFAO @ChristineEwing7 @ABCthedrum @philipruddockmp Well put!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to C Kenny poorly thought out opinionating does not equal good journalism. This is Crap. Go to school and do s… https://t.co/noImXUAlKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathywilcox1 How about something on Adani $s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One should never take @mirandadevine seriously. She's a RW sloppy hack with no journalistic skills to bless herself… https://t.co/1JbAD1UCcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this fool ever draw breath? https://t.co/5zSrgmPwlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition of the really really stupid. https://t.co/723uFhK7vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and a Picture tells a Thousand words https://t.co/E9YgVqB1tS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just another 'man' thing. https://t.co/gowZEt2wwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't hold my breath waiting for MSM to start that. https://t.co/kWqaW7w957]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shop: Gifts That Give Back to Our Oceans https://t.co/oH5scfhmjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A further spoliation of Indigenous people's for the almighty $. Shameful poverty porn. https://t.co/Px2XeJutKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nielsentaya @MeckeringBoy @Qldaah @smh @TurnbullMalcolm Just another tanty from little lord fontelroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause Dutton and me other mates don't like it. https://t.co/ncz4WudNNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All part of the "kill Bill" strategy. Ain't working though. https://t.co/6mJchQqCuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But has he read it? Can he read? Can he comprehend? Seems not. https://t.co/ZISTMHSAdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is getting f....n scary https://t.co/w4amaga3Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeckeringBoy @TheKennyDevine Oh, thanks for that. Something about Murdoch rings a bell. Don't read that rag coz its toxic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! https://t.co/uli2tbW4ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKennyDevine @MeckeringBoy who the hell is grace collier anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She thinks whining is the Australian way. She's wrong! https://t.co/tABIUt9wbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All it needs is "Blame Me!" On it https://t.co/n0M3vSWtaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham stand up fight back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banking and Finance Royal Commission might fix that! https://t.co/i4Am8O3vFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably difficult for a pustule to look in the mirror. https://t.co/WzMAPYGobR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's won't give him a ring of confidence however https://t.co/J2sSE4fqfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note he is pointing all fingers back at self. Liar, liar! https://t.co/IdgQ5zC3fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Fly High Tyrone you will live on in all of us, we will never forget your name! https://t.co/qg9H86LFeY via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Contact: when Indigenous Australia becomes entertainment, everyone loses https://t.co/2flqWzqE2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another LNP Ring Of Steel https://t.co/3NApaOb2fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Minister Susan Ley: Keep pap smears and pathology services free! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/dyjTZzovW0 via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is line ball which between Barnaby and Scumo will explode first. What are the odds? https://t.co/4yL5y1kCmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like an angry boil that needs lancing. https://t.co/CTaBSbXg6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems he has his substances confused. Or maybe his sniffing confused him? https://t.co/apZ0pgyICF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the other is TOXIX. https://t.co/sTdhw1rOai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe that pesky liver is playing up? https://t.co/nm5ATY0YhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LottoLand hey! This Saturday's numbers. https://t.co/TQInUXJN58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pigs flying she will! https://t.co/H74fuKVZJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicare was NO LIE! https://t.co/v1ZxBi7eh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government by the people, of the people and for the people now of the elite, by the elite for the elite. https://t.co/AZcplpvMpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the “People’s House” will be out of bounds for the people. FACISM&gt; https://t.co/GaBnrmHzHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another prime example of the stupidity that calls itself government in Australia. Grow Up Fool! https://t.co/f3kMN792Tt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where she will interrupt, interrupt and interrupt on every question as per the script. https://t.co/35HMOVSbUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMcKim @earthma23 George does not know what Appropriate Behaviour is. It's alien to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have thunk it? https://t.co/hWu1TK0Vxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What moral compass? https://t.co/7nCm2T1Idg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If these are the elite it shows how very very far we have sunk as a nation. https://t.co/4OcPNMEspc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - Tyrone shouldn’t be dead, bullying must stop: https://t.co/ZhZAR0WlgP via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree! https://t.co/W2g9faNaVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More like exposing the LIE that she was ever on the side of battlers. https://t.co/3TuG5nBsGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wonder what that nutjob thinks or says because its all hate, hate, and hate. https://t.co/OGOdZarP1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe just turn them OFF period! https://t.co/3mByTlKHVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[again and again and again. What is the use of question time when you Never get an answer? https://t.co/vtbAUOBVPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenCiobo  is a bully boy thug as well remembered ‘slit her throat’. https://t.co/gtYNhRXf9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and it will be “Labor’s fault!” https://t.co/fr2uuRATCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bkjabour @grogsgamut There has been nothing civil about debate in this place for many years and its getting worse e.g. Barnaby redface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeckeringBoy @1petermartin @smh @theage but hey never let facts get in the way of union bashing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryFallon2 @banas51 @lyndeldarling she hasn't read any history so far so I would say that's a No from her. Besides reading and PH ..NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vjmahon @vanbadham we can now see how well that is working for them eh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Doug Cameron for calling out these anti worker trash bags for what they are. https://t.co/a4EA7LfwHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing and hoping. https://t.co/5Ek1hnEzig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham and every time a worker is killed or injured on a building site these names need to be published with each report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara @ernmalleyscat I suppose it is good to have another option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[X has shown his true colours on this ABCC bill. A pox on him and his cronies. https://t.co/nOmtOMIOOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You bet we will and then some! These crooks delight in screwing ordinary Australian workers and union members. https://t.co/FUwz9qdE4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[X and his cronies are elites. https://t.co/e5QQU1o2Dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well let there be a pox descend on all of those senators. Start counting Building &amp; Construction deaths. https://t.co/8L7MTxo2Xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is actually a Liar https://t.co/3xtySxFaDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure Gina would be watching on smiling. https://t.co/nm8QMwkjaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just write "Hillsong"! https://t.co/EBHCZRJPVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz and his face is always red.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MT Has no compassion full stop https://t.co/Py4dsB7YWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LennaLeprena @YouTube lately Tuesdays are not much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myofoz @LennaLeprena my wife and I had an apartment at the beach in Danang (1 bdrm FF w cleaning x3 perwk) $450 pm. .Much Melb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long? Long? Shortest parliamentary sitting year in history me thinks. He's just nuts. https://t.co/CTjMaA87hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really is re fowlment! https://t.co/gO7fUjgeG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like you can take the jackass to the well. But as it has dried up from climate change it will drink the mud anyway. https://t.co/xLpVDXAK9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull has been nimble and agile in Not Governing. https://t.co/LpRYKZUUkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe she's just growing old disgracefully like the rest of the current LNPIPA bunch https://t.co/mRhFq1fKaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still resonates today Van and will continue until mysogenists are brought to account for their brutality.
Women sti… https://t.co/sX9IuvMAmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull: Prime Minister Turnbull must sack Minister Dutton - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/uJLDhgoRrK via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lanesainty @interUNFAO @mirandadevine Well @mirandadevine is a serial alleger, but nvm a factual warrior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As nationalism is weaponised, Australia desperately needs to embrace inclusive patriotism https://t.co/bxEkDA8n6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition update - A slow-motion train wreck https://t.co/sZOVEIRWPh via @UKChange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And taxpayers pay for her to play. https://t.co/Y1HPO5j6L7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our taxes at work to tell us more lies. https://t.co/iVzLPr7kI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LesStonehouse the cows thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw come on, cows have integrity and far more intelligent than PH. https://t.co/sCcw2kdvAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mavsmum @apgf2009 @davrosz Please x plain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Poor Nikki' should spend her time more productively like watching the grass grow or paint drying https://t.co/SpduuTK2X9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So let's all call out racism by shouting out #Iampoliticallycorect https://t.co/PMACLFDjzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@upbeatme @apgf2009 @davrosz was that to go with the dicshunarie?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>