<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like a daylight diamond heist except the guys in balaclavas were given the keys to the safe https://t.co/96Gliwses2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollyrwalker @ninetonoon @radionz I enjoyed your selection, Holly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In today's @SundaymagSST column in @SundayStarTimes, when a salad spinner is the best thing about your week, PANIC https://t.co/2Hj0ZeAeA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She parents, solo, with style &amp; grace, &amp; now she has a #YourWeekend column! Nice one Amie Richardson â¤ï¸ https://t.co/BF2QFIVeHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusieFergusonNZ @nytimes Mine too, Susie. And any of her little mates; I'll make sure they feel it too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemWilder @DearMama_ Gah! Wednesday! Not Tuesday! (Thank you - I've tweeted the deets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longlostleah @DearMama_  Gah! Next Wednesday 1 Feb. Here are the deets! https://t.co/HuZLnLXOd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psst! Break out of the baby bunker Tues night, Wellington, to hear @DearMama_ read from her fabby new book, plus Q&amp;A. This is yuge! Bigly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganjwhelan @radionz Hugely enjoyed your earlier interview with 'Train Wreck' author @sadydoyle! Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebrittmann Oh, Britt! Loved our cuppa â˜•ï¸ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In today's @SundaymagSST in @SundayStarTimes, why my summer doesn't look like Nadia Lim's, and other grumbles https://t.co/qmFzVMqmGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DisClothesline @WMNewZealand It really was!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneOLO sign of the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Civic Square hoedown! #wmwelly #wmw #wm_global https://t.co/6cqY4l19IY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On way! https://t.co/y33TE3oJQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald can dance. We're gonna march! #wmwelly #wm_global #wmw https://t.co/mlRJBoYjbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready to be live streamed to Washington. Foreboding sky is my thumb. #wmwelly #globalwomensmarch https://t.co/nYa0KtDERw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneOLO This is a fun crowd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drying in the sun ready for this morning's #wmwelly! #wmNewZealand #womensmarchglobal @WMNewZealand #WMW https://t.co/hxjsYED8UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm marching in solidarity tmrw in Wellington. Any other Nasty Ladies wanna join? (I hear there are tortillas at the end! ) #WMWelly #WMW ðŸ‘ŸðŸŒ®]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRhodesPianist Amy Liptrot's memoir The Outrun. Sublime nature writing, as well as achingly sad. You'll want to see Orkney afterwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kate_DowlingNZ @SundayStarTimes @SundaymagSST Kate! So many I had to leave out! Darn the pesky word count. (Thank you x)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonjayelich1 @SundayStarTimes @SundaymagSST No, Sonja - thank YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whaeapower @SundayStarTimes @SundaymagSST Oh, I'm glad! Yes am in complete awe of Tig Notaro, and the shoe shop Queen x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack @RFStew @SundayStarTimes Chortles! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adudding I binge-finished yr book last night. It's elegant, wry &amp; loving. Enjoyed how you wove in the dilemma of memoir-writing. Bravo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack @SundayStarTimes A funny column every week, AND you can cook? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Nasty Ladies! Put your hands up! Today's @SundayStarTimes @SundaymagSST column is your crushbook for 2017 https://t.co/M3rrDSGww1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealEricYoung See you at the Caroline Bay carnival!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to everyone I've met, befriended, reunited with or was dazzled by on Twitter this year! ðŸŽ„ðŸ¾ðŸ•¶ðŸ‘™ðŸŽ‰â¤ï¸ðŸ“šSafe &amp; happy hols, all x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @clementine_ford So glad! Merry Christmas and happy reading xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annaloren @HeySamuelHarris @brooke_bath I don't understand this on any level but I love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PimlicoPlumbers Charlie, my Dad (Terry McFall, formerly of your firm) sends you and family his best Xmas wishes from New Zealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NationalGallery Quit with the ukuleles, guys! You'll wake the baby! (We used to study photocopies of his paintings at school in '80s NZ!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRhodesPianist @PimlicoPlumbers Oooh, my Dad used to work for them. Fabbo firm, and the loveliest clients!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RPT Smoking kills the working poor; cigs were often their only affordable pleasure. I've been sad &amp; angry over this since my childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No sympathy for working-class men with lung cancer, wrote a dying AA Gill in @thetimes this month. Nor those with COPD, I'd add.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amy_may NZ couldn't be further from Orkney but your book spirits the islands here. A gutsy, saltysweet, breathtaking read. Wonderful you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book of the year. Yes! An alcoholic Millennial recovers in the blasted &amp; beautiful Orkney Islands. WEEP HAPPY TEARS! https://t.co/UF8i8huW8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Melania Trump parody video that did made me snortle: "Beef. Pickles. Sesame buns." https://t.co/4lR2xPeDFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania can handle it. But can we? Today's final @SundaymagSST @SundayStarTimes column for 2016. Mwah, darlings! https://t.co/3coLKN4NKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @RealEricYoung ladies, I think we can all agree that Eric Young has just become three times as attractive. #bighearteric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusieFergusonNZ Somebody needs to light a scented candle, unblock a chakra and take a good hard look at themselves in their third eye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Em - Emma Lange, as in Bang - has a brain tumour. Go to my FB page to read more &amp; please, consider giving. Thank you https://t.co/QSKe4Z5HxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want a compliment, phone your mother." AA Gill, unrepentant, even in his obituary https://t.co/ufOYTMKJqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ Ooooh, I want one of those! Can they also do cats, small dogs, and children? Imagine the time we'll save!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not every day I can truthfully say I once peed in a cup for the Prime Minister's wife. God, how I love this country. #drmaryenglish â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack His "Fame in the 20th Century" is among my Top Five. Such a brilliant book. He invented brainy snark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealEricYoung @TheSpinoffTV @SteveBraunias @DianaWichtel I thoroughly enjoyed both pieces. Thanks for the links!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack today is typically elegant, snortle-funny, and full of zingers https://t.co/sq97iSmY9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In @SundaymagSST today, I get myself into a post-quake, post-truth snit. https://t.co/xgaOP1Cegi @SundayStarTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyberjohnboy that is the role I remember him by. His vulnerability made me cry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want him for my grandad https://t.co/ux38PNnSS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudithCollinsMP, Your ambition could be a drawback now so just dot your i's with little hearts &amp; use a feathery pen. This will help! Mwah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstMcDougall Yes, but equally what kind of rhubarb fool would leave such a bag unattended?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longlostleah Just a hot take after two Countdown mince pies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a shame there's apparently so much comedy value in the prospect of a woman running for Nat leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonjayelich1 I don't know exactly what animal that is, but it walks like how I feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fasciating analysis from @simonbwilson https://t.co/JaVsZr93Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, this could make a fantastic girls' trip to Sydders! https://t.co/HZYPq8qmZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaqTweedie You can tell a lot about a man from his ornamental borders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing he could do his get out the secateurs. His topiary is a chuffing disgrace #parnellreacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusieFergusonNZ @Mihi_Forbes Somebody needs to calm down, empty their colostomy bag and have a gingernut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In today's @SundaymagSST column in @SundayStarTimes, my wedding day identity crisis. But boy, I looked good!  https://t.co/W5UKAw26MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Don't make me come down there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Beck! I'm trying to raise your consciousness, here! ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Shopping Hell Day 1: death to all sexist calendars https://t.co/pAHBQ4DVV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SundaymagSST @EleanorBlacknz This was an excellent profile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven I can't believe I'm saying this but I'm going to need more cat videos. Just getting the order in before Christmas. Purr! ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyRF @RFStew @IvankaTrump all those millions and no fireguard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madeupinblue if I was at your conference I would be facedown in my notebook weeping quietly by now. I don't even understand the first slide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ Thank you, Emily! (*Clinks imaginary wine glass*)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @SundaymagSST @SundayStarTimes column is a whinge about kids taking over my house. Dedicated to parents #blessed  https://t.co/Zw1UUejm8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ She is extraordinary! Congratulations from our family, Carol! (See you down at Kelburn Medical!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessirklein @nytimes Deserved. Grown up comedy for Nasty Women everywhere. Big tick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadine_millar @TheSpinoffTV then we're both in trouble ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadine_millar is a brilliant, exciting new voice. Always, always worth reading!  https://t.co/ZSYjbiIpAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adudding Your book will be my Christmas gift to myself. Ock, Ock, Ockhams! Well done, Adam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahELaing Um hello, Ockhams much? (In the style of Carrie Bradshaw, congratulations on your nomination, Sarah!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mathewrodriguez @HadleyFreeman Gwyneth consciously uncoupled from humanity some time ago (hashtag Hamptonslife)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary wears less makeup for a keynote speech. Is she 1) dying 2) brave 3) getting sloppy 4) nuts? Note: no other options are available)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's @SundaymagSST column in  @SundayStarTimes. Kind of like The Shining, but without Jack 'Crazy Eyes' Nicholson https://t.co/tqJbTm6fWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely little Peri. Bringing cat and dog people together during a terrible week. Sleep tight â¤ï¸ï¸ https://t.co/XEjqNKX1na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessairini @rnz_news I want this man for my Grandad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahELaing @DavidSlack Quit &amp; then give everyone handmade vouchers for Xmas gifts, promising to do their washing-up. No need to thank me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HAVE MORE GOING ON THAN THIS https://t.co/GRD4imQ2j6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaMBarnett @SundayStarTimes Thank you, Angela! Everybody has their own Emma, special women that they are ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just supported The Guardian and its network of independent journalism. Truth matters!  https://t.co/ySxZ7Y3jjz #guardianmembers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywalljourno @gdnmembership nice one Tony. I will follow suit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @radionz, @ninetonoon, @JMulliganRNZ, @CheckpointRNZ, Nights and @SusieFergusonNZ: we love you bigly. BIGLY. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBraunias @hollyrwalker Likewise, Steve. I'm sorry not to be able to make it. Congratulations on the book! ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbwilson @SteveBraunias No, gawd bless her. But I read she had magnums delivered to Portland Hospital when she was a million years old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbwilson @SteveBraunias magnum of champagne in the limo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBraunias You're like the Queen Mum in the London Blitz. PROPS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielthoma Fantastic placard - I Love Being Gay. YES! March, honey. MARCH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anzacbiscuit @SundayStarTimes i know that Ms Em is a dear friend to you too, Greto xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kareninauckland Oh! Karen, that is such lovely news. Thanks, girlfriend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's@SundaymagSST column in the @SundayStarTimes is a love letter to female friendship. I'm with HER â¤ï¸ https://t.co/wuCW5inh2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so inventive, plus full of LOLZ. Vintage @DavidSlack! Cut out and keep! https://t.co/PYBvhdnk6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/IRJukLWMTr We all need to channel Nancy Wake right now]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>