<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Global growth in mind as IntegrationWorks appoints new CEO https://t.co/J0JxyAvFA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drone footage of #Wellington region #beautifulplacetolive @Wellington_NZ https://t.co/ocG72uRu2m via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanmekongman @aarongrowwelly Shame about the #jameverywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanmekongman another fun mystery parcel for Aaron! #weloveourmums https://t.co/0G7iqAcENE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Curtisgwalker We've finished we will see you soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this business model: subscription based salon quality hair colour. Challenges the assumption that the status… https://t.co/3rwaaZC48k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas at the WREDA office was brought to us by Mariana. #shebringsthehohoho https://t.co/xGzvlKBoEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hohoho #wreda #icesculpture #Christmas https://t.co/2ajWwTVt5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hohoho #WREDA Christmas in the office. #gohardorgohome https://t.co/BwkPUvuwkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching girls to fly #drones - would be great if we had this programme in NZ. https://t.co/5zDK0o4wJf @TechFuturesLab #futurecareers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaManins I hear ya sister!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiLandingPad @teampageproof  That's Gemma to a T. Very organised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a new desk? Cool little Wellington company sells fold out cardboard desks from $160. https://t.co/h7EClbWuoF… https://t.co/DBQ6RotPG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for a new Business Growth Manager working with Wellington's screen and digital businesses. https://t.co/0vAgvZ3MbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are looking for new staff - Sector Development Manager: Science and Commercialisation https://t.co/CEe6hHxe3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've just had an idea for a world-class product with the potential to make millions - now what? https://t.co/WJoo0cbVfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pledgeme @tanmekongman We call him Tanfastic. Congratulations to everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Value of customer acquisition for a client less than $10k over lifetime shouldn't be done in person. @gaijindan #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find people who will run through walls for your company. There are people who will do 3x sales of other staff. Pay them well. #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't fix everything with tech and product you need to integrate sales. #NZSMJ @amandapey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product has to have healthy tension with every part of the organisation. #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When doing sign ups ask for minimal details: email &amp; name #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for problems 1 inch wide 1 mile deep &amp; people will pay for fix #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're hiring at Raygun, a New Zealand based tech company. Currently in the process of building out Team USA... https://t.co/LAfGdinsNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloInPerson you never fail to deliver. Keep em coming! Another great intro. @CameronMehlhopt thanks for the coff… https://t.co/mCEiUY6HG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwibank FinTech Accelerator: Do you want to build the future of NZ's Fi... https://t.co/XRxQIJesj2 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotDrewBroadley Drew that sounds awful. My heart goes out to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to work with talented Kiwi expats? Post NZ jobs on Kea’s website – and yes it’s free. https://t.co/29mpoEVcYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @HelloInPerson I loved meeting @Traject_NZ and learning about the #R9Accelerator. More please....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzaudrey I'm glad you found it useful Audrey. Hopefully this will become an ongoing programme. @callaghannz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfantastic one day it will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone out there know about drop shipping?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotDrewBroadley Yes I want to hear this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley start-up Perfect Day Foods: creating milk proteins similar to craft brewing. Watch out #nzdairy. https://t.co/dMT82wF66w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfantastic an early morning thinker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for a great coffee chat @so_likeleigh. @HelloInPerson we suggest a Xmas get together for all HiPsters so we can see each other again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfantastic You're eating ice cream at 7am?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Founders of Wellington's Underground Market say their early  #businessmentor was crucial to their success. Great work @MentorsNZ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaManins I'm really excited to see what you come up with! It's all blue skies baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paper run
Checkout Operator
Waitress
Bar Tender
Data Entry
Market Analyst
Account Manager
#firstsevenjobs #first7jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for another great #hipstermeetup @HelloInPerson. Thanks for the chat and ideas @roseanna_g - all the best on your travels!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't NZ companies win govt tenders? https://t.co/2Ac7KX1MLy Because some of the tenders are 700 pages long! #Tenders @ianapperley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is this guy? We guess he is a businessman receiving an award. https://t.co/XPK8keZfY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did anyone else spot this error? #notwayneguppy @DomPost #fail https://t.co/r7SdwfAO9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scale ups love peer to peer contact with other business owners. WREDA can help with these connections. @Grant_GrowWLG #itx2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scale ups focus on maintaining repeat orders, steady committed employees; diff challenges to start up phase. #itx2016 @Grant_GrowWLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges for startup founder to share knowledge and build a management structure as the #ScaleUp. #itx2016 @Grant_GrowWLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scale up challenges discovered so far: leadership/team, changing focus, governance. @Grant_GrowWLG @GrowWelly #itx2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on how to help  $10m companies become $20m companies. @Grant_GrowWLG #itx2016 https://t.co/wdJHIAQrI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grant_GrowWLG #itx2016 WREDA engaging with 450 businesses each year to understand needs and offer assistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to hearing how Wellington businesses can #scaleup. @Grant_GrowWLG #itx2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shagility once bitten twice shy. I won't park there again!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$42 for 4.5 hours parking! outrageous @WilsonParkingNZ Your signs are horrendously misleading. #NotFair https://t.co/rOGiuh27CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @HelloInPerson for another great coffee introduction. I loved talking #futuretech #education with @BellaMulligan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to my next #Hipster already. Thanks @HelloInPerson https://t.co/0CULrL1B4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Congratulations to Rachna Bhasin for Forbes recognition" by @FaulkClaire on @LinkedIn https://t.co/YgR3ojeYyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great chat - I had to look up #SoulCycle. Thanks @HelloInPerson https://t.co/0CULrL1B4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Could your next market opportunity be GLAM? " on @LinkedIn https://t.co/T4qaGqBUwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Strategy: Wellingtonians are more than twice as likely to work in ICT as people in other New Zealand cities https://t.co/LAJo6qzpIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's awesome John-Daniel and Zheng! Take on the world! https://t.co/1wr7cQChqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr: vaccines, flu shots, blood tests, now being done at pharmacies in the U.S.  Moving away from hospitals &amp; clinics. #future #health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr: understand how your market analyses and measures cost &amp; value. Hospitals and countries vary enormously. #healthtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trends in regulations towards approval with evidence may speed up new medical tech release to market. But other challenges. #future #health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google took YouTube videos through deep learning and found that cat videos are very important to us! #bigdata #future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Catherine Mohr: we are able to 3D print hollow body parts. 3D printed hip replacements by Ossis NZ. #future #healthtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr: using fluorescence to show surgeon exactly where cancer is. #future #healthtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr: dogs are being trained to detect cancer. #future #health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health tech AI systems will monitor the huge data streams for individual health. #futurehealth Dr Catherine Mohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biomarkers genomics proteomics, imaging agents machine vision, robotics regenerated med, 3d printing, personalised med. #healthtech #future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr sees future medical products as wearable tech; point of care becomes where the person is. #futuretech #health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Mohr: World is getting healthier living longer regardless of wealth. Thanks to vaccines, antibiotics, medical advancement. #world health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to hear from Dr Catherine Mohr leading medical scientist, robotics surgeon and entrepreneur. @BizDojo @CreativeHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sorry to hear about the passing of Rob Neru @advantage4me. Rob was a great guy. https://t.co/FfOsaFc3Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raymond @datatorque look after team &amp; families, provide events: Easter egg hunts, Star Wars movies - build strong teams. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep a warm list of potential recruits and take them on as soon as they become available. Raymond @datatorque #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Businesses are increasingly  looking for talent that haven't finished their degrees yet. Finding talented people is most important. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kari YouDo: Wellington has small network to tap into eg can use to help immigrant's partner find a job too. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ doesn't offer the scale or salary that other countries can offer but skilled immigrants like lifestyle, security, non corrupt. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@intergen Simon Bright: recognise staff have strong work ethic so choose to add more staff rather make them work harder. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Achieving high growth: Raymond @datatorque a good peer culture will self regulate. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kari Reiter YouDo set the bar high for staff and the right people will enjoy the challenge. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High percentage of women in Wellington internship programmes. Gerard Quinn @GrowWelly #tintalk #womenintech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerard Quinn: Internship programs help students to become more employable &amp; match make talent for companies. #tintalk @GrowWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raymond @datatorque: Culture is v. important, consider the whole life of staff including family. Need challenging moments in role. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have clear career paths for staff so they feel connected to the business. Simon Bright @TeamIntergen #tintalk #staffretention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key to attracting talent: Simon Bright @TeamIntergen have clear values for potential staff to latch onto. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kari Reiter YouDo looks for staff with resilience, great work ethic, and coachabilty. New recruits must do a build prior to hire. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 Wellington businesses have combined growth of over $125m. #tintalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington tops percentage growth with 7.9% growth. "Something bubbling away in Wellington business community." #tintalk @GrowWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready to hear the results of the latest TIN100 report #tintalk @nzx @GrowWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product management means being customer centric, condense that and then figure out how to build it. #NZSMJ @nedwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavIsSavvy kiwis take time to perfect products services but Americans go to market earlier -rough n ready. #nzsmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Own the space between your words when you pitch. Own the commas too! @SavIsSavvy @ashalhashim #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in company should know what a great sales lead looks like so entire company can attract them.  #nzsmj @SavIsSavvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LocalATLast use marketing to qualify sales lead and filter leads out using given criteria. Pass qualified leads to sales team. #nzsmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Predictable Revenue: a great book on sales. https://t.co/7oTFBhWr3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make cold calls with your reps, get hung up on and let them see you handle it. @ashalhashim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add value first before expecting a sale or ask from potential customer. Give a lot to get a little. @SavIsSavvy #nzsmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good sales ppl identify key events that are crucial to their customers world. Solve their date issues and hurdles. @ashalhashim #NZSMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashalhashim sorry if I mis-attributed this. Hard to distinguish between the beards!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>