<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirandadevine Agree with previous tweet. WTF is an African Australian? 
We are "AUSTRALIAN" ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrMatthewLC Really? You encourage people to prioritise football over Mass? Definitely Novus Ordo mentality. Shame!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Hollywood 2017. Where's Senator Joe McCarthy when you really need him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KymKarath Indeed, a vile racist attack on this young man with special needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Ridgeley finally takes over as frontman of Wham!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acstudio Merry Christmas Angela and family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholasham1 @ScottBaio I'm heartened not all of the beloved SOM family share your view Nicholas. Merry Christmas Nicholas and Scott.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickbarnesaus @HarryCook Harry, Harry, Harry.. so left wing and so dismissive of the facts. "Actors are always right syndrome" one thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Defence Ministers of Norway, Sweden, Netherlands &amp; Germany ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚
And the US Defence Secretary nominee ðŸ‘ðŸ» https://t.co/sfkAZqqAdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch @NopeFrancis Oh dear. https://t.co/0l9sEmwlIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[53 years ago today, a good and decent man was gunned down by Lee Harvey Oswald in Dallas Texas. RIP Dallas Police Officer JD Tippit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just returned from a magical evening with @_DionneWarwick @TheStarSydney Beautiful lady and beautiful music. Thank you Dionne ðŸ’›ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cindy_Wooden @NovusOrdoWatch Socially disadvantaged with expensive smartphones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who's @amyschumer when she's not having her period?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sound of leftist elites around the world slashing their wrists is music to the ears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the cancer of Vatican 2 spreads @NovusOrdoWatch @NopeFrancis https://t.co/NElPHISO7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch @guidomarini_fan @DameinZ The last valid Pope to wear the Triregnum was Pius XII. And he knows that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirandadevine @australian No mention of it on @abcnews of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DameinZ @NovusOrdoWatch @NopeFrancis No idea, it was posted on instagram by clickvaticano with no info attached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear... @NovusOrdoWatch @NopeFrancis https://t.co/Zpay2E7Fys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickbarnesaus And if the cock doesn't win, Triggs will be hauling the AOTY committee before the HRC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US election? Irrelevance on steroids. In the trenches, give me Putin any day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fifthwavefem @O2 @JadeEONeil Dear oh, dear..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fifthwavefem @Abby_NYC Damn you Bobby Goldsboro, you sexist bastard!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the witch-hunt of Cardinal Pell, continues...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchbishopBlase @roccopalmo Pope St Pius X, most vigilant guardian of the Catholic Church against errors of modernists, Ora Pro Nobis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustinzito @Tumbleweed_News Nailed it as usual, Dustin ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acstudio That's a yes from me ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eton_NHM Great photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCthedrum @JaneTribune So the, 'I had a Catholic upbringing which is why I'm an atheist' says, too many humans not enough sharks. Really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichRaho @NovusOrdoWatch Hiding his Pectoral Cross so as not to offend the great unwashed. Just like his heathen mate Francis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods And his party just re-elected him as leader??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebbieTurnerDTO @TheCharmianCar1 Love and prayers to you and your SOM family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJBElementary @KansasCatholic @Diocese_of_SLC   When nuns were Catholic. https://t.co/nH2ToCHBQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What sort of simpleton listens to @triplej in the first place? ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@History_Pics It's just a nice photo. Much needed relief from all the crap going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellcloyd Thankyou Debbie. I'll send you a brief note of my wonderful experience, seeing your Dad and you in Sydney.
Love to all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch It wouldn't take long for Cardinals Burke or Sarah to give it respectability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustinzito Go for it, Dustin. Proud of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evdiocatholicsc @KansasCatholic What part of Catholic is missing from this? The whole damn part. And who the hell is St Ben?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch Another dangerous idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholasham1 Off to see Dame Julie &amp; Emma in conversation at Sydney Opera House on Sunday. Memories of Dame Julie &amp; you at State Theatre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveKinlan I find that sometimes as well. If I post it via my phone, but delete it on iPad, I have to go back to the phone and delete it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope @JamesMartinSJ At 12 Jesus among the doctors in the temple going about His Fathers business. No SJ feminist input required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope @JamesMartinSJ Another delusional Jesuit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep appeared disturbingly unstable at DNC yesterday ðŸ˜–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimball1000 Half black, Jim. Remember his mother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dustinzito Classy very classy ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow!! No chance of anyone challenging @GillianTriggs on @QandA tonight. Soft leftie panel including Laundy. Easy run for the irrelevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guidomarini_fan Didn't he stop wearing it once Francis appeared. None of the beautiful sacred vestments of Benedict XVI. 
Too Catholic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No not there ðŸ‘ŽðŸ» https://t.co/JVIIMjmv2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kilimandege @nickbarnesaus Probably pedos hiding under those sheets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clairepink24 @PopeLeoXII May Our a Beloved Lord bless you on your holy journey. Will you still have access to Twitter in the seminary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whozenexxt @nickbarnesaus @RitaPanahi @SoniaKruger Agree, but unfortunately a certain gold Logie winner fits the current AOTY criteria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scotts2c @ABCthedrum Chen yells and sticks his pen in others faces. Acts like a left wing anti-Christian bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellcloyd Kindest wishes to you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi @nickbarnesaus The shrill of the banshee. What a hateful woman @vanbadham is. Sad sad sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MCITLFrAphorism @jcdrex Hopefully Aaron was properly vested and not serving at the altar like a Novus Ordo fashionista?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMartinSJ @KansasCatholic Disgraceful. Trust a Jesuit to endorse such an insult to our Blessed Mother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholasham1 @ChartersandC Happy Birthday to your Mum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch Slingshots to distribute Holy Communion to the distant masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy for UK. The people have spoken and the traitors and bigots can eat shit. Rule Britannia ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¬ðŸ‡§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholasham1 That other iconic film in your brilliant career. RIP James Aubrey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope Two Priests, 2 weeks ago in my local shopping mall. They were both from my local FSSP parish ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholasham1 Nicholas, Golda Meir, Indira Ghandi, Benazir Bhutto, Margaret Thatcher etc,  broke it many years ago. And with humility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnalive @NopeFrancis Lots of empty seats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading home to England. Sydney Airport 22nd April 2000. https://t.co/lIKPOPPZBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickbarnesaus ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º Amen To That ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º Our Great Flag ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º Our Only Flag ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch Does HE vote standing up or sitting down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WashArchdiocese @KansasCatholic @ACHSWashDC @Cardinal_Wuerl Sister Act ðŸ‘ŽðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope @LetsLivein21stc Same. I checked his page. All hate directed at Catholics and the child in the womb. TROLL on steroids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Sydney â¤ï¸ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º https://t.co/dCmiZHMXxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovusOrdoWatch @Pontifex See that crucifix. Have it removed immediately. It offends me and my Muslim mates. https://t.co/L9X7zTH3e5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACurrentAffair9 Anyone who saw Bill Shorten jogging last week, would have seen that his tits are bigger than this dopey Sheila's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__NSS__ The scariest bit was during Aly's acceptance. She was crying and applauding as if she was at a North Korean rally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__NSS__ I'm sorry I watched it. She was inducted into Hall Of Fame. 15 minute+ acceptance speech pushing wacko leftist agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__NSS__ And what the fuck is the go with Noni Hazelhurst? Seriously mentally unstable leftie wackjob. Tears for Aly ðŸ’©ðŸ˜œ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dolphinmaria In a predictably coward response, @sturdyAlex blocks me, because I stood up to his attempts to bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, as Canada burns where is @JustinTrudeau?  ðŸ˜´ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sturdyAlex @dolphinmaria Oh, I understand in the current geopolitical climate, the significance of your intolerant response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dolphinmaria @sturdyAlex And Red Ken was London's first atheist mayor, with Boris being London's first Christian Mayor ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlboMP Politics aside, you put this in my letter box and expect me to vote for you. Souths..really? Keep dreaming. https://t.co/bC2LyP1l9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eharris_it @KansasCatholic @Pontifex He's an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrMatthewLC @Pontifex Another shameless photo op.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope But he is a muslim leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchbishopKurtz @KansasCatholic St Pius X most vigilant guardian of the Catholic faith against the errors of the modernists. Pray for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope Oh look a sick child. Pull my humble little fiat over so I can bless him. Yes, here just near the TV cameras.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProtectthePope No they don't. Just another shameless stunt from a not so humble egomaniac. Pope St Pius X..Pray For Us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@N1K0LAK1 @PopeLeoXII @TRobinsonNewEra Sounds like the jews are trying to buy protection. It won't work fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnalive @KansasCatholic Wow! A see through sacristy. As sacristy's in Novus Ordo parishes have become public spaces this is unsurprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@americamag @KansasCatholic But of course. He brings muslims to the Vatican. Not one Christian Refugee. He is the scum of the earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope @TonyHWindsor shows due acknowledgement and respect to ours and indeed his acting Prime Minister @Barnaby_Joyce. Suck it up TonyðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailycatholic @PopeLeoXII So the cattle and fish would be offensive to vegans. They've got to go as well then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicky_rome @CardinalChito @KansasCatholic A de facto church? Catholics kneel before the Blessed Sacrament NOT dance like fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicky_rome @CardinalChito @KansasCatholic An altar &amp; most importantly there is a monstrance which I assume contains the Blessed Sacrament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicky_rome @CardinalChito @KansasCatholic A joyful faith, yes. Not a disrespectful. This belongs in a circus tent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardinalChito @KansasCatholic And your point @vicky_rome? Catholics do not behave like this in a Sacred Place. Tagle is a Protestant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardinalChito @KansasCatholic Another Francis clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN Sec General aspirant, Helen Clarke playing the Gillard gender card. She obviously doesn't think she's otherwise qualified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crystalallclear @__NSS__ Yummm!! I'm enjoying eating my pork chops even more as I read this.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>