<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally started watching Black Mirror tonight. I'm all over it after only 20 minutes! https://t.co/5YSuIUn0k7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally had a day off with Alva after too long. Huge lie in then awesome Japanese food at Zakura Izakaya on Baggot… https://t.co/zq91jXUA5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a time to be alive. @Boojum_Dublin scheduled to arrive as I get home in an hour. Then its movies o'clock all n… https://t.co/TgkAgzoSBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Resident Evil marketing team, How the eff does this size bullet come out of that gun? Like... I almost can't h… https://t.co/om5ocWSGM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so disheveled and tired this morning and all I can think about is my 3 day weekend starting at 5pm today! https://t.co/rOrcKBzQRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIG TOBLERONE ACQUIRED https://t.co/NG0g8q8YpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched an advert where a rastafarian type dude milked skittles out of a giraffe. Cocaine is a hell of a drug. https://t.co/tSZxE6hCs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My girlfriend is on her way back from England and I sense a big airport toblerone in my near future... https://t.co/M6kIs8QVBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JodySinclair_ oh absolutely. I've checked a while bunch of reviews on two places that say the animals are left alone when irritated etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found out there's a cafe in Tokyo where you can pet hedgehogs and bunnies because it's Japan and why not! https://t.co/XjjOuZ2SSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got my first MVP on Titanfall 2. https://t.co/KU1YYboqmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanOhOgain @CoupeReVille @dearbhlala stunning colours on those pieces!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK toy fair? Take lots of pictures of cool shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGarvey1981 okay maybe THAT Dick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGarvey1981 YOU'RE HIRED #NoDickPicsPlease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That being said. I wish I wasn't the only person running the store twitter Monday to Friday. I barely have any time for social media lately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love being busy and I love my team. So fucking solid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, new comic delivery days are nuts. I'm pretty sure it was 9am about 20 minutes ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGarvey1981 I need to get my script together FAST!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ckyhellion I don't know what it is about the orange but it stands out so much. There's crew necks and hoodies too. They're class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ckyhellion I needed to show the world!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vans have new camo stuff in stock. I'm going to buy it all and be invisible all the time. https://t.co/2XUyvcMZVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishComicNews no its cool I just totally forgot you don't focus on stuff outside of Irish creators/books! https://t.co/FlrdLjxOPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Donald Trump news today has put me in such a bummer of a mood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishComicNews @GeekIreland @comixireland you dudes should get all up on this!! https://t.co/lzdI5Iv0r2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to make chilli and realised I left my huge ass pot in my last apartment when I moved. Ain't that some shit. https://t.co/iAKJOxuxNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is it. Piers Morgan has finally lost the plot. https://t.co/dqqAzZipd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great management opportunities within a great company. Get on it! https://t.co/EvtcxYKc3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My girlfriend made fun of me for spending my lunch money on Legos three days in a row. https://t.co/OE0AZWTtGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK will do. Currently replacing jeans as I can never keep a pair longer than a month without ripping the crotch out of them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK you in the office today man? I'm not in yet but wondering if you know about the yesterday's pins coming in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenBaReid @SMLNTHNMCK no worries dude. Be sure to check out P-Macs too for some seriously good food and drink!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK @BenBaReid it's called Cassidys, bud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP first pair of skinny jeans of 2017. Another pair. Another hole ripped in the crotch. Another lost receipt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my new Comics are for everybody Pin. Thank you @RedCube_Studio! https://t.co/6FNnpVaId1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickRoche that is beautiful, Nick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshcanPress you're so welcome, Matthew. I'm a ridiculous Guardians fan and this book just makes me so happy. https://t.co/0yqLPMFv53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattGarvey1981 is it still weird to marry inanimate objects?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but seriously tho, how sexy is this gold embossed cover for CURSE WORDS? I love it so much! https://t.co/k6VrS4mKY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picked up a few comics this week. Still so behind on my own pulls but I'm so into the new JL/ MMPR, Rocket Racoon a… https://t.co/mU0LDTpSn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey God damn. I've said it a thousand times but you've always drawn a great deadpool man. Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If buying a house in Ireland means I have to eat ham sandwiches and give up burritos then I'll happily live in a box forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all heroes wear capes. They also throw shit at people who deserve to have shit thrown at them. https://t.co/cJHLlI7Hlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to watch Scott Pilgrim and relax the rest of the night now. Been working since 9am and my back is in BITS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesSoule I know I will. The Gold Embossed cover had me bouncing around my shop with excitement today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely so excited for this book. The master @CharlesSoule never fails! #NCBD https://t.co/TDHb9aeVN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey Shalveyworld! I'm in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been so flat out today that I can't do comic posts until I'm home. Woe is me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CUTE COVER ALERT!! Check out @ChrisSamnee and @COLORnMATT's awesome cover for BLACK WIDOW #10 out tomorrow. Many fe… https://t.co/OEToHMVhou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Adam working super hard trying to uncover the secrets of the DC Universe in the pages of Before Watchmen. Go… https://t.co/60TAWAAj5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesday = New Comics Delivery. Looks pretty tame but the Graphic Novel restocks and merchandise is being processed… https://t.co/SEwbVjcQ1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK have we become one? We should set up a weekly conference call to discuss all things Rebels. 5 eps in now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyburkejnr @xTwoShoes new from first to last is enough of a blast from the past for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyburkejnr @xTwoShoes it's obvious I'm the only person on twitter who doesn't listen to HIM.  I accept my defeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I'm so into Star Wars Rebels. Season 2 is kicking ass! https://t.co/DI80QLkYuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey @RedCube_Studio you're welcome man. If there's anything else I can do to spread the word just let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ordered my Comics are for everybody charity enamel pin from @RedCube_Studio. Brilliant offer and for such a fa… https://t.co/NZJWonL2Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xTwoShoes I don't know man. I thought we were friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFlanYearns @xTwoShoes BOO YOU WHORE!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You serious @xTwoShoes? https://t.co/s22YxQ5v2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God Damn that new @FFTLAST song with @Skrillex is just pure magic. It makes 10 years feel like it was nothing. So c… https://t.co/95YTk6BUly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just booked flights to Tokyo. I am gonna eat Ramen and punch Godzilla in the face. Also, Disneyland. https://t.co/0FKUjfM8Oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy mother of BBQ Sauce. I'm so happy that @RedsTrueBBQ sauces are stocked in Dublin  now. https://t.co/qVSRAB3x7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up at 1pm today and it was glorious. Much needed day off after what felt like the longest work week ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK I'd say so. At least ramen is mad cheap over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanOhOgain I've seen such a contrast in what people are saying about the switch so far. What do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK Jesus dude is it that good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've honestly drank around 6 litres of water today and I am unable to move quickly without my belly sloshing around! https://t.co/YJITvO8UQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really excited to finally have my good buddy @MattGarvey1981's fantastic new HC in stock at @FPDublin - Only €10.99… https://t.co/uGIEIC7QtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously need a shower but The Bourne Ultimatum is on. Why is today so difficult? https://t.co/1vlTtXd3uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kokoro and Star Wars Rebels for lunch on this busy ass day! https://t.co/BMAZ1Ir44g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMLNTHNMCK dude I would love to but I'd prefer more time to save money. Missing the cheery blossom bloom will suck tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj True. Most of my excitement came from Guardians 2 and Spider-Man trailers then news of Avengers filming in Glasgow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kierawaringx the way things are currently going its probably best to keep your expectations low. They managed Harley so poorly in SS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj PS I'm not sure if that gif was actually from the show but it made so much sense to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj I remember being a kid seeing something about that old skool Japanese live action spider-man series and… https://t.co/TkDGdGFn67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj I'm the same. Are we so spoiled as consumers that even a huge budget super hero movie doesn't get us excited? Are we broken?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cazlou1980 you're right. At least the have something going for them in that aspect. I still think star wars has the right idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even that new Justice League image had me like 'eh it's alright'. No excitement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what it is about the DCEU but after Batman Vs Superman and Suicide Squad, I don't think I'll ever be sold on another DC Movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj I should really schedule my work posts. Life would be much easier! https://t.co/M5Vjk7cDXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is cool considering the absolutely shit day I've had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure being in the mix for best Irish Comic Store in the ICN Awards. Some healthy competition in there as… https://t.co/9TqVmy2JUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm booking flights to Japan today. So expensive. So worth it. Excited to visit Tokyo/Kyoto this year! https://t.co/F9Qm9XLW4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah OK we're doing GamerCon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steoleary87 glad you enjoyed it man. Yeah definitely need a catch up soon. I've been so shit at making plans every time we talk about it 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I taught my parents how to use Netflix over the phone tonight. I think it's safe to say I've just made their lives 75% cooler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wondering if it's worth exhibiting at GamerCon in March. We've got quite a bit of Gaming Merchandise in the shop. Could be cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still so pumped that I own this bad boy!! Please keep the awesome deadpool merch coming @hottoysofficial… https://t.co/uGboJ7rw0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganraghalligh so sick. I had to sanitize my hands about 8 times!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to the customer who paid for their items with a blood stained note today. It's cool I didn't plan on hav… https://t.co/VCfgZzIuJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm broken today. Woke up at 2pm. Went for lunch. Went back to bed until 10pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steoleary87 I reckon you wouldn't be lost at all. The new viewing order actually considers Rogue one as the first. It ties into A New Hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017. Continue as you mean to go on. In woolshed having wings and beers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xTwoShoes WhatsApp me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent last night watching movies, eating crap and playing Battlefield with Alva. Glad we decided to stay in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year, Everyone!! Thankful for a solid year both professionally and personally. I plan on eating more burritos in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone with NYE plans in Dublin, Hit me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to any and all who picked up LOVE IS LOVE this week to support the victims and survivors of the Pulse nig… https://t.co/nQpAYmNStM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to skate down to the deli and grab some lunch. Owning a Skateboard again reminds of being 16 again. Only less of a delinquent.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>