<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel XL International Giveaway @androidauth #giveaway https://t.co/cG9ahSTAdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb did you remember your hat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess this joke backFIRED... https://t.co/WlomtsjZJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm I like the inclusion of a QR code though. That's cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[?? This does not fill me with good feelings. https://t.co/RYtC0SFVW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel XL International Giveaway @androidauth #giveaway https://t.co/ovU0VtHIcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei Nova Plus International Giveaway! @huaweimobile @androidauth #giveaway https://t.co/7C5MA7KWX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve tempting eh.Pretty darn cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle dammit. they skipped ETH2!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great groove! @garyhoeyband #Pandora https://t.co/f8Fljjkbbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve Congratulations. :-) Great photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve @scottjpalmer @myleftkidney yeah it's been open since Wednesday I think..a whole week! LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve @andrewb liar. There was no internet in your teenage years! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb @Coleadve yeah. It could do with an update eh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ I'll give it a go - thanks for the suggestion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ that's not it. My inbox in webmail was completely empty. Strange. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @vodafoneNZ we seem to have issues with our paradise email. Senders are getting "cannot be delivered" messages. Any ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve yeah I thought/felt the same. No stealth there!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve no broadcast tv for us.. Watching news via TVNZOD. Kinda ironic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#eqnz
WOAH. That just kept going and going and going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+1 don't mess with the aquifer!!! https://t.co/fnZ7hRy1nC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbstractCode yep. Exactly what's been killing my i7 Surface Pro 3. One java process I didn't even need, consuming 80+% of my cpu #death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel XL International Giveaway @androidauth @BaiduMobile https://t.co/zdIP2irygk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfaceSupport thank you. I'm impressed by your responsiveness, and appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfaceSupport Hi battery charging is a lil better but discharges fast (1 hour left @ 59%) &amp; major thermal prob :( https://t.co/TLdFdPTtt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@errolwi I wonder if the mould is still useable... I'd love to build a sim cockpit.. #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy blue?! What the hell.. That word should be "now". Thanks Swype. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy def wasn't you. I finally found the manual section in settings, AL3Pro is blue useable again!! https://t.co/7AvPqY5RTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy pretty sure it's nothing you did. Google Now Launcher won't set either. Phone has clearly spazz'd and needs a kick. :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @scottjpalmer I think the real joke here is "2 Adults"... !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy 'set as default' drops me back to the Huawei launcher. Almost unusable as a launcher :( https://t.co/LxtNs15wse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy :( I dont like my chances of a fix then! https://t.co/7W2kJguGij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy what can I send you to help? Logs from somewhere? Build info? Video of problem? Happy to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy uninstall/reinstall didn't help. backup won't restore either. How can I help you understand the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @chrismlacy random weirdness. AL3 beta tried to auto-update while I was in a call, now I can't set it as default [Huawei P9/EVA-L09] :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to Win the #Pixel XL #Android Smartphone Giveaway https://t.co/vgIs9qg8j3 #pixel #android #pixelxl #google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve chat with @richwalknz, he is experienced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb @scottjpalmer @stevebiddle I'm so glad it's no longer covered in ...cookie time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel International Giveaway! https://t.co/Cp92UEwmlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel International Giveaway @androidauth #giveaway https://t.co/Cp92UEwmlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfaceSupport thank you, that link is helpful. Surface has fully charged now! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfaceSupport everything on the dock works, and Surface knows it has power. Just not charging or very slowly, and hot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurfaceSupport thanks for replying! I noticed it yesterday. Did full shutdown/restart and unplugged/replugged dock power cord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicrosoftNZ Hi can you help me understand why this is happening with my #SurfacePro3 ? -- plugged in, not charging https://t.co/oW93PCwgpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Pixel or Pixel XL plus a $100 Amazon gift card from Android Central! Check it out!!  https://t.co/leZLbTAmZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am taking part in the #Honor8 phone #Giveaway!  + contest link @honorglobal @AndroidAuth

 https://t.co/8Hum5k4X7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honor 8 International Giveaway! @androidauth #giveaway https://t.co/8Hum5k4X7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action Launcher Pro has been the best launcher since its inception. And it just got better! https://t.co/JUTZzpJrII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirNZFairy @WetaWorkshop I'd take my wife and kids. We'd all love it! #FAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful!  TV959 is airborne!!
https://t.co/cGDVRDrkaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve try installing Nova Launcher. That might do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve depends entirely on the launcher. Most oem launcher allow ordering by name, date. Also folders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb it's a fantastic show. Sneaking suspicion I'm going to regret not buying the wings+rnzaf combo ticket. I love TVAL's work too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb come and stay in Palmerston North or Wairarapa, two airshows in consecutive weekends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb hmm. Thanks. Something to keep in mind. P.S. Are you coming down to RNZAF 80th?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb I want one of those. Learnt anything shareable via a tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markl_nz too simulation, not enough extraneous game bling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy I think the case for a nexus had been very strong since the N4.
...which I *just* replaced with a P9...

:/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Octane on prem has arrived!! Hooray! https://t.co/XPZVpSOZFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moto G4 Plus International Giveaway! @Moto @AndroidAuth https://t.co/Y7hwVfqlMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve of course. : p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve @ajobbins @BruceHoult @TheJessjess I'm just questioning your life choices. You want a decent coffee, followed by overpriced swill!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve @ajobbins @BruceHoult @TheJessjess then?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nexus 6P CaliCase International #Giveaway @androidauth @mycalicase https://t.co/cpFIWtmBFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flying_geek enjoy! There's nothing like a SCi. Beautiful aircraft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flying_geek opposite end of the spectrum, but there's ask L39 for sale down south... ...cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flying_geek must be some kind of Cub?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danmikhael @skullysystems @TechCrunch oh no! I was looking forward to seeing these guys take over the world! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismlacy interesting. Apparently AL3 is "power intensive" ?!

Seems unlikely, but I thought you might like to see https://t.co/CssY8gBWoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnePlus 3 International #Giveaway @androidauth https://t.co/Rknmx8Zh0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb awesome. I neeeeearly bought one, then decided I really wanted a 6P, but it wasn't as comfortable to hold as a P9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewb what have you got now that has a fingerprint jobby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins my phone came with one cable + one tip adapter. Handy enough.
Bought the P9 instead of N6P.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnePlus 3 International #Giveaway @androidauth https://t.co/e1N5HDxVvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve easily = early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve oh. Yeah Hutt High closed easily because if it (1.15pm)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed up to get the Android Voicemail App https://t.co/g6oNJa4D12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making sense of chaos, and providing meaningful estimates to "piece of string" work https://t.co/xpX968Wia1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flying_geek @zkarj @Rosspnz @markl_nz work will still be there when you get back ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's quite a interesting paragraph to read https://t.co/mzzuSQIrvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecochrane exactly the same for me.
First week of April lawn dug up and a hole in my driveway! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChorusNZ just wondering when the hole in my driveway might be fixed - It's been this way since first week of April https://t.co/xsAxpn4e5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm thanks for the info - I appreciate it. :)
Will be interesting to see some battery stats in a few weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm what's the battery life like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm did you like the P9?
It looks like a great phone... Struggling with the &gt;$1000 price though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle always cool in the circuit at night when those guys joined (NZPM)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjpalmer @stevebiddle @zkarj @flying_geek Cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @saintswgtn ! #nbl2016 champions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nightwyrm @Coleadve @simonpnz yeah that's a good one actually. Guardians of the galaxy? It's a bit weird in parts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve &amp; @freitasm also, apologies for the very late reply. I turned off all notif for Twitter... Hangover from running two apps for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm I think the two coloured images are very different.. The skinny image is much more white/blown than the squarer one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve @Nightwyrm @simonpnz astro boy? Or are you looking for something that 1) isn't animated 2) is from the D.C. or Marvel franchises?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've missed a few home games, so we're really looking forward to this one @saintswgtn !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwimatt001 NFI sorry. I don't use it.
When are you back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG G5 International #Giveaway @androidauth https://t.co/Yz3cyTN6d6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nexus 6P International #Giveaway @androidauth https://t.co/dSkBhWNbcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Coleadve https://t.co/it8LymVf1o

It's a very old idea. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjpalmer @stevebiddle @ajobbins @zkarj @flying_geek @dannews @TheGrandVizier Yep That's what Cessna call them but we cant on the radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @HPE_ALM #Beta is out! - Have you tried it yet? - https://t.co/kQm70RiPFK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>