<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When did my country become 7th grade? https://t.co/orWyw5Eru5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix @washingtonpost Were Bowling Green defendants "planning an attack IN BG"? DOJ release specifies NO plots of theirs targeted US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAMMY DAVIS JR. Arie Crown Theater, Chicago. 1969? https://t.co/YcEs5CshjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very helpful clarification from a knowledgeable source. https://t.co/ptTwSXPGZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze @joshgreenman That is not what Obama said at all. He was reflecting on the teachings of this guy from Nazareth? John 8:7?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNextBigNurse @charlescwcooke "Privacy to do what, Senator? Fix prices in a hotel room?" It was the last real confirmation debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNextBigNurse @charlescwcooke @Potamoose I covered Bork's hearings--a full debate, Bork was magnificent.And lost the vote.Very different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke @Potamoose Certainly. But they used the constitutional power for partisan, factional purposes. Not what Framers had in mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackie Robinson, born 98 years ago today. https://t.co/70FZGoymuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anneapplebaum @parisreview A little knowledge is a dangerous thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RHOBrooklyn It's an All-American immigrant story, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwsparkles @johannacox A joke! Lighten up! I don't like screamers and ranters and the utterly humorless. Blocked. Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwsparkles Statement of fact. The order uses outdated terms, opaque directives. OLC, DHS not consulted, etc. Ask any knowledgeable lawyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An example of how the fake news that the Quebec shooters were Syrian refugees was deliberately spread on Twitter. T… https://t.co/E2Qc8FFICc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8richard6 Yes, but neither is a Syrian refugee. I'm trying to find out how that falsehood spread like wildfire among some people. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8richard6 Wrong. Canadian authorities say only shooter was white male Bissonette. Where did you get the false story about refugees from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPLogar64 @CommunistRalph @adbridgeforth No Syrian refugees involved in Quebec shooting. Lone white male. Where'd you get the false story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WV4TRUMP1 May I ask: Where did you get the false story about Syrian refugees doing the shooting? I'm trying to track it down. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CongAhvathKesef You know, it was not Syrian refugees? Canadian authorities have named one white male as the shooter?He likes Trump, Le Pen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMcCafferty3 Ma'm, may I ask: Where did you hear the fake news story that the Quebec shooting was done by Syrian refugees? It's important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@capehog Crickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@capehog It's an honest question. Can you explain what happened to his secret plan? https://t.co/XuzcpFTsHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Trump already had a secret plan to destroy ISIS. What happened to it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His dad was murdered by terrorists. https://t.co/M1C3Fht4Km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defense Secretary Jim Mattis and so many others predicted this. Did Trump seek his counsel? https://t.co/I9wTovimZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bawling. #refugees #veterans #AmericaTheBeautiful https://t.co/T5NqJDIot4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There seems to have been a misunderstanding. Foreign tourists ≠ foreign terrorists. https://t.co/wrfDWrYblD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximilien03 @JZHoodie Oops! Just realize I missed your sarcasm! Sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximilien03 @JZHoodie American Nobel-winning scientists: So many immigrants! American science wins because we get the world's best minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke True. The religious minorities section, along with his blunt public admission it was for Christians, might be an issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No longer the party of Reagan. https://t.co/ngizKttboF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guypbenson Must respectfully disagree. This is what Trump wants--chaos, attention, stirring dark, visceral energies and profiting off them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredKempe @DamonMacWilson @NATO @theresa_may @Number10gov @UKNATO  @NATOpress @USNATO @GermanyNATO @CanadaNATO Yeah, good luck with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump in the Oval Office today. Noticing there are no pictures of his wife or children in this shot. https://t.co/q2Hj8hKck4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peaIDonaIdTrump I am proudly biased against the Ku Klux Klan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, Trump. https://t.co/YBAkRfyv63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RegulusdeLeo A) we just hired 50 people; B) the facts of history, science, crowds etc may frighten you snowflakes; it doesn't change them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's NSC chief's son declares exactly what this is: A "Muslim ban," whatever weasel words his dad and Trump's mi… https://t.co/7CxF6MgXcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 70 years and more, American science has triumphed because the USA got the best minds in the world. Now that's at risk. Thanks, Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huggjea Please try to educate yourself on the nexus between American innovation and immigration. https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke @LPDonovan Ignorant blowharding feels good to some people. So does bigotry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_NeoKong But I know facts frighten alt-right snowflakes. Better the screech your ignorance than actually learn. Go suck your thumb then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_NeoKong No. Now get out your crayons.Listen carefully.The fact of American science for 100 years is we get the best minds in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweets4tom Did you even try to learn facts? No--you are one of those little alt-right snowflakes who cower from facts and flee truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman Linked to 1955 Emmett Till Murder Tells Historian Her Claims Were False, via @nytimes https://t.co/JLd2dwbE5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweets4tom Please learn the facts. American innovation depends on immigration. Facts frighten snowflakes, but try: https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@efilnikcufecin7 Learn the facts of the nexus between American innovation and immigration. Even if facts scare little alt-right snowflakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derekahunter The bigger impact is likely on future applicants. See here re: American innovation and immigration. https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_NeoKong Please try to educate yourself on the nexus between American innovation and immigration. https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PollySigh1 @PaulBlu They're called "facts"--I know they frighten little alt-snowflakes like you. Try to learn: https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SomeRandomGuy5 The facts about American innovation and immigration. Ever been to Silicon Valley? https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waskov6 The facts about American innovation--the envy of the world--and immigration: https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsBankBiology You don't know the facts about American innovation and its relationship to immigration: https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haveaclue85 100 percent stupid answer. Please watch and learn. But thanks for playing! P.S. I hate anything latte. https://t.co/0pClP9Pt2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend who works at a top research university's computer science department says they've lost 11 prospective Ph.D candidates to the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaDupuy My point is that USA is now acting like a country that fears so much, it can't handle a film director's visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee Excellent read. Sobering. I think Obama reached out, connected with white voters more than you do--but you peg this moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowflake America. https://t.co/ardFTmhF7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee Majority of Trump voters were anti-Hillary,not pro-Trump. We didn't have a transformation, but a historically crappy candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimgeraghty @LouiseMensch I think we misread 11/8 if we think a revolution happened. Most voters'd tell you: 2 awful candidates, 1 worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimgeraghty @LouiseMensch And, by the way, in August, post-conventions, I told colleagues, friends I thought Trump would win. She sucked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimgeraghty @LouiseMensch Nah. Hillary. By a country mile. Anyone out on the trail knew it was no contest. She lost it more than he won it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF? Putin's Russia. https://t.co/Z651rgQNtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a slaughter of Jews. https://t.co/mvLXLMbC1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird that the Press Secretary thinks the perfectly non-pejorative word "demonstrator" is a vicious epithet. It's n… https://t.co/VZ3pbBFJh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @CNN They are demonstrating in support of their beliefs, "participating in a public display of opinion." Am. Heritage, 3rd ed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final proof of what was long suspected: Emmett Till was killed for a lie. He was 14, in the wrong place:Mississippi. https://t.co/fuOclTV4rS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you ruin the schools and trash liberal education: Citizens who cannot think.  https://t.co/5273EH6kyc via @UPROXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @dandrezner Precisely. It is the fallacy of an ahistorical mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It happened in Alternative Chicago. https://t.co/qS3yV2YdgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derekahunter I am not dismissing "the concept of voter fraud." I am citing a FACT: the local officials who run elections deny this claim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Secretaries of State of 50 states--Republicans and Democrats who, UNDER OATH, run our elections--say THERE IS N… https://t.co/EvbMQ2OXLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilsonWPA I don't use "pro-choice" or "pro-life" because they are inaccurate. No one is "anti-choice" or "anti-life." It's about law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilsonWPA @pegobry I try to stick with "pro-abortion-rights" and "anti-abortion-rights"--the constitutional issue we debate as citizens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is triggered by a free press in America, and, being an alt-right snowflake, he is lashing out. https://t.co/VWnJ31tVp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Snowflake?
https://t.co/oJiUMA3K9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man took an oath to defend the Constitution, now using his White House position to try to bully the free press. https://t.co/VmNcxnC1Wm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usacsmret Would you please define "Alt-Left"? And please provide your sources for the definition and the origin of the term. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aqenbpuu, the last time I checked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was disappointed they did not find the continent of Atlantis yet." Genius. https://t.co/A5ankPPzcV via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do the same thing. With @openculture. https://t.co/eyLgmhlFsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie @thegarance Talk about a snowflake. That screed is the crybabiest thing I have ever read. Almost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, fine, whatever, but--what about the ALTERNATIVE FACTS?? https://t.co/s8TlTNCl4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this count as "voter fraud"?
https://t.co/fWk9AU9gvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your service, my fellow American, @USMC Cpl Ali J. Mohammed! https://t.co/kReep4Kc0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrisinAL Good footnote that we should add to Lady Liberty, to keep her promise accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless these good people. https://t.co/L7i0twxsQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twood9891 Wrong. The Revolution was fought against a GOVERNMENT that had already waged war against the people. Not against one man talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is un-American to punch a man in the face because you don't like what he is saying. That this must be stated is a sad sign of our times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four-year-old daughter kicks two-year-old son in the face. In front of us. Denies it. My wife:"We don't do ALTERNATIVE FACTS in this house."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May 2014: TRUMP: "If I decide to run for office, I’ll produce my tax returns, ABSOLUTELY, and I would love to do that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May 13, 2016: TRUMP: "I am under audit now and as soon as the audit ends I’ll release my returns."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the love of sweet Christ. https://t.co/5oJtNyqQSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls: "Alternative facts"? "The party told you to reject the evidence of your eyes and ears. It was their final command." -Orwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardNixon103 Actual facts and stats: Nielsen ratings, DC metro ridership, chopper photos taken at noon in '17, 09, etc. Your hard facts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The party told you to reject the evidence of your eyes and ears. It was their final, most essential command." --Ge… https://t.co/NjQsDeAf9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pegobry @RossalynWarren No. Pew and other longstanding polls show the opposite. Your source? https://t.co/WS5Bt8f4Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kymanne2010 “The Party told you to reject all evidence with your eyes and ears. It was their final, most essential command.” ~ Orwell, 1984]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kymanne2010 Actual facts and stats: Nielsen ratings, DC metro ridership, chopper photos taken at noon in '17, 09, etc. What can you cite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A provable falsehood. https://t.co/XNPSrYMSzg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>