<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle In context, this comes across as though you're trying to invalidate how I understand my own experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle I don't understand what your point is supposed to be though. Like are you trying to say I'm WRONG, that *I* didn't choose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck this nonsense. I'm out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I experienced X"
"Well, for me, I experienced Y"
"So?"
"It's just I experienced Y"
"Okay..."
"I experienced Y, my feelings were very Y"
"…"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way some trans people just absolutely REFUSE to allow you to articulate an experience different than their own....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle YOUR transition is not MY transition. MY experience does not have to mirror YOURS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle WHAT. DOES. THAT. HAVE. TO. DO. WITH. WHAT. I. SAID.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtistGenn Dense. Wet. Extremely poverty overlapping with extreme wealth. New- lots of condo towers. Large Asian community. I dunno?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle Okayyyy... but again, what does this have to do with anything I'm saying???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not in a good mood right now so think carefully about what kind of nonsense you want to put in my mentions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steambelle Good for you. The fuck does that have to do with me and my experience?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["first time the word transgender has been said onstage at the superbowl!"

WHO GIVE A SHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is to say, we've all been rah rah rah Teen Vogue and all, but Phillip Picardi is shallow consumerist sheltered no-perspective garbage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guy, Phillip Picardi, is the same fuck who was also acting like BRANDS need unity and togetherness in this time of need earlier today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The appalling joke of this guy acting like he's the expert on LGBTQ attitudes towards that song while ignorant of t… https://t.co/eh9XOCuX6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACTUALLY IT IS *NOT* YOUR LAND, INCIDENTALLY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And while I'm on the clusterfuck of "Born This Way", I'd ALSO like to remind you that "This Land Is Your Land" is Colonial Settler Bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs Popular does not mean unquestioned or uncritiqued. Also kids are kids. They've got different needs/priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think that's some fucked up blasphemy or are terrified of what that might "imply", that is very very VERY much YOUR problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also fuck all of you:

I was not born trans. I became trans when I CHOSE to transition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PITY US, CISHETS, FOR WE CAN'T HELP OUR DISGUSTING CONDITION. https://t.co/kbXXOLGhd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES I AM LOOKING ALSO AT YOU MS. "VOGUE".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death to mediocre white cishet popstars and their false gay icon bullshit which lingers even as they relentlessly exploit / insult trans ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*siiiiighhhh*

This is probably happening all over the place tonight, too. https://t.co/hGW2s4ajUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ami_angelwings HOORAY the return of Off The Grid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born This Way: a song celebrating marginalized identities that is only actually enjoyed or appreciated by privileged self-satisfied "allies"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey white cishet liberals: even the LGBTQ community has extensively critiqued "Born This Way". Do you ever talk to ANYONE???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joffeorama I'm still really mad at him for the transphobic gag at the end of A Mighty Wind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am back and I am coooold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the awful soup truck I go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisSMcClain Probably. I think it'd have to be the Dominos.Ca site to have my address as an option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ice_Cream_Jones Like I know they won't do it by phone, I'm wondering if they'd do it on the WEBSITE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ice_Cream_Jones The Domino's website seems to have an option for paying while you order.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…to know for future reference. Like if I gave someone my address and they just ordered the pizza to be sent there on Dominos.ca?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's getting around when I need to go out to the truck, so don't have to time to find out if this is a workable option, but would be good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if Domino's online site lets you order a pizza for someone else?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravisSMcClain I did! Thank you. :) 

It just won't be in my account until tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish there were pizza places that accepted paypal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to have to trudge through the snow to the stupid soup truck and stand in the stupid line with the stupid bigots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxx_chaos @ami_angelwings Yao Ming even makes other basketball players look weirdly tiny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cos I mean like DAMN I could go for a pizza and some brandy right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am getting very sick of never being able to access money on weekends. :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah well it irritates me how every show or movie has a bunch of fucking heterosexual love story bullshit at the ce… https://t.co/80NI4apuiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingdamnit @ami_angelwings @filbypott Yeah, but... look at that Han. That is definitely NOT Harrison Ford. Only knew it's him from context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSteve2 A lot of people seem to not actually know of LeBoeuf's history of incredibly awful behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ami_angelwings @ingdamnit @filbypott Did the publishers not have rights to the actors' likenesses, btw?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ingdamnit But... it has nothing to do with the Conway Bowling Green op-ed attached????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ami_angelwings @filbypott I've got a bad feeling about that writer's dialogue choices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ami_angelwings @filbypott I don't know about y'all, but that "I've got a good feeling about this" line REALLY grates on me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See also: everyone deciding Jesse Singal, David Frum, Shia LeBoeuf and JK Rowling are suddenly heroes of hashtag the resistance. e_e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We really really REALLY need to start remember that a crisis does NOT require lowering your standards and ignoring everyone's bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's... like... three inches away from "homophobes are secretly gay" and "president tweets like a teen girl" bullshit. Tra la la.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got $20 says all the "conservatives are the REAL delicate snowflakes" is going to engender all kinds lefty homophobia and transmisogyny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blakestacey That's a cute... whatever it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if fascist imagery and costumes have become more or less popular in BDSM circles over the past 5 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys I hate to burst your bubble but I'm the next Doctor Who.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOLDIE_ice S/M Feminists don't screw in lightbulbs, they screw in carefully arranged and scheduled meet-ups in someone's basement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain YOU CAN'T HELP THEM TAMRA. SAVE YOURSELF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain Please make sure to stop your OWN episode of Voyager before assisting others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain …a Voyager-related emergency, the Emergency Manual Override can be used to cancel the episode. Do you understand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain …there should be a button labelled "stop", or marked with a small square. This is the EMERGENCY MANUAL OVERRIDE. In event of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain Tamra, I need you to breathe. Calm yourself down. You need to focus. DON'T PANIC. Now, look to your remote control...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta …different consumer preferences, and I'm not sure any of the three really serves us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta …really just says a lot more about you than about the situation. The media is providing different narratives for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta Whether you're seeing them as blundering baffoons, villainous puppetmasters or tough practical decisive leaders…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta I think it can just lend them a different mystique that helps anyway. Much like the "Bannon Great Manipulator" does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBonvillain But look at his little hood. I wonder if his mom knit it for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta …gained from following along with the soap opera of which fascist hates which fascist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta …paying attention - help? Like, aside from maybe spotting weak links and putting extra pressure there, what's to be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraerin @RaeBeta But... how? How do salacious details of the tensions within the ranks - that are already well apparent to anyone…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksej EXACTLY like with "alternative medicine". Works great if there's nothing actually wrong with you and you just need a placebo and time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksej No, it's still crap. I think it only works if you didn't ACTUALLY have any real problems in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was Curry's year idc idc idc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my head the Warriors still won, by the way, because I periodically forget who the other team even WAS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight them when you need to, but don't, like, go DIGGING for reasons to give them attention. Over shit like their SUPERBOWL picks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LRT- Seriously. If he's not getting punched, I DON'T WANNA HEAR ABOUT IT.

Stop helping shit little nazis be celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOLDIE_ice First question: why does no one know the term "switch"? :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagsVisaggs Also I wanna eat a giant fucking salmon while drunk on a bus some day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenFrug Oh Gaga just dressed in a costume EXTREMELY evocative of Dazzler's first look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay this one made me LOL. https://t.co/xy6b9p7dnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG I think I am falling in love with Mahershala. https://t.co/0V0dBb46tG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhhhh that makes sense.

Word should get out to Oly's community then: protest Brennan by protesting the shitty law. https://t.co/GTDaY5h9fX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaga is going to pay royalties to John Romita Jr. and Chris Claremont right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then stop voting for his cabinet picks and shit you ineffectual careerist weasel. https://t.co/kJFunAPTiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTW, how was Lady Gaga? Was she all disappointingly bland and non-commital white cis liberal and stuff like usual?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is she DOING in Oly anyway? There to help a usury corporation win a case against poor people or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to admit, I do kinda like the idea of Cathy Brennan having been specifically 86'd from The Brotherhood and Le Voyeur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly Underrated Simspons Character: https://t.co/imrI4JrZfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@its_so_soft You shut your lying mouth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrandonfrmNJ @MTFIII Oh god I'm so sick of old-style gritty FPS games. Enough already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANYWAY... wake me when it's time to ignore the Grey Cup and then snark about it.

zzzzzzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagsVisaggs I can't quite put my finger on it, but I SWEAR there was SOMETHING back in the fall, and another in the Summer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT DOES THIS REMIND ME OF...? https://t.co/FjtwpXBhST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs They still can't afford Ben Whishaw, Idris Elda or Judi Fucking Dench.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also... Hi, America. If you are upset about football tonight, just comfort yourself by remembering the looming threat of fascist autocracy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has Colonel Mustard reverted to chanting his campaign slogan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hayleyglyphs What, you expect Americans to know any British actors actually within the paygrade of BBC Cymru?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alfa Romeo ads in my feed? I can live with this. https://t.co/7bLot1SCbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I say England's greatest Prime Minister was Lord Palmerston"
"Pitt the Elder!"
"Lord Palmerston!
"Pitt the Elder!"
"That's it!" *pow*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpricecomicart @Steph_I_Will It sounds counter-intuitive at first, but it starts making more sense once you eat enough wings.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>