<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nerdarama @emmetbroaders @Bed_Forever_ I got accused of lifting my own tweet from Reddit last week. They are overprotective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh shit I didn't realise Breitbart was hiring characters from Guess Who now. https://t.co/adCP5FL3hH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Penguin bars need to expand their repertoire of joke formats or risk being left behind. Let's see an *extremely [blank] voice* or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hemorrhaging followers after disagreeing with the bag men, a known capital offence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Got it. There's a class of art that you are happy to use for your own personal gain without any consideration for the artist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits "That's the way things are" does not make following that way the right thing to do. You can be better than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits The difference being that your name was attached to that stuff. It's no help if a joke is seen by millions without credit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Good for you. I've an essay about why it's fine for me to sell CD-Rs of Bags of Glue on the side of the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits but only if they find out you've lifted their content]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits If you can't credit, don't share it. With an audience like yours you have a responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Got it. There's a class of art that you are happy to use for your own personal gain without any consideration for the artist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits You can always do it, but you choose not to. Nobody is forcing you to post lifted content uncredited on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Got it. There's a class of art that you are happy to use for your own personal gain without any consideration for the artist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lifting by omission: apparently fine https://t.co/phRSM8xj3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits @emmetbroaders or you could only post things that you can credit because they don't just appear out of thin fucking air]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetbroaders I look forward to reading your new action-thriller novel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see they had twitter as well https://t.co/dr9spZwGYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tagging someone in a comment to show them a post is like screaming their name repeatedly in the supermarket when you find the cereal aisle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'll watch Children of Men every week until I pinpoint exactly when it becomes better than reality https://t.co/Ksdd6TMV1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As suspected this tweet has been deleted. Retweet far and wide https://t.co/1bp1n5e5IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll never guess how much abuse I got from that numbers tweet during the week. I'll give you a hint: I'm a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most likely action by Irish gov't in response to Trump's executive order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a theory that no joke has aged worse than every single reference to Who Wants to Be a Millionaire in the Simpsons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wikileaks is stooping very low by doxing these innocent sharks https://t.co/K0mF2Kf1dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancisTheTwitt I prefer accusing them of stealing all of their stock from Reddit as a guy in a fedora pockets Time Outs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hexplex Right, but it wasn't. Unless there's some other Reddit post I'm unaware of, which you could link me to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hexplex some lad nicked it to post on Reddit from here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number of times Theresa May referred to the US as Britain's "best bud": 6
Number of times Trump's motorcade left her behind at the mall: 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HughsNughs I'm leaning into the darkness in case of nuclear winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one hour thing is certainly a very specific trope of 24. But babies were few and far between. All and all, I'm not feeling this pitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who am I in this scenario that a terrorist has targeted my baby specifically and I also have access to interrogate them? Am I Jack Bauer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A single baby is a very low bar for a terrorist to set themselves https://t.co/UHw67YNJiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["hit by car while refreshing notifications" https://t.co/g9Pzcvejjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I shouldn't drink this for breakfast like a viscous latte but I am still very tempted to buy https://t.co/J3uddl3TAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day on Twitter https://t.co/HqYIkLBRKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mentions this morning vs my mentions this evening https://t.co/1Da0d9KaNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 prediction: North Korea hacks control of the world's jukeboxes and plays the theme song of Star Trek Enterprise on an unstoppable loop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I know how Oppenheimer felt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone nicked my joke about the relay logo to post on Reddit and yes some of the takes are of course awful https://t.co/1buUARlkKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers, they are relentless https://t.co/MXvQnZynzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is in the wild https://t.co/iDIE0wiUmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's one thing I've learned today it's that an awful lot of people think women don't wear watches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ohjann would it have been too much effort for them to link to the tweet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnorthside that's the sort of pessimism I can get behind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnorthside well nobody has explained the joke back to me or told me to kill myself, so I believe this is an above average experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetbroaders my mentions are making me dizzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that sure blew up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy 1: OK. Nail polish on the hand means it's a woman.
Guy 2: You can't see the other hand's nails. How do we make… https://t.co/Dc38kOjZ7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nibORee honestly I can't imagine how you could have been more sound about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An absolutely normal reaction to being asked to be considerate https://t.co/OFm7mydMNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetbroaders I'm confident they're capable of this while still ruining countless lives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be disappointed in capitalism if Nestlé's marketing team haven't spent the week working on a Rolos sponsorship of the new Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryosull [distant sound of a fog horn in the docks] ah, that must be my shipment of spurious tangents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can define what "bread" is and I'm now scared I will be devoured by cannibals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda @oceanclub @MajorThrill @ownohmanny @johnorthside Then you are either being disingenuous or a fool I have no intention of educating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please set out the guidelines on stealing bread to feed your family. How hungry are they? Is pizza bread? Yes or no answers only please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda @oceanclub @MajorThrill @ownohmanny @johnorthside You honestly don't see the difference between Richard Spencer and Katie Hopkins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda @oceanclub @MajorThrill @ownohmanny @johnorthside well if you think so but you seem to be having a lot of trouble comprehending it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda @oceanclub @MajorThrill @ownohmanny @johnorthside the world is not black and white with a simple set of rules, imagine that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryosull In what hypothetical scenario would that many hypothetical scenarios be useful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda Oh no, it's against the rules. I just can't stop you because that's also against the rules. Violence is always wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faduda look, if you really want to punch her I'm not going to stop you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a debating tactic https://t.co/h1AihazTzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please fund my team's development of a high-powered laser that will burn this tweet into the surface of the moon https://t.co/UnZSYobgcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: We're all on board with the good thing?
[Liberal pulls up in overloaded articulated lorry]
L: Hold on, I've some hypothetical scenarios.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sheer amount of misplaced forethought by NBC in the Friends pilot building a set for Ross's apartment but not Joey and Chandler's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand how teaching a hawk and parrot to fetch and harass fascists for my entertainment doesn't fall under free speech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you stick a teaspoon in your mouth you're
a) 7 years or younger
b) out of normal spoons, desperate
c) a weirdo with a Peter Pan complex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just remembered that those chocolate petit filous exist and I am now desperate to pick up a six pack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancisTheTwitt or to put it another way... https://t.co/UnZSYobgcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancisTheTwitt I'm talking more of the masses (here &amp; generally) who need to model everything as a simple set of rules applied universally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But what about this different scenario? Why isn't that the same thing?" - almost every single argument made on here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptainWavey I may as well be using a deck of cards in that case. I'm no Luddite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free speech is under attack because Piers Morgan has repeatedly refused to make a personal appearance on my Solitaire Let's Play channel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the most sophisticated joke I will ever make]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Third Man (1949) https://t.co/GmZjb51nkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, it took Star Wars 40 years to get to eight episodes but the Fast and Furious franchise did it in just 16.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guarantee you that Star Wars title was "The Young Jedi" up until three weeks ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You shouldn't punch nazis
You shouldn't punch anyone
You shouldn't move at all, even to eat

At what point should I stop generalising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to start storing these here https://t.co/q0yYQ5QGF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Teknogrot in my experience they tend to be the talkers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leedalyire I've known for a long time that it's going to get me killed one day. But you've got to stand up for what's right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're swell people. It's really sound to ignore the performer and annoy everyone within earshot of you. Go to more public events please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to the constantly talking couple standing behind me at the gig last night who when asked to stop talking told me to fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really simple folks: the only people you're morally justified to punch are nazis and anyone with a "hit me" sign taped to their back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On closer inspection this lad seems to think people are using nazi as a synonym for "supporter of free speech". Christ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind whatever the fuck "supporters of free speech" means here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "get off" here is indicative of a complete inability to distinguish between what is ethical or good and what is… https://t.co/ERWCk44iNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonSpittle Good luck tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Trump needs to do is put together 3 coherent sentences with some basis in reality and the media will reset; "sombre" "ready to lead" etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been home sick for a week but I get to go to this tonight, a date burned into my mind by @AlisonSpittle's Twit… https://t.co/7qGCmaK263]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is really outshining our abortion prohibitionists when it comes to being petty about crowd sizes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give it until the end of February before Trump starts to publicly demand that Japan acknowledges the existence of Pokémon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey fascists, why don't you try to make Venezuela great again first?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These so-called progressives riot for free air, yet never speak out about the lack in air in outer space because it's not trendy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The far right sock puppets are having a really hard time keeping the mask from slipping https://t.co/d8OKLJampM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ, look at who Irish Central have given the @POTUS account to now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilverStGroud technology never works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilverStGroud please make this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know when someone takes up two seats on the bus and you're annoyed they've broken the rules? Fascists are like that but with genocide.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>