<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Flynn, @WhiteHouse national security adviser: #Iran is "on notice" https://t.co/bkKxYxWF7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @dbyman: Why Trump’s Policies Will Increase Terrorism—and Why Trump Might Benefit as a Result https://t.co/s4o7BnflIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sincerely hope this is untrue, but #Trump admin continues to surprise https://t.co/UPsIRQIwHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama 'fundamentally disagrees' with Trump's immigration order https://t.co/MQgcnqyZ7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon Is Given Security Role Usually Held for Generals https://t.co/sYZOA1iK5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW, those charged w #terrorism-related offenses since March 2011 did NOT radicalize thru networks of #Syrian and #Iraqi immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, #immigrants/#refugees from #Syria and #Iraq are responsible for ZERO terrorist attacks in the US https://t.co/nEAsXEPgup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anxiety About Muslim Refugees Is Stoked Online by the Far-Right Media https://t.co/ctzZySs3L2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like shameless self promotion... Thanks, @DanielGHajjar! https://t.co/TULOLpy8Ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House discussing asking foreign visitors for social media info and cell phone contacts https://t.co/GBoVd8vYpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More likely "imminent threat" merely another example of fear-mongering like that used in #Trump campaign re… https://t.co/05bpfGOIIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in the #DC area and don't support Trump's #EO re #refugees and #visaholders, join me and the amazing… https://t.co/U3rF1oQvfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Commando Killed in Yemen in Trump’s First Counterterror Operation https://t.co/zyoxayWcXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Federal Judge Just Issued A Stay Against Donald Trump's "Muslim Ban" #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/4mlnNJNJ30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @POTUS truly cared about #humanitarian issues in #Syria, he wouldn't have signed #EO re #refugees #NoBanNoWall… https://t.co/nQe0GhVjM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran to ban US citizens in response to Trump's order https://t.co/sWuTClo6Bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Iraqis file lawsuit after being detained in NY due to travel ban https://t.co/SoXIa80ktt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a tragedy #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/1JfJJ3XGbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece. I'm so lucky to have worked with the incredibly strong and inspiring @OulaAlrifai for a short time.… https://t.co/27lYqS9WhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrageous- majority of #Assad, #ISIS, &amp; #AQ targets in #Syria are Muslim; at same time, ZERO Syrian refugees charg… https://t.co/JHBluGgbtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given @realDonaldTrump's back and forth on use of coercive practices, this announcement is only marginally reassuri… https://t.co/mnvALIquZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NPR: Young Girls Are Less Apt To Think That Women Are Really, Really Smart https://t.co/H5TWkVktLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for saying what everyone's thinking, @GloriaBorger. Especially proud to be a @colgateuniv alum tonight. https://t.co/YsHGKVzyyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeamusHughes @_bCliff looking forward to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon of day 6: @PressSec @seanspicer calls #media "opposition party" and says press "should keep its mouth shu… https://t.co/l4OtlHVHeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexzfinley a better solution for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on waterboarding: 'We have to fight fire with fire' - despite evidence #torture doesn't work https://t.co/1l4sY7Xr2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not supportive of this #EO, but #SaudiArabia, where majority of 9/11 hijackers came from and #Wahhabism thrives, is… https://t.co/Dy2F9f6Yt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For second time, @PressSec @seanspicer avoids clear answers re: alleged reexamination of CIA detention sites and interrogation tactics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump draft order seeks review on terror interrogations  https://t.co/3hpwYm1NGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a wonderful use of government resources. @realDonaldTrump, you are POTUS - let it go and get to work. https://t.co/qe4wbGys5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bill has already been introduced into Congress to remove the US from the United Nations https://t.co/TAtj7sN9o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When asked what #Trump will do with #Guantanamo and 40+ remaining detainees, @seanspicer says no decision has been made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@seanspicer now says NONE of those present at #Trump CIA speech were there with #POTUS, all were "CIA people"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We rely on the government for lots of data. What happens to that in the era of ‘alternative facts?’ https://t.co/NptZCTvMBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked if #Trump admin will work with Assad against #ISIS, @seanspicer avoids direct answer, says USG will parter w allies sharing US values]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump administration's continued embrace of authoritarian leaders is a dangerous trend, esp as strategic allies ar… https://t.co/MXx6wE5MPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the #alternativefacts keep on coming... https://t.co/qpnhPS8ukj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic partnerships should not take a backseat to quickly defeating #ISIS, itself an unrealistic goal https://t.co/PyhOQjdOhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, #alternativefacts being thrown around once again https://t.co/lkiCNqGdaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, You Look Like an Arab Country Right Now https://t.co/7aVcQj9sE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning of day three: @KellyannePolls defends @seanspicer's blatant lies as #alternativefacts, also known as lies https://t.co/S86Fw6cHPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smashed windows, chaotic confrontation near inauguration https://t.co/61AFrp87uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican senators "seem to love big government when it comes to imposing what they believe" https://t.co/hWGtaLWvar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES: "Equating violent extremism exclusively with Islamist terrorism misses opportunities to solve the problem." https://t.co/tYOF6canIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not only are America’s institutions particularly ill-equipped...to stand up against Trump; in some cases they may… https://t.co/wFGSASSfoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jihadwatchRS Bigotry aside,  before peddling alarmist rhetoric about Muslim converts becoming terrorists, get you… https://t.co/VrFDLreQ81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narrowing focus on #CT in direct opposition to stated effort to bar Syrian refugees and limit travelers from terror… https://t.co/76uE7kGjQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skeptical of post hoc claimed link to #ISIS until verified - many US persons made similar claims that still lack su… https://t.co/uhTebUhVzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impact on future of chemical weapons taboo? - Reuters: Assad linked to Syrian chemical attacks for first time https://t.co/CsBaxtUbtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F.B.I. Arrests Wife of Killer in Orlando Mass Shooting https://t.co/556LRqLUXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PT Get to know the #WiSeInitiative women and keep up with their work: https://t.co/sYaUv9UVAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @MaggieCaroline1 for creating @AmSecProject's #WiSeInitiative! So excited to be on board with such stellar ladies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potentially frightening consequences: Trump team seeks names of officials working to counter violent extremism https://t.co/hO8WZrO8bB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredibly dangerous to declare intent before investigators release statement. Discipline and facts should rule in… https://t.co/YTh7ZiYQEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump supporters who commit hate crimes have been https://t.co/pMx7goaT6G https://t.co/Fuu65uTlk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian army, Iraqi militia accused of 'slaughter' of civilians in Aleppo https://t.co/Zp9syuSPbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbyman Thanks! Really appreciate it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Levitt_Matt @gwupoe Thanks Matt! It means a lot coming from you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RashaAlAqeedi Thanks, Rasha! Hope all is well with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Op-ed with @amhitchens: What is inspiring homegrown terror in the U.S.? It’s not just the Islamic State. https://t.co/2FXEZVrRrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My newest piece for @GWUPOE: Since March 2011, 178 Americans were charged with terrorism-related offenses -- 79 cas… https://t.co/U4b4YzbkwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielGHajjar Thanks! Looking forward to feedback!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Party May Have Triggered San Bernardino Terror Attack: Police - ABC News - https://t.co/mIdZ8sEd7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel accuses Iran of sending Hezbollah arms on commercial flights https://t.co/Sa3R5eMDBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Syria is anything but #Hezbollah's Vietnam - read my newest piece in @gssreview to learn why: https://t.co/UDYvgT8eIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Trump Rises, So Do Some Hands Waving Confederate Battle Flags https://t.co/09S4fwcp6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're reading anything on Trump today, this should be it: Donald Trump and the Normalization of Torture https://t.co/9bcQOdLYPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. authorities warn of al Qaeda threat to election https://t.co/RzDBEn4zJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Birth of Terrorist Deradicalization Programming in the U.S.?" by yours truly, via @gssreview: https://t.co/eS1WHWmXyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY, NJ Bombing Suspect Rahami in Custody After Shootout  https://t.co/1gXXCNLiyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marchello Dsaun McCain, brother of American #ISIS fighter Douglas McCain, admits lying to FBI terror investigators https://t.co/cM4ezir5uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“And we should not forget al Qaeda, because al Qaeda was the cradle from which ISIS came.” https://t.co/oBEj6W0d9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hoffman_bruce: As ISIS "[consumes] all the oxygen in the room” for W CT officials, “nobody paying attention to AQ” https://t.co/oBEj6W0d9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning from the Sahel: Al Qaeda's Resurgent Threat https://t.co/OgxcMMHVjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is Qutb’s message-adapted by later jihadi ideologues-that unites local &amp; regional conflicts into global movement https://t.co/7CfPNA0K8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PT, @ReutersWorld: "Sunni leaders in Iraq and Western diplomats fear the Shi’ite militias might commit worse excesses in Mosul."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PT "Shia militias detained, tortured, &amp; abused more Sunni civilians during US-supported recapture of ISIS-held Fallujah than US claims"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special Report: Massacre reports show U.S. inability to curb Iraqi Shi'ite militias  https://t.co/HNCTpupqMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS using female suicide bombers in defence of Sirte – pro-government forces  https://t.co/zXGpCHo4Ui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeamusHughes Sullivan appears to either have no knowledge of/refuses to acknowledge Garland (May 3) &amp; Usaama Rahim (June 2) attacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another of many American ISIS recruits connected to Junaid Hussein https://t.co/q83jyfSCko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PeterRNeumann: "He walks you to the cliff, and you’re supposed to decide yourself whether to take the last step." https://t.co/9SrqIUOUFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shin Bet: #Hezbollah has made priority of sparking terror attacks from afar, but not clearly expressing involvement https://t.co/xMUWyLXIot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dearborn man lied about dental visit to join Hezbollah https://t.co/Wb4CP5eo7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the link below for more on balancing "concerns over entrapment with the need to disrupt terror plots" https://t.co/ainpd9gC7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To date, 100 US persons have been charged with ISIS-related offenses. So far in 2016: 22 arrests. More info: @gwupoe https://t.co/rG4nTA7Xgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Charles_Lister: AQ "coordinating" dissolution of ties for "sake of preserving long-term viability of JN &amp; jihadi strategic objectives."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PT: "Latest reflection of a new &amp; far more potentially effective method of jihad focused on collective, gradualist, &amp; flexible action."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be fooled by the rebranding -- JN "remains as potentially dangerous, and as radical, as ever" https://t.co/8CkHp6BwHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorist or Disturbed Loner? Munich Attack Reveals Shifting Labels https://t.co/h6X8CcXmtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Absence of narrow terrorism indicators is not followed by the absence of indicators of radicalization &amp; violence." https://t.co/QvHm3PswE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hizbullah Urges End to 'Political Support' for Terror, Slams Nice Attack  https://t.co/Q3ZFaYebXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi Shi'ite cleric tells followers to target U.S. troops fighting Islamic State https://t.co/fREayDdd2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read for anyone interested in terrorist, specifically #ISIS, use of the internet https://t.co/DLAIzomnBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underreported and arguably most interesting component of cases against Yassin and McNeil  https://t.co/TT0rqTCor9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mahin Khan, arrested July 1, pleads not guilty to state-level, #ISIS-related terrorism charges https://t.co/SgdMCLWTZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bahrain arrests 2 over June 30 bombing, blames Iran - says suspects trained in weapons &amp; explosives by IRGC https://t.co/Bt7dKNKZ1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rotella: ISIS delegates much more autonomy to FTFs than AQ, sends more FTFs back to countries of origin to conduct attacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rotella: "organized crime and terrorism are overlapping like never before"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>