<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewKick @MikeCarlton01 we like our dingoes too much - maybe a white pointer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe me there is way more painting and drinking coffee than actual gaming. https://t.co/XcX8caO0Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Jesse my miniature wargaming hubby @ArchivesDavid wants to know who you are painting https://t.co/AjGirdV3ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Blocks Part of Trump’s Immigration Order https://t.co/Ei4Fn2ia8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Park Rangers to the Rescue https://t.co/MGtLk2uyh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maudeygirl 4 of us here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Sorry cats, doggos run the internet now https://t.co/rd20Z6tC2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MillarLaura @ausarchivists @CassPF @morethangrass almost as good as this one by @CassPF https://t.co/Ogt83J7Fwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop MPs wasting taxpayers money on personal expenses - Federal corruption watchdog NOW! - Sign th... https://t.co/g86hilkYfm via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Commutes Bulk of Chelsea Manning’s Sentence https://t.co/m3bdTvm3Yu 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/86utyavvLF had to pay the huge sum of $640 for school fees this year at our local public high school!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Begging for bacon pug style https://t.co/gAlkDW7yga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cleansing ale too? https://t.co/G1Po6HGge3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you feeling today @beet_keeper ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pork belly and fish &amp; chips at the Rowing Club https://t.co/s6Gk6f2hwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beet_keeper bloody hell! Sabotage? One day I will tell you my yoga mat/bike/ broken collarbone story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowy the tawny frogmouth. Photo: Judi Gray https://t.co/5BvrqegXRA via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Nation Candidate ‘Not The Right Kind Of Bigot’ Hanson Says https://t.co/yqB63r8iEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who needs a vacuum cleaner when there is a pug to clean up spilt flour https://t.co/FiuLtR0xLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wragge check out Conman on Vimeo for more Alan Tudyk goodness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Colbert, Michael Stipe, and James Franco sum up 2016 in song: https://t.co/i5jklzq7Nw via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Max impression of a polar bear waiting silently near a seal air hole https://t.co/rWuxh0351a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me at The Heart Foundation Gear Up Girl 2017 on 12 March, 2017!  https://t.co/0BFlbd860c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superglue it - it's the only way it will hold together. https://t.co/WDZnKMn8RL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive fur seal squashes car in Tasmanian driveway https://t.co/jSGgU7ua5H via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexischnauzer Max has had it twice. Recovered well with pain relief and fluids. Keep him away from ham sausages and other fatty foods now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frisson of excitement going to work Christmas party today @srnsw https://t.co/5QACV2WeNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mansours_sydney been trying to get someone to look at a broken blind for over 3 weeks now. Your customer service used to be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a cyclist I love getting a letter asking me to object to a cycleway. Especially when they don't put their name o… https://t.co/DOgkBKUIil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone needing a sauna should just head over to Sydney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor nephew scored an own goal😟]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Max agrees. Will only enter water if there is a duck. https://t.co/doWMkAMyws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo of the Day: Best of November https://t.co/uPWtfasJYV via @NatGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the State Theatre in Sydney to see Bill Bailey tonight. https://t.co/3Ihd5fTCpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell to a wonderful friend, colleague and mentor to many of us. Vale Sigrid. https://t.co/zizsx1fzxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project films of Royal Easter Show https://t.co/BcEAnPXAKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project did address vicarious trauma for staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project statistics https://t.co/W0io4D1vhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project also uncovered blank tapes in the collection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project more whoopsies https://t.co/z0mrnqqaSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project whoopsies! https://t.co/gc7B0zx7OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project film preservation and access requirements https://t.co/U9fpuZmW0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project leant heavily on NSW Digital archives team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project @srnsw metadata fields for videos @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/LcetfwKNxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project included tributes from Martin Place Siege such as notes teddies photos etc @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation included Gaol Photo description books https://t.co/CpAHpC5cOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emergency Digitisation project focused on these formats @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/WIWuWG7Snu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna Gray on @srnsw Emergency Digitisation of At Risk Archives project https://t.co/2A28t7EWHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damon Rees: up to now NSW Government tolerant of the cloud but should we now become cloud first @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damon Rees: often technology people use in private outstrips what Government can provide @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damon Rees NSW Government Chief Information &amp; Digital Officer up next @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikejonesmelb @morethangrass @david_b_fricker @glhhlg @ausarchivists Liquid Learning confs always very expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screenshot of digital archive from Chelmsford Royal Commission @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/P4y9JCU7SP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analytics Centre: NSW Govt mashing data @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/CUsqCGgnC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuel Check: Govt use of aggregated data from non Govt sources. Legislation passed to requirevsubmission of data… https://t.co/xfogYcrjay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State Archives and Records Authority https://t.co/wUEMv7jgqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolf Green: technology can remove pixels from de-identified photos @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DataNSW where you can load your open data @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolf speaking on potential difficulties of Blockchain and long term records @srnsw RM Forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain being investigated in NSW @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/0UseireRcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting NSW Govt data https://t.co/L76KQLpxZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storing NSW Govt data @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/32pY8rVzYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MyServiceNSW @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/C1Uk3pBYy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transaction Data NSW @srnsw RM forum https://t.co/URQ72eB8Cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole of NSW Govt approachbto data @srnsw RM Forum https://t.co/7yCkP2pPbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partnership models for open data e.g. Fuel Check which tells where cheap petrol is @srnsw RM forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srnsw Records Managers Forum today. Rolf Green Manager Information Policy &amp; Innovation on States of Data. Also an… https://t.co/ux8r0XBoJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim!! #CrowdedHouseLive https://t.co/MKekFa4iMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewieandmilou for you https://t.co/BmKFI3DGmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stewieandmilou excellent. Lovely night in Sydneyvand Crowded House are playing in front of the Opera House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely Kiwi lads #crowdedhouselive https://t.co/D9O75hojUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for proud auntie retweeting #gojake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican confirms Francis did not renew terms of Burke, Pell on worship congregation https://t.co/sQQN2HYslJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay. Nephew scored first goal of professional football career today @CCMariners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthD53 specially his lopsided ear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for her to come back inside #notsafewithoutschnauzerprotection https://t.co/c8fYTK5pGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can send as much prosecco as they like to Sydney! Silly Brexit people. https://t.co/SWxc2z95uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircut today: short back and sides with fluffy tail https://t.co/Up8uPQC7MN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markival this is just awful. Feeling for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So today no wifi at work, no email or Google Play at home #blamingtrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be compulsory in schools and workplaces. https://t.co/YFDxSbOQDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver lining: 9 American states passed gun control laws yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling the need for a Neenish Tart today and David Jones food hall is unfortunately very close to work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the skies over Sydney gently weep. https://t.co/jNy8YRyMMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I'll go home and watch something more cheerful like The Walking Dead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home fireworks mostly banned in Australia. We just have the big official ones like NYE. https://t.co/mg5RlYIcrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Fish &amp; Co for @ArchivesDavid birthday https://t.co/d0xEUslgxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchivesDavid getting ready for battle https://t.co/kTPPlE8By1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear ... Kath and Kim got it right. https://t.co/EblMqJR7oV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sneezed all over my phone #damnheadcold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Force is obviously very strong with this one.. https://t.co/NKYw6txQaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent and handy to have a person with 2000 Twitter followers on board. https://t.co/AlPxUIjksd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grumpy Donuts Opens in Camperdown on Broadsheet -  https://t.co/5oYMuoXoyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't mind a bit of consultation https://t.co/BX1YLNfxgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like a job for an archivist. https://t.co/yM7IJEmFkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could do a short black https://t.co/GSQiwWJRNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My boutique loot ftom @ausarchivists conference #asalinks https://t.co/5ovy5h3SPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky the @ausarchivists conference just finished https://t.co/kI2KKgXyA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My knees feel for you https://t.co/pXM1Bpj4hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive - I was asleep the whole time https://t.co/ZXCpJq9uFO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>