<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#education Imagine if the 100s of millions of A$ spent on inefficient private providers had gone to TAFEs around Aus https://t.co/X3q9zyzy0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nswpol @GladysB wants to give Aussies plenty of time to put hand up for NSW police boss ... the ones who've been hiding for the past 3yrs+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1johnhampshire @joshgnosis Seems Latham (remember Howard "grip of death"?) may share trait with @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/VLxUYGjuIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Seem I'm getting to this @LiberalAus fed govt: yesterday #ScottMorrison blocked me, now #PeterDutton. Guess the truth is hurting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol OK, #peterdutton now officially demented https://t.co/wjazltjgu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis Worst case of Relevance Deprivation Syndrome I've ever seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micmehmet @joshgnosis Real soon now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SydneyEditor1 Neville Shute's On The Beach brought that to an earlier audience &amp; a 1959 movie w fantastic cast shot in Melbourne 1958-59.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Let's just say this again: Goldman Sachs, Turnbull's old mob, says 60% of @LiberalAus corp tax cuts will go… https://t.co/kGjHNVnZt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnews @freyapetersen "Land of the free" always a bad joke, along lines of "all men are created equal" in Constitution of slave nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PmPaulKeating @davrosz Venal politicians have probably made it nigh-impossible to stuff that genie back in the bottle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz @TheKouk - #PHON having a "position' on energy is like @SenatorMRoberts having a "position" on climate change #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nswpol Maybe this is why inglourious basterd Baird baled out - so he could get a taste of fees as a banker again https://t.co/YsjsxbySzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tech @nytimesworld @markscott82 @nytimes And the amount of bandwith used by site advertising increases 30% annually too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoshFrydenberg "Tech neutral"?! Minister, if the engines of state are in neutral when it comes to tech Australia is falling behind #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Geez, &amp; we thought Australia had an agonisingly long campaign! Maybe English is hoping he'll get lost in th… https://t.co/ADLZzFw1iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol As John Kennedy Toole described it, a confederacy of dunces. In Aus terms, also a fair sprinkling of out-&amp;-… https://t.co/7WXQ92bx5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisa_alba @43a6f0ce5dac4ea Trump's own actions have done more to delegitimise his presidency than any acts by others could have #uspoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NannanBay Yep: shame they had to chop @billshortenmp off at 1.30pm while he was still answering. Let's how @TurnbullMalcolm goes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Not only are our political donation laws a joke, they apparently can be abrogated at the PM's whim: https://t.co/yRBCOeKz85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Oops. @TurnbullMalcolm apparently has learned nothing since US election, took Trump at his word #fail https://t.co/S31OjhsE5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EVERALDATLARGE @geeksrulz As has been demonstrated repeatedly down the decades. Purely politics for plutocrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol (sigh) How good would it be to have an Australian prime minister not only prepared to talk like this but ev… https://t.co/a7HGi5d0pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#climate #agriculture Finally: a clever, considered -- &amp; eminently achievable! -- plan from someone who knows what… https://t.co/zB26wOeINg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis Until Aus has real-time, transparent notification of all political donations, a whiff of corruption will hang over body politic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrDenmore As Brooks notes, it's not a Republican admin but corporatist - &amp; this is tie that binds @TurnbullMalcolm to Trump #auspol #uspoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens @smh Oh yes, I'd never say don't try it - nothing wrong w the concept. Not sure our @LiberalAus Trump fan club all that inviting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHSommers @CollegeFix This story is encouraging on many levels after days of enduring The Don's chaos streaming live from the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sydneygrrl @geeksrulz @ezraklein @voxdotcom As our homegrown varieties demonstrate on a daily basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens @smh Convince talented ppl to come to Aus instead of US? Unlikely w our toxic fed govt. Trudeau will win them for Canada #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea True. But "saving Christians" largely incidental Bashar's aims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PPantsdown @ItsBouquet More like "Soggy peas in our time."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea What odious crap. Is Bizarre Bashar trying to rewrite history?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#education Dang, I'd like to do this course:
https://t.co/x6U5J79fPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lifelovehateooo @Forthleft2 He finds cartoon fish more entertaining than all this prez-schmez stuff, obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef What have Suadis ever done to Australia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli I bet @realDonaldTrump would sign up for this because he's a smart man, right? Isn't that what he said? https://t.co/Kmk2ZLUech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronnie1924 @elliemail @pryorlisa @TurnbullMalcolm True: he was far more Ollie when he first stepped up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people pay high price for private transport? Because it provides an irreplaceable mobility, utility &amp; status https://t.co/9X8sasDPFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep @ItsBouquet Not bad Bill, but feel free to release your inner PJK any time you like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa @elliemail Victorians used a word, etiolated, to describe an ephemeral presence. It's how I see @TurnbullMalcolm. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one: https://t.co/BS5aMEAvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @RobMax4 @TurnbullMalcolm Now you mention it, he does have something of a Neville Chamberlain air about him, doesn't he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirThomasWynne @guardian - @TonyAbbottMHR, hate to say it but it's been all over for yonks, mate. We've just been waiting for you to get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargotSaville @joshgnosis Anthony Weiner, the nominative determinist who wears his disgrace rather lightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaYaKnoMi @thealien_earth @amazon @SumOfUs Geez, pretty soon they'll be able to impeach Trump  by popular acclaim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon Shocking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli Some pretty good insights:
https://t.co/83ISJ0K6xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_cronin48 Since they are patently not pro-life (once kids are born), let's revert to real descriptor they try to avoid: anti-abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucerossbrc And I don't think Travolta's face can move much any more, but still - your point is sound!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucerossbrc Keith Urban, Nic's hubbie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Wonderful record on techmeister PM @TurnbullMalcolm's watch, eh? The Man Who Won't Be Told. https://t.co/hAWR4hOiSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi @43a6f0ce5dac4ea #Banthetoddler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee @geeksrulz Be better if it were Put-rid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli Get the full story behind @realDonaldTrump's voter fraud bullcrap. https://t.co/koZBYO4xCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tech This is likely to cause a few problems:
https://t.co/A3ItG7qYzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMcIlroy @ScottMorrisonMP Oops! I've upset poor Mr Morrison &amp; now he's blocked me. #hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMcIlroy OK, @ScottMorrisonMP officially a gibbering idiot. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiccoliMp Hard to escape notion that dedication to your ministerial duties did not meet w approval at the top of @LiberalNSW. #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny Oh, so Trump's rescinded his EO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#energy I knew Australia was getting ripped off blind by the sector, but this is simply appalling. All Aus politica… https://t.co/B67VJs8vEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol Next on mealy-mouthed Malcolm's to-do list: "Work out how to surrender Aussies' PBS pot of gold to US Big P… https://t.co/Hu64f8oLxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @BellaFlokarti @Qldaah Sure, but key lesson for developers &amp; govt cronies is - they can get away w it while raking it in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjukes Don't think he ever ended his campaign rhetoric, even after inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#economy #taxes This story offers a great way to defeat the profit-shifters. Cmon, @TurnbullMalcolm, follow The Don! https://t.co/5qftLMSq9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli #auspol Could irony be greater: no chemical weapons in Saddam's Iraq; but there may be now. Confirmation ne… https://t.co/BBEUDMR7KW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qldaah While Sydney is despoiled by frantic building of tomorrow's slums: lookalike unit blocks that lack any amenity &amp; destroy any nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JlSpback @MrSirUgly The elephant in the Israeli room: world's decades-long tolerance of land theft under guise of rptd worthless treaties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moorehn @MSMWatchdog2013 Of course, SCOTUS decision giving corporates same standing in law as ppl cleared the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moorehn @MSMWatchdog2013 Next: return of the robber barons, these days known as global corporatists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PurePapua @MdmAbsentMinded I suspect this is well understood by Jakarta: so what has happened manifests govt policy. Aus won't protest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacktheInsider @Forthleft2 Seriously, I feel like a spectator at the descent of US from greatness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol 2/2 Array of vested interests - corporate &amp;/ or religious &amp;/or political &amp;/or social - will need to be foug… https://t.co/wP5Hd94Q7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol They can do this because, alone among liberal Western democracies, Australia does not have a Bill of Rights… https://t.co/1gpEQy2R2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GiacomoJhall68 Hope you're managing to deal w the damage, friend. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ch150ch @randlight @autostraddle Thanks, appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#global #economy #auspol #uspoli A sign @realDonaldTrump may have lot more trouble w the US economy than he thinks. https://t.co/G0UQWVVEUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scattermae777M @LaLegale Wow! Great shot! Possible caption: "Payback's SUCH a bitch!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICYMI Lots of ppl have seen this by now, but I can't let such a powerful graphic go by unacknowledged. https://t.co/EJ4tzRcJOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Yup. Pretty decent minister too, overall. Not as though @LiberalAus is overburdened with obvious talent. #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randlight Always wonder why so many hard Right globally have links to religious oddballs. Faith usually precedes politics. Which prevails?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absurd gush by UK media. If only her name had been Caroline Sweet, eh Neil? Touching you ... touching me https://t.co/vnkXKZV8iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I first saw #JohnHurt in Midnight Express, had no idea who he was but his talent shone like a beacon in lacklustre cast. Well done, sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylepope @MrDenmore Finally - tho by largely keeping focus on effects of Trump's wild claims, @paulkrugman &amp; others avoided hyper-reaction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randlight @Talaolp Abbott's idiocy is best revealed by claim that as a backbencher, he doesn't feel obliged to support govt policy #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKouk Obviously, a wall along Mexcan coast is needed &amp; I'm sure the Mexicans will leap to pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaybwun @HuffPostAU Certainly highlights one of democracy's main flaws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaybwun @realDonaldTrump Certainly a verbal tic that particularly afflicts political class, tho PJK often used it to hilarious effect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I was talking about ALL domestic carriers based on personal &amp; anecdotal evidence of past 6 months. Latest was @Qantas out of Toowoomba.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus domestic air #travel steadily becoming a shambles w frequent cancellations/overbookings ramifying into critical delays. Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajhill_alan Ah, damn. Would have loved to have caught up with him one more time. Thanks Al.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICYMI Is it just me or is this a bit like sheriff in Blazing Saddles pointing gun at his head &amp; saying "Nobody mov… https://t.co/U8Gog1SAUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blahblahellis @ajhill_alan My minor claim 2 fame: meat workers were prepared to take pay in kind but union said no, so: "Snag in pay rise?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CordeiroRick Sure this isn't @KevinSpacey's grandad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajhill_alan @blahblahellis There's evidence famed Daily Mirror market report head "What a friend we have in cheeses" came from My Word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heckmotor97 Many humans clearly feel a deep need to convert others just to validate their own beliefs, religious or social.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Hildebrand @newscomauHQ So many seem to be invested in highlighting what divides Aussies, rather than what unites us. Please stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli #auspol Amusingly, @facebook &amp; @Google now display characteristics of print MSM models they disrupted. Plus… https://t.co/2Ps3zOVAyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#uspoli #auspol Relentlessly, evidence mounts that @realDonaldTrump is a clinically deranged narcissist. https://t.co/eAR223fhsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glopol_analysis Ah yes, in way @TeaPartyOrg rallied those who would benefit most from ACA (Obamacare) to protest against it.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>