<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizensFedUp @jasonselvig @realDonaldTrump @mermerdee exactly, not just Hillary voters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mvanvol_van @deejay90192 oops, have boycotted Exxon since Valdez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaibatsuNews I believed this from the moment it happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hinterlandg @CitizensFedUp It's sad when I feel like siding with another country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mysteri759 @CJFinNM just a good con man, still playing a con]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig @ChelseaClinton Today is the day I started following after that very tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Glad you're not shutting them out like the Republicans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidDWilliams5 @RVAwonk Also in today's Ark news passed a bill to change the constitution Marriage=1 man + 1 woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RahKaMira @bannerite @MSNBC Thanks for the warning, "click"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid And during the campaign it was "... but Hillary..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cahulaan @disgustedvoter2 Plus, there were a few senators who called PM trying to smooth things over. I doubt Bannon could "fix" anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wonkette I hope Arkansas is next for the foot, and I live here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff Funny, I turn them OFF every time they show trump or one of his minions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fayetteville, AR! They always help make up for some of the embarrassment our legislators have become! So proud of m… https://t.co/fJOQVfyNCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans on the run: Watch what happens if you try to schedule a meeting with Sen. Tom Cotton https://t.co/FH1M0x9iTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSerwer @bannerite I'm afraid they're making up lies so they can send US into war - raise approval ratings and raise money for cronies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum It would be better if REAL news outlets quit having her on to spew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope a few more join him! https://t.co/V3PMhEmojR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, how Arkansas continues to embarrass their residents! They're also trying to change the constitution to Marriage… https://t.co/qWAnk4J81e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USARedOrchestra @elayted Wonder if they'll nix the Budwiser ad? Betting they will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJFinNM On purpose - Bannon wants to destroy the whole U.S. institution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiHamilton5 @JuddLegum @thinkprogress She's very educated in lying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Impeachment isn't good enough - should be arrested for treason - sooner the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress: Require Trump to prove he has no Dakota Access Pipeline conflicts of interest: #NoDAPL https://t.co/sM2a4zZKgh @moveon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavily Militarized Police Raid Results In 76 Arrests At Standing Rock - Video https://t.co/p05lX8UaG1 #LiberalsUnite via @JesusChitChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feh688 @RoguePOTUSStaff I'm hoping it's treason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff  I hope with all my might, SOMEBODY, somewhere, is laying the ground work just waiting to arrest him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Time We Stopped Calling Donald Trump a Christian https://t.co/d6Wi2jgoCS via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJFinNM The masks and tire irons gave them away. Trying to get protests a crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirdIsTheWordUS @GeorgeTakei @UCBerkeley @BreitbartNews Face masks and tire irons gave them away. Trying to ban all protests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked Draft of Trump’s Religious Freedom Order Reveals Sweeping Plans to Legalize Discrimination via @thenation https://t.co/LRpKFgsEJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Resistance in Red America: Budweiser, Ford, and Dale Earnhardt https://t.co/knP92Nr50X via @shareblue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This “sanctuary city” sheriff will not be bullied by the Governor of Texas https://t.co/phhkpWoIJW via @shareblue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian oil exec found dead after caught bribing Donald Trump to lift U.S. sanctions https://t.co/QPQqP2wQx1 via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelani9 @dacollar1 @PageSix And let us not forget that Santa is white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePamelaE @zeebap2 @YahooTV  They should send Kelly elsewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @SenateGOP Can't anything be done about that??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot believe the vile, underhanded actions - I DO think we're in the middle of a coup https://t.co/MiPBjpRHvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joanwalsh we are going to need a media platform for some good folks like them, @maddow , @JoyAnnReid, @Lawrence etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfranken So proud of you! Show the rest of the dems how it's done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anomaly100 Oh I think that's a great idea - now if the other networks would quit putting them on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Muslim Ban Protecting Trump Profits Is Impeachable Offense via @politicususa https://t.co/21ooMqGazA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who voted for Trump believing that the Supreme Court was the most important thing should feel vindicated.” https://t.co/tinQN1PmPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Congress: Stop Bannon's national security takeover https://t.co/UbLPLplI5W @moveon #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green-card holder dies a day after being prevented from returning home by Trump's order: reports https://t.co/bqZYuNLpZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The People Are Leading the Politicians in the Fight Against Trump via @thenation https://t.co/vlbNtYD8zR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who abused their executive power at Standing Rock? https://t.co/z8RM57H3Fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California's Political War With Trump Just Got Real https://t.co/lCgqfEcFJW #LiberalsUnite via @JesusChitChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Why Democrats Must Fight Trump's Extremist Supreme Court Pick Neil Gorsuch via @politicususa https://t.co/kNCU8X9ABq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow Yes, the networks just keep on putting them on. I change the channel or turn the tv off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery Convoy Of 'Military' Vehicles Flying 'Trump' Flag Spotted In Kentucky https://t.co/LoMPeUHhyi via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/M0vOVYBHOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueBlueLiberal @WhiteHouse Or will they delete the holiday by EO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind When I woke up today, it was suddenly a travel ban - what the ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerMartinis @DangereuseProd Reason for ban, for religions to turn on each other, instead of turning on the one who created it-division]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@admiralmpj @allanbrauer I've heard Bannon wants CA to exit so there will be more red state counts. We can't let that happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPM @now7grandkids Guess the admin's talking points must've taken root overnight - now it's a "travel ban" --  ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought we were "withdrawing" from the UN, now we're "calling" on them?? https://t.co/x2P7Zpm4Ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omriceren @InSpiteOfTrump Wait!  Thought we were withdrawing from the UN, now we're "calling" on them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dark history of the White House aides who crafted Trump's "Muslim ban" https://t.co/B8tOczUwHX via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies Who Are Joining The Resistance And 'Standing Up For https://t.co/J8C4Iy3RHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, The Muslim Ban Isn't About Safety https://t.co/vIG65DlQN7 via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Against Anti-LGBTQ State Legislation https://t.co/LLgFQFA1bL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanweisman @bannerite @jestei @nytimes Probably coulda controlled Trump, bot NOT Bannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind and are you a "christian"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_cracknell @2017Ace @SMShow @andersoncooper Also just read EO coming at the end of this week to RE: Anit-LGBTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LRBitisnot I live in fear that we may never have another election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How stupid do they think we are?? https://t.co/HTvpf1fPDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert Why don't that point that stuff out to him or else quit going to these false testimonials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn I fear the house has been compromised, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon Just Became One Of The Most Dangerous Persons In America https://t.co/8Rheq7l1GV #LiberalsUnite via @JesusChitChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me &amp; @alfranken and call on Trump to reverse his executive order:  https://t.co/Btj0H9GDAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/FAnPa9G8TG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RF_P0TUS Plus the 7 million 3rd party votes against him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CletisStump @Kalaax008 I am wondering when and who the next group will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to my local gathering in support of our immigrants, ACLU card in hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcjohnson I keep saying this, get looks like I'm crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig is it true Banning wants CA to exit so blue states are reduced??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What This Election Taught Me About My Privilege https://t.co/2zaGmyM0lE via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress: Require Trump to prove he has no Dakota Access Pipeline conflicts of interest: #NoDAPL https://t.co/sM2a4zZKgh @moveon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A MUST read! https://t.co/MeZJEyFmGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunflowerSoul71 In one interview during the "race", he did say that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terrashifter ?? Half of the news reports say they resigned, half say they were told to leave ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me again why there's a need to cut ACA, SS &amp; Medicare?? https://t.co/zn8VYua2Ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMichaelSpicer @DangereuseProd Ha!! Could these be some kind of code for "help"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump Makes It Clear After Taking Office That America Is Under a Fascist Regime via @politicususa https://t.co/40RN7cgRST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To change everything, we need everyone. Join me April 29 to stand up for our communities and climate #peoplesclimate https://t.co/BA1r8xzPnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Illegal Voting Lie Is Part of Larger Republican Attack On Democracy via @politicususa https://t.co/xbHUILFucD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, This is Why Women Really Marched https://t.co/xO1q1a7iE9 via @johnpavlovitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone else experiencing FDSYS website being down today?? Has it purposefully been taken down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberating Word: The Muslim Registry https://t.co/yhq243Dm6O via #constantcontact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenpeaceusa I just decided to renew my membership today - had let it lapse, but no more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer @BadHombreNPS You have brought a little ray of sunshine and hope ! Way to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Keystone XL and DAPL. Join the Pipeline Pledge of Resistance. #noKXL #noDAPL https://t.co/nxRfqd7yBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Keystone XL and DAPL. Join the Pipeline Pledge of Resistance. #noKXL #noDAPL https://t.co/eIOZap9QAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OpposeTrump! Call on the the staff of the @usacehq to help stop Trump's pipeline plans! #NoDAPL https://t.co/9kippMzNG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports: Centers For Disease Control Climate Summit Canceled After Election https://t.co/OxyLgwQgAY via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should lose theirs! https://t.co/AjW4hPM3pE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UALocal393 When we lose our unions, is when we lose our rights as workers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnPersinos1 He has no idea what he's signing. They hand it it to him and he signs.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>