<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@azzamckazza I had four days off Twitter, Facebook &amp; the news &amp; loved it. But I'm thinking I need to pay attention again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john I'm reading @rickperlstein's Nixonland, which is simultaneously (oddly) unsettling &amp; comforting in its relevance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening Twitter right now is like stepping into a hurricane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BluejoWalton I'm appreciating them! I avoided Twitter for a few days for my peace of mind, but today I feel I can't avoid it. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress Amazing how quickly the replies fill with pro-Trump provocation. Seeing that a lot these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, this is my first glance at Twitter or the news in a couple of days. And holy fuck that shit's bad. Love &amp; support y'all. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw this incredible anime in 2004 - been trying to remember the title for years. Finally found it! #Tamala2010 https://t.co/mh7t3QKcZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks great: Paul Diamond talks @NLNZ on the history of the depiction of Māori in editorial cartoons (1 Feb):
https://t.co/MNbUJ0qbZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GyanS I reckon they're scared. Even their vile agendas are constantly put at risk by this volatile incompetent man-child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @hamish_keith Wasn't he hinting at a run for California governor recently?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @hamish_keith I'd be interested to know who else in NZ has had donations from him. In particular, think tanks &amp; political parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia As a dual citizen myself, I look forward to donating $1.25m to Elizabeth Warren in 2020.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I see folks saying Trump's bizarre tweets &amp; press conferences are all a calculated distraction, I think "W… https://t.co/NRBjg80EeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs That's about the best we can get these days...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs No (he said, nervously)...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit. Time to build a wall! https://t.co/r7wd1zMUvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrIsaacCates I liked it. It's very like original Star Trek in tone (&amp; lots of details). Also has a very distinct look &amp; aesthetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, guys... GUYS! I was looking at this giant gigapixel image of the inauguration and... OMG I THINK I FOUND THE A… https://t.co/bXd2fswtpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I particularly liked the title sequence &amp; end credits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched. Can't believe it took me this long to see it! https://t.co/h0FceYhZno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SikotiHamiltonR Having said that, I'm WAY less concerned by hyperbole from some on the left than by what Trump et al are doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SikotiHamiltonR There are genuine fascists in Trump's circle &amp; he's instinctively authoritarian. But no it ain't a fascist country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of the saddest bot-generated captions I've seen. https://t.co/xGeU55Q8d1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old Man Yells at Crowd https://t.co/4gtkStb1Z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compare &amp; contrast: Al Nisbet in The Press &amp; Bill Leak in The Australian.
(h/t @edmuzik).… https://t.co/x0XYJJ84P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @_hi_tide Steady on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik Aaaand across the ditch...
https://t.co/GTQKPO54cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik Such elegant penmanship. Excellent use of colour. All those boobies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieKoyama "Arty-farty comiques."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieKoyama When talking to non-comics people, I sometimes end up using vague terms like "more literary/arty/experimental comics."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RidicBowe @AnnieKoyama In France, some have used "roman graphique" to separate literary/arty comics from low-brow BD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieKoyama @kilgorebooks I prefer a term that refers to the cartoonist's aesthetic, rather than the financial structure of the publishers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieKoyama @kilgorebooks I associate indie w non-DC/Marvel comics that share their aesthetics. I've seen it applied to Image, Dark Horse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic Kirby story. He grew up in the tenements, no stranger to street fights. https://t.co/12YAWsgHVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great soundtrack, too. From the weird ominous noises in the opening titles to the main theme &amp; the haunting Prayer for Peace. #Gojira1954]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched this last night &amp; OMG I had no idea! Dark, powerful, moving - a revelation! #Godzilla #Gojira #1954 https://t.co/uz2148cbPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inkandleadnz The BEST way to start the next four years. A giant collective announcement that the fight has begun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the 1st day in months that looking at Twitter in the morning made me feel energised &amp; hopeful. Thank you to all at #WomensMarch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU @RobertMackey Basically, I'll take any reassurance I can get right now... o.o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU And https://t.co/R2QVBbY0lZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU If it's any consolation, I've seen reporters saying no-one's sure who the people applauding actually were. https://t.co/V17jdRgJ8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an excellent comparison. https://t.co/fYYS84h50o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU I can't stop laughing at this! Eat the bride's family?!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile (and this thread is just part of it)... https://t.co/8BD2vxo0VE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that post-inauguration honeymoon period lasted about 0.0001 seconds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is a good antidote to yesterday's despair. https://t.co/MAqkybhEZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDave @Jacob_Brogan Turns out Firbolgs are Medium in Volo's Guide, as are Goliaths. Seems like an iron law since 3e.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See, that's what I'm talking about. https://t.co/uTyQWNQOLx https://t.co/NgaShaPCP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDave @Jacob_Brogan Ah, good point! Thanks, I'll go look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Brogan @DCDave But in 4e they were medium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDave @Jacob_Brogan Correct. Only 3rd party material.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RadioActivefm are playing Springtime for Hitler. #wellplayed https://t.co/ysdremJo2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonathanKing A Tromp supporter just posted this photo on FB; I like how obvious and sad the combover is here. https://t.co/U5boeyzumt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I should probably just log out of Twitter &amp; go ask my Half-Giants question on https://t.co/FZ3oLKD7lZ or something, but...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I assume it's a balance issue, but I'm not clear why Large size would unbalance things so much. Anyone able to explain that to me?
4/4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was expecting Half-Giants to be Large size, but it looks like there's never been a character race that wasn't Medium or Small. Why?
3/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at easier versions, I note that they're always given Medium size (at least since 3e, when the size thing was formalised).
2/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to think about something else, so: I'm designing my own Half-Giant character race for D&amp;D 5e...
1/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini I'm reading Nixonland (by Rick Perlstein) right now, a very effective corrective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STOP SAYING THAT. https://t.co/hmVW03mvaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome distraction. https://t.co/CR7BIKJ6pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he's finally impeached &amp; imprisoned for corruption, I hope we get to see him with his hair ungelled &amp; undone,… https://t.co/lkUAiMGm9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaqTweedie Mark Everton! Oh man, this takes me back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaqTweedie Haha! Was Marcus Lush in there too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concerned, But Not Wanting To Offend, Canada Quietly Plants Privacy Hedge Along Entire U.S. Border.… https://t.co/YjuDJ9haOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP @EliMatthewson's mentions, but the responses to this TrumpTroll were too splendid. https://t.co/T5SnyjrSDn https://t.co/UEWnDaifQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaqTweedie Also YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel ashamed RTing this. You will feel ashamed reading it. We're all ashamed. EVERYONE IS ASHAMED. #welcometo2017 https://t.co/txlHjMnTWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fitz_Bunny And 5 minutes later, was hunched in the corner sobbing &amp; raving: "I am too the strongest man ever, no matter what she says!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fitz_Bunny Or if Superman kept leaning over to bystanders and yelling "ha ha fuck you, meaningless ants! I could crush you all LIKE THIS!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the reason these Trump supporters wish he'd stop tweeting is that it exposes the ugly reality behind their co… https://t.co/7a8as7zSp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnMilkspill Oops, I'll look into that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Alt Right in 1966.

(From @rickperlstein's Nixonland) https://t.co/YWCqplyJzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @nachomadness Would make a great double feature with Grave of the Fireflies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso Christophe Blain's Isaac the Pirate: https://t.co/8KA3ZKMLXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @nachomadness Does he read French or Japanese? Because that would open up all kinds of possibilities... ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso I rather like this PRE-history graphic novel, set in Britain ca. 10,000 BCE. https://t.co/rmLgs1kDgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso This is early 20th century history, but guaranteed to be of interest to any teenage boy: https://t.co/e7BLuXNeND ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suggestions for @gtiso &amp; his 15-yr old?  Interesting historical graphic novels (with PRE-20th century subject/setti… https://t.co/a3LTBLVnXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso Fiction? Non-fiction? Any particular historical periods preferred? And are you wanting kid-friendly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso A NZ one: Kimble Bent, Malcontent (by Chris Grosz): https://t.co/9luqcOS3B8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john Also, they love knowing the target number. So they can cluster round a spinning die, tensely waiting for the crucial number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john TBH, I allow all kinds of stuff, and just improvise the effects, usually ignoring the system &amp; maths entirely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john Less than that can still be a hit, but missed the called location.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john I like the disadvantage idea: easy, simple. Or you could say they hit the called location if their Attack roll = AC+5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OregonZoo @austinkleon Getting in touch with her inner mammoth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hold the pad so they can't see it's blank." https://t.co/hJV5xpgvu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ Mustard with EVERYTHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now if only Obama would do the same for Leonard Peltier...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES! Finally! After years of unjust incarceration, this is long overdue. https://t.co/BbyHQ5XERa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomedySci National day of mourning...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly this Friday will inaugurate a brave new Golden Age of American Poetry! https://t.co/IkBnWy8g7m https://t.co/O6nwGmjzJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a specialist appointment cancelled today because of this strike &amp; I support the doctors. When I see a Dr I wa… https://t.co/xQqVZRS7ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dillamonster That could be Dear's theory. After all, he was an "adviser" on the alien autopsy documentaries...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you've ever wondered what William C Dear, infamous initiator of the 1980s D&amp;D panic, is doing these days... https://t.co/vRoDoHxHZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobproehl @rickperlstein Yes, @wcl_library doesn't have that one, but that's definitely on my list. May end up reading the whole series.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiplet In its defense, so is a lot of lovemaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, let's see if @rickperlstein can shed some light on the awful slow-motion trainwreck that is contemporary Americ… https://t.co/RSEiKtTOtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humani nihil a me alienum puto.

Nothing human is alien to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FergusVUP @rachaelking70 Hell, I'd sort those in return for borrowing privileges!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>