<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump lets deal through he'll want Australia involved in his wars. What price denying sanctuary to 1250 lost souls? A 'dumb deal' indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These people are NOT in prisons.  They have committed no crime @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time they should use Skype. If Trump hangs up they can just blame our crap broadband.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delicious as this is remember over 1000 human beings who sought refuge are being traded like unwanted garbage. In our names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General memo to any US military planners that this is basically a 7.6 million km island full of extremely toxic snakes &amp; spiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back almost no commentators predicted the looming Austro-American war that would shape global politics for most of the 21st century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House of Cards has nothing on the real stuff going down right now ...  https://t.co/UZdIsBEJEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got all the way to the counter before realising this may not be the best basis for tonight's Chilli Con Carne https://t.co/qSAKR2csyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sing along now ... Not a puppet or a muppet  https://t.co/DRQWRc7q4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rewatched The Elephant Man to remember Sir John Hurt. Compulsory viewing for anyone who tries to tell you about 'the good old days']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emmett Till: Woman who triggered 1955 murder of African American boy admits lying ... https://t.co/Hb39pzD016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite actor. Just watch him in 1984 &amp; I Claudius. That's all you need to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No other actor made us squeeze into the tight shoes of the oppressed like John Hurt. Thank you for 1984, Elephant Man &amp; Naked Civil Servant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump won't 'settle down' any more than Robespierre, Mao or Hitler - extreme nationalists need constant fuel by enemies, battles &amp; victories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dangerman_2 those crunchy little corners come at the cost of our souls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crumpets are round people - disruptions like this explain Trump. You muck with people's breakfasts and they will turn to anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelissaCadzow it is a warped tear in the fabric of the world. Crumpets are round #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square crumpets are an act of apostasy - I'd rather starve https://t.co/H2VJ4YnbMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disability institutions in U.K. the cheap &amp; nasty option under cuts.  Same deal here unless we watch out  https://t.co/CLgLKqKY52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope she took some dragonglass https://t.co/4O1QY98pij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a triumphal miserable little creep Bill Leak is ... https://t.co/mGOQIZEHUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Kimbo had a new haircut?  It looks like it's about to fly off like one of his missiles https://t.co/8RQqdRP8cW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Special relationship" - drink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news out of Perth - those poor families :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @AltNatParkSer twitter feed is the best thing on Earth right now. Public servants serving the public rather than a regime - awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then - to top it all - there's Australian flag condoms &amp; we're not seeing the police coming in to whip them off https://t.co/v8uJApNkyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there's Oz flag thongs, budgie smugglers &amp; undies.  It's like you can fart on the flag &amp; step on it but singe it and everyone loses it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean we put the flag on Chinese made t-towels &amp; oven mitts in this country but tactical response teams aren't barging into our kitchens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flag burning isn't something I'd do but in the end it's just cloth not a living thing.  Looks like police jumped the gun? #AustraliaDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow #AustraliaDay feels a bit dull without @TonyAbbottMHR doing something weird like making the Queen a Duchess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like the worst of both worlds - we can't be honest about the invasion or reflect on the remarkable achievements of that ragtag colony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading rattling tome on impossible job they gave Phillip. Having national day on 26 Jan means this gets obscured t… https://t.co/RpQlM0fKnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like Turnbull always says there are 'bigger issues to deal with' than #changethedate, SSM &amp; republic but he never deals with anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 'getting hammered to celebrate white able bodied people day'. I'm working &amp; won't be joining you until you #changethedate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're can't be socialists in the billabong, that's where the swagmen are (with apologies to Bob Hawke)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but not joining applause for #ausoftheyear - we don't need research to end 'suffering' but action on barriers https://t.co/Z6yWUpJXfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually #ausoftheyear what would be great is if we gave people with spinal injuries jobs, access &amp; decent supports https://t.co/FnECFzvgzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public magpie warnings should also be on billboards @abccanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newbies to #CBR need to know that our magpies have developed a taste from human flesh like #TheWalkingDead …  https://t.co/SHaUrhI8cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm quite excited by the potential of #alternativefacts i.e, 'this slice of cheesecake will reduce my weight']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump giving oxygen on crowd numbers is incredibly poor political judgment. He could have said 'it's fatuous &amp; I'll be judged by results']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So of all the people you could fling one of these at they choose a group of young lib try hards 'and their lawyers' https://t.co/rZApk7DcCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanya_plibersek @ICCSyd and If you want a real ordeal try finding a disabled toilet in just about any venue built before 1990]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevanShields @NYTimesCohen Melanias choice of blue was also a coded signal to aliens - prove that I lie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I get the Women's March - that's about an issue - but the rest of them seem to think we're in endless cultural thrall to another country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So for all this - and I loathe him - who comes to a pro or anti Trump rally in Australia? 
We're. Not. In. America. Srsly. #cringeworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice colour - wonder if he has golden shower curtains too? https://t.co/3luErIdutX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I thought you might like the box my dress came in. It's a handy size for odds &amp; ends like oversized diamonds' https://t.co/FKTYZrLjnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenashburn @chriskkenny @SenGillibrand @EWTNNewsNightly maybe his nickname being 'mad dog' provides the clue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now they're putting America first can we PLEASE finally put Australia first in some things? No more silly foreign wars like Iraq for a start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to unfollow @potus or @WhiteHouse as you transfer over to the archive site for Obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was Barack I'd get on that helicopter and go far far away #Inauguration https://t.co/NSToLyfrpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect lots of blood you poor patriots. A very dark warmongering speech from @realDonaldTrump #Inauguration https://t.co/74cvfLMHeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's watched some historical speeches alright but they're not Kennedy #inauguration https://t.co/DEpv2iAudP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of talk about blood - remind you of anyone?  #inauguration https://t.co/Zl38F5F13m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Protected by god' - cue lightning #inauguration https://t.co/gmYnZkM512]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fecking hell - he's the real deal #inauguration https://t.co/o6NstEkn6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A frightening belligerent speech in the style of a dictator #inauguration https://t.co/T3x4NUFxjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He hasn't changed one bit. Belligerent, angry &amp; xenophobic. A catastrophe awaits us #inauguration https://t.co/CJhvgaA3pz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sniff #inauguration https://t.co/rpl0OQhrDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So right now is Pence Obamas VP? awkward #Inauguration https://t.co/Zr1qkqxZJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shudder looking for a spine to run up #Inauguration https://t.co/agj6OiFhAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence looks like a caged Great White Shark. Possibly as dangerous as Trump #Inauguration https://t.co/FwADQVFF2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disability mentioned &amp; Trump shuffles uncomfortably #Inauguration https://t.co/o4EzrNNvmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the poetry reading they should do TS Elliot's The Wasteland - appropriate &amp; would take about 4 … #Inauguration https://t.co/gSiv802XTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we have the music from Omen III #Inauguration https://t.co/wfLqn4Ozhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the faff spouted by privileged people in the name of an impoverished refugee carpenter from the … #Inauguration https://t.co/YtyCikNukK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['New Destiny Christian Centre' lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fuhrer looks angry #InaugurationDay https://t.co/LoMCZXPYqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trumps all look the same to me #InaugurationDay https://t.co/460LQM8z2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary has guts. Hats off to her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carter &amp; Clinton still barely on speaking terms lol #InaugurationDay https://t.co/M0jfkjwA8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter looks fantastic #InaugurationDay https://t.co/MhKUEQ2lX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile we've exhausted the scmaltzy military songbook #Inauguration https://t.co/mKwQsbbKxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary is so gutsy - imagine how petulant Trump would be if this were reversed #Inauguration https://t.co/CxIaUsc2AJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just people going on a series of short car trips #Inauguration https://t.co/Ll42s3D7T9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like go in and out of those doors just to muck with people's heads https://t.co/PNpuIvtPdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what happens if they don't come out? #Inauguration https://t.co/7ilfMRYrCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a doomsday clock #Inauguration https://t.co/F3oq6561x8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So are there only two guards in the entire White House? #Inauguration https://t.co/bOFgoxund3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should not be normalising a President who rejects democratic norms &amp; endorses sexual assault, violence, racism &amp; ableism #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['How are you feeling?' would have to be like the worst question you could possibly ask Hillary Clinton #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like 2008 just without Bono or anyone actually qualified to be President #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you imagine the bottle of vodka that Putin is cracking now? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need an infographic to understand all the Trump children &amp; wives #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you look at George W Bush with an almost fond nostalgia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all those talking about peaceful transition don't forget Trump wouldn't commit to peacefully accept result if he lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment Michelle Obama wonders what to do with the box of Cadbury assorted #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS thank you for rejecting torture &amp; restoring the light of human rights and American democracy in the western world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania might surprise us - she shows signs of style &amp; elan and some reserve too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes - Trump #Inauguration preacher this morning says Catholics are servants of Satan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Significant that first event of #Inauguration is to be a service by a far right Christian hate preacher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpInauguration will only feel real for me when Pauline Hansons representative photobombs the CNN coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is new @POTUS @realDonaldTrump mocking people with disability - what a disgusting person #TrumpInauguration  https://t.co/o6H3cRLsf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump not even in yet &amp; the satellites stop working https://t.co/1x808KQB3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of #NDIS thrown out on a busy news day - very cynical @cporterwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advocacy non partisan but increasingly seems the only way to keep an #NDIS would be to change the Govt. Hope they prove me wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull govt killing #NDIS vision by inquiries. Increasingly looking like a sad end to bipartisan support Australians promised in 2013.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On another note how do I get a Chad style Presidential seal for my MacBook Air? #planetamerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama letter to Trump 'Take care of the blue crockery its Ming i.e, very old ps. the nuclear codes are in the bottom of the shredder. Ta. B']]></document>
	</documents>
</author>