<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[short term future of #highered &amp; DOE. Private college memo could be Falwell task force playbook  https://t.co/8DKqU7t3DO via @newsadvance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is "holistic” higher ed's latest innovation star? https://t.co/XMGwlQ3Z3I #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Falwell as Education Adviser, His Own University Could Benefit #highered https://t.co/BJZYADJoR5 via @UpshotNYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! This hits a little too close to home. https://t.co/QINFCMmqd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Ginsburg makes her first visit to the military institute she remade https://t.co/kZ1EVxIu9d #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty cool #highered opportunity! https://t.co/7fhf99EvVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia universities see chilling consequence to travel restrictions https://t.co/2H0s07dBiu via @richmonddotcom #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees, immigrants, international students, and others are valued members of @JMU community https://t.co/RXUgFayEW2 #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higher education leaders denounce Trump's travel ban https://t.co/2jj7229XVG #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegMulrooney @broscheid Curation seems like good heuristic for processes of teaching and learning, lots of layers… https://t.co/0jfXJ0SGj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia ranks ninth in U.S. in local food sales #foodcomm https://t.co/fEHCbc0Wk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academics consider how to rebuild public trust in higher education https://t.co/XMomuIQkVb #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Gore revives climate summit the CDC abruptly canceled https://t.co/7Wcf2hqoU5 via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Skills gap' causes strategic reassessment from universities https://t.co/m8XcKWY79U #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES, me too. What about for #higheredVA? Poll finds Virginians willing to pay more taxes for ed https://t.co/LEm8TZNsWJ via @richmonddotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important #higheredVA governance issues: Senate finance kills Va. bills to control tuition https://t.co/PhDfJ2hFfq @roanoketimes #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA Bipartisan group of state legislators highlight more than 20 bills aimed at improving higher education. https://t.co/He57fDOgia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP budget leaders urge 3 percent raises for state workers, higher pay for new state troopers https://t.co/W2BJO6XEmV #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just spreading dubious arguments; spreading dubious policies, hearings, and executive orders. https://t.co/YKmGYYM7Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loan refinancing plans killed as Va. legislators tackle dozens of higher ed bills https://t.co/Jh7PxsWBd7 #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#highered VA Female-Only ‘Nerd’ Dorm Helps Keep Women in Engineering https://t.co/FACy5uPPTZ via @chronicle #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Story of how #higheredVA has been best bank for VA lawmakers. Editorial: The latest attack on VA colleges https://t.co/28ZbknHizE #Highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA bills would help, hurt undocumented immigrants - https://t.co/o2gi1eL4la - @washtimes #highered #DACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing terribly surprising but all still important #highered issues for 2017. https://t.co/7tCraGZQ5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA wow. UVa President Sullivan will leave when contract ends, asks board to begin search https://t.co/k63kxZjtr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why everyone should consult librarians more often? https://t.co/GaBqsU6FfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia lawmakers say they plan overdue debate on college costs, accountability https://t.co/jeLJcdN2b4 #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like big deal. How Much Did A Coding Error Affect Student Loan Repayment Rates? https://t.co/D2538xAAOU via @rkelchen #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@partners4edu #higheredVA poll: 48% Virginians believe no #highered funding crisis, other findings https://t.co/wdg26qjNyr via @roanoketimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthropology groups organize Foucault read-in for Inauguration Day https://t.co/G5rtv4RBdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With limited knowledge of grant conditions, I would take too. Thurgood Marshall College defends Koch $$$ https://t.co/DkACcS0ytd #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reimagining the College Transcript | Higher Ed Gamma https://t.co/AlBJs2Eivd #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Transparency in Higher Education Will Help Improve Student Outcomes https://t.co/zr3G81S93A #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite losses, overall enrollment at public Va. four-year schools shows slight gains overall https://t.co/0Y1QVzbcxn #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research documents life impact of attending a liberal arts college https://t.co/HX8QNvXHhM #highered #liberalarts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA legislative update, lots of submitted bills. Thanks for helping us stay informed @SCHEVnews! https://t.co/GbJ4RHWX3H #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds say too many career-training programs, for-profit schools leaving graduates saddled with debt https://t.co/HrwJXNUqbB #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like big deal for #higheredVA. Virginia Democratic delegates to seek new student loan authority https://t.co/RfQLbmaQwB #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Recruitment to Native Communities Has Got to Be Different' - The Chronicle of Higher Education https://t.co/cqpaeOoHpN @chronicle #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For higher ed officials, General Assembly session offers few dollars to chase https://t.co/Yd7k4dvjlA via @richmonddotcom #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge: Georgians shielded from deportation may pay in-state tuition https://t.co/sz3jHKCuOl #highered #DACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's most spoken languages in a single beautiful infographic https://t.co/E8QiO7nppF via @MatadorNetwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education bills target virtual learning, student debt, loopholes in Virginia's financial aid system https://t.co/Lzc9bi1Xsb #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginian-Pilot editorial: Colleges: An economic idea that works https://t.co/R5h21RM0N3 #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#highered can engage &amp; emotionally support students w/o customer service frame. Customer Excellence: Goal for Univ https://t.co/FuHK0wSg8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For-profit #highered exploiting veterans to exploit 90/10 loophole. Some for-profit colleges preying on veterans https://t.co/Ojfqx58YE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA Virginian-Pilot editorial: A budget proposal of smaller ambition https://t.co/G4IE9moMRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little-Noticed Document Could Hint at Trump Higher Education Plan https://t.co/L7M8tgoEa9 #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College And University Enrollment Is Down For Fifth Straight Year, 24+ year old bulk of drop off https://t.co/ii5MdeIIfE #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed, would love to work on #liberalarts #CBE. Rethinking Credentials: Power of Soft Skills https://t.co/oqCDIcACNw #edtech #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leading from where they stand #higheredVA #leadership https://t.co/0Sz5m3N5lW via @Comm_College #comm_college]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Richmond joins effort to recruit low-income students https://t.co/hJgok5jIAk via @richmonddotcom #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roanoke Higher Education Center names new executive director https://t.co/7yuDw8j2SG via @wsls #higheredVA #multiplepathways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: 'We’re going to work something out' with Dreamers https://t.co/CLvEAHaYZN #DACA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama websites preserved as part of UNT collaboration | University Business Magazine https://t.co/iHjuwMnS5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can institutions best make the case for higher ed to legislators? https://t.co/Z0iuELCiiK #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Higher Education Be ‘Trumped’ by State Lawmakers? - The Chronicle of Higher Education https://t.co/5CTABudEMC via @chronicle #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#highered &amp; Sanctuary Campuses. Great case for institutional engagement &amp; ethical reasoning. @engagedjmu @JMUMC @jmu https://t.co/s5IILDmnHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higher education needs a transformation of its value proposition (essay) https://t.co/xpgcCCBOLV #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial woes make co-ed unit a must, MBU officials say https://t.co/2rpSGEulos via @dailyprogress #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Hollins University president ready to roll up her sleeves and get to work https://t.co/eTzZKzIB7e via @roanoketimes #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad that @jmu &amp; @EMU_News presidents joined others from #higheredVA and national #highered urging new gov leaders to continue #DACA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump could reverse Obama’s actions on college sex assault, transgender rights https://t.co/hce2Pq6vX6 #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How America wrecked its public universities https://t.co/vcI03VKYJg #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pandagabe Can you elaborate? As community, institutions, squads, teams, individual debaters? Suspect many are trying to connect &amp; engage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of #higheredVA signatures missing. #highered leaders: Save program shielding students from deportation https://t.co/CeP51yyy6F #DACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#higheredVA signatures? Presidents call for continuation of Obama program protecting undocumented students https://t.co/a6BX6aFrJE #DACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DACA concerns for #higheredVA. Post-election fears of deportation continue at UVa https://t.co/2jZXRazNJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity for Shen Valley collaboration &amp; innovation on digital credentialing? @liujc @MegMulrooney #higheredVA https://t.co/rhjgY8kdyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On rising college costs in Virginia, House budget committee is told the state is not to blame https://t.co/eyC6o5JdiV #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposed bill: In-state students take priority at Va. universities https://t.co/eDXUDo7sw9 #higheredVA #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing. #higheredVA impact?? Report finds disarray at VA econ dev partnership, urges withholding $ https://t.co/icOXG0GDzq #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Not quite the #highered police leadership one would want for #campusclimate. #higheredVA https://t.co/A4iSlPmfjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong #higheredVA. Virginia Tech president calls on university to double minority enrollments https://t.co/Ph31yBvnDx #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higher Education Has Lost Control of Its Own Narrative - The Chronicle of Higher Education https://t.co/G6KnQizmz1 via @chronicle #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polls: Americans Increasingly Mistrustful Of College Costs Leadership And Value https://t.co/9DzMKssFwG #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undergrad tutors presenting on supporting English Language Learners at @NatComm national conference. @JMU… https://t.co/yk5olJ2yF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We talk a lot about civic education. Here's how to get kids really engaged in it. https://t.co/7GUz6CnDjt #civiceducation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What 12 State Schools Are Cutting, or Creating https://t.co/2GG5gPeMA4 #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Highered asked to share budget pain with Virginia state agencies https://t.co/lSuoDtc5s2 via @richmonddotcom #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inova lures U-Va. to Northern Virginia with $112 million research center https://t.co/nGPSLaaWaR #highered #higheredVA #cancermoonshot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ‘iron triangle’ of access, quality, and affordability for #highered. https://t.co/mmuEtUENKL via @sharethis #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple pathways important for #higheredVA. Scott Miller: Diversifying education to diversify the economy https://t.co/8hpRw04epu #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#highered campus climate. https://t.co/e2RulzoD1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School Committee members eye starting debate league in Worcester https://t.co/Tbk0L6pTFW #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Op/Ed: Public support of higher ed. not dependent on private funds https://t.co/mLI1b74j8o via @dailyprogress #highered #higheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Relative Value of Alt Pathways in #HigherEd: Evidence From Virginia https://t.co/9LBBkoolqL #HigheredVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickjsciullo @NatComm @GSUCommDept That is great, congrats!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authors discuss new book challenging the narrative about colleges and the 'skills gap' https://t.co/0zw7xM3PfK #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to live where education matters &amp; those governing #highered take it seriously. Impt #higheredVA resolutions p… https://t.co/BEbqZqvO7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Involving faculty critical to planning &amp; using assessment data to improve learning. New study #highered attitudes https://t.co/PUVL3Au0oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black-white disparity in student loan debt more than triples after graduation https://t.co/KRxelYTrff via @BrookingsInst #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higher education should be a public good, not a private commodity https://t.co/ua4RqyPn9O #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMUCommAdvocacy Lots of good job opportunities for environmental advocacy and health advocacy graduates!! https://t.co/vbBV2U0NZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#highered value beyond job placement, must include civic life prep says Ed Sec John King: https://t.co/1TV1I5gESP via @DiverseIssues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Higher ed would be central in a Clinton administration, but who would carry agenda in Congress? https://t.co/LWnSBYuDlq #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not fast enough, most faculty and classes could do now. Faculty: OER use could triple in the next 5 years https://t.co/7PFjJOO2gq #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MegMulrooney Maybe some promo packets that depts and orgs can use without much time investment? And this? https://t.co/YEYsOGYPBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50-State Comparison: Statewide Longitudinal Data Systems https://t.co/lR73LC4r7x via @edcommission #highered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liujc 21st century digital learning attitudes scholarship #highered https://t.co/HCNYwifB6R]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>