<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP to this man's best friend! She can now hang with her pal Guiness. https://t.co/b17J10arjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bubbawatson @MarkWahlberg @WMPhoenixOpen @ESPNCaddie should be free burgers in return for the ball!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MapleLeafs @AM34 Best Birthday. Sat with Bob Nevin and watched Matthews score at dinner #class #LeafStanleyCup winner. #BigRing!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug @loolee0125 I think I wore that Gr 8 grad shirt in Winnipeg 5 years later #markpacked #alittletight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good looking threesome post Andrean Christmas. Grand-Maman is so proud! #dontsayshort #bigmaninakilt https://t.co/WV2uzsDUVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@standrews1899 an absolutely amazing Andrean Christmas 2.0 #brotherhood. So proud to witness!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexPSGroup @MarkSeidel well it certainly was a great tilt. Loved the heart on both sides. #nextyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSeidel @AlexPSGroup I just feel bad for these boys. Don't think any should bear the brunt losing this way. #lovethebanter #kidisastud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSeidel @AlexPSGroup maybe we keep it to a stat like the ineffecient PP instead of pointing to 1 kid??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexPSGroup @MarkSeidel seems the Canadian hockey "establisment" love pointing a finger. All KIDS played great. #congratscanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexPSGroup @MarkSeidel well sounds like some adults are hanging a "shoot out" loss on a teenager. A "shoot out" loss!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSeidel @AlexPSGroup good for you guys!! Pounding a kid within minutes of a loss! #cheapshots #youguysfeelbetter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPronger I am an Olympian in the "airing of grievances"...weak on "feats of strength" #focusissues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPronger do I have to put the tree back up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanPronger My holiday season is never complete until I get my always late Xmas card from Cali #loveit #wheredoesthetimego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug looks like Mom is teaching Vincent. BTW @LouiseLugli has the best potato recipe #gooooooodbird #wishwewereinseatle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter has talents for Christmas decor #whoknew #gotskillsfromdad #merryXmas https://t.co/QW6YWtfH7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrScottEddy the highlight is the "airing of grievances". #classic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jughead3459 @sachockey kids on his naughty list stayed for a full contact skate later #oucheemomma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah my boy does great things on his grandpa's birthday #papabutch #rip https://t.co/OIVv2Id1K1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Bday Dad. #RIP #chocolatecake #caramelsauce https://t.co/4eC7VlEoOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor nice when referrals come in that fast! #buildingthebrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor @RLPSignature yup! Diamond is a Good one. Top 3 Percent. #hardwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor was great getting another excellent well priced listing today. Love referrals from happy clients. #buildingthebrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor our seller is thrilled! #highestpricever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am proud of @monlug ! She is my sister. Reading her tweets and realizing she is making a difference. #littlesismakingabigdifference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to go @SBallardRealtor !! Over 4 M in sales in #VictoriaVillage in last 2 weeks! #buildingthebrand #highesteverprice!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomt411 @NHL can I open a pastry shop nearby? Opens at 7 pm.....Dessert Nights? #timbits #lineups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor so excited to list an original on the ravine today! Details to come! #buildingthebrand #workinghard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor Sold my Exclusive listing at 138 Sweeney for top dollar! My clients sure are happy! #buildingthebrand #hardworkpaysoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor we just keep doing more and more! 118 percent of asking for 7 Knighton in Vic Village #buildingthebrand way to go!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snoop_dog hey you need a realtor for that move to the Big Smoke? TO? The 6? #wordsweuse #illhaveurback #bringascarf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikelalonde1 way ahead of me and my BlackBerry #oldschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikelalonde1 2 halftys make a fullty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor great to get another "coming soon to mls" sign up today. #victoriavillage #buildingthebrand #detached #bungalow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jughead3459 put a canada goose big jacket on that and it looks like me after a big D scores!! #riverdweller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor another sold from a referral from a past client! #condo #buildingthebrand #happybuyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthyPhillys view from the Best Toronto #Foodtruck guaranteed! They do to food what I do to Real Estate!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor Hope we do not run out on Saturday!! So many have reserved their pumpkin #greatPumpkinGiveaway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPSChrisBoddy #firstprolongedslump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor we hit 15Million in sales so far this calendar year. Congrats to us! #moretocome #doingwhatworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things to be most thankful for #mykids #awesome #goodlooking https://t.co/SwpQegwrgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson #bestjobintheworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson that is what great agents do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I met Arnold Palmer. What a great story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor 2 first time buyers out of 1 home is so exciting for these happy clients. #neighborhood #buildingthebrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor love when I sell people their first home. #condo #neighborhoodreferralagain #buildingthebrand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 years in a row!! My girl wins Golden Gloves for best goalie in entire organization! She rocks #prouddad https://t.co/k19c2knzaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GolfChannel should have had the team each have a ball to pull out of arnie's bag on first tee #rydercup #RIPKing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jughead3459 on pace for 100 plus??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome quote! Get up and pay the rent! https://t.co/ITHo7zHSSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saying, I bought some milk today and found this. I dropped it! #groceryerror #badDefence https://t.co/m9KkbfXvMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilthyPhillys can't wait to have this truck at my October event #feedthemasses #luckyneighborhood @SBallardRealtor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourMorning really loved the @InMUWeTrust interview. Great to see role #good work. Passion is so contagious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourMorning gave them a chance, finally, and they are THE show to watch in the morning #refreshingchange #fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So nice to see @noahlugli2 so hard at work already early in the season on his twitter pic #scholar #focus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday tomorrow Mom! Here she is with some of the grandkids #inspiration #rolemodel #mom https://t.co/koWEqSAU1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day of school for Mack! Uniforms!! Yay! @LouiseLugli #minorniner https://t.co/FUcc4RRBKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor yes their expectations too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor another happy customer last night!! Can't believe what he got!! #doingitright #referrals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarbucksCanada paid for a morning sandwich and had to leave as they were to busy to cook it. #happensoften #toobusytocare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarbucksCanada your store at the shoppes of don mills has awful service. Has for a long time. #doyoucare?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sachockey @DarrinCaron @JungadlerTV safe to say the boys "finnished"??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor love it when a happy past client refers us great listings! New great condo coming to market tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_drjo well you deserve gold for community passion!! #passion #energy #greenlights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The famous Dr Jo doing good again! Does she ever stop making the world a better place? https://t.co/MITaK137yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericab11 have no doubt she feels the same #bonding #loving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueJays what is going on with colabello?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLPSignature @Jim4Realtors Our office rocks for doing this. They just keep doing things to make us better. #wegotanedge #better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBallardRealtor @InstanetNow our clients in the #victoriavillage love using it too! Really easy. #investment #realestate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseLugli @monlug mom you have to follow @MrScottEddy - he travels the world. You will love his stuff!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseLugli @monlug twitter makes you smarter mom!! Imagine all the recipes you can get and share with us! Or travel tips!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug @TwitterCanada @LouiseLugli MOM! Yay!! I love twitter mom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does every country music song mention alcohol? #newtocountry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLPSignature oh yes!! That is one big Pike! #needabiggerboat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda of seats I wish I brought my glove for! @BlueJays https://t.co/6zXuOJzEiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@golfrmom funny stuff!! Fish may be heavier then grandmaman #cut #svelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@golfrmom my mom is the fish whisperer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey world!! My mom is a better fisherperson then your mom!!! Nice catch mom!! #olympicgold https://t.co/yzlUYICM0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson @sharonakkanen that is a "cat" original for sure! #classic #original #awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson haha. Well I am not sure @sharonakkanen needs an excuse, but she does love fresh tomatoes on her burger and of course wine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson Hey when can we expect our tasty Cali Lenny tomatoes via Google express? Burgers are begging for tomatoes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phillstables Sexy signs Phill! How is London real estate? A tad busy here in TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@golfrmom well kid would never hit my cart. I am NEVER in the middle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson OMG!! I only have bags of cash but also a HUGE appetite for Lenny's hotdogs and frosties. Does cash cut it in cali?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlarson certainly will. What would you like in your coffee?? And can I buy it on the spot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCToronto unfair is getting killed selling a truck on kijiji. #throwawaythekey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShiDavidi @hockeytoronto carapazza get a sit down with his bosses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug at the queen's plate!! Big Hats everywhere! Bucket list! #betbetbetbetbet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnReis @hockeytoronto love Roman Polak. Hard working leader! #babysteps boys! #babysteps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateBeirness is that cricket feels like? Will they stop for tea at some point?? #gojays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPSChrisBoddy can we not give the ump some sort of "disorderly conduct" ticket? #scroogeofCanadaDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoreyHirsch totally agree. Awesome day in hockey y'day. Great fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoreyHirsch but that was MTL. Does Nashville have the same hockey-centric media?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSNBobMcKenzie they have 3 plus years to work it out and the future is possible strike? Say it isn't so. Strikes hurt fans. #workitout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jughead3459 still confused? Nice work sanchez! #luckyduck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug is all the excitement about the HUGE NHL trades and activity? What do the 3amigos think of the trades?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DinaPugliese but they ARE winning where it counts!! #stickandstones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reeleer @Reeleer @AerLingus do they understand how much you travel? #bigtimeloss #gotmakehimcranky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monlug yes you did! #knewafastballwascoming]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>