<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay imma stop before I cry happysad tears in the middle of Disneyland. âœŒðŸ»ï¸ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that is an incredible gift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And everyday for me is a reminder of his legacy and another reason to be grateful for the guidance he gave me while he was here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But everyday it gets easier and instead of sad and empty now that he's gone, I feel my heart filling when Something reminds me of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I can't do that anymore, and it hurts like hell but I'm learning how to get through that. It's a work in progress. I'm new to this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And normally, I'd stop by his class to say hi and tell him how they are. And for a little while, it'd be like I never left and I loved that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had it not been for my time with them and Mr. Payne's support. And today, I got to talk with these people I haven't seen in 5-7 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I met some really amazing people and figured out what I wanted to do with my life in that class. I wouldn't be the person I am today ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I saw four of the kids I worked with while a TA in Mr.Payne's class and it reminded me of some really amazing things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kidkelly do you know what playlist the XM preview channel uses when previewing your show? I'm desperately hunting for one yesterday's songs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, drinking beer is like buying a soda, but the syrup is out and you take a huge sip of carbonated water. Like, this is not what I want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you know it's real: you and your best friend do the Aladdin musical finale "Friend Like Me" reprise choreo while watching World of Color]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one will ever love anyone the way dogs love everyone. ðŸ¶ â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I came to this theater to watch Arrival, and yet, I said Passengers when I saw a poster of Chris Pratt anyway. And bought the ticket. Oops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyFavMurder the female driving app you mentioned on the Bell House episode is @SeeJaneGoInc and it's live in the OC and will be in LA soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thanks for tolerating the book you hate for me." - @amywalsh who has finally gotten to my least favorite reading assignment of high school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw it also tells you to share your screenshots. I am not a fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like this is 100% the motivation I needed after realizing EXACTLY how far behind I am on my #NaNoWriMo novel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Best Friends Are The BEST Best Friends, a series, Volume 37294629: https://t.co/2iAWqizeWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Starbucks I'm at just had a last call for alcohol and I am amused and also confused because that just happened?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've had lightning and thunder storms for the past 16 hours, and honestly this is the most relaxed I've been in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW. I thought I was getting a lot of unpleasant campaign emails from candidates for city office. But then I checked my spam filter.  ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel hot. And not the girl kind of hot." - my eight-year-old brother explaining he feels overheated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after years of spelling "Hilary" {As in Hilary Duff} I only JUST realized my mistake. 

I'VE EVEN BEEN FIGHTING MY AUTOCORRECT ON THIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @HillaryClinton becomes our next president, I'm gonna really have to work at not misspelling her first name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found out that my typing speed is above average, which makes me feel better about having completely abandoned proper form in 3rd grade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywalsh I even bragged to dad about it. Baby steps. Baby steps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@amywalsh just turned to try to look at a section of her hair that is curling strangely and yelled "Fight Me!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@taylorannlaw and I just discovered we each only like opposing halves of a bag of @mikeandike Zours. #soulmates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom to me: "they put salt on after so you'll have a very salty pizza"
@amywalsh to me: "just like you"
Thanks. #same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My neighbors drove off in their loud, obnoxious sports cars and were revving the engines and I can actually smell the exhaust in my room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ridiculously proud of this woman right here. ðŸ˜˜â¤ï¸ https://t.co/0KHkBucYDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw to clarify she wants to do double date married couple things and have children in the same daycare. These are our life goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to have those married times with you" - @taylorannlaw who is often scared I won't get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually at the point in my life when I'm not certain if someone's engaged or married relationship status on Facebook is a joke or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw but, like, of all the issues to have, I'm pretty chill with these ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this is the highest evolution. We've transcended purchasing our vices and have returned to the barter system. @taylorannlaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like they say you become your best friends... @taylorannlaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw and I are trading beauty blenders for stickers, which is hysterical because we are corrupting each other with what we buy most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You've got your old guy celebrity crush, I have mine, and everyone else has theirs"- a conversation I never thought I'd have with my mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom has such a type and I can't stop laughing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyyonamine OH MY GOD SO THE CODE WORKED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyyonamine hahahaha no. I almost got it to work but each time I added a cover it deleted the previous one or logged me out. Uncool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that doesn't include the other 2 hours I spent trying to do these covers. With 2 computers and 3 wifi networks. I am so sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've actually been at this for an hour and a half.  And all it does is say please wait. Whyyyyy #erincondren WHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been trying to customized 2 photo Erin Condren covers and the website is so slow on both computers that that I'm gonna miss the sale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You need to get a boyfriend so we can do this..." @taylorannlaw to me in a regular basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The British: 
"What should we call them?"
"Well they're angry all the time.  How about Angryland?"
"No, wait. I've got it. IREland."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malekamau I read that there was a twist that explained everything but for all the ways I imagined, I didn't think of it until it was there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malekamau well now I am a puddle of tears. That ending was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can hear my mother watching the 2005 Pride and Prejudice film downstairs and if anything gets me to do something today, that will be it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malekamau okay good because I was debating starting it and this is reassuring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸŒ¿ðŸŒ¾ðŸƒtoday's to do:ðŸƒðŸŒ¾ðŸŒ¿ https://t.co/vTIoHgHSkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*my brother walks into the room*
"Okay, guys. Here's two dead jokes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw @amywalsh low key proud of these abilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw I wish but no. 2005]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I Write Sins Not Tragedies" was released half my life ago. ðŸ˜§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw where did you find that picture of me?!?! ðŸ˜¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw more like motto. Lifestyle choice. Modus operandi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw Be blessed. Not stressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case someone needs this imma leave it right here.  https://t.co/JdG80sZ99x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw this might be my favorite thing I've seen this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywalsh at Pieology: "It's cute that Zach thinks 6 pieces of ham is a lot."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To put it into perspective, this is the first September I'm not in school since before my sister was born. And she's about to turn 18.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things I didn't think would be a problem until they were: Everyone's back to school except me and now I'm sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katzmeifyoucan I just added him to my VIP email list so I'd get a notification. I'd probably combust if I kept refreshing my inbox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the best part is I'm zero% surprised by this response and honestly would be concerned if there was anything more there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent several hours composing an email to a professor and days agonizing over sending it and he replied back with two words and ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw : "I'm so used to being single."
Me and @amywalsh : "Taylor, it's been a year."
{same tho}]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like omg so proud of my Scorpion King. Sweet precious child. So proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing about #CursedChild is everyone is starting to love Scorpius as much as I have for the last 9 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I didn't think so. I mean, you're a Slytherin not a Gryffindor." - Me to Christine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His advice for men whose wives are upset with them: "just shake your booty" until it's better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His song "shake your booty shake your butt" is second on his CD in case you were wondering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world would be a better place if everybody just shook their booty more." - dude rapping on the pier right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double the throwback because my best friend turns 22 today and Timehop knows how important she is to me. https://t.co/IO7XdNrx6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm twenty-two for a moment.."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using my birthday as an excuse to make several of my favorite people watch my favorite movie. ðŸ˜ŠâœŒðŸ»ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been waiting forever for this one to pop up on my Timehop friendships. Love you lots @apriosmtz94 #est1999 https://t.co/Y0OBuSkZhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw at first I was gonna try and fight this but wow. Yep. It me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadpersaud first of all YES, second of all where can I find it??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw IVE BEEN SINGING "HAKUNA RATTATA" FOR THE LAST WEEK HOW DID I NOT SEE THIS BEFORE NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RileyNeldam "Gwen Stacy is dead" We both agreed that HAD to be the lyric, but I couldn't hear it well and was trying to find an alternative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Personally, I enjoy sunburns" - @amywalsh (who might be a crazy person)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankly, I'm surprised it took me til mid-July to get my first sunburn of 2k16. I didn't think I could stay indoors that long but I did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A month from now, I'm going to be hanging out with @apriosmtz94 and I don't think I could even BE more excited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YulinKuang thanks times a million!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YulinKuang @kirstynhippe are lyrics for #IShipItSeries out yet? My sister and I are fighting over a line and it's driving me crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywalsh if you don't have it by the time I get home I will be shocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS THE NEWS IVE BEEN DREAMING OF FOR THE LAST MONTH. #IShipItSeries https://t.co/IazYY1EByO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YulinKuang my best friend was in China the last 5 months and was able to snap me. 
@ashleyyonamine can you help Yulin out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five minutes of Facebook browsing and two new engagement posts later, I think I've had enough of Facebook for the next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apriosmtz94 if this doesn't speak volumes on how the three of us function, I don't know what does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My best friend's boyfriend made an awful pic of me his profile pic for insta and Whyyyyyyyyyy??!?! https://t.co/bmUjCfw8gA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesPWolpert will you be releasing "Here in Your Arms" anytime soon?  I've been sustaining myself on little clips of it but I need more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw the cutest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylorannlaw aren't we the cutest? https://t.co/wXcULfxDp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again reminding me why @ErinCondren life planners are my forever go to. So cute, so functional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really impressed with the @ErinCondren 2017 life planner launch. Delivered two weeks before it was supposed to ship and no mistakes!ðŸ˜ŠðŸ™ŒðŸ»ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyyonamine love youuuuu. Come home to me and let's sit in traffic together.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>