<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@5liveSport @Minarzouki Jesus she knows her stuff 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViktorFagerLFC @M__Griffiths so if he has the money like you claim he has why not buy him or at least try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncrossmirror @England @VauxhallEngland @vauxhall @LFC Jesus state of that. He's average]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbieSavage8 no Robbie he's got it right you retard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanCastles ah shut up you fucking bald cunt. Worry about your own team@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverKayTimes they're 18th in the championship go back to bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker go away leave me alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker I always maintained good starting 11 but squad is shit now fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker sure your squad is shit too you Fucking little moron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker ah not no but because I know it means so much to you to be "right" love rubbing it in your Fucking eejit face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker says your man. Be fucking in bed depressed for a week if were me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker ah just give me credit and admit you  wrong for once in your life ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker ah cause other teams playing shit and flukey we come 7th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker ah my Fucking arse you know I'm the only one who loled at him from start and proven right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TronTromatic @GaryLineker hahaha sure he was according to you too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaves Origi on hahah. Bye!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to make another change there jurgen you fucking eejit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck me some shit players on that team that I can't handle. That Wijnaldum offers sweet fuck all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman don't overreact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViktorFagerLFC he is shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 @JimBoardman I know yea I get some buzz off his tweets though. Thinks klopp is a god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman @tkirby8 what? We were playing awful for a while before we started losing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman don't overreact now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 sure what good is that really? We are useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 we are the worst. I anticipated this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely can't handle Origi's all round play at times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can see the pattern of this game  already. It's the exact same as soton yet worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Langie_77 an early goal and we will win comfortably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Langie_77 I am an angry little tweeter and everything is very much tweeted in the moment 😅😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Langie_77 FYI I use twitter to rant and its my form of counselling myself. Everything not to be taken at face value 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only one film is called T2 that trainspotting thing can Fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BumperGraham why don't you always enjoy it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris78Williams @BassTunedToRed @thisisanfield if my nanny had balls she'd be my grandad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeKelly1 @_ChrisBascombe @TeleFootball hahaha so should he not get the credit when we are doing well too? Nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman at what point in your head does it become ok to "overreact"? If you aren't slightly concerned of late results then get the boat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RorySmith well...they do? They've bought players that have apparently strengthened their team have they not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticise Sturridge all you want. While he has declined slightly the manager has to find a way to utilise him to his strengths. Fuck off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoMarmir @JimBoardman it's not just this game that is been taken into account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman hahaha. Sort of tweet is this? We are playing appalling of late you can't ignore that fact. Something needs to change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Lallana is back to his usual averageness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheazy9 haven't a clue state of this team lately my god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the balance of chances Southampton have had over these two legs it should be 8-0 on agg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What.Is.Our.Defence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take for Emre can to get dropped?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman @buttonmoon1979 all very true and I hope  he stays forever but contracts don't mean a whole lot these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman @buttonmoon1979 just cause there isn't a release clause doesn't mean that we can't gets lots of money for him, it's inevitable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman @Phil_Coutinho @LFC hahahaha contracts mean absolutely nothing these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was the same with American Sniper which I also liked but...cmon! #IfItWasntATrueStory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah here! I like Andrew Garfield and Hacksaw Ridge was good but that's not an oscar nom performance or film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker yea then telling me have to download the app too fuck that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker yea I did then had to fill out a little box and my email and they send the result apparently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker there was a good few I can't even remember and I dunno didn't get the email yet 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker yea but a majority of the questions the two options wouldn't be me at all so answering ones for the sake of it I felt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker ahhh one of those things. Nonsense now I'd think 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snafuspecker what is that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeKelly1 @prabinLFC but every team will improve  in the long term, course I'd give him time at sort of fool wouldn't?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmcpheat @GraemeKelly1 wtf good is it being in a Final if you don't win it? Same as being knocked out in the first round. 10 points behind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeKelly1 @prabinLFC lol haha! How? Also why no mention of Tottenham? Ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conormceneaney yea it really was brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Manchester By The Sea hype is well and truly real. Probably the best film of the year but I will never watch it again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honored 😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/Dagl1fFEnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burnley Bournemouth Sunderland and Swansea. We've  come on leaps and bounds 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's positives- it might bring some retarded Liverpool fans down to reality and help them understand klopp is my god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntoGriezmann @ViktorFagerLFC he is in his hole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeKelly1 for Fuck sake. Then buy new ones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman what do you mean today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkyDwan hahaha I'm not watching it thank Fuck. I hate a majority of the players on that Liverpool team it's hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimBoardman serious who pays you for writing they are having a laugh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkyDwan ah fuck that state of that Liverpool team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever happens in that game conceding two goals at home to that horrendous  Swansea side is a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carra23 hahaha stupid article yet again and I'm a Liverpool fan. Spurs have been consistently better than us in recent years wake up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bosselona @TheAnfieldWrap ah yea because things like that happen every year don't they]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elgeorgo81 @TheAnfieldWrap @Bosselona nothing to do with that. Clyne isn't that good. The squad is shit, coutinho only Wc player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivEchoLFC Jesus Mary and jospeh people are insane@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elgeorgo81 @TheAnfieldWrap @Bosselona clyne solid my arse. There's a reason our defence is so shit and he's part of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elgeorgo81 @TheAnfieldWrap @Bosselona obviously. Probably tell me clyne is better 🤣🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAnfieldWrap @Bosselona so you think we are better equipped now than when we had- Suarez/gerrard/alonso/riise/mascherano/finnan/Torres 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DietmarHamann @elessard10 yea sure and neither this team and won't be winning anything this season either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEAMtalk Jesus what sort of headline is that? More of a test for Man City you fools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carra23 if ibrahimovic has surprised you (not we) so much? Sort of contradicting is it not? You thought they'd compete and hed  fail? 🤔🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carra23 why do always say "we all thought this or that" when you only thought it? And why did you think Utd would compete at the start-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsMNF hahaha Jesus Christ. Well then klopp is fucking nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushmarsh14 im fairly sure I've your prison break season 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 ah yea would have taken that before hand. Ye prob just edged it I'd say but ye should be beating that team #ArnoldSchwarzenegger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 😂😂😂😂 it's a joke and why I'm not convinced at all by klopp. Origi firmino wijnladum klavan. All of them tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 so so bad I hate them all I think. Sturridge on the bench 😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tkirby8 state of that lineup my god #divock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol at that lineup Divock Origi starting a game at old Trafford instead of Daniel Sturridge is all kinds of fucked up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball @GNev2 what's life like as a manger in Spain can we have a behind the scenes look into that? 
Thought so. Shit pundit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carra23 @ManUtd how's he proved us all wrong? If you had a clue you'd know your stuff about him and know he would be class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryAndy81 @LivEchoLFC @LivEchonews @DanielSturridge you're obviously Fucking stupid anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Hannibal show so far is laughable cheap Fucking nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker @MJP_74 Jesus swear you won the nobel prize you eejit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncrossmirror how is that a master class? Will be less attractive to other clubs and he should sell him asap if e doesn't want to play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely little lesson for Nathaniel Clyne here. The biggest myth in England]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georginio sideways passing wijnaldum is some player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha Ragnar Klavan Estonian player of the year imagine how bad the rest are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus how many times does that retard firmino lose the ball a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushmarsh14 @paddypower hahahah Jesus state of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tony_Scott11 😂😂😂😂 Jesus best of luck with that]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>