<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriots are getting fisted hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilM91 @Ciara_Roons on the way into town now pal will give ye a bell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_Roons @PhilM91 Exactly â˜ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_Roons @PhilM91 the living room is it Phil yea? ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rabona to a back heel then the finish from Dembele, filthy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great finish from Dembele]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible start for us hopefully we can pick ourselves up its only the first game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yelrucnelle I didn't think so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yelrucnelle he's fucking quality in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tbreadhomeslice say it's quality! With a lineup like that thou don't think it can be bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That lineup fucking hell https://t.co/bVQlcCQasA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 years gone today! Ireland will never see the likes again! RIP luke kelly https://t.co/liZ210vsAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payet off to Marseille for a medical! https://t.co/UA3LHKCbBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yelrucnelle Ahh won't ruin it for ye just my opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was a bit disappointed with Trainspotting 2 last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tbreadhomeslice @ThomasFoy3 @DanoOBrien7 Quality night ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 Grand yeaðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 Was looking for a ticket for me and dano going to see trainspotting 2 later and going out after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 Looking for one or two myself if ye hear of any let us know I'll do the same ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanieOBrien @yelrucnelle Oi you cunts? Manchester rubbing off on ye already ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yelrucnelle Tell her to fuck off haha you enjoy Manchester Ellen ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this chap in our first team squad and we'd be laughing https://t.co/QnTVD7um22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The life lineup for this year is dirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainspotting 2 tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's up with this lad just standing there @SkySportsNewsHQ #SkySports https://t.co/8U7A5kZhyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That new inform Seamus Coleman looks absolutely filthy on ultimate team!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gavin Peers with two goals already hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tbreadhomeslice That's the oneðŸ‘†Yea exactly what we were doing anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tbreadhomeslice Time ye going at? Me, Dano and Foy and a few others going the one around 8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully Ryan mason gets better soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasFoy3 Cracker ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanoOBrien7 @ThomasFoy3 she's electric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fucking state of that! what are Juventus thinking https://t.co/hcmwMKU2m9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at his face that's what football is all about! Top class from Everton https://t.co/1E5eksiMzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasFoy3 Yes Foy â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me be the one that shines with you, in the morning we don't know what to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last exam tomorrow thank fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly pats fans need to get their heads checked moaning about not signing Brennan and Bisto! There not the players they were in 2013]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking wish I could go on the trip with the lads tomorrow Fucking snapping I've an exam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dundalk away and Higher Vision festival on paddy's day what a day that should be!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First exam went much better than I thought it would of!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Simpsons knows what's up! Up the RaðŸ€ðŸ€ https://t.co/Dy5TuCPKMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha fucking lakeside darts has gone to shit in recent years but this takes the biscuit ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/iVlqNHuoFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year everyone have a good one ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasFoy3 seat for 1 please pal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1995Curley say so! Heard they were quality the last two nights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking dying with a cold but sure we'll drive it on! looking forward to live forever laterðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hook a brother up https://t.co/1wAqhaxFnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanieOBrien hahaha cunt that wasn't me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasFoy3 was a good shout alright! Great dayðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing videos of the hangar, really should of let the lads twist me arm and went frankie rizardo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outlets were actually decent for once today! Think that trip though was just an excuse for us to drink on a train again ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone have a good dayðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsOnlyJk yea came on about 10 past 9!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking night last night!! Damo dempsey was quality as always and Patrick Topping smashed it in D8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Apollo House #apollohouse #HomeSweetHome https://t.co/16iG8Ab8R4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good start to the next couple of days! Passed my theory test today and Damien Dempsey and Patrick topping tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilfiSigurdson yea I can see that ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sean_tougher @Kaincallaghan97 just all about the money! Too many names on big wages! That's why finn went back to rovers as well I'd say!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 yea I know losing out on players to fucking bray!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 didn't hear about him coming in! Yea there throwing around mad money they got mccabe and arron greene aswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 keep hearing about Brennan myself but heard the other day about flood going to bray!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaincallaghan97 yea 100% pal we kept fagan so we should be building on that but it's just not happening! They'd wanna announce someone soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the fuck have rovers resigned Ronan Finn?? Not good news for dundalk at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What time are the fixtures coming out at does anybody know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a taxi last night was near impossible fucking joke!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great things happening at #HomeSweetHome, was just told no food needed at the moment so keep that in mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge three points for the blades tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College nights out are always mad! What a night last night though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effort of college and work today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awhh sit the fuck down https://t.co/3dbgFgJrZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simoncoyle96 constantly seem to be signing players they do ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be great if pats could announce a few signings instead of watching everyother club announce there's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celtic fans singing Go on home British soilders ðŸ‘ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted to see Clarkie go! Great servant to the club and always appreciated the fans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College assignements can fuck off haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atmosphere at park head is fucking on another level tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon Scotland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just woke up to see that gobshite actually fucking won the election! Honestly what's wrong with you American #ElectionDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simoncoyle96 @TwiAgeCom Hahaha fucking odd I didn't tweet that twitter must of done thatðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's my #Twitterversary! I have been on Twitter for 5 years (since 8 Nov 2011).
And you? https://t.co/VmPA4wLNer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenes in that cork end when they scored reminded me of fagans goal from 2014! Great scenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossLFC95 it popped up pal just giving ye another RT ðŸ‘ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWelsh_x @eflow_freeflow very true I would ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filthy Git just filthy https://t.co/1E2rgwT9CW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a manðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/3Dybu9yAKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus drivers announcement just now! "Due to damage been caused to buses there will be no buses going through bawnouge tonight" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That fucking mass event on Facebook is fucking gasðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the dundalk players are only coming down from the Mandy over the past two days that's why they were shit today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracker! #NowPlaying Forget - Original Mix by Patrick Topping â™« https://t.co/jK7XIpS4Oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean gannon won his 4th league in a row today just let that sink in!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great goal by hazard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yess get the fuck in!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How celtic haven't scored yet I'll never know ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cork was a cracking trip anyway! Shit result but we made the most of the night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished an 8 hour shift after coming back from Cork today get me to bedðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tattoo fixers time! #StandUpToCancer #TattooFixers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day this was!! https://t.co/2k0uxlxOhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shutupyoufag few players have to go and bring in decent ones for us to move forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shutupyoufag hope so! Blades are wouldn't say that about us thou hahaha]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>