<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I love lamp. (I just wish it wouldn't rattle so much when I walk by it!) https://t.co/KLCa2gWGOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iMarkMyWorld Ill stand upfront holding a boombox up while it plays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeRobertsVO https://t.co/UQPd4RNorW
Hope that helps. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special congratulation to @JessLL for being one of the community weapon skin winners with her "Who Wants Toast?!" Gnasher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the winners, all of these skins are very creative and awesome looking! https://t.co/8D5XBOaUn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PezRadar You gotta respect his commitment in making your life harder though, lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday i told my barber i much prefer snow to rain. Then today it stops raining and starts snowing instead...coincidence? I think not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seriously_Soapy Yo put me in coach! Let me play, I can sweat with the best of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PezRadar I bet @Seriously_Soapy will love that Classic Baird...*Davs sweating intensifies*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My personal favorite out of the artist armor designs. :D https://t.co/4ejMvCfzPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got all the Year of the Roaster OW skins i was after, now i can go back to playing for fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KadaburaDraws Your art style is unique and super rad! Next time you open up commissions id jump at the chance\ to get one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dragonrlh Nice! NOW BUY OVERWATCH! So we can play. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my wants! https://t.co/B7OJuxCqWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arukun14 Woah! Don't blame me im gonna need to buy them all as well lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grexoz I is disjoint, you should be getting three of each day one. *shakes head*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyFantasiWorld Its one of my favorite pieces! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see @MyFantasiWorld finally on twitter. Phenomenal artist, outstanding person and a truly passionate Gear h… https://t.co/2LFIRochGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BChapy @Tac_Com @JessLL Yeah she's kind of cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robauten Ha! I take it you got the voice mail. Agreed would love it if all three of us could get together like that someday. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These all look super rad! Amazing work by everyone that submitted designs! https://t.co/J7vss2X7rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robauten Me and TCB are having a lovely dinner and talking about you. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LambentHammerB Sorry was too busy, but looks like Stoic got it correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DasRootin Ma poor wallet! I need them both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many phenomenal artists in the Gears community. You all rock! https://t.co/0ZDSkxODMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Welcome to the big suck, Sgt.Fenix. Ready to hit the road?" https://t.co/Cy02EHP1Zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look sharp people! That's not search-and-rescue!" https://t.co/7ZvyWuZCVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man @suda_51 what are you up to? Is that a new No More Hero's....OH YEEEEAAAAAHHHHH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickRoche This piece is really rad Nick! Freaking amazing work! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham Once i saw that design i knew i had to go out right after the movie and pick up the Black series Tank Trooper figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham Personally i i really liked the Tank Trooper deign the most. That helmet is just so goood!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love those Medics...and the #SpoopySkeletonGearman https://t.co/rlP11lPLU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KadaburaDraws HorrOreos, Stir-Fright Rice, Tomb-ato Soup, Corn on the Cobweb, Hallo-wieners, Sandwitches, Boorito.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KadaburaDraws Ghoulash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopped at security, they brought a guy over, he asked me if I had a Gears of War Boomer statue in my carry on. Me: Yes, Him: Freaking rad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LambentHammerB I think I have season one but not two. I may pick it up when it goes on games with gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LambentHammerB Heck yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Parasidian Especially Gungrave and Megaman Xtreme!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really rad game shop opened near my parents place since I left. Snagged some gems I've been trying to find for a lo… https://t.co/60JB3eTUZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing Uncharted: Drakes Fortune for the first time. The remaster looks pretty good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends, Mario Party, shots and New Years the perfect combination. #TeamWaluigi #Whaaaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glovestudios Honestly your design of Prowl is probably my favourite. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WisdomThumbs The renders from the teaser and announcement post are really good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude that is one super rad Marcus/JD piece! Nicely done! :D https://t.co/sDHmr58LPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRazoredEdge Glory to the UIR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crobos_ Ha! Good luck with that dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRazoredEdge Huh never thought of that before. Thats actually pretty unique way of seeing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadDogMalcs @JessLL She just flirts with everyone. SO FLIRTATIOUS! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRazoredEdge Thats what i did...but thats all i did then left. XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RetroTypes Good suggestion, not so easy for me but sill a good suggestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessLL Or! Counter point, i hide in my hoodie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Falloutt I love my bro, as we walked away he hit me on the back and told me i was an idiot and then started to chuckle. XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Parasidian I'm so nervous/awkward that I can never tell when a girl is actually interested in me. RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cute girl behind cash started to talk about One Piece since I was buying a figure. Apparently she was interested in me...so says my bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grexoz *slowly shakes head in disappoint*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grexoz Nope, see it again and come back with "This was a great movie".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlamazonianRage YOU REALLY DO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grexoz Then go watch Rogue One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlamazonianRage Apparently if you play as him on Nepal he says "Welcome to the Himalayas!" in reference to the Yeti in Monsters Inc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends, beer and board games make for a perfect evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL THOSE CRITS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The inevitable buying of Star Wars merch after seeing #RougeOne. Love that Tank Trooper design! https://t.co/gNhgPvIfW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dexter_art Have to totally agree with you Dex, the design of the tank troopers in #RogueOne  was amazing! https://t.co/f2Kfjh4gqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlamazonianRage Ended up getting most of the Holiday skins, but the Reaper one was the only one I truly needed. https://t.co/HIhd8sCrr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now to re-watch A New Hope...awww hell the whole original trilogy why the heck not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RogueOne was a phenomenal Star Wars movie. It put the "War" back into Star Wars. Have to say it ranks up their with the original trilogy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna see #RogueOne with the family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Merry Gearsmas to you all! https://t.co/OKhvK2fA2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came home (Ontario) to a surprise party waiting for me with a bunch of my friends. This was the greatest gift  I could have ever asked for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BonnieJeanMah While on my hunt for them I saw quit a few of him at the various EB Games located around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Golby_mkII Absolutely your design for him, especially how you placed the forks on his back! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very accurate. https://t.co/LFJWGqVdXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love @PlayOverwatch's world chat. Stuff like this brings me great joy. #Monstars https://t.co/QNSXSmdwgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bizkitdoh Sorry can't help you with that. I'm not the one who makes those decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bizkitdoh Because it looks cool. :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One UIR soldier is worth ten COG cowards. Ahahaha!!! https://t.co/S9oXn8rLWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Riskieren Just give in and spend your Overwatch coinage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave up trying to get the OW skins I wanted so I just used my coins to get the Reaper, Zarya and Roadhog skins...but now their mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreatureBox Phenomenal piece, would love to see it as a print.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my new beer mug. #SuperFightingRobotMegaman #Skullman https://t.co/Z7un8JyDqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The luck was real, during the studio gift exchange I got the #1 Golden Ticket inside my gift. I chose the Gears 4 c… https://t.co/rjZa5Udf3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little bit of not so trivia. I may have been the one to suggest the pose for the Marcus Mystery Mini, in homage to… https://t.co/qf655uWsCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much holiday cheer! Love it! :D https://t.co/x6Dy5RS3YY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's moving on up, all that sweat finally payed off...but that smell will always remain in the mp lab. But really d… https://t.co/lZrWI3LDxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham Yeah i was also surprised, but i actually prefer her being their then him since it kind of makes more sense overall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham But since they created a completely different look for him in G2 the ending of G1 didn't make as much sense anymore, so changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham The idea was to have the ending be more significant, since in the original it was just an "early" model of Skorge that appears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcburcham Well...of course! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BChapy No I want the ones from across the street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished reading the first issue of the new Venom comic, loved the direction their taking it and @Ger_Sandoval's ph… https://t.co/Sns4oeQQuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was told to prepare for a snow storm but instead I got a very nice Ontario style winters day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Parorou Such an amazing art piece of Gum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me the fate of #SpiderManHomecoming now rests solely on whether or not Shocker's dune buggy appears in the movi… https://t.co/u6yPbY6c7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkChaoz95 @BChapy They both have completely different voices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Riskieren The standard "Aspho" UIR soldier is my all time favorite Mp character! All hail the mighty comrade!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was really looking forward to Let It Die until I realized it was a PS4 exclusive. Now I'm sad that I won't be able to play it. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arukun14 @CoalitionGears The attempt was real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My attempt at bringing some holiday charm to the Campaign QA area at @CoalitionGears. https://t.co/HgGr3Kldwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seriously_Soapy @vitzyy Noodlebox isn't as good as you guys make it out to be!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessLL Ill be on the look out for a Marcus then. ;)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>