<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Your kids go to public school? https://t.co/w7psHDcT5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseArreguin it doesn't qualify as hateful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyYoung63 * sticks head out of garbage can*,...throws cat*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'cuck' thing. https://t.co/zvDKiuORc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Du hast by Rammstein ♫ https://t.co/nNdkvwV5rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinMazumder @GrubersMullet @KellieLeitch @HuffPostCanada statistically speaking, would you guess the attackers were Muslim or non Muslim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher and postal worker unions? https://t.co/HgBDB2vP4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not white nationalists because half of them are police informants. #QuebecCity https://t.co/OKklq2o94K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslims have been killing Muslims for religious reasons since long before we were born.  #quebeccity https://t.co/hJeZcdIok2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a chance https://t.co/9S4acQSJ3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how long, if ever, it will take Bill to realize just want to stupid tweet this was https://t.co/ThUBBzuLls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisatozzi @Peggynoonannyc don't worry , you'll make it after all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is some smile.  https://t.co/sqfWNE6fUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vag just does not lend itself well to the furry community. https://t.co/qqAutEn59y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell @aterkel he is setting her up for a future presidential candidacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nypost the she wasn't much of an agent anyway. Fine attention whore though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Boys - In The Morning
https://t.co/MuoBOJ6At8 https://t.co/MuoBOJ6At8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost there used to be a fourth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hitfar is always been at the leading edge of inventory management 

 https://t.co/T16nSsL45I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business One - EDI Success Story | eBridge Connections @Hitfar  https://t.co/T16nSsL45I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill during that period, the media itself will have done it five times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinBelam @StrategicThghts not forcing government to pay for play. time has nothing to do with women's bodies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizaCKNW980 @WoodfordCHNL @MartinBelam this has nothing to do with how you use your body, this is about how the government uses our money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianlilley @Banks_Todd @globeandmail @DougSaunders according to him, the 500+ sexual. asaults didn't happen in Hamburg last NY either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke @ChrisMurphyCT @washingtonpost possibly the loudness discourages people from using them. Just sayin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying I Know It's Gonna Happen Someday - 2014 - Remaster by Morrissey ♫ https://t.co/fI6je1dF18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer is 💥 the Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld @BBCNews @bbclysedoucet their balls are far bigger than yours, social media dickhead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the smooth fluidity of a drunken horse https://t.co/r6BIJjnpTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulfeig @piersmorgan like the 30 year old college student that wants us to pay for their birth-contro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Have To Fun - Original Mix by Volta Cab ♫ https://t.co/khRPZUkmhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Headhunter - Talla 2XLC by Front 242 ♫ https://t.co/NZ1TLt6n3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sucker punch. What a tough guy https://t.co/KK3o5WaTL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardroeper @paulfeig @piersmorgan i'm sure the investors agree with you Richard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh, the "Bill Clinton defense". https://t.co/xOxtLDa8lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomArnold @NotDateline @Kneel_son6er @POTUS you might want to see if you've doubled up on your meds today Tom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowlinglibrary how many persons of color were in book one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cselley @ivortossell it's just a simple way to get idiot journalist talking about other things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity worth $3.7 billion, beat all of the Republican opponents, then went on to beat. an opponent that spent twice as much money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think this was a mistake then you're easily led astray. @ZekeJMiller https://t.co/CpAIcAg50G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one was their for the #Rotherham kids. https://t.co/qiQncZkog8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men are busy working. Won't show up. https://t.co/XZZIfytNHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't this homophobic? #WomensMarch https://t.co/uEMDHIFcd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Implode by Front Line Assembly ♫ https://t.co/O5Hcln6EdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CEDickson @ezralevant  no lingham will ever go anywhere hear that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleyCsanady Nice grammar writer girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicious. Make it good #Netflix #netflixcanada https://t.co/KXSyE7YvG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @nytpolitics I believe there is salve for this butthurt. Give it a try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check the replies. Trumpers are  good folk https://t.co/66o9XKXj5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shikhadalmia fascist is a fun word isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne @Oddschecker Best way to exploit the punters is to exploit their bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dangainor @tanzinavega 96% actually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Sheep On Drugs ♫ https://t.co/vwRP6s66tW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brad_duren @GreatDismal The fact that you think it's a strange sequence of events, is reason number one why it happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezralevant @CBCMontreal my kids are excited to see Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OutlawTory @Magusiak don't forget they made a point of making the ultimate villain white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cselley @acoyne hey! Leave Seeley alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No you aren't, you bitter old hag. https://t.co/GrxDucxn1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationallampoon Schools are funded at the state level are they not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama invited Al Sharpton to the White house. https://t.co/H1844SX6hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This reads like an Onion tweet. https://t.co/JkAoN53MPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emery_Mike aye. She blocked me for that.  🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People like Tom Arnold get killed, not assassinated, in any case. https://t.co/qVMVQuF6Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add a quick vagina steaming and It's tea time. Cc:@GwynethPaltrow https://t.co/DGoANTrjJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Racer Northwest Pale Ale From Surrey BC. Excellent. https://t.co/KPAwHYKPh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lwwillow1 I would not be surprised if this actually existed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kingsthings Clinton is much better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau unscripted is going to be the gift that keeps on giving. https://t.co/Or0E93VUTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westham009 @piersmorgan so you're saying 'ancestral homeland' and 'homeland' are the same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westham009 @piersmorgan she didn't say ancestral homeland, just 'homeland' She is a lawyer. She knows what words mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @westham009 in fairness there is a video on YouTube of Michelle Obama calling Kenya Baracks homeland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Attacking all attackers" this is a problem? https://t.co/kamc7NcqCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey dress that way because it allows them to perform better, silly. https://t.co/cvooi43Ahm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljholden @GreatDismal you don't have to watch to know this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomArnold @taraclocastro @flowerytwats2 bigly is an adverb Tom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithboykin @WoodfordCHNL what does that have to do with anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a bunch of lunatics. https://t.co/oxTWLUaNnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a load of lunatic, ,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomArnold @piersmorgan Trump didn't say anything not already said by Michelle Obama https://t.co/6l85qwd4GP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kashanacauley @ron_fournier @realDonaldTrump you understand English don't you? And you've heard of Chicago? New Orleans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @JuliaDavisNews @realDonaldTrump so that's the only thing he's done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No it wasn't. Nice headline though https://t.co/NkNPieU5m6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know what I'd. say if somebody said something to me based on us sharing the same skin color. https://t.co/mOyHQwoQji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindyfinn I hope you never get introduced to pure evil, but if you do have someone let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimesworld The human catapillar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustSchmeltzer @PoliticalLine @realDonaldTrump at this point I think Mr. Lewis should be working on anything. It seems he doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge pet peeve is Milsums co opting the American black and experience to claim victimization. It's low. https://t.co/sK8XYfo1FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/CBcoE3uMbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Know you're rights' from a guy that admires Fidel Castro. https://t.co/JY8du9pHOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to take a seat in Congress and then sit around for 30 years doing nothing you deserve to be called… https://t.co/oUT3y2ykWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@exjon we call that a smile Jon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJGerson @realDonaldTrump all talk, one action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every tweet I see about John Lewis infers hes done nothing since elected. Civil rights hero become a paperweight. https://t.co/YJlb74LFZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's pretty racist to launch this on a Friday night.  #MichelleLegacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white man!!! https://t.co/JAZ0XyBm0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baseballcrank @joss @SpeakerRyan he did Firefly. He's not a complete idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame lies with the DNC superdelegates, it's a simple as that. 
 https://t.co/wKNR03bxwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is funny until you realize that most men support abortion. Lets them clean off the hook.  Other than that, LOL https://t.co/ImINI2okVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seceedercat @acoyne @KellieLeitch well, someone is confusing the word elite with elitist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@spark_show @Prem_S @lbastura @CBCNews is Justin aware that just because you're transsexual doesn't mean you're gay? #cdnpoli]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>