<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabibYasir He's a 70 year old Man-Child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabibYasir I'd say it's way worse 12 year old's have a better vocabulary than he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear of the passing of #AllWhites legend Steve Sumner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNewton @Tegal1234 I'm betting that you'll get the full service for year 2 of their contract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 *All games live provided you have SKY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNewton @Tegal1234 That being said it's piss poor that they haven't launched the pop up channels that Sky have on connect yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNewton @Tegal1234 I think it has something to do with beIN 2 being their dedicated non English channel (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the few Rugby players I actually admired such sad news such an awful bloody disease MND hopefully one day we… https://t.co/HtoQYykfPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1JamieScott @patrick478 @NiallGunner That would be ideal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's what an independent judiciary does it's nothing new. https://t.co/dOzwORMXET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's what an independent judiciary does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndraFBCSports @Blitzboks It really looks like they will run away with the World Series this year unless Fiji, NZ or England get going fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji I'd be frightened to say that to my mum (or sisters) growing up around strong women who would bash the shit out of me if I did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether it's in a GT3 or a V8 Supercar racing at Bathurst is always top notch #B12hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what Maro Engel is going to say to Shane Van Gisbergen when he gets back to the garage #B12hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wowowowow this race is outstanding I want to see more of this #B12hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnzoGiordani @Scousek1w1 Top trolling Jeremy haha I better win it in a few weeks at the ACFC game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 @NiallGunner I reckon when they go to the triple round robin they should axe the playoffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 @pineyzb I'm picking Waitak, TW, ESAFC, ACFC for playoffs but am open to being wrong Hawke's Bay were the better team today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@official_lesdog I'd be all for a Taranaki based A-League franchise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #SSPremiership season has to be the most exciting ever any team in the top 5 can win this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have thought @AucklandCity_FC in the unusual position of 5th after this round of action #HBvAC #SSPremiership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @HawkesBayUnited deserved win over @AucklandCity_FC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibardy Teams will struggle with the heat at Bill McKinlay games but I think you'll come good I have faith in @JoseCoaching and team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamWelly Feeling like you're in an oven yet?? always disgustingly hot there in summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive congratulations @reckonsemoji and @grumpybirb https://t.co/ZHflfz0lJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFCspook Yeah they're playing well but if any team can get a result it's you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFCspook People forget you smashed them only a few months ago #ShortMemories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoutriver Sometimes I wish she'd just go away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Avi_Lal Yep and still the Brisbane 10s to come next week 😴😴😴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @nicki_mtm Definitely with you on Hamilton being one of the best for football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using massacres that never happened as a justification for Trump's immigration ban is perhaps the dumbest thing I'v… https://t.co/Lxcx2EnfrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grumpybirb Yay all the best Roz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji @lailaharre All the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @YouTube I am very much a leftist myself BUT I can't endorse what is happening if you disagree debate the person don't riot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@official_lesdog That would make complete sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamWelly If I wasn't working on Sunday I would be making the trip across Auckland to Billy Mac as this will be a great game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't the winner obvious MVG for sure. https://t.co/i6iwLJnplo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCity_FC @HawkesBayUnited Should be a good game can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoutriver I'm just bothered by Bill English in general.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So September 23 for the New Zealand election #VoteNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pineyzb That is really sad news I remember her smashing the field in the Auckland Marathon in 2001 at 52 years of age impressive run RIP 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarelleSindos I'd say you should be 3-1 up by now the only team showing anything on attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool should be 3-1 up by now they are battering Chelsea #LIVCHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool deserved that #LIVCHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarelleSindos Bloody sideshow bob great goal though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarelleSindos It will more than likely be 3-2 I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNormanS @timfarron I'm sure Trump will be livid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunar New Year Cup Champions congrats @AucklandCity_FC ugly at times but job done #KIvAC #LunarNEwYear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reid Drake on for stoppage time #KIvAC #LunarNewYearCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonRichards4 @NarelleSindos @Clemans4Kim Have to agree with Simon Kim has been excellent tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 minutes added time nervy moments #KIvAC #LunarNewYEarCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCity_FC It would have been worth 3 points if it happend in that stadium in a few months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Micah for the last few minutes #KIvAC #LunarNewYearCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kitchee go close again #KIvAC #LunarNewYEarCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kitchee looking likely #KIvAC #LunarNewYearCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent shift from @CameronHowieson tonight replaced by De Vries #KIvAC #lunarnewyearcup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some sloppy fouls being given away by @AucklandCity_FC #KIvAC #lunarnewyearcup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCity_FC Damn it I thought it was going in for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tintin25 Same here my Cantonese isn't so good. @AucklandCity_FC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bleacherbible Please let it be the saints. (AND NOT SELLING)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still 10 minutes or so from starting but live streaming of @AucklandCity_FC vs @HK_Kitchee can be found here https://t.co/Rs8SDiOwD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCity_FC @MuangthongUtd @FCSEOUL Live Stream is up for the final now https://t.co/Rs8SDj681G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oche_balboa Jesus Christ I don't like the man but it's not like he's Kim Jong-Un he's the president of the closest ally you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HassanShibly So basically she got fired for doing her job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibardy Oh no big mistake that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnzoGiordani I was thinking about going there too if I can be bothered catching a bus and a train across Auckland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnzoGiordani Can't get it at Billy Mac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnzoGiordani Do you still want the coffee machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 @GMB You poor bastard I send my sympathies nobody should have to deal with that nutter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz I bet the players are thrilled at the prospect of playing on artificial turf easy win though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a tie for Sutton United a home match vs Arsenal #FACup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oche_balboa Plus a ban would suggest that it is permanent without exceptions not 3 months with exceptions (And I'm opposed to this order)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oche_balboa I'm not for it cause innocent people will get punished but brand it what it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oche_balboa A 90 day suspension of travel from ALL citizens of 7 countries regardless of religion is totally different to a muslim ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel for Stoinis New Zealand dodged a bullet #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly not out #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia have the jugular and the choke is happening #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the choke happening? if they do it's a disgrace #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand up and take a bow Stoinis #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dealing in boundaries now #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoinis can win this for Australia #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibardy Whoops yeah them too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If any team can knock off 94 runs in 10 overs it's Australia rule them out at your peril #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Avi_Lal That's gotta be embarrasing but nicely done @manuz05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great batting Stoinis I give Australia a big chance for victory if he keeps going like this #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dare I say @CricketAus are back in with a chance here #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clementine_ford @couriermail I'm quite relaxed about being mocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's clearly taking the piss. https://t.co/OKRyzMFuMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibardy @pmbillenglish He doesn't want to offend his new friend Donald by the looks of it #Disgrace #SpeakUp #WeAreBetterThanThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliefairey One of the things I love about Mt Roskill is it's diversity I would certainly welcome more refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HypnoKiwi It should be called "You are evicted cause we are demolishing this for developers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall Well to be fair in Mt Roskill I felt I only had one choice Michael Wood of Labour cause the other candidates were ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall Some deals aren't as bad like the Greens or Act refusing to run in Mt Roskill to help Labour and National.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac A 16 hour #MeanTweets special and it will still be too short.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonCuttingMAGA I'm a liberal and I don't agree with that either your nationality should not determine your ability to enter a country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VitiWOS @WorldRugby7s @fijirugby I reckon they should keep Sydney add Suva and a New Zealand tournament at a new venue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VitiWOS @WorldRugby7s @fijirugby There is no reason why there can't be three tournaments in the region Sevens tour needs to expand!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminryan Suva needs to host a tournament I think the Rugby League 9s tourney in Auckland has killed Wellington 7s off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Brown92 @IndraFBCSports @WorldRugby7s @nz7s @fijirugby Perhaps a three week Oceania stint go Suva, Dunedin or Hamilton, Sydney.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>