<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if @algore and @MittRomney will do that same &amp; #DeleteTrump
#resist https://t.co/jWwvRF4byY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto So, to clarify, the list that @PressSec referred to, contains attacks that were widely covered. PERIOD. Cue....@melissamccarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawsaluto @ActualEPAFacts 
Reality check.I find it hard to believe @PressSec doesn't realize that they have alien… https://t.co/3da2XBETUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many more of these resolutions issuing support of our allies will need to be issued before the @GOP does the ri… https://t.co/vAEAdiUFxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain 
Oh how far we have fallen. In less than 3 weeks with #Trump, US is now a threat to Europe.… https://t.co/GxaxttvkDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Sounds like he is compensating for lack of knowledge required to make decisions &amp; low poll#s-more areas that he comes up short]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a sad state of affairs that the GOP can't develop a moral compass on what is right versus wrong without someon… https://t.co/kLbaVMlfFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GrabYourWallet 
#Resist https://t.co/ioifA4XS5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCormackJohn @jaketapper You assume he knows who Mao was &amp;is familiar with history. He still thinks @FDouglass2020 is alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ungaggedEPA I don't know what is more disturbing-the fact that they reject science or that they aim to discredit it
#ClimateChangeIsReal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS And he, alone, scored all of the touchdowns. And the crowd gave him a standing ovation for an hour
#SuperBowl #Alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats @jehmufordnc 
Hopefully you can come together &amp; represent the people-Not Wall Street, BigAg or Corp I… https://t.co/VCFBTbUo8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historically, the American people will think the actions of @POTUS were similar to those of an Authoritarian and it… https://t.co/5aH20PqTyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Any idea why the recording device was disabled during the Putin call? https://t.co/qyT4T9Czre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @CBS @ABC @FoxNews 
I believe in a #FreePress and 
#IstandwithCNN
We all need to work together to ensure our Constitutional Freedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mllnialnews @POTUS44 And with Russia. As a child of the cold war, I never thought I'd see that day. 
#GOPhaslostitsway
#silenceiscomplicity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AltRight is NOT Allright. https://t.co/VZYol1h6sL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse Just to be clear, I am NOT a paid protestor. I am someone who has a fond regard for the Constitution &amp;a deep love for the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse @realDonaldTrump 
If the judicial branch isn't supposed to be a check on the executive branch-exactly what purpose does it serve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse @realDonaldTrump Have you actually read the motion on the #muslimban The argument seems to be that judges… https://t.co/fLTHUsXGrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensasse Great point in that we do need more civics education today. Can we start with @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/TKaR9sna1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio You are right sir. We are better than that. Please speak up before we aren't. 
#GOPmusttakeastand
#silenceiscomplicity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@educatorsresist @Alt_DeptofED
If you live in NC, your senator wants to hear what you think about DeVos. RT and spr… https://t.co/pa5kOgpzug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovernorHogan
Please speak up for the state you represent - A state with a large population of immigrants.… https://t.co/fzdkPLQMZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain I know you love America as much as I do. Speak up.
#silenceiscomplicity
#TheResistance
#resist… https://t.co/eCt5cUYhTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alt_labor If confirmed, do we have to say ....  Brought to you by Carls Jr.?
#idiocracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryWHStaffer @CloudContact 
She was upset it didn't get the press it deserved. There is now a fund, thanks to her
https://t.co/81Ed1Nlx5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad commentary and @SpeakerRyan  isn't alone. 
#GOPhaslostitsway
#sellout 
#WeThePeople mean nothing anymore
#Sad https://t.co/JJysEM3LT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 But wait. I'm confused. Is it or is it not a ban. I can't keep it straight.
https://t.co/7USXA3VbRa
#muslimban or #nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you #RosaParks for never giving up!
"You must never be fearful about what you are doing when it is right."… https://t.co/dg8qsl7bjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC @marcorubio @SenatorLeahy @TheDemocrats 
Stand up for our Country and Stand up for the Constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryWHStaffer Maybe she is looking for a good stock tip. I hear her clothing line isn't doing so well. 
#GrabYourWallet 
#TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC @marcorubio Can we all agree with @SenatorLeahy ? Join together with @TheDemocrats… https://t.co/wdJuejVkCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FDouglass2020 You are one talented fellow!  
#BlackHistoryMonth 
#FrederickDouglas https://t.co/1i8pC5zTnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts @resisterhood @shawsaluto 
When did targeting human beings become part of the GOP mantra?… https://t.co/lOrUDfVIVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samsteinhp #MayaAngelou said it best "When a person shows you who they are, believe the the first time"
#resist
#TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts @shawsaluto @resisterhood 
Keep up the GREAT work.  
#resist
#nomuslimban https://t.co/jUWqGh81uR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeland Security suspends travel ban
https://t.co/TTK6ocqi39
One small Victory for #TheResistance One Giant Victory for the #Constitution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawsaluto @resisterhood 
Interesting thread about revoked visas affected by the #MuslimBan   
#TheResistance… https://t.co/pT0FAecfoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @realRogueLeader @washingtonpost We have been speaking up about Russia sir. Where is the outrage from the GOP sir?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBuss878 @jjouvenal @PressSec Whose definition of Western values?I use the Constitution to define Western values and they are compatible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenAlexander @Medium @educatorsresist TRANSLATION: Few Americans have donated as much money to the GOP as Betsy DeVos has.
#DumpDevos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikkiCZ @TIME @resisterhood @realDonaldTrump Wow. The SILENCE is DEAFENING. 
#MuslimBan 
#falsenarrative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBuss878 @jjouvenal @PressSec I have friends of all religions and all of the refugees I have met have been gracious and kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBuss878 @jjouvenal @PressSec Not at all. Have you actually ever met a muslim or a refugee from one of the banned countries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WriteTF @Call_Me_Dutch Thank you Dutch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now.... This is how to #DressLikeAWoman https://t.co/Whd7siaXLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Paris fits his ban. The Trump supporter in Quebec doesn't. 
#falsenarrative
#MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristinannthom @jjouvenal Liars is so harsh. Alternative truth teller? He simply provide #Alternativefacts for the AltRight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjouvenal So when @PressSec said only 109 people had been affected, he was talking in THOUSANDS. 
#MuslimBan 
#Alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CloudContact @Lost_In_Georgia You set the bar so high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lost_In_Georgia @CloudContact Critical thinking helps!
#sciencematters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ Maybe he was meeting with @FDouglass2020  to discuss the great things he going do! 
#blackhistorymonth#blackhistorymonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsK12 @arneduncan Did @realDonaldTrump and  @PressSec learn about @FDouglass2020 from Betsy DeVos? 
#DumpDevos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@resisterhood @TIME @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls can spout fiction about #BowlingGreenMasacre,but can't condemn a supporter of his
#sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogueNASA @redbubble @teespring I saw some on @amazon today as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehmufordnc It's not lies, it's Alternative TRUTH! Like #alternativefacts but worse!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickBaumann I understand it is a YUGE problem in Rural America. Bigly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepDonBeyer Thank you sir.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonCentral @realDonaldTrump I see a statement was issued today on the Louvre. Was anything ever issued condemning the Quebec attack?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well....there goes the rest of our allies.
#resist
#StopPresidentBannon https://t.co/ypwuuFPjlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME @resisterhood Did @realDonaldTrump ever issue a statement after one of his supporters committed a terrorist act at a mosque in Canada?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @robreiner #silenceiscomplicity
#GOPhaslostitsway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawsaluto @SenJohnMcCain Vladimir is indeed a great man fighting against oppression. We could use your help here… https://t.co/9RJyfGRPIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Draintheswamp and fill it with oil? 
With @exxonmobil running the @AltStateDpt I guess we shouldn't be surprised-E… https://t.co/OXIWOLnvkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Maybe he is up to pay tribute to all of those lost in the  #BowlingGreenMasacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steve_vladeck @K8brannen @KellyannePolls Channeling your best 'Onoin' headline for @PressSec? #alternativefacts 
#Knowledgeispower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar @SenJohnMcCain 2 weeks in&amp;we are close to war with Iran &amp; China, we are mostly ignoring Russia &amp;offending allies. Not Good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq @K8brannen Not wrong. #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC America agrees with you. Now do it. #russianhacking https://t.co/MvLvfnmzfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT @jonlovett Can we check the readout on it? https://t.co/VKbk9j5wzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Where is the outrage from @TGowdySC @gowdy and @GOPLeader They are strangely silent on this. #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Woman's place is in the House.... Or the Senate! #dresslikeawoman https://t.co/SgnbyZUD8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@resisterhood In light of all that @ActualEPAFacts @altUSEPA is dealing with - The Lorax seems appropriate. #filibusterfiller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kacalbobby @SenJohnMcCain @CBSEveningNews Oh Please. It is irrefutable proof. You can try and deflect. It doesn't change the FACTS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kacalbobby @SenJohnMcCain @CBSEveningNews Knowledge is power. It helps to expand your horizons and get your news from multiple outlets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kacalbobby @SenJohnMcCain @CBSEveningNews I rely on MANY news sources,here is a montage to simplify things for you: https://t.co/7USXA3VbRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alt_DeptofED Time to #DumpDevos 
We need a strong advocate for Dept of Ed
Keep up the hard work!
#resist https://t.co/aptaWFNM5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithellison @washingtonpost It appears he has not turned in his ethics paperwork. Does he even *want* this position?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Senator - Must we wait until all of the gray areas are colored before Congress will act?… https://t.co/soMLvVIiqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Watched him throughout the entire campaign and NEVER got that vibe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Maybe he missed his afternoon nap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Day12:Look at the NSC, Russia, Iran, Mexico &amp;Australia. In your heart of hearts, are we on the right path? 
#StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And maybe actually take the time to learn about Frederick Douglas. He was a great man. @PressSec could also use the… https://t.co/eR4UsSGat3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well...if they are anything like the transcripts that are being leaked...I am surprised it hasn't driven someone to… https://t.co/uehH4jCzGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCardin Thank you sir! Looks like we will have a few battles to fight this year! 
@altUSEPA @AltEPA 
#cleanwater matters .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lIjXU8IbYz
Hey @BadHombreNPS 
Be careful! US Troops may be coming for you! 
#BADHOMBRES
#TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xcdSlrVSmD @AltStateDpt
 Oh the Irony. Remember when @SenJohnMcCain @marcorubio were concerned about Russia?
#GOPhaslostitsway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts @altUSEPA This must be stopped in the Senate. No common sense. Are they trying to expand Flint? Wor… https://t.co/N2R40NDHGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best news I've seen all day. Thank you so much @MarkWarner 
#NSC
#StopPresidentBannon 
#TheResistance https://t.co/9NAwrKm8Sc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loondale No.  But I can use the facts to draw reasonable conclusions.  It's called logic, my dear.  You should try it some time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loondale You are right.  Suspected.  The FSB did the autopsy.  Just another of many bodies attributed to Putin.  😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loondale He was linked to #RussianDossier body sent to FSB &amp; they reported heart attack, hardly a reliable source
https://t.co/qFz4bIx0ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then there was the case of the Agent who was murdered. Maybe there is some validity to the dossier?… https://t.co/UEuCBkQE3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorLeahy Sir you are correct. How can we as a Nation go down the path of accepting anything less? The US #Constitution must be defended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BmoreBloc Has @GovernorHogan come out against the #muslimban yet? State Dept has cancelled active visas last night
https://t.co/DRkc8OH8Vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovernorHogan We are 5 days into the #muslimban &amp; State Dept just issued notice visas to be revoked. When will you speak up? @SarahPinsker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 days in. The US is now considered a threat to our allies. 
#GOPhaslostitsway
#TheResistance https://t.co/r26klRerW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[released https://t.co/RA84GtRu3i
@AltStateDpt Revoking visas notice? Is it for people who are in US or for travellers abroad
#muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum He is a great negotiator and he always follow through on agreements. Just ask one of his many contractors. He owes them bigly!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>