<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity against actions of @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/fo2q2hYRLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis: You cannot reject refugees and call yourself a Christian https://t.co/WcjRqBUfs0 via @USUncut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation can only be misogyny - The Republicans' health uncare priority targets women &amp; @TeenVogue again reports… https://t.co/F8498aPfbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow - "You might live longer if your doctor's a woman" https://t.co/FonlyOIW4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign! PETITION: Stop Govt. funded big irrigation @NathanGuyOtaki https://t.co/YQ2HC2YBHv #SaveOurRivers #Ruataniwha via @GreenpeaceNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Rick Hanson (@drrhanson) thoughtful, timely, important - Love What's Real - Just One Thing https://t.co/EyXLT9TJmK via #constantcontact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcoming the New Year - Let us make peace our priority in 2017 - so the lotus will rise from the mud… https://t.co/JjiQ7ZETLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Originally about a relationship, a theme tune for our times - Cream "We're going wrong".  
https://t.co/87AmDgeoha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumaosheng good catch - cool photo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems timely - attributed to Mark Twain - "A lie can travel halfway around the world while the truth is putting on its shoes"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could US Mayors, Governors, and CEOs stop Trump from wrecking our climate?? Find out:  https://t.co/wzM1FtPrBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature, contemplation &amp; learning how to reduce suffering - autumn colours at Eishoji, Kamakura - a few weeks ago. https://t.co/7OkWpSOguM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ai Weiwei's (@aiww) show in NY - Laundromat. His art powerful witness to the humanity &amp; desperate state of refugees https://t.co/bntRRY5kUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To whoever that apoplectic gent is on @radionz with Wallace I would just say remember when the use of Ms was going to wreck the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Koanga 2 maintain heritage seed collection - vital work- Give to The Seed Campaign https://t.co/iSWvlOPDAI. Raise funds on @generosity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my must-read book list. I've been feeling despair about our impact on life on earth - need to reconnect with the… https://t.co/H5Qa1M8WiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My philosophy in life is to go to a place that's degraded and fix it up" - from gorse to bounty in Southland - the… https://t.co/P61JRCzlSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! A great plan for us all - to plant, and to tend the soil and living environment that sustains us https://t.co/pXouDYfz8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So lovely - and a bit of envy coming your way! https://t.co/AKalgVdrk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting how "God" is used as a cover by people who lack humility &amp; human kindness &amp; use their power to damage t… https://t.co/iFsUArk5nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of her! https://t.co/rEFA8uD7DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this: Norwegian Energy Minister @Oeddep must withdraw @Statoil from our waters without delay #Teikaroa  https://t.co/5wjIfTFQnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help - Stop @Staoil and @Chevron seismic blasting for oil in NZ's oceans https://t.co/ERXHrVWg2r #ClimateAction via @GreenpeaceNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helplessness and hope in the face of impossible forces https://t.co/rM0cJrPH32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important not to lose focus on the essentials for life itself https://t.co/orBzhUzYGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 inequity, cost, poorer outcomes &amp; alienation of medical staff, money siphoned off by big corporations, illness bi… https://t.co/LVpuHMrt18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White people https://t.co/bhmSSg83k2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't she be asked to swim in it- dive in, head under water, swallow a bit - proper swimming if it's so clean https://t.co/6KDugevM7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like greed and focus on $ yet again stuffing things up for animal welfare - this time, for local bees https://t.co/ftPK9qJegl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many tragedies, such important humanitarian work https://t.co/zjIQD0xWRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bo_recka @Pomegranate_NZ   That's fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get the feeling they want to wreck anything of value https://t.co/pWZl80D3aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if nature, like corporations, had the rights of a person? | Chip Colwell https://t.co/xEYeaJVdYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Wellington? don't miss great food from Pomegranate Kitchen(@Pomegranate_NZ)pop up at Moore Wilsons. Spinach pies… https://t.co/YEf5BdtbbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Indigenous people's issues are issues that affect everyone on earth &amp; we must address them seriously" Yuko Tsushima https://t.co/8BrNQkJNTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderfully persistent &amp; informative Jen Gunter flames the idea of, &amp; products 4, "vaginal shame" https://t.co/TuLDyyYAkJ via @DrJenGunter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting - get your copy of “The Ultimate Guide to Email Copywriting” https://t.co/C7AM31Sfga via @ramit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree! And because they also carry the idea of winning and losing they are unfair and can cause distress https://t.co/WHD8ikisi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go if you can - Jane Fulton Alt photography arresting, moving, layers of meaning, beautiful, imho https://t.co/zDIGGOXulp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brilliant collaboration between humans and rats ( who'd have thought!) and such a worthy cause to support - spons… https://t.co/Jnw05iFoWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The extraction model of rapacious money- making, not creating something useful but mining it for profit - a disaste… https://t.co/rZ9i3a8MQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Nye on how science illiterate leaders endanger us all https://t.co/WFR5xxoI7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Quotes in Remembrance of the Father of Permaculture – Bill Mollison (1928 to 2016) https://t.co/mRxlRSdSAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still time to donate to Matuku link &amp; help save significant wetland  &amp; native bush for all to learn, cherish &amp; enjoy https://t.co/fQAZh2oeOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tikorangi Thanks for the recommendation - looks v interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shy?  Reluctant to go out to social events? This is great. Go out or Stay In? How to Decide, in One Chart https://t.co/ty40qCuJ7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvelly: Two punch-ups, two outcomes https://t.co/LiVilZLHo9 via @nzherald https://t.co/x6t0Zm3Uex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tui in blossom - another great pic from Pete McGregor - https://t.co/7syLykso71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding peace in difficult times- Sign up to follow release of Independent film about Thich Nhat Hanh - Walk With Me https://t.co/iYUaIJRj98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please give generously to save the Matuku link - Te Henga wetland, home to many rare wetland species  https://t.co/fQAZh2oeOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemarieNorth A universal language - as is the caring you are providing. Such demanding work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosemarieNorth Sweet image evoked - in the midst of desperate situation. Sending my appreciation for the humanity &amp; courage of your work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington spring at play https://t.co/hkWXh3VL59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over and over again, evidence that we humans are failing the planet and jeopardising our future https://t.co/eVyCHoQVdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has freaked me too - creepy invasion of privacy by @facebook - outing patients using cellphone &amp; location info https://t.co/zsVDoQL0dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devastating people's health &amp; well being, w a govt who r either incompetent or want the bubble/illusion of "growth" https://t.co/M6gu1rw8An]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrageous! If Doc DG signed off illegal swap of protected conservation land for farmland, he should sign off too. https://t.co/k8Lmhb2QYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this call to govt to ban Kiwisaver from investing in arms, weapons and war https://t.co/NaUPeMHFxP via @actionstation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful clouds over #IslandBay this morning - compensation for our winds -#WhyWellington https://t.co/fZ6f8FSvOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's great! https://t.co/kCDOFgCpLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainbow over Taputeranga - some showers over #Island Bay  but not a bad place to be #WhyWellington https://t.co/jnqJgjMK5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more excuses @johnkeypm - your indifference to the impact of poverty &amp; suffering on NZ children is shocking https://t.co/s0AwWBYkat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IndraNooyi commit PepsiCo to using only truly responsible palm oil now #conflictpalmoil https://t.co/pvf6l0G9sq https://t.co/X5VFpqCqRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brief respite from the rain for people &amp; dogs @lyallbaynz but more to come https://t.co/R6R45hzZTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dutton and Aus govt the most culpable - should also "risk prosecution" for human rights abuses - https://t.co/7Q0a1E3ZPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We do not need tears...we need action. https://t.co/3LvzqFzIn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign 2 stop world's 1st deep sea mine! It’s in your hands @loews_hotels &amp; @metalloinvest to end this risky business https://t.co/wZ8Wke2jFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All around the world indigenous peoples the best stewards 4 protecting forests, w best solutions to protect wildlife https://t.co/QGo57i6Zuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened to grass-fed cows? Palm kernel use scandalous. I just asked @Fonterra to quit palm kernel use here: https://t.co/Mb2Ts5Olqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Korimako - New Zealand bellbird - wonderful song, difficult to photograph - well caught by Pete McGregor https://t.co/yaQlGIB7KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future hero - will learn to protect humans by detecting mines or Tb - such a sweet rat pup, such a big role in life https://t.co/I9q9GfEkfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trees rule! How millions of trees brought a landscape devastated by coal mining and quarrying back to vibrant life https://t.co/7LWLWUVtFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this petition: https://t.co/4VFQmyzjf5 via @actionstation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful work with sound - wonderful (&amp; unfamiliar to me) Australian birdsong, soothing water - a tonic from nature https://t.co/I00iIteBg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathetic! - like blaming a murder victim for putting themselves in the path of a flying bullet https://t.co/t7kcasGYCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful newletter w reflections &amp; photos on "gardens, landscape, growing &amp; making" from Dan Pearson &amp; partner Huw https://t.co/8blyzeJNUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow - Wide Open Sky #nziff - inspiring determined teacher bringing music to outback children-so moving, such impact https://t.co/eKck5m4Osh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover Hope they give u lots of support.1 person, no matter how loving, can't be everything. Sending hugs, so tough 4 both of u.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover Maybe she doesn't need u 2 be happy &amp; +ve all the time - trying to be can be so tiring &amp; depression takes advantage of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dale_dixon Just a simple Iceland poppy #OrangeFlower https://t.co/yeB5cGy43w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeronikaMeduna Very sad that we are losing you and your excellent reporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @johnkeypm - not just hindsight! #Chilcot report says it was clear at the time - wrong 2 attack Iraq, appalling &amp; probably criminal acts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilaHanan @abrahama999 I read it, with great sadness for you and horror at the apparently unstoppable forces of aggression in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what @Pontifex would think of your efforts for the poor @honbillenglish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A fundamental conflict between contractual &amp; clinical objectives where profit &amp; cost dictate clinical operations" https://t.co/kJrtbTKR2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental nightmare! A toxic, bee-killing mega-corp has just been proposed. Say no to @Bayer @MonsantoCo merger https://t.co/WOihi3NN0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover I guess the work he does requires that kind of bendy relationship with reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Island Bay today - rain, mist and dull grey - but still not a bad place to be - #WhyWellington https://t.co/FNjOsUIxYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferrovial is the new operator of Manus Island and Nauru detention centres. Tell Ferrovial to end operations NOW. https://t.co/9u5VqhG3ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s Papahānaumokuākea? It could be the largest protected area on the planet, if we act now… https://t.co/9EoJFpNuZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice who Key aligns himself with https://t.co/IPJCMUbvLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky News journalist left speechless as leave MP tells him 'there is no plan' https://t.co/4ItUFniAGq via @HuffPostUKPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And achievable for all of us in Wellington - Town belt, Bot gardens, Otari Wiltons bush, the bracing south coast etc https://t.co/zgnLJcVvUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So tricky to deal with political polarising thru fear &amp; hate. If we focus, in outrage, on making them wrong &amp; bad, aggression &amp; harm worsen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are liars and then there’s Boris Johnson and Michael Gove | Nick Cohen https://t.co/37C4ZBGyzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very clear explanation/prediction of Brexit - @OwenJones84 thoughts about the impact worth taking very seriously https://t.co/AwMd1c0nai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giselledraws Good distraction! Few days ago saw different Pseudopanax (crassifolium?) with kereru scoffing berries https://t.co/hR8aBZRU0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lies, damned lies and the damage done - Trump in Scotland https://t.co/y0aPEUzW9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't help but wonder how long it will take for bumper stickers saying "don't blame me I voted #Remain".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumaosheng Nor mine - much prefer to miss them!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>