<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That could be any bobcat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems should McConnell this nomination. #SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While treatment of Garland was unconscionable, it alone won't make Gorsuch illegitimate justice. Getting confirmed with &lt;  60 votes will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio you've spent the last year proving that doesn't matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the runner up be named Justice Congeniality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Bout time I was recognized as a Top Dem. :) https://t.co/eKcv9CUWqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 8pm I'll be watching BC v Wake. Good guys are only 6.5-point underdogs there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are doing #cleanFebruary. It's like you #cleanJanuary people never looked at a calendar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump pretty sure they still had more people at an impromptu protest than you got at your pathetic inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like most terrorists in North America, Quebec shooter was a white, male, right-wing pseudo-Christian and Trump supporter. Let's ban them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psst. Anyone have a connection for an avocado dealer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump start with yourself, Putin and Comey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not one of those "D"emocrats who threatened to move to Canada, but I am one of those "d"emocrats who's considering it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dydd Santes Dwynwen Hapus! Have a good cwtch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandtriggs I guess Trump thinks she voted for Hillary, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like @seanspicer or Dippin' Dots. #conflicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm old enough to remember when the most racist things in DC were Jeff Sessions and the football team. #GoodTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's kind of like we all got the same 2017 lie-a-day calendar for New Year's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio having "serious reservations" about a cabinet nominee is like me having "serious reservations" about eating more than 1 chip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If STEM ed is fundamental to the jobs of the future, than #SchoolChoice means giving up on our kids and grandkids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope this isn't too demoralizing, @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/UGDQ7sx6cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the opposite of strength. @seanspicer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEFCON 1. This is not a drill, people.

Sierra Nevada Recall https://t.co/QLMmN1Nn5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yay!" --Flint, Michigan https://t.co/OsiIRSnChA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer still insisting inaug was most watched ever. Counting people who watched reflection in their tinfoil hats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest takeaway from this briefing is that @seanspicer doesn't know what "duplicity" means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is dusting off one of W's favorite toys. https://t.co/XrmFCUsfm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secupp does it include cabinet secretaries? because that would be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Atlanta Falcons are about to have more fans then the ever have before. Cumulatively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take some comfort knowing @seanspicer thinks my #PhiladelphiaEagles are killing it this weekend. #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Guess it's true what they say about the size of a man's hands vis-a-vis the size of his inauguration crowd size.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've gone from Yes We Can to Yes We Klan.

David Duke: We did it | TheHill https://t.co/fiCTdn8FIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there an inauguration today? These crowds are great. #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps it's the time I spent in CT, but if we have to watch our better angels float out of reach, I'm glad they did it on a @Sikorsky bird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think President Joffrey is about to demand Hillary's head. #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, America. We'll get him out of there. And, 4 years from today, we'll get Pence out of there, too. #inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie it is. But dissent doesn't impede the transfer or the peace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with democracies is they don't always get the leaders they need, but they always get the leaders they deserve. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of supporters disguised as empty mall. #Inauguration #ShelteringInPlace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to Putin's Amerika. #Inauguration #ShelteringInPlace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a sucker for a good fife and drum corps. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going after grizzlies is just another attempt by #DeVos to infringe on our right to bear arms. #GetIt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How old I am now:

Wife: Why are you limping?
Me: The rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. The Rangers really #DeVossed that game last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump there will definitely be a lot of people there on Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps the best thing about Stranger Things is Matthew Modine's portrayal of Ted Danson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ? Dems have to ask re: 2020: who has best chance of beating incumbent President Mike Pence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump "That is the definition of a racist statement" -- Speaker Ryan referring to Trump's comments about Judge Curiel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The conscience of Congress. https://t.co/nGwHL3UQhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should being a Trump voter be considered a pre-existing condition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At work. It is 72 and sunny. In 2 days, when I could be on a trail, it will be 32 with freezing rain. Yay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost @zblay the fishbowl is the exact opposite of "literal"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC She really wanted one of those taco bowls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, it took 8 years, but America finally found its death panel. https://t.co/EIPrFHk4mc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump has already had more scandals as president-elect than Obama did in 8 years as @POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marco has his fightin' boots on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is why @realDonaldTrump's face is so orange those prostitutes should have their livers checked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok. He did it. He displaced Bartlett in my rankings. #FarewellSpeech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix @nycjim @BuzzFeed wish we could have had a debate about wikileaks' ethics several months ago, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews she was getting a lifetime achievement award. Not sure White knows what "uppity" means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanaHoule exactly. As soon as enough trump die-hards see the reason and won't punish them for it. They can hardly wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ego over country. guess we should get used to it. https://t.co/OlNylNrSpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, seriously... did you see what the DNC was wearing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what a Russian stooge looks like. https://t.co/pHRyuCVKQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be the first time I've rooted for Arnold @Schwarzenegger since Commando.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: no force in America does more to reduce the number of abortions than Planned Parenthood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump she came in 2nd on AI. Just like you did in the popular vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Seriously? a WICKED one-liner? Y'all must be huge Sinbad fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have the required lack of self-awareness to be a Republican politician. https://t.co/nvaMiAc4Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill 239-194 is near unanimous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this a jellyfish or did @SpeakerRyan misplace his spine again? https://t.co/znHJh9QIZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 is the worst! 🙄

Skier Jean Vuarnet, who struck gold with tuck position, dies (from @AP) https://t.co/WAaqrWm0xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your call is very important to us" is a lot harder to believe the 398th time you hear it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another "responsible gun owner" https://t.co/4QmfU7G4Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump, to clarify: "unprecedented" means without precedent; "unpresidented" is what the US is about to become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we have an Elec. Coll. If it doesn't stop a demagogue who colluded with antagonistic foreign regime we might as well abolish it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I haven't bought your Christmas gift yet you are probably getting a subscription to #VanityFair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinajacksn @HuffPostPol they misspelled "traitors" in the headline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't inaugurate Putin's stooge, @realDonaldTrump. Either we have a country or we don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats Army! It was a great game. It is a great tradition. And my hat is off to Navy for doing it, but 14 years was too long. #ArmyNavy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe machines do make better employees than humans. I've no doubt a coffeemaker would make a better Sec. of Labor than Puzder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think I've ever seen a Hardee's that wasn't at a turnpike rest stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a guy who claimed to be smarter than the generals, @realDonaldTrump is sure picking a lot of them for his cabinet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I wasn't following @OfficeGovEthics before today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matt_Forster this one still around?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is having twitter meltdown over recount. No obligation to treat him like a president when he refuses to act like one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy smokes! #WeAreBC and We Are Bowl Eligible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course it was a flight to Allentown. https://t.co/Dq2xzoO45V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The yearly onslaught of ludicrous cologne/perfume commercials already has me missing political ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quintoCT they still calling that a conference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: there never was anything to prosecute, but I sure played the deplorables like a fiddle. https://t.co/nlI7gPdZVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect:  Now is Not the Time to Criticize the Galaxy Note 7 - McSweeney’s Internet Tendency https://t.co/BIg5DaLBN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last hour in our national humiliation. @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/LRgDMk0uLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt @MSNBC @DorisKGoodwin saw the spot. Could be true, but based on assumption of Romney apptmnt. Actual picks so far are contrary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt you are the MSM. Part of it, at least. More than a little irresponsible to keep demonizing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump appoints an AG who couldn't get confirmed by the Senate 30 years ago because he was too racist by 1986 standards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only two words Obama could say to calm my fears are "squatter's rights"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know @maddow never wanted this--saw her heart break on live tv--but the next 4 yrs are gonna be huge for her. And she for us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix So, they're just a relations staff now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a perfect fit then https://t.co/Nm9Ooec4x8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>