<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @RawStory great write up of my latest piece about Fox News crediting @realDonaldTrump for Obamas #JobsReport… https://t.co/2MYGh4fJDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah Politico Jared Kushner's a hero to LGBT community, it was great that he pushed for Mike Pence to be VP. #fail https://t.co/y05JTdjYor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow a pac almost completely funded by one man - Christopher Egan - claiming to be morally superior. Love it --&gt;… https://t.co/xj00sH6Iwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That point on the Friday before the #SuperBowl were you start taunting all your co-workers who don't understand why… https://t.co/MxYzktk95V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live feed of news reports after Sean Spicer's latest press conference. #morewinning https://t.co/SH2nX4H9U0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox &amp; Friends uses Obama's last jobs report to declare Trump gets  #morewinning. Full story at @mmfa --&gt;… https://t.co/4l8BH1CgOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final #JobsReport that included President Obama's time in added 227,000. Not a bad send off Mr. President. Come bac… https://t.co/PQvslvJyFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieOGrady too true, but maybe it's just me but I don't recall her making such outright gaffes during the campaign like this or alt facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieOGrady thanks. It was the weirdest thing I've ever woken up to trending on twitter lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@positivelydruid no no the changes won't affect people currently 55+ they will still get Medicare as is at 65. Those under 55 out of luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PJ Media caught me and my forgetfulness to double check autocorrect changing Gorsuch.

Fun piece, loved it. 

https://t.co/Y7TfkqMJoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw a pro Trump ad by @AARP. Trump's guys in congress want to keep Medicare for those 55 n over but gut it for us. It's generational warfare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy on #morningjoe declares Trump is fine as long as he doesn't be Hitler. Glad to see the bar is set so high for America's president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACPhila_Old sadly you're likely right. But I think she is in for a rough ride. 2 gaufs in two weeks starts to add up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDejam Kellyann always tries to con her way out of everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the names of all those who lost their lives at the Bowling Green Massacre:

Kellyann Conway's career

Let us give thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJimSnell one comedian should not have to bear the weight of the entire republic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gotplatanos @Alter_me I'd say more of it had to do with an establishment that needs to retire &amp; a professional political class with no clue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dryanshea I do not know why my fellow progressives are anti-free trade. Trade has lifted a billion people out of poverty. Its a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionthroat worst part Milo feeds off this stuff. They are doing exactly what he wants. So you could say they are making a fascist happy lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With twitter abuzz about NAFTA &amp; #freetrade remember global trade has more 2 do with cheap shipping than trade deals https://t.co/mVM0Atu1nS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok lets do this. Donald legalize political churches. Then I'll start a religion with one tenant: Dump Trump. #resist https://t.co/puAmWD8Zyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chickylala so honestly screwing with free trade will do little for jobs, might raise prices and is unlikely to slow global trade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chickylala also economists note that the drop in cost of shipping also had more to stimulate trade than trade deals https://t.co/mVM0AtLCMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chickylala no problem I got it from Steve Chapman, but many economists also have noted it https://t.co/I14Bm2Gznf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So everyone knows since NAFTA went into effect U.S. manufacturing output has risen by 54%. Look to automation not free trade for job losses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GasparePartini1 @catduffy I know right? This is how our mornings start now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Steve King wants to strip away all supreme court precedents upholding #obamacare. See bill HR177 --&gt; https://t.co/YPyrAfdB9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually @realDonaldTrump freedom isn't a gift from god or government, it is something we the people must take for ourselves. #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait Donald Trump bashed the Celebrity Apprentice at the National Prayer Breakfast. WTF? https://t.co/k1yHlXLMSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBednarki14 it is a standard we must enforce. In DC 600,000 of us marched the day after Trump was inaugurated &amp; we did it without violence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gotplatanos Milo has been delightedly trying to get students to riot against him on campus and get him kicked off. UC Berkley fell for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBednarki14 all it takes is one bad actor to help Milo get national attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Berkley I don't like Milo but should you really smash windows over him visiting? https://t.co/QZ3AK0aI76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @realDonaldTrump is arguing on the phone with Australia. Makes total sense. #DumpTrump https://t.co/S8YK5CWuTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to crucify Neil Grouch's nomination as much as anyone but I think his high school Fascism Forever Club might have been an ironic joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump wants a federal #RightToWork. Great lets just gut worker rights completely. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mktownsend2 doesn't mean she deserves to win reelection lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susan Collins to vote no on Devos. Someone wants to win reelection after all. But Collins deserves defeat for supporting Trump on so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #PressOn subscription drive by The New York Times is only worth it if the Times is willing to do the work needed to get to the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon Stewart is clearly ready for a comeback and just in the nick of time. Go get'em! Full video here --&gt;… https://t.co/byVq2xOsoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great first video @gaywonk! Keep it up. https://t.co/ST8Oz82VSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The energy from the left to stop the #GorsuchNomination is amazing. We can make a difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow my second 1 million impressions month ever! Thanks everyone for likeing and retweeting my stuff who helped get… https://t.co/U3Yu4IpYsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnigmaTrain no one thought Trump would come out of nowhere. Honestly I think the next president will be someone no one has heard of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Mitch McConnell use the nuclear option to get #gorsuch on the court. Then Dems in four years can nominate a… https://t.co/OjBARnSDCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook I hate you https://t.co/9Fh9YBJ0QM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I get defeated I get to go home -- @Sen_JoeManchin. The way Congress is going that is a victory. Love that line Senator! #morningjoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a man of my word, I do what I say -- @realDonaldTrump on nominating Gorsuch.

I believe you Donald that's why I #resist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see Senate Democrats lining up to oppose Neil Gorsuch. We should thank Donald Trump for helping the Dems find their backbone #SCOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup and that's why its time the LGBTQ movement rid itself of big money groups. https://t.co/iQ1rzttopk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Supsupsup7 her parents are not even part of the 90k with visas affected. They are just two of the duel nationals affected. #themoreyouknow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resist those facts girl @Supsupsup7 like not being detained at the airport does not mean not affected

https://t.co/CdV1DhzG2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh @supsupsup7 that number is just people who have visas that could have been stranded cause order came without warning. Not people applying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah having autonomy issuing waivers doesn't mean actually having autonomy issuing waivers. Oh n yes 90,000 people… https://t.co/LQPvBHNcay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlurtVonnegut yeah but knowing Trump he will give Mexico a great deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah lets slap a big sweeping ban up and then let every ICE officer be a one man judge and jury. Makes sense.… https://t.co/nCz7eVhmos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexMorash ccing @paulkrugman and @econjared, thought you guys might get a kick out of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @CNN on hiring @StephenMoore the Worst Economist in the World. Via @Craigipedia https://t.co/tepXFayzpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love a good fact check - https://t.co/FjYzwyus6E https://t.co/iJh7avOtoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to stop him is to #resist. Refuse, resign, resist. Bannon and Trump can't run it all by themselves. https://t.co/gZLkT7Bf2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are my family, all my great grandparents were working class immigrants. https://t.co/0ifd8moeuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The light keeps dimming on all those just trying to be free. America is suppose to be the land of hope, not disdain. https://t.co/Y8sRtEa0o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Mar-a-lago? Great I'd like to make a reservation for 90,000 people for the immigrants affected by Trump's tra… https://t.co/nCJmXO5HDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We beat back -- for now -- @realDonaldTrump's exec order to hurt LGBTQ Americans. But we must prepare to fight agai… https://t.co/2mOPpZ9w0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok now they really do have a class on everything

https://t.co/aGfilhPqGO https://t.co/8xmNeSSmtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think Trump not issuing an anti- LGBTQ exec order means we are safe guess again. #resisttrumptuesday https://t.co/3BlxCfSTQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To say that it is amateur hour at the White House is to slander amateurs - David Brooks on @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/P0XYOMBPNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to crank out some writing today. #TuesdayMotivation https://t.co/Dttdogbijf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The LGBTQ community dodged a bullet -- for now. We will never be safe while @realDonaldTrump is president. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#morningjoe stop blaming 30 somethings — Trump is 70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe's got a look on his face of oh god I helped elect a dictator today after the #mondaynightmasacre. You gotta live with this #morningjoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump channeling Nixon's Saturday Night Massacre with his own Monday Night Massacre. 
https://t.co/ytP6co6Edp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump first came for immigrants, now he is coming for #LGBTQ/Queer workers. We will never be safe while… https://t.co/xNspGJCNyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer defends Muslim ban that federal lawyers said looked like "an intern came up with over a lunch hour."… https://t.co/vn718aq610]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama was a great president and he continues to be a great American.

https://t.co/13n1iCuz1X?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP to #BoycottStarbucks. Ok but all us latte drinkers are liberals. #Fail https://t.co/ylnxOuoZ2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me watching @seanspicer squirm on #morningjoe trying to explain away the chaos the Trump administration caused. https://t.co/zIM5PW6Jtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriceSnow boundaries https://t.co/gt3suBFYZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @CodyLinley for being my 30,000th follower &amp; to everyone else who keeps following me for some reason. You gu… https://t.co/vHQnfeGWqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While last night we had a victory over Trump's #MuslimBan we also saw a Mosque in Texas burned to the ground. #TheResistance has work to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice! Judge blocks parts of @realDonaldTrump's horrendous assault on Muslims. #TheResistance 1 Trump 0. https://t.co/ghfgIKJotg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada coming off better than the greatest nation in the world. You did this Trump voters! Hate does not make us gr… https://t.co/foaDVjVy3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists are shutting down JFK airport for illegally detaining legally entering immigrants. This is what… https://t.co/1KkWzgSc44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @LiquidDietMusic has the song that describes this last week and what the next four years look like. 

https://t.co/8PDu7DIW1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevhev79 @ItsDanAvery @jayrosen_nyu its a mix of her being somewhat clever and too many journalists being lazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #MarchForLife is held on anniversary of roe v wade to fight it. 

Someone told them that 70% of Americans support the ruling right? #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of reporting that worries me. #LGBTrights are in danger.
https://t.co/GYwjrqnvCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a #LGBT/Queer march on Washington, this might just be it! https://t.co/b1cmnxJT8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anti_orange1 @J_Truthiness I am saving it its such a great image. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence's words about respecting life ring hallow while he tries to deprive the poor of medicine. Pretty sure Jesus never advocated that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its going to just be one of those days. https://t.co/r4NzKykrUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's reign of fear for immigrants has begun. #resist 

https://t.co/8vxszc6Vpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidTweetsLies I and a lot of the other alumni are routing for you to succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you needed to be reminded why corporations are not your friend I give you Elizabeth Warren: https://t.co/SdWBqw8SZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCHomos has Capital Pride co-oped the march? Was hoping not to be inundated with a 4 hour infomercial for the banks https://t.co/YHT6KoXzOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see a @deltalambdaphi colony started at GWU. Good luck guys, its an amazing fraternity to join.
https://t.co/h9oNgEOlQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffBull5 this is one of those tweets where maybe your talking about me or Donald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Jackson was far from perfect but he ran the bankers out of DC, not invite them into his cabinet like someone… https://t.co/uJfB6rtqvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Jackson was flawed but at least he actually won the popular vote.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>