<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders real estate 'rebranding' as Ray White is all about getting exposure to buyers in China. Tell it like it is @DomPost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ weather this summer - the answer to our tourism problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a whale of a time with krill snacks. Match with Rosé. Not bad https://t.co/8Ldwhq9dCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind gust or earthquake? Anyone? #wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Camping breakfast all sorted. Thanks @bluefrogbrekky https://t.co/C42hCGffeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Wonderfully witty and wildly opinionated AA Gill. https://t.co/zJtU2SADPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks sooo edible. But I dare not. #champignonsNZ https://t.co/HhlWBkge0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the on again - off again Wellington summer my tomatoes are on their way. Go camparis, go! https://t.co/89gYxdPn8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArbourDining @kaikouracheese I love the crooked little smile on that goat #cameogoat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CurdNerd: Biddy has donated a truckle of Cwmglyn to auction - all proceeds going to ... https://t.co/3ywUWKh2Qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Daniel, Sarah, kids and goats @kaikouracheese  - so glad you're back in production.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silky light duck parfait with a glass of pinot @noblerotbar Wellington. And sun is shining! https://t.co/S8kU0fZs2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the virtual reality of #WellingtonAdventCalendar? Follow up with a full immersion experience @NZLifeLeisure Insider Guide, Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! Take a peek inside the Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar https://t.co/SzE5in1wJc via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good cause RT @CurdNerd: Your chance to show your Aroha to the family and team of @kaikouracheese  https://t.co/uqzHtQDwGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd I've just tried a terrific Gorgonzola dolce made in Nelson. Need more of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd I haven't visited @thedrunkennanny but I have partaken. The cheese is very very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ceviche and margaritas and a happy buzz @nicolascantina in Nelson  tonight. https://t.co/aZcLAeHAfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[black sesame ice cream on rose petal ice with creamed corn, grass jelly, red beans and condensed milk.  #papparich… https://t.co/sOtBUtubKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd call this a fail. #notagardener https://t.co/dvGWmj6Nfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blast from the past and still so good. #martinboroughwines https://t.co/5bXkJVTw90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd done! Great idea. I'm off to Wairarapa. Will stop in and see Paul at C'est Cheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top chefs bid to save cheese https://t.co/2Urd0TXHZ3 via @nzherald https://t.co/V7g4aDMQ0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mashing the grain for TJ family summer brew https://t.co/9H2KpLtwoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[more on the artisan cheesemakers’ plight from NZ Herald. Includes good video with Biddy. https://t.co/qJDvU7JMMD
#NZCheeseMonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mt Eliza Cheese story on Life &amp; Leisure website. https://t.co/3l9YjWiFmE
#nzcheesemonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting our cheesemakers at the Beehive today. Read my blogpost https://t.co/B98Z7YJw8P
#allwearesayingisgivenzcheeseachance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here they are... https://t.co/0PSzrBV4Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jill @mountelizachees and Biddy of Cwmglyn take their cheese and their fight to Parliament. Will they listen? ... https://t.co/Yp5hFDTNDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheesemakers @mountelizachees and Biddy feed the lawmakers at parliament #nzcheesemonth… https://t.co/BLJj4AVd6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The South Island from Makara. Clear as glass. Who says Wellington can't turn it on...when it wants to. https://t.co/xoyfPyN4x3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI well, of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delaneymes_ @SKYCITYAkl @Brooke_hs Forget the date, take the sake, Delaney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Less is more - except when we're talking butter. Thanks @lewisrdcreamery https://t.co/ajAm9o7Tls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, what shall I spread on my @lewisrdcreamery sourdough toast? #betterbutter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ontrays @CurdNerd Such a shame Ferndale stopped making raclette here. It was very good. I still have their grill. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tasting notes: strawberries and cream in a bottle. Big on nostalgia, a bit too sweet for grownups. @lewisrdcreamery https://t.co/e9CkgThqTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We missed out on Jamie’s Italian but newly opened franchise, #PappaRichnz  is a welcome addition to Wellington’s Malaysian eateries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd What’s this with the cheddar?? I’m coming late to this conversation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd @stevetnz Snap. I have one of these raclette grills too. Ferndale's NZ raclette was fabulous but no longer available.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iced mango,fresh lychees, watermelon balls and jelly cubes. One of many wonderful a.... https://t.co/svJnMKe6bg https://t.co/Iy1CKoXRZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tasty bowl of Chilli Pan Mee at #paparichnz - new Malaysian restaurant in Wellington. Standing room only. https://t.co/pVQZs6tHqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating live octopus for kicks on TV One is a real turn off. They are intelligent creatures - the octopus I mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the story behind Mt Eliza raw milk cheese in the current issue of NZ Life &amp; Leisure. Printed edition. #nzcheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to picking up some brined pork off the beach in Wellington, courtesy of @BluebridgeFerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting down with a good book - Visa WOAP programme. Yum! #wellyonaplate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your blue good with anything RT @mountelizachees: @NZeats good with blue cheese stuffed apples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone out there making a particularly good mead or calvados?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would like to know how much sugar is in the healthy raw snickers cake in @DomPost   Caramel and choc mousse implies quite a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robot_ranger All power to Robyn Toomath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robot_ranger yes, I don't understand that. TPP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax I agree with that. Soft drinks should be a lot more expensive than milk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax it would be easier to avoid sugar if the cost was a factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax a bit like climate change- I don't think we have the luxury of time to keep stalling. There's enough evidence to start on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax and why do you think a sugar tax won't work when a tobacco tax certainly has - in NZ at any rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax so what's your solution?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax but you are UK based, I doubt soft drink sales are falling in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgainstSugarTax is this the industry speaking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot believe J Coleman MP is a trained doctor and can't see the need for a sugar tax #Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @cuisine magazine The best issue in a very long time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyWi18628806 @bustedblonde It’s still staring at me reproachfully but I can’t afford to get sick right now so I’ll leave it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know what this is? Looks like a shaggy parasol but I'm a bit scared to eat it https://t.co/t3fYgKFZFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, it's 4 men versus 1 swordfish who fights for an hour before being hauled out of Cook Strait as a trophy. #sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuslush Brown eggs: a conspiracy of hens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Orange wine tasting in Welly today @WhitebaitWlgtn  - opening new horizons. Thank you @Camdouglasms https://t.co/0Cy979TZve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cooks on ‘good’ food they hate – and ‘bad’ food they love https://t.co/tXjd3hXLkb
I think: tetra pack custard is better than the real stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensational destination dining experience @bistronomyHB in Napier. Lucky Hawkes Bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goût de France. #GoutdeFrance NZ launched in Wellington this week. Read on and salivate..passthesalt.co.nz/2016/03/23/gou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goût de France. NZ launch in Wellington this week. Read on and salivate..https://t.co/p1StReuS5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming Sad his passing but what a great life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell to Pierre Meyer, a great chef, a good man and a Wellington treasure. At  https://t.co/sAQLwCb00p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodWritersNZ: You are what you eat, so don't be fast, cheap, easy or fake.
~ Anon .. Unless you like tarts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a chicken meat substitute from peas? The only winners here are the chickens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re soft drink tax story on @sevensharp - It's not just the tax, it's the message. Good call UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK sugar tax on soft drinks such a good thing. Why does NZ think it's too hard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red IPA from @HopFederation is absolutely lusciously gorgeous - calling out for smoky pork ribs, but sadly only salad for dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying from Hamilton to Wellington with pitchfork, as you do. @airnewzealand helpfully searching for bubble wrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frightening RT @MartinBosleys: Glorious. https://t.co/d3n3TXcBoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could @DamienOConnerMP not know about @kaikouracheese ? Defies belief. #getlocal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mountelizachees @CurdNerd @whitestonecheez One or two new ones (for me) to try. Puhoi has done well and nice ... https://t.co/7LKUXI4qPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mountelizachees @CurdNerd @whitestonecheez Got it. Hard to link on iPhone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mountelizachees @CurdNerd @whitestonecheez Not the whole list. Unless I'm missing something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog abduction trumps person abduction on Stuff website. Why am I surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd @whitestonecheez I'm wondering where I can find a list of winners. Not on the cheesemakers site yet ??? #nzcheeseawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous Gouda! RT @mmmcheeseplease: #nzcheeseawards champion artisan cheese: Mercer extra mature gouda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved. RT @mmmcheeseplease: #nzcheeseawards champion new cheese matariki Wangapeka dairy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glorious lamb tagine @CasitaMiro on Waiheke. Great food, great service. #memorablemeals https://t.co/2obPSrxTYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous new cheese for me - cows milk. Tastes fruity, herby, umami salami. Real name- Wangapeka Matariki https://t.co/w8HuztMBK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCityMarket in Wellington closing? What the ...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mountelizachees emailed you about your cheese today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd Nope. But all very interesting stuff. Nothing cheesy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's the product https://t.co/K8Rb0q57qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot the difference...having closely read the ingredients these are the same product. #gofigure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fame! RT @southstarbrew: @NZeats @CurdNerd @GGeckoCheese you would be the envy of the nations food writers, ... https://t.co/Y8cQmtFWRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southstarbrew @CurdNerd @GGeckoCheese and get thrown off public transport!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any foodie suggestions in Newmarket? Am roaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurdNerd @GGeckoCheese Excellent cheese from the gecko. Sadly too stinky to buy and sit in my handbag on this 26 degree day in Auckland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. Down and dirty, in a good way. RT @CurdNerd: Kau Piro from @GGeckoCheese - my kinda stinky cow. https://t.co/U0gD9UWnIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Italian Job. On the menu at La Pancetta Greytown. Lovingly cured by @ProdigaDaughter https://t.co/lrIgVNjYNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eek! 24 items on my To Do list. #holidayover]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>