<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "Certain Countries" very vague, no facts. Are you suggesting here that we are not capable of protecting ourselves? WRONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just to be clear, the COUNTRY did just say who can come and go. We just disagree with you! Not up to you alone ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "So-called Judge"???  What the he'll is wrong with you??  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great! So you're leaving??  Can I help carry a bag?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @realDonaldTrump @mike_pence @PressSec @KellyannePolls SHAME ON ALL OF YOU! America wins!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RollingStone @Nickslive GREATEST BAND EVER!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump An ILLEGITIMATE destructionist has taken over the government  GET SMART U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattmfm SHAME ON YOU DJT!  ILLEGITIMATE  @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farai @donnabrazile @voxdotcom @KellyannePolls Kellyanne, how do you face yourself and your children? History has already judged you poorly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper @washingtonpost Thank you Senator Carper! Standing up for public schools is so important!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lets be clear We all know Breitbart is paying for the chaos and you are Breitbart  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerconish This and starting a war with Iran starts his Friday.  Disgusting ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well at least he tried, You're just doing a really bad job...PERIOD!  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey Iran! Please know this idiot is ILLEGITIMATE  Shut the F up Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd I wonder if today "Revolutionary" has a meaner, darker definition, and "Tory" means standing up for those 240 year old ideals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Empty threats BULLY. ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump THIS coming from a guy who cheated out of serving the country. Don't you cringe every time you face military personnel? BAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Millions protest against you. 3MM more people voted for Hillary. Millions more people at Obama Inauguration ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnKennedy @wolfblitzer  Two problems here. 1 @PressSec said it's not a ban yet Repubs keep saying it SILLY 2 Argument is Cowardice SAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper Thank you, Senator  I am with you on this decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iankoski OK thanks Ian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper Thank you for your NO vote on Tillerson. Very grateful for your stand against this nominee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons Why are you in the "Not voting" column for Tillerson? I thought you were a NO vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJ_PsychGuy @SenatorCollins @lisamurkowski Echoing that same gratitude. Thank you both for your NO vote on Betsy DeVos. So grateful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actually it's about discrimination and stepping on America's ideals because you and your friends are cowards. ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban @Bakari_Sellers Mark Cuban, you're fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yottapoint @charles_gaba Amazing is the exactly correct word to use here! @jeffsessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons @JohnCarneyDE Very Proud of DE, always!!  Thank you gentlemen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realJeffreyLord Blindly adhering to the party line ruins your credibility.  I know you're smarter. Prove me right! @CNN @andersoncooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaleJr @GelarBudidarma Thank you Mr. Earnhardt. Integrity matters. Character matters.  You display both with this message]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @BarackObama THANK YOU for this statement Mr President.  All former Presidents shld unite against this threat! @VanJones68 @jaketapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons @NewDay @CNN Thank you Senator Coons! You make DE proud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomLlamasABC @ABC @jonkarl @CeciliaVega The three of you are courageous and authentic.  Congratulations, we need you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper We're with you Senator Carper!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 I am speechless  So frightening! Sharing everywhere!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump In your own words BAN! You lie so easily, but America rejects you by the millions  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why do you insist on dividing? Your strategy is failing. ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidKHarbour I spent the afternoon protesting at PHL airport &amp; came home to see your beautiful speech. Thank you for those gorgeous words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sagesteele Hey, your privilege is showing!  It's ugly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjholmes @KellyannePolls @GMA She is focused on spreading misinformation and avoiding intelligent conversation  HORRIBLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wrong!  Liar! ILLEGITIMATE on so many levels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GStephanopoulos @ThisWeekABC @GMA Why do you give @KellyannePolls on your network? She Refuses to answer questions, spreads misinformation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkWJohnson  Sir, you have my sincere respect for your heroic service to this country both overseas and on Twitter :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why is a man of no faith so concerned with Christians? Try having concern for ANYONE in the path of violence  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wrong! Lindsay Graham and John McCain have integrity.  I know, that's a word you have no familiarity with  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DE Congresspeople here to support American core values in Philadelphia! @matthewjdowd @jaketapper @VanJones68… https://t.co/YyBQfWqp4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphia is out and loud. Standing up for the documents created here 250 years ago! @CNN @matthewjdowd… https://t.co/mVIKciK6yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WerdyGirl @JohnCarneyDE @LisaBRochester @ChrisCoons @SenatorCarper So great to see DE represented so thoroughly!!  See you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper @PHLAirport @RepBRochester We're on our way there too!!  Thank you for your support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @Bakari_Sellers @ananavarro Your roundtable today were all intelligent voices of character and integrity, except Jan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Good riddance One voice of hate silenced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only been a week, understanding the traditional protocol, but America needs a joint statement today from former Presidents! @jaketapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are now a religious extremist. You refuse to learn hard lessons from the past. I will fight you at every step SHAME!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_pence Hypocrisy in its highest form. No character No credibility LIAR! https://t.co/9Jp1JCRMXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do former Presidents speak up WAY out of normal boundaries of protocol. @BarackObama @billclinton @43georgebush @JimmyCarter39th @CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons Thank you Senator Coons!!  I am with YOU!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper @nytimes Thank you Senator Carper!  I am with YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Jake, you are doing a great job to insist on facts and expose these dangerous people and their horrifying agenda.  Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto I don't recognize our country anymore.  Horrifying day in US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany You sold your soul to this horror.  You have no  credibility  Shame!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@netanyahu @jaketapper Hey Ben, you're not the role model anyone should look to. Wall or no wall, Israel remains in deep conflict.Bad idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons @TomCarperforDE @LisaBRochester Is this how things work?  Can you guys do this?  If so, please do. DE s… https://t.co/gqxC1yEjGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump In just 7 days you ruined 250 years of American strength and integrity! So deeply shameful! @KellyannePolls @mike_pence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd Building walls&amp; closing doors tells the world we're scared and have no confidence in our ability to protect ourselves. SAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto Thank you, Jim, for your response to this hateful person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper Please keep fighting Senator Carper! I am deeply troubled by the actions taken this week by our President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes COWARD. ILLEGITIMATE  You are a dark stain on American history and it's only been a week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes @washingtonpost You are nothing more than a Coward and a hate monger  ILLEGITIMATE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDiamond1 @POTUS Horrified!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You say you want to be a President for everyone, but where was your support for the MILLIONS marching last week?  SHAME!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @DailyNewsBin @realDonaldTrump You have shamed us in a significant way DJT!  FRAUD  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Outright lies! Alternative Facts! ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great first week Diplomacy trashed! Credibility shot! Overreach with executive orders! Disrespect toward Civil Rights MAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons Just think of the celebration 4 years from now when, whatever gets built, gets torn down! @TomCarperforDE @LisaBRochester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN @jaketapper Whoa!  Way out of line!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd Hypocrisy is rampant now. The country seems unrecognizable to me...and that's not because I've lived in a bubble in the East]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Which American people? Straight, White, Christian, men? Your actions are in direct conflict with this tweet. All talk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCarper @EPWDems Keep on them Senator! We are with you here in DE  Country seems unrecognizable, but our DE Congresspeople will help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gives me such joy!! @CNN @ABC @NBCNews @CBSNews @matthewjdowd @jaketapper @DavidMuir @chucktodd @jimsciutto… https://t.co/zdguSDDCLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoons Thank you, Senator Coons!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Don't worry, 2020 is coming. You'll finally have your historic election #s. The greatest rejection of a sitting president!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec Spicer, you should be so ashamed No credibility No integrity Dishonest Unpatriotic @matthewjdowd @VanJones68 @jaketapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Was it hard to hear all those guys thank President Obama for saving them? @BarackObama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs @PressSec Yesterday you said you wouldn't lie and now today you're backing up your boss's lies. NO CREDIBILITY @jonkarl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffzeleny @CNN Very cool!  Thanks for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan More lies from more Republicans Shame on you Mr Speaker!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @washingtonpost @realDonaldTrump is a massive liar and everyone must be vigilant to call this out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerconish Disappointed that you would ask for such a stupid vote when there are so many other important things to discuss. Do better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd @DJ_PsychGuy And Hillary was criticized for using the word "Deplorable".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmariepipes I will ALWAYS be with HER!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why were there no questions about this??  Seems so obvious! Disappointed! @jonkarl @VanJones68 @jaketapper… https://t.co/nNrM4PDXv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattmfm Why is that?  Seemed like an obvious question especially today??  Disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "Alternative Facts?"  ILLEGITIMATE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec Oh nice, you want a "do over" LOL Another "alternative fact"?? Truth is you blew the FIRST one. Credibility gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so painful to watch! @chucktodd you are a hero!  @KellyannePolls you are an abomination. Horrifying https://t.co/8bxWFcdP2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer Disgraceful Dangerous Disastrous Reprehensible behavior! @CNN @ABC @NBCNews @CBSNews https://t.co/A3jDwVwb1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer Out of line! Unprofessional! SAD! @CNN @ABC @NBCNews @CBSNews https://t.co/BOYJwxZtD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto Great tweet!!!  Great point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @jaketapper So is this how it's going to be now? DJT tweets his real thoughts and then someone else tweets the script?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton WE LOVE YOU HILLARY https://t.co/NYiqw7hKUq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>