<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AhmedDHussen will C-6 ever be passed? Stuck in obscure senate committee that rarely meets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allenlangdon this is causing bags to be stolen I pay a fee for the bottles you collect, should pay for the bags too. #bringbackCityrecycle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Youth Group That Launched a Movement at Standing Rock https://t.co/rug0E3lSNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllenLangdon then the producers can pay for bags. This is a profit margin grab by #smithrite-the city did not do. We should not pay them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap… it’s a purge https://t.co/SYAWnX48SH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stand with Sally Q. Yates More guts than so many lawmakers #nobannowallonstolenland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 #recycling bags stolen. #Vancouver supplied as many as  needed New #MMBC Contract #smithrite says 1 only or pay #knowwhystolen #taxdollars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada we are not blameless; we are not a beacon. https://t.co/JWbAqi8Aap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end, his mother was not deported…held for more than 33 hours, handcuffed for some of it &amp; denied a wheelchair https://t.co/hIQSXDuT8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jurists in the US will hold democracy in their hands and fascism at bay. Here’s to Judge Ann M. Donnelly &amp; other judges who ruled to protect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Trudeau’s Canada. Metis land defenders block Trudeau-approved fracked gas pipeline  to defend water. https://t.co/Gx90DfB4U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Canada: Metis land defenders block construction of Trudeau-approved fracked gas pipeline https://t.co/Gx90DfB4U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau  When will immigration C-6 be passed to get rid of its anti-immigrant immigration policy Bill referred to obscure Senate comm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran to ban US citizens in response to Trump's immigration order @CNN https://t.co/B1IQlE3GEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today as I, a US Citizen &amp; CDN permanent red, work with a @rainbowrefugee Circle to bring a LGBT refugee to Canada, I yell #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year ago.    https://t.co/vvt97ai1K1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White house principal deputy press secretary, Sarah Huckabee Sanders,  is Mike Huckabee’s daughter. Is this nepotism? #illscratchyours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is cleaning out high level bureaucrats US Border Patrol chief ousted after Trump revealed wall plans https://t.co/W77udqbq53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump protest cover of Rufas Wainwright’s Going to town by Lily Allen https://t.co/mqBooFF0Td]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It begins. Hear that Homeland Security is trolling US College campuses too. U.S. Deports 90 Somalis https://t.co/1mhrenbBFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom of the press is threatened. Trump’s Chief Strategist Says News Media Should ‘Keep Its Mouth Shut’ https://t.co/O9TA8Q3yru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that man delusional or diabolical?  Trump just gave a remarkable new interview. Here's a tally of all his lies. https://t.co/Pg8hoHxnpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research on midcareer professors makes case for support after tenure https://t.co/wTrVq9K6Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to protect freedom of press or the press will not be free Felony Charges for Journalists Arrested at Protests https://t.co/Q1L7eKkU4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstory on the image still uncomfortable... Munira Ahmed: the woman who became the face of the Trump resistance https://t.co/gW9nOgC4sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is The White House Trying To Tell People With Disabilities? https://t.co/pVnGWHHn0T via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Won’t Back Down From His Voting Fraud Lie. Here Are the Facts. https://t.co/jZuSukgnZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damnit! President Self interest Trump takes executive action to approve Keystone XL, Dakota Access pipelines https://t.co/3Id9yRFj15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12/5/16 Trump sells his stake in #DAPL 12/31/16 Perry (Energy sec) resigns two DAPL energy boards 01/23/17 Trump will push through DAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians watch candidate Kevin O'Leary and stop him in his tracks unless we want our very own you know who. #notmyPM #notmyPrez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer: ““Sometimes we can disagree with the facts.” Wait. What? #alternativefactsarelies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wider Racial Gap Found in Cervical Cancer Deaths https://t.co/uNVUkongYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#alternativefacts are #lies. #Nogaslighting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That man’s media attacks today are to draw attention from the women’s march. #CNN #MSNBC don’t allow it. Ignore the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That man says  “an education system flush with cash, … “Show me a public school flushed w/ cash, where teachers don’t pay for supplies #lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump White House takes down website pages about disabilities https://t.co/qyLBsvWQlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What My Great-Grandfather Taught Me About Trump and the Press https://t.co/AJI64x38AT via @longreads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family calls for inquest after Saskatoon woman's death https://t.co/SsKaFVVE34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This should be called the dumb and dumber administration. #thatman @chettahhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A disturbing look at how charter schools are hurting a traditional school district https://t.co/23WzDOUHtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Secret to Surviving the White House Years: Books https://t.co/PSX8ZTu7Ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Canadians among 5 dead after Mexican nightclub shooting https://t.co/AHuagVS1hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyAl4sop An analogy is x is like Y, a metaphor a thing regarded as representative or symbolic of something else. #grammar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlanta mayor to Trump: 'John Lewis an American hero' https://t.co/AwmCRRGqCk via @wsbtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it comes..MO Lawmaker Who Wants to Eliminate Tenure Says It’s ‘Un-American’ - The Chronicle of Higher Education https://t.co/KIOz1Xg9Oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What August Wilson Means Now https://t.co/rCjFjJVd1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions: "I'm not sure that women or people with different sexual orientations face that kind of discrimination." #postwhat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A year of loss, fear, and hope in a Chicago school” by @GregoryMichie https://t.co/tBa1s9mxpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealTrump2016 Its wrong to exclude Charlie Brotman. #justwrong #probablyhislast #haveaheart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only folks with privilege to think that the experience of all women are the same as white women are white women https://t.co/DEhkEqgXVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vancouver cracking down on homes &amp; businesses that don’t clear ice, will they fine themselves &amp;  other gov’t? #worstoffenders #glasshouses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I will crown Trump the king of the runaway adjective. #terrible #wonderful #notawaywithwords]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Prisoner https://t.co/X4cqpTceF0 via @texasmonthly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver's street clearing plan too late for disability advocates - NEWS 1130 https://t.co/pcv5hPHYQB via @NEWS1130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raulpacheco thanks sorry if i missed it cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raulpacheco are you willing to share the excellent electronic version of the 4 sentence rhetorical precis?  very helpful to my MA students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 year old missing Commercial and Hastings. https://t.co/lhay5IWQxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their Country, Our Land: Why Indigenous peoples have a problem with #Canada150 https://t.co/dXUkTS8XJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy dismantling before our very eyes. Is anyone in the US watching or acting. https://t.co/PSsgQIeLLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Assessments went up 36% and on top of it lose our homeowners. House now not worth assessment #christyclarke #fail #nothingforhomeowners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't stand to be in the world without her girl, but damn 2016 Debbie Reynolds Ingénue in 1950s Films, Dies at 84 https://t.co/HR7IpzBhd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tenure protects Academic freedom. Oh its WI right. A lawmaker calls "The problems with whiteness ' course garbage.' https://t.co/zsBS7TVzEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell of a dance party and debate going on in the hereafter right about now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women of color in the Academy - Staying Fit: Mind, Body and Soul   Professional development at Stanford. https://t.co/LXuavbkePL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transition Team’s Request on Gender Equality Rattles State Dept. https://t.co/cQiarPQAff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daphne Bramham: Patients with chronic pain are collateral damage in opioid epidemic https://t.co/guqwYyA05x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance Policies on Slaves: New York Life’s Complicated Past https://t.co/YNsqpyM0K8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leak reveals Rex Tillerson was director of Bahamas-based US-Russian oil firm https://t.co/9TfCQoCHO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SI_PeterKing Most excellent was hoping so. Thanks for paying attention up here in the North. Have beers to suggest if you make it this far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandersen87 @si_peterking @vancouversun He “retired”. Not sure if it was a desire or a push out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SI_PeterKing Cam Cole’s last sports column. Thought you would like to see. A Vancouver institution. Our loss. https://t.co/5NFgpvlJxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cam Cole’s last sports column, he says “Also, Twitter trolls. Sports was never meant to be this angry.” Indeed, sports and life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder and Worry, as a Syrian Child Transforms https://t.co/hDQQA5HBoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So BC &amp; Vancouver you will raise my medical as a couple, raise my house assessment 30-50%, add more for the opioid crisis #fillingcoffers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop calling the Syrian conflict a ‘civil war.’ It's not. https://t.co/aqdxSv9KIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Native Youth Association to hold gathering about safe spaces for queer youth https://t.co/tiliVvxLMe via @georgiastraight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children trapped in building under attack in Aleppo, doctor tells UN https://t.co/n0DA18jfov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're horrified by events in Aleppo, here's 6 charities that can help Syrian people https://t.co/LALogIxJ0v via @HuffPostUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘A Complete Meltdown of Humanity’: Aleppo Civilians Gunned Down as They Flee https://t.co/DuuOKGC3wW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So getting Wall Street out of Washington? Rex Tillerson as Secretary of State, not so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez, we Vancouverites make a big deal over a few cm of snow. The biggest problem is the inexperienced drivers, not the snow. #ilivedinWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frightening.  So many frightening things. https://t.co/XIJdqvl1KI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Viewing Boys Don’t Cry in 2016 and the culture of calling out. Jack Halberstam https://t.co/URtLHPvf7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beloved Horse Blanket Donated To Standing Rock - The Emotional Note Will Move You To Tears - https://t.co/0Ax5P3MCPy via @Shareaholic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Why is there a trainee driver on a 14 bus on today of all days?  Trainer showing him the gears. @OhLord #busesareascaryplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink At this time from UBC to Dundas and nanaimo area ok to take the 14 or better to take the 99 and hope I can get home from Broadway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showing’ everybody up again, as she does. Congratulations!@gjladson elected president of NAE https://t.co/4PvPJ46evb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UBC Might have been good to just cancel today.Getting to campus was truly dangerous. #notworthit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the folks boycotting and yelling about Santa being white, you all know he is not real,  right? #christophercringle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing Rock Sioux Tribe’s Statement on U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Decision to Not  Grant Easement: https://t.co/U6VB7LjJrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Officials to Explore Different Route for Dakota Pipeline https://t.co/mkZyz5K9xX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last #566 class with #UBC West Kootneys MEd cohort Watching them present thoughtful, thought provoking final projects was a privilege. #BCED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uglier times afoot So, so, much work to do. And I mean those in more dominant positions, especially settler white folk, &amp; cis and het folk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chimamanda Negozi Adichie on the election: Now Is the Time to Talk About What We Are Actually Talking About https://t.co/5AkIVv2bPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth About Young Immigrants and DACA https://t.co/TCgtW2WDTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Asians, no blacks. Why do gay people tolerate such blatant racism? | Owen Jones https://t.co/L108bdNFre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power Imbalance at the Pipeline Protest https://t.co/ri0BUToqDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This news just in billionaires with no public service experience now run US government…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: no obligation to establish boundaries between his business empire and his White House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Why isn’t there an article about police actions at Standing Rock last night? Unarmed civilians &amp; water cannons in freezing weather?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>