<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Kickstart books about Borders and Democracy by CrimethInc.  https://t.co/c9m3efea9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must-read thread https://t.co/8ZHiD3aNVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalesAnarchists Do you guys have meetings at all? Fairly new to Cardiff and I really want to meet comrades and organise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 times 20 times Plymouth Argyle, 20 times 20 times I say, 20 times 20 times Plymouth Argyle, playing football the Pilgrim way! #LIVARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess he also has a PKK  flag hung up too, right? And a football shirt of the Turkish national team?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silent Witness' terrorist character has an ISIS-like flag in his house, and several red anarchist circled As. Set designers, I don't even...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hug your friends and throw a heavy molotov (not necessarily in that order) https://t.co/p8oRi5SzdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No better time than Xmas to dive into this famous… https://t.co/QRSF7pEwd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To his credit, at least Fellaini is 'consistently' good at getting yellow cards and just generally being a terrible footballer. #EVEMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Queensferry https://t.co/5kBv2vpn2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least D.C. Antifa managed to do something in response to the NP, nice work comrades. https://t.co/DfVLM57akD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegan birthday cake made by Mum n Dad! Nommy nom nom @ Cathays, Cardiff, United Kingdom https://t.co/pXa7l1hX9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*standing ovation* https://t.co/S6srSu7izY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nah, come on, SOMEONE has to help out Daesh. Might as well be us." https://t.co/C0ylcFT2fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, 20, steady on, May https://t.co/wAu9Y5WWJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[livestream of Hector Bizerk's finale https://t.co/Ilugpzzcni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait until I'm dead, then I won't need a job! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the best to #YPG #YPJ #SDF who are sticking it to Daesh right now in #Manbij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alex Jones "attacked"! You sell it about as well as Cristiano Ronaldo! https://t.co/SqnJy2o4Cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumbling prick Alex Jones, never fails to make people laugh https://t.co/AtGK79haqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeFairweather watcha doing now, Joesheshpf?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterNorthDevon @TheresaMay2016 good at colouring in, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing that Leadsom, who has claimed £149 THOUSAND in expenses, has the gall to call anyone/anything else "vermin." #keeptheban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new video has emerged that destroys any argument by the cop defenders. Straight up murder, again. #AltonSterling #RestInPower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn state your name cuz "stormzy innit", what are we doing today? "governin' innit"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solidarity with the folks in Raqqa who are feeling the brunt of Daesh's anger over major defeats. Some brutal images coming out of that city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drew_christ @thisispolica @BBC6Music Which song?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anarres has its problems, but I'd give both my legs to live there: https://t.co/kHyxX7sjZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson = Trump with a thesaurus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn Laughing at Cameron, until you remember Boris...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[vanguardists and intellectuals. To be 'political' has to mean to ORGANISE at GROUND LEVEL. We need to fight the rise of nationalism. (2of2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick thoughts: leftism needs to bail on parliamentary politics. Its propaganda needs to come from the working classes, not from the (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like the Welsh don't know or care about how much funding they receive from the EU... It's not coming from anywhere else, folks #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jem_Collins Hartley-Brewer just went #AllLivesMatter level of ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[evacuations from Old Trafford due to a suspect package, thought to contain LVG's contract for next season. No wonder fans are scared!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Follows, The Babadook and now The Witch - suspense horror is thriving right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BruceTollafield my mistake, it's a polo tournament ... of course it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[khaki trousers and navy jackets; suits, hipster shades and tight golden dresses with $$$ purses - St Andrews #StGeorgesDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jem_Collins "discussions" and "twitter" - never a good pair of words in a sentence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[even though he'll only be replaced by some other douche and nothing whatsoever would change, still, #ResignDavidCameron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NKT3hsZHUU Good old 'libertarian' capitalists.. this guy has 320K subs. Mother of God..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still waiting for my pre-ordered Polica album which was released on the 4th March...  -_- @AwesomeDistro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz Woohoo the magnificent bastard! Okay, question: Which game universe/world would you most like to live in and why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you couldn't make this shit up https://t.co/UjYXYjsTKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz oh we all love you, Laura! I hope the low feels fuck off very soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took Glasgow about 2/3s of the set to wake up and realise they were watching @savagesband but… https://t.co/LC0lptKIGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasgow, if you don't want to cook, get out of the kitchen. Head-nodding to Hit Me is sacrilege. @Savagesband and Bo Ningen were awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 if you're too knackered to do Barca stuff later, let me know and we can do it on friday instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn I think in cases like these the students who think that this type of no-platforming is stupid should counter-demonstrate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz if you were only allowed to play the games of one publisher, who would it be and how many games would you put in your buttholes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn the whole no-platform thing is getting out of hand They need to talk to antifa; you no-platform Nazis, not gay-rights advocates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn inconsiderate prick. Now I'm late for the 4pm £1 pasty deal from Warrens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere between Stirling and nowhere https://t.co/bJW0LjxEaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was ok, I guess https://t.co/P9QcozXK6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I buried my heart in a hole in the ground" @ SSE Hydro Arena, Glasgow https://t.co/VZyZHJIf51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firewatch is a good videogame. You should play Firewatch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhoWillSpeakForEngland https://t.co/0AyafqYGKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz WOOHOO! Does this mean you'll critique your own videogame butt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz *furiously refreshing twitter*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeFairweather really sorry bro, much love &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 I haven't actually listened to any of them yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz I was going to make a really horrid joke and then I remembered J. Clarkson made a similar one and I vommed a little in my mouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioWonk @Shelia1965A @rickygervais There's a fundamental difference: empiricism = fine. Claiming objective truth= arrogant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioWonk @Shelia1965A @rickygervais I don't think badly of empiricism, I just don't think it should be so arrogant as to demand objectivity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shelia1965A @jamenta @rickygervais I think you're reading my tweets as though I'm shouting at him; I'm not. It's just a discussion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shelia1965A @jamenta @thek00laidman @rickygervais So you're only allowed to respond to someone's public discourse if you agree? Silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shelia1965A @thek00laidman @jamenta @rickygervais he's having a public discussion on twitter; we're allowed to disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioWonk @Shelia1965A @jamenta @rickygervais I'm merely saying that demanding that there is objective 'truth' is a 'belief' in empiricism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioWonk @Shelia1965A @jamenta @rickygervais I'm not religious/spiritual, so I don't have a hidden agenda to disgree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickygervais @daNASCARoracle @ProSonicInc sorry Ricky, but 'THE truth' doesn't exist. Neither do concrete, absolute 'facts'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamenta @rickygervais HAIL EMPIRICAL EVIDENCE! Hail the one true method for finding the one single truth! Scientism is a stain on science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting to see many liberal centre right tweeters annoyed at #antifa for facing down people shouting 'sieg heil' and 'niggers go home']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz I already own the game, so you should give it to me out of spite for all those who do not yet own it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well done to all #antifa opposing British Nazis today in #Dover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz I got it working, thanks anyway. Well done, it's a damn compelling game, all the feels *internet hug*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz blahdy sjw tumblr feminazi try'na take away me freedom of speetch wot abawt my opninions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurakBuzz hello, odd question, I'm having problems launching Acceptance on my PC (somehow) , is there anyone I can email about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 that film was effing terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 should've banned Critters 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 what? I'm struggling to remember how it was controversial? A little bit of bullying and sexual aggression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 I'll need to give it another watch. I remember enjoying it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 I can't remember much, but it was low budget, set in a cafe, a bunch of teenagers smoking and drinking coffee being smartasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GMF that you're ever gonna meet @ Glasgow Royal Concert Hall https://t.co/qOWFQnNRAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the Denver-D killing it tonight, I still want Manning to go out with a superbowl victory. Great rivalry, gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 yeah I saw this the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Clarkson: clueless *insert expletive*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 it's quite a lot to ask them to make an album comparable to that one, though. Truely one of my favourite albums ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewNoel73 yeah .......... it was ok. Just ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the new Daughter album is gorgeous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow I got featured in an ambient/drone compilation by Soft [free digital download] https://t.co/F3s1YG9mgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how much does Oculus rift cost? https://t.co/2GMnqYKkOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doritos, dip, alcohol, darkness, alone = time to play Outlast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn so won't the real Donald Trump please stand up? Please stand up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredBobJohn Cuz I'm Donald Trump, yes I'm the real Trump, all you other Donald Trumps smell like dump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is Strange is a damn fine game, a narrative which nicely blended cheesiness with really compelling moments. Mad crush on Chloe as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Succeeded at @ThisWarOfMine with 4 content, full-bellied folks laying down some horrific revenge for the murder of Marko back in day 14 #GG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we have no excuse  https://t.co/cx5HwtLhdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage because academics can't possibly have an opinion contrary to yours; they MUST be crab-people or aliens or something. Muslims?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please donate a couple of £ for Mike's funeral. Mentally ill, armed with a bb gun murdered by police https://t.co/ZVGudvXx7q via @gofundme]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>