<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner @SenatorCollins @lisamurkowski disappointed you voted for Tillerson. Need to go get another vote against for DeVos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSerwer is that Rasputin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP @washingtonpost Jill Stein in that photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbernstein there were stories out there that Kushner was unhappy with some things. I can't imagine he's as bent on destruction as others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner it's not astonishing. Decorum/rules gone (for now) &amp; has been trending that way for 6 yrs. expect worst &amp; fight w/ what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pstarf @nytpolitics so google it if you don't know and learn. Not sure Trump even did that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SanhoTree @seanspicer @jaketapper cred already shot with those who care abt facts. Hope this reaches more. Admin lies r disservice to US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are told today that truth no longer matters. It does.
We are told human decency is the concern of the weak. It… https://t.co/28W2MWCsDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@owenburke @AndyRichter @thehill Dems will probably clean up their water in a dozen years. And they won't be thankful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @JustinMBoudreau Sam Elliott though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamespmanley @JohnJHarwood @NBCNews I don't think you need to be concerned with Liberty becoming a bball powerhouse if that's worrying you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @msdeb903 still plenty of people in this camp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayrano @crampell @washingtonpost Trump is feeding Republicans enough to keep them in tow. He's a slick salesman. SCOTUS pick for ex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken they didn't even think about Garland when Dems or media weren't asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there were ever a red line for Republicans, Trump crossed it Friday. Or not. https://t.co/9F5i3wPhHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmackau @rubycramer @timkaine stop pretending you can follow a grown-up approach w/ R's. They did not and will not for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @jamespmanley this is worse than Idiocracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer Trump will do whatever he wants until Dems or Congress show they can stop him. Dems need to play tougher b/c they can't bargain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper maybe it's some Hill staffers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben that's fine. . .but it doesn't require a ringmaster and circus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben it's weak. has to showboat about everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer really hope you are right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samsteinhp everyone knew this was coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecMacGillis @washingtonpost some people still not getting it. old/proper rules are gone (for now). Dems won't get enough in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg @Fahrenthold @Tyrangiel get stuck at SMF (Sacramento) for a few hours. You might find yourself trying it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tyrangiel  Are $ available if I got to a march/protest organized by right wing/conservative groups? I might have to rethink this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSerwer they'd do it to Coons and Dems again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktumulty @GlennKesslerWP especially strange given they are occasionally spotted in area (incl by me)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @SenSchumer seems critical at this juncture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samueloakford we knew this after election night. So far R's (some) stand up, spread plumage, and sit back down on cue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgeller well it's not all that independent if POTUS can do this. I'm not an attorney. How is judicial protected from further action?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss at this point, there's no wall keeping people in the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is great. that you for sharing https://t.co/DulfZYeN7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @FoxNews they appear to have corrected article and headline. Update to tweet would be good if they haven't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigHairPlasGras plus a wide swath of the mustache spectrum is on display]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @flmolly Nat Zoo located in Rock Creek Park &amp; next to other DC and MD parks - several thousand acres. Good luck zoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniferJJacobs this probably won't help their business in DC area. seems like a miscalculation by local establishments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Green_Footballs @kurteichenwald it's back on there now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw if true, they should be FIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/2T8QKEXxn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @mawilner any of them stay standing or do they all sit when told to do so?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNPSAlaska @NotAltWorld @jasoninthehouse what is the purpose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @Chris_arnade 46% of the voting population to be precise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @DavidDiSab why? Keep head down and stay out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @ROB87390579 @David0Monroe been learning a lot from you recently but this seems to be nitpicking. Sure looks like he has]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi checks and balances is something I learned when I was a child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bother with the separation of powers? https://t.co/KaqmoePvAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin well, that's a problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @jdawsey1 @kelseylh he'll ask "mother" to do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben @PaulBegala @HuffPostPol perception, deception and money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait what? https://t.co/vpfQqnipNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben @jameshohmann it's reprehensible if true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovPenceIN @samfbiddle @mike_pence suddenly change your mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCardin how about calling on Republicans in Congress to stand up for what was their beliefs fairly recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer they've all shelved any morals they had to hop around like flies on the pile of crap they've made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom yes but it's impacting folks with papers, it's a policy that's ineffective/detrimental. People can't just keep quiet &amp; take it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeWoodTR @CahnEmily it's also nearly impossible to enforce a ban vs. those truly committed/&amp; energizes anti-American radicalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel forgot about this. Wow! Eat crow Peter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben you periodically say things like this. It's usually a joke but now I'm considering it myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind @jbarro has he made a more recent comment? Not everyone is forced to kiss the ring like Pence, Ryan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan huh. you elaborate on taking diametric stances re this issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews I hope Cholula and El Yucateco hot sauce aren't part of the buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports John Coctostan is a hero for taking on the Underhills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMatrix09 @crampell Cheney doesn't have to fall in line as Pence feels he must do.  That said, I'd like to hear Cheney chime in now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs @GovPenceIN I think it deserves an explanation. Someone in the press should ask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbclaurak great job today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto what's new on Trump-Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBegala @JasonKander @danpfeiffer @washingtonpost of course it is. Best solutions to problem in next 2 years? 4 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben @JGreenDC the Bends is really good though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samsteinhp Timely though. Trump might want to look into putting dragons on the Mexican wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustinHunt @jamespmanley @SteveKopack why is there hot blue fire cascading across the desk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom any worth following? Seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald testing the market]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss you were stoked when you saw her apply Brut by Fabergé]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonlovett @ddale8 "we all know you will keep every promise. Do you have any additional news to communicate to the people?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP @Bencjacobs I'll know ppl w/ fewer voting rights than in Mugabe's Zimbabwe after this if courts/justice dept don't protect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @lifebythecreek probably not as easy as you make it sound. Note: I'm not saying they aren't erring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecMacGillis how much money would it take for you to work for Trump? Maybe $100M wasn't enough for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben here's an option https://t.co/pFKlcrNO2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build Your Own Trump Wall https://t.co/3ywX23gJ4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben I found that pick of Selleck you were trying to find https://t.co/iuTus05WNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is great news https://t.co/RtiKPC3pCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner were you considering it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLaCanfora you've probably heard but in case you haven't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revived Hammerjacks Will Offer A Place Of Experiences https://t.co/Nz3VNWE3de]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben @nytimes @peterbakernyt You can likely reason with your son. Huge difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[order on interrogations is a White House document https://t.co/kMNcfV0bsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfavs off the rails. depressing. sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmkaplan @jamespmanley this is so depressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben and apparently only happens in States that voted for HRC. strange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben Turn on, tune in, drop out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP I thought it was a cover for upcoming onslaught of voter suppression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tour of F. Scott Fitzgerald’s Baltimore https://t.co/qPoBhtOAmo via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonKander Russia investigation doesn't help the agenda/ want cover for heavy voter suppression now that they have total control of govt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samueloakford I do appreciate the work you are doing. Keep it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshtpm @jamespmanley is he making you guys fight too many fires again?I know it's not normal. But the method was effective during campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben or if he chilled out to some music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @mletterle he did this during campaign with constant redirects and ancillary "scandals"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerrapinHoops 18 years? That was 18 years ago!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningmoneyben the problem is she likely means the exact opposite #habitual liar]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>