<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This trip to Michigan is gonna be a wild one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, who dis ðŸ–•ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threesixmonica us Colombians do it best ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 16 days I move back closer home and start a new chapter. Too excited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonroach14 hey, where you from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a cute, fun, loving, adventurous, great sense of humor, wild, freaky,  LOYAL girl in my life. #whereyouat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump majority of those bad dudes drive cambered Hondas. Acknowledge it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump let's put an end to all this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump let's make a difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump and to allow truck owners put a big lift on their truck and put tiny low pros on their 25 inch American force and rockstars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you know what Trump. We need to focus on the real problem in our country. And that's allowing people to camber their Hondas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBestMeninist @JellyShareCom this shit should be illegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itslifethought @CoolestLifeHack not always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CauseWereGuys I want my first daughter to be a sheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laryssa_lake half a hit I'll knock myself out hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laryssa_lake I can't even with that girl lol she laughs at me. I used to more than she could, but getting old ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laryssa_lake takes very little and I tap out lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish best chokers are the ones that look like my hand â˜•ï¸ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm blessed to have all these gorgeous ladies in my life that keep me on my toes at my worse ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruckP0rn @Sie_corl get me in this â¤ please and thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I was in Oscoda right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threesixmonica not my business though lol ðŸ¸â˜•ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's ridiculous is the amount of people I know that cheat on their significant other lol  What's real and what's not anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr they both suck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new @IPrevailBand album is flawless ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way my girlfriend eats her string cheese is seriously the cutest thing ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my job. I take pride in my work so others can travel safely @SouthwestAir @HawaiianAir https://t.co/T4nDXNzBaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally been in the bath for 4 hrs...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennyross2013 the experience is unbelievable out west]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sie_corl @MattKav28 just tryna help a bestie out ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandaa37 that shit is too dangerous for me ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then oscoda bound Sunday for the night! ðŸ¤˜ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get to see my girl tomorrow and annoy her for straight 5 days ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop climbing your mountains, no matter how scary they seem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam- I have a heartburn again              Me- You need to have a heart for that 

ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr dude... that's fkd â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the pile of bird poop I stepped on earlier has a better chance as president than Trump or Clinton #FactsMatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good fucking lord ðŸ˜© https://t.co/pHjLiGqhDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish hahah gotta ease her in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish what you wanting to get???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hmikazes @bbrendenn that's my boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 days left until I'm home bound with my babe â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My god do I have a beautiful girlfriend ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elkins_rachel and they're absolutely right ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want right now, is to be deeply stuck in a mud pit with an 18 pk lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonKIRO7 @KIRO7Seattle that's all he's getting? I hope the kid is ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long distance sucks ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@summmerlee1 people will never understand this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being 2,200 miles away from your girlfriend fkn sucks, but knowing in a few weeks here, we will be together for good is worth the wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I did that today. Fkn scum bags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hit and run when the car you hit has a little kid and don't be surprised when a lifted truck is chasing you down ramming into you. Smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr lolllll you swear i said that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ’£ keep the bomb emoji though... makes sense... just like the removal of the aux port on the 7...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised apple still has the American flag on there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple ðŸ”« Wtf is that? You guys are soft as fuck... smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the day #SouthPark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 3 years of her being my best friend, one of the closet people in my life and now my girlfriend, it's safe to say I'm ready for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't even explain how excited I am to move to Kansas City and have my best friend move in with me â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alina_enokhina don't yell at me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to miss my mountains though ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super pumped about it... Like super!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a sick note, I move to Kansas City, MO next month ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fkn thirsty ass fgts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When guys message your girl at 11 at night saying, "hey Hun, how is your trip?" It's great bud, better than anything you'll ever give a girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm slightly obsessed with my girlfriend #sorrynotsorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr don't need to get your panties in a bunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr and then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr and then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr you have 8 days to wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate having the fear of putting 1000% into someone and getting 20% in return . In general â˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only a couple of weeks left until my babe is out here with me ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr I'll hit on him all I want. Fight me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First night not having my girl to sleep with really sucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard for people to be real with each other?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-minus 8 hrs until I'm flying out to see my babe @sraniefisherr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 days until home bound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threesixmonica I just started yesterday and haven't caught anything cool. Waiting for charzard then I'm done ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threesixmonica I need a charzard asap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr seems to be a great trend in that town. Find out people's true colors after a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr I can't wait babe â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr it was a joke that you didn't take too funny :/ wont happen again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr not even close to being true lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr but you're not chubby at all lol...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna have to start bulking up so my girlfriend doesn't have a shrimp of a boyfriend anymore #thestruggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr fk out of here ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish I'll be in Oscoda probably around 3ish. So we'll get together after you're off work and start the weekend off right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish see you on the 5th ðŸ» round two brotha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr @RelatableQuote I feel like the first, third and last picture are screen shots of our conversations ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool thing about working your ass off, is being able to do anything you want. Michigan bound in 3 weeks to see my girl @sraniefisherr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradenMorrish I do that on the daily ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr your selfies are better than your nudes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trobins92 true brotha. And soon we'll be able to do shit monthly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know why I sign up to work weekends... I have no life lol I need to change that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Courtnelynn I love your bf a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threesixmonica @willdarbyshire sensitive pussies blame guns for everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 hrs on facetime with @sraniefisherr lol most I've ever FaceTimed anyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 20 year vet co-worker "I'm offended when girls wear American flag bikinis" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've been looking for love and it's been in front of you this whole time ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr I know you like it! You were laughing last time we watched it â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sraniefisherr you're watching it??? ðŸ˜]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>