<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@_RyanBarker that vid doesn't show it, but he was clean through there was no amount of effort that I could of put in to get there ðŸ˜£]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKintu @Roachie1127 I feel like you're actually a bit rattled you know ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKintu @Roachie1127 I think it's Lamps, gerrard beckham scholes you know ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKintu @Roachie1127 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ you know I hate stats I'm playing in that regard. But genuinely, Lamps very underrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaKintu @Roachie1127 deep the stats and contribution by Lamps tho... I'm just saying it's not that clear cut ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_elias7 I'm agreeing with first picture, think it's a fair statement to make]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_elias7 think it's very fair to say, who's been better over a similar period? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ absolutely killed me here, basically put him through on goal myself https://t.co/pCOHf0bvN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeKizzi @Mike_elias7 haha was tryna initiate a bite for you Kizz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now all three players have retired and you can reflect, I think it's fair to say Lampard was better than Gerrard, probably Scholes too. ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeKizzi @Mike_elias7 let's try again. Thoughts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a side that is minus David James. Scholes deffo inhaling a Stevie G fart tho https://t.co/9AarvNDB0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys always conceding worldies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that Hennessy again? ðŸ™„ https://t.co/enOwT1GgEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbieEvans_ both pony. https://t.co/IsMt4nbmtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It says it all when Sissoko is  struggling with a left back who had the physique of a 13 year old boy. 30 M.I.L.L.I.O.N.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Onomah needs to go on loan to a National League side and get absolutely shown up. Too dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How have we fucking won that!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All 4 of our goals were so lucky and I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm gonna be punished for laughing at Liverpool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool have been fucking abysmal. If Klopp doesn't make 3 subs at half time I'd be very surprised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wolvessssssss. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is too messed https://t.co/ByKO1W1S66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But not as much as I miss @NChadli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top boy you are Bobby x https://t.co/n6BmDbZhua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea are just creasing at everyone  this weekend like https://t.co/qbHIfgA5yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Leicester go down, I can't explain the joy in my heart I'll feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgemontella Leicester arsenal weat ham and united?! ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgemontella oh 100%, just tryna get a nibble off a few gooner mugs. Still gotta play Liverpool away which will tell us everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh and Wanyama is a man mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also Toby Aldeweireld is the undisputed greatest thing since sliced bread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe Lloris made two mistakes yesterday, or the fact we were absolutely shite and still nicked a draw. #ItsOurYear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bournemouth are gonna be the bet sheggery init.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THERE IT FUCKING IS. SIGGY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That goal was fucking cold. â„ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might as well sack him right now https://t.co/Cgj1FJoC1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players are always getting their first goal against us, Gabriel Jesus gonna be another name add to the list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nailed on debut goal. https://t.co/7QkSdCuN04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The comments ðŸ™ˆ definitely a bunch of northerners who've only dealt with white trash and their livestock https://t.co/uWZxVOByDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeezLouize @AndrewLloyddd @OhioV1 you shouldn't. ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewLloyddd @OhioV1 @NeezLouize "I agree with what he's saying minus the insults" embarrassing mindset ðŸ˜‚ðŸ–•ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeaverKing69 @Joe96__ in bits man, straight on the group chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't want that game to end boy. ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pogba needs half time, absolutely rattled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pogba?? That's inexcusable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Ademola Lookman slipped through the academy net before making his Â£11m move to Everton https://t.co/CfsG2hb4BT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oi I read an article about Lookman the other day, and he has literally come out of nowhere as a baller, wish him nothing but success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTBoateng he really has ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jsacks winks is an absolute boppers for reference, you'll see in due course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTBoateng 100%. All the top sides are backing 3 at the back and it's because of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted Man City to lose the moment I saw Clichy wearing a different set of boots on each foot, diabolical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And his first real managerial challenge is undeniably, currently failing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ballague will insist it's the English leagues fault. But maybe Pep has been blessed with settled, incredible sides?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Man City don't get top 4, what is Pep Guardiola really saying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayRPL he's way too good a footballer to sit on the bench though, I think he should do a Payet personally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah he wouldn't get in our 11 at this moment, he needs to somewhere and play though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proper used to like Sturridge but his playing style in Klopps systems so weird. Goes missing, needs to go somewhere else, like Tottenham ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_elias7 @OhioV1 I wouldn't have dier in there, tbh I don't even have a suggestion, but Marc Pugh is better than Hendo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 Henderson will ruin everything though just saying ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 this is beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesssss Costa you little rebellious favela fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingsfrancis30 ðŸ˜‚ that is heartache]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingsfrancis30 it was all fun and games until Messi fancied showing up ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No banter I'm watching Barca and thinking all they need are Danny Rose and Kyle Walker ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been getting slated in group chat and he does that the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've reached that point where I think Soldado was better than Janssen. ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oi scorcher that was dece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FA cup soon to cure boredom anyways. ðŸ™ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can get through some fucking food when I'm bored mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend 90% of my days working out whether I'm hungry or bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elite batty bwoy https://t.co/BlCcGSxXZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clichy needs to drop his beard to match his sideburns, looking patchy like his clubs form]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azpilicuetas nightmare tonight. https://t.co/ywmHLLLdao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tottenham have made a terrible terrible terrible week, just a terrible terrible one, thanks @Dele_Alli and all at @SpursOfficial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oi @GaryJCahill didn't like something that was said there ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 @STEPHENSTINSONN that was a difficult time in life boy, took my frustrations out on miss crump and them man ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 another 10 mins ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my days not Fabregas, this could really get long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eriksen the boy again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kane's playing like a new born giraffe. But second half we go again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eriksen you are the boy tbf you little Danish Delight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur Football Club PLC pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too much hype around this game, I'm flapping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you mugs have pointed this out... https://t.co/bOBGVf06zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm fucking fucked. New year new me n that ðŸ¤¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Brown is such a cunt ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old Firm is a joy to watch for the atmosphere alone, nothing like it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking cunt of a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dominated from 18 mins to 90, first away win in a while, Allis better than Zidane, coys init]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 I was screaming for him to get binned ðŸ˜­ worst call of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yoooooooo. Danny Rose I will apologise forever to you. You're messed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Yes. Yes. Game done finally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The break ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional Boxing Day booze up got me feeling wounded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday night blues on a Wednesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is an actual joke ðŸ¤¤ https://t.co/eNriVZgIjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed the traditional Xmas eve festivities at the Fox though I can't lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Christmas in 6 years I'm not fucked. Dinner gonna be a movie ðŸŽ¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhioV1 ðŸ˜‚ curtain calls and F64's]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>