<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Invitation to Cherrywood Open Day-9th Feb- 1-8pm, 10th Feb 8am-8pm &amp; 11th Feb 10am-5pm Video here https://t.co/NdX8221f6x @DublinSinnFein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump another massive generalisation by the White House's temperamental juvenile. Exactly how dumb is this man?? #GodHelpUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muireannf Trainspotting? Amazing? brilliant - loved it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EndaKennyTD Please cancel your St Pat's 'week' trip to D.C. No Irish leader should legitimate anti-immigrant bigotry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to see #Trainspotting2 today. Best movie in years. Dovetailed nicely in the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know a lot of people fear Donald Trump. Fear is the wrong reaction. The world needs to be prepared for the consequences of his decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would SF want to be with FG? Ye do nothing to progress GFA. Give unionist voters a choice - start working in the north? @nealerichmond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no ! I'm being followed ! By who? Eh..... a camera crew #spies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loreillysf @SIPTU @DermotLeary Shame @Shane_RossTD won't meet unions in Bus Eireann dispute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelgredmond @josephamadigan It won't help Beacon South Quarter residents &amp; I can't see how new builds are substantially protected either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzoneill sounds like a computer program so (Euromils). Did you win it? I didn't. Anyway I'd hate to win €88m I wouldn't be able to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRegsBlog @josephamadigan tnx JM. Was referring to Beacon South. We must come together for residents of BSQ. Happy to give whatever support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRegsBlog @josephamadigan good piece, practical, realistic, no doubt but fair on homeowners in this case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josephamadigan @HeraldNewsdesk how can it help the current residents in Beacon South Quarter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fixing problem at Dublin Airport could start by bringing passport control closer to plane. Distance too far for a passenger to "disappear"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josephamadigan @HeraldNewsdesk You're in Josepha government - what will be done to help them and prevent future occurrences like this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely delighted that @moneillsf is the new Sinn Féin leader in 6 counties. Someone with real leadership qualit… https://t.co/lYBHLfrkqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely condem the shooting of a PSNI officer in Belfast tonight. Justice for the culprits, a full and speedy recovery to the officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onbbc2now @BBC Some snooker hall positioning by Perry in #Masterssnooker. In consistent play. Glued to tv though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moneillsf gets a huge welcome at @sinnfeinireland #unitedireland conference. @DublinSinnFein https://t.co/YiULBNTh2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought provoking comments by @noelwhelan at @sinnfeinireland #UnitedIreland conference in @MansionHouseDub https://t.co/Xq1rspk4u1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinPMeagher "the debate on Irish Unity needs to be deshinnerized" - so true. @sinnfeinireland @DublinSinnFein https://t.co/joaCgkPBtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryLouMcDonald #UnitedIreland conf "@FineGael &amp; @fiannafailparty are the government but have unusual setting arra… https://t.co/krYSePjfBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting points brought up by @AlexKane221b on #UnitedIreland &amp; insight into unionist identity &amp; unionist contem… https://t.co/IC4KbZzoBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS44 the world is going to miss you Obama. Many of us outside  US worried about the nationalistic, irresponsible, juvenile who took over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shouldn't forget those who lost their lives in Tehran. Seems most were firefighters. People doing their jobs.… https://t.co/9BB0sILeAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V best wishes to @M_McGuinness_SF. A hero to many &amp; a giant in the history of Irish politics. History will judge hi… https://t.co/NjDwNIMG5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathypower @morningireland Enda &amp; GFA - horrendous. Irish gov negligent in its role on Good Friday Agreement. #Shame #HeadlessChicken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gloriadlgc @BarryDowling78 @kennethroraback @shayhennessy More than a tourism attraction !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LHannon_Fotos I believe media apologies should be the headline on front page &amp; sincere - good luck with that #SomewhereOverTheRainbow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeLaSalleCtown EXCELLENT !! Not enough awareness - good job @Zeeko_Education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteMerrigan #brexit England will be better off, Ire won't benefit soon as housing crisis/office space shortage impedes FDI. UK could split]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long shot here - can anyone swap 2 BellX1 standing tickets in Olympia for 2 Elbow standing (Olympia Sun Gig) - still going to Elbow anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJPMarshall @DavinaDevine @PMVTrust Interesting radio during the week - homeless guy "people love us at Xmas but ignore us otherwise" #True]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GCraughwell #Brexit can we catch the boat or already sailed. Insufficient office space &amp; a housing crisis. Surely a consideration for FDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full house in the teachers club. Briefing by Alex Maskey on the situation in the North, DUP #RHI &amp; possibility of e… https://t.co/gQL4n2fEBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama as @POTUS is nearing an end. I think history will judge you favourable but I fear for @realDonaldTrump - arro… https://t.co/TEQ5QjKaMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The north of Ireland is clearly a priority for Westminster https://t.co/mMPGo2pbqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another one following the "Adams Look" @nealerichmond - will I buy yiz razors? https://t.co/jK2czzE0Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This photo says it all. The flat-earth brigade take over in Stormont. Ain't no democracy there at the moment. Just… https://t.co/dckr9L5YRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for the "Adams look"? Looking well by the way https://t.co/IH2LfN1uTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheIrishTim Sinn Féin passed motions on @dlrcc re: harbour co. Central government takes liabilities &amp; invite to Mi… https://t.co/NDUokyUzP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful @DublinSinnFein motion on @dlrcc Potential DunL Harbour Co liabilities must be central government's responsibility @DublinGazette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful @DublinSinnFein motion inviting Minister @Shane_RossTD to discuss potential liabilities of DunL Harbour co. @DublinGazette @dlrcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally Journalism X - great idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sign of the times in 1987. https://t.co/UJ7QOq4Agw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eamon Donnelly of @IMPACTTU  very clear on Hospital Overcrowding @morningireland - Good Job Eamon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expected comment from Minister for Children &amp; Youth Affairs on stabbing of Tallaght youth. After-all it's her constituency too @KZapponeTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding Chicago kidnapping &amp; battery video deeply disturbing. My heart goes out to victim &amp; family. Give him justice &amp; them -&gt;years in jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office365 it's resolved now.  Thanks guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else having issues with Office365 / Office 365 tonight? No online apps available and mail features gone too??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FineGael @Revolution_IRL oh yeah and so did this. Cop yourselves on https://t.co/DkD5iEjdTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FineGael @Revolution_IRL Eh this happened in 2016 during the centenary too https://t.co/VJY6hvfrMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD travelling on the 44 a stunt? Well maybe he'll will use it everyday when traffic is chaotic. He will in his arse! #stunt #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be surprised if Ross resigns if Stepaside Garda Station doesn't reopen #vinb - 2017 Garda plan due to appear in Dáil soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GCNmag @TheOutmost didn't read article the term "commit suicide" not used anymore. It's "take own life" as"commit" suggest a sin/religious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did this happen to these parked cars? Don't think anyone was injured. What of the car that caused it? https://t.co/wjNfByay3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to @NARACampaigns protesting on animal rights. It's great to see people, especially young people fighting… https://t.co/OHx24ff3h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenJones84 very well spoken re: The legacy of George Michael https://t.co/50sYoTLIoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad news tonight about George Michael https://t.co/8b2TGiwrQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to everyone who helped out today in @TescoIrl in @DundrumTC in  aid local projects and @TempleStreet https://t.co/5Sg12uRMbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to Ballyogan residents fundraising in @TescoIrl  @DundrumTC for @Temple_Street Hosp and community project… https://t.co/TzRAt8DFlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm positive that if the state attempts to evict those in Apollo House, a sumani of fury will be unleashed by The Irish People @HSHIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many technology professionals in the government?? Worrying - truly worrying. https://t.co/Eh4rpUTQbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to #HomeSweetHome in Apollo House tonight. https://t.co/7gAauFgC4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE - what's going on guys? Broadband down AGAIN !! Bad start to VirginMedia in Ireland - get it together !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningireland Dancing with the stars - "he has great moves" thanks for smile on a dreary Monday morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkCork50 your statement is correct, but still no truth commission for all victims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God #vinb is not healthy before bed. It's just too argumentative but the potential outcomes are terrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFFG - juggling goodwill of peace process. Cahill/Stack = pawns. Its the yellow brick rd &amp; Oz - I'll never run 4 elections again #vinb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtenews Worst case scenario could cost Ireland €161bn if Sellafield accident? Eh worst case scenario - we're all dead !!! No? @IrishEnvNet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great initiative by @LUAS, @ichhdublin and to everyone who contributed today @sinnfeinireland @DublinSinnFein https://t.co/x8eAfSXIlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaaleinster Congrats to @CualaCLG on winning Leinster champ today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't forget that today is world aids day #WorldAIDSDay https://t.co/x7n7GdCUW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see @BorisJohnson being Lynched by the British people. Looks like he led a campaign that he didn't believe in. Do politician's lie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if the popes visit has anything to do with #repealthe8th?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI @raphaelsbank @DublinAirport Adjust overnight? Was told that on Saturday. It hasn't ;-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI seems like BOI authorised a payment, despite no cash dispensed.  Do @raphaelsbank operate the ATMs in @DublinAirport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nealerichmond @DublinAirport @bankofireland @dsmooney seems a UK ATM operator has been debiting a/cs &amp; not giving cash - skimming maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD Who operate the airside ATMs @askDubAirport? According to @bankofireland there seems to be ATM fraud in the Dublin Airport??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who operate the airside ATMs @askDubAirport? According to @bankofireland there seems to be ATM fraud going on in the Dublin Airport??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who operate the airside ATMs @DublinAirport? According to @bankofireland there seems to be ATM fraud going on in the Dublin Airport??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to Ex-England footballer Paul Stewart speaking on sexual abuse https://t.co/XLreaH4shK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Will it take 139 years for your website to be updated with the new map showing the new Pheonix Park tunn… https://t.co/pTSVlRDULZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southside Travellers Action Group take @EndaKennyTD to task on #TravellerEthnicityNow @sinnfeinireland @SandyfordSF… https://t.co/Z3ZZxdGl8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching questions to @EndaKennyTD on cyber security. Clear desperate need for IT professionals in politics - shockingly weak! @GerryAdamsSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an empty pub in Dorset Street, biting my nails and hanging on for 6 minutes #COYBIG #AUSvIRE - Come On !!!!! https://t.co/CTZkPVUk0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still finding litter of politicians running profiling campaigns when no election.@nealerichmond wouldn't do that, w… https://t.co/aQQg8wlAzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got notification today for @FMIHeadOffice about some Christmas jobs if anyone is interested https://t.co/nD49Ibyl4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drivetimerte - ask Hines will the be selling off smaller sites once the roads go in - bet they will !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending @dlrcc joint policing public meeting in Stillorgan tonight @SandyfordSF https://t.co/alQ2vPVmUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump victory represents a failure of the entire political establishment to its job. He's still a dickhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First night of @dlrcc €151million budget meetings https://t.co/94j0Xmoa6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear USA,
Please don't elect @realDonaldTrump as @POTUS. That would be like letting a child run a sweatshop. The world needs stability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanTubridyShow Claire's story -such an emotional an inspiring young lady from Dundrum - such strength so humbling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubFireBrigade good job tonight guys. #DFBLive @SandyfordSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteMerrigan @IrishTimes @IrishTimesOpEd Debatable surely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely day for a stroll on the pier https://t.co/s7HEJjWAFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Halloween. So happy to be a tiger tonight - arrrggghh !!! https://t.co/qHlbmuGyXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian holding the fort in Belarmine for the fight for our swimming pool @SandyfordSF @DublinSinnFein https://t.co/sM0NZXi4uE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>