<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RocketLabUSA Hello have emailed re getting media access to Mahia launch for @upthisway. Any chance please? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlombardifoxtv Intrigued what #patriots would want for Garoppolo trade to Browns. 1st round pick?...or would a 2nd rounder do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanschwarz thanks a lot have just emailed with some potential interview times All the best R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanschwarz Hi Alan trying to set up a chat with you about ADHD Nation for @upthisway @radionz Best email please? Thanks Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarfield Hi Simon keen to speak about Timekeepers for @upthisway @radionz Best email please? Thanks Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a player... https://t.co/UHhAk8O1Ve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Chris @NakedScientists on pandas in peril and a new biomarker to detect (and potentially treat) prostate cancer https://t.co/cmjjLLkiqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Drone repellent technology developed by @DroneShield https://t.co/VcFAUWigal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotic rubbish rescue: cleaning up our seas @RichardHardiman @RanMarineTech https://t.co/48MY6oLeI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why our seabirds are eating plastic @DJShearwater @ucdavis @davis_egsa @gabynevitt https://t.co/nVZOzKAwFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Block @consumernz reviews 3 'As Seen on TV' products for us. So do the claims stack up?https://t.co/lzTUWyI81W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petergnz with Netflix download news and competition for mobile wallets heats up https://t.co/FfFvvHC0Zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some stunning images of new Shanghai Library design. https://t.co/04V0sG4Llu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists say dinosaur-killing asteroid made Earth's surface act like liquid. https://t.co/MZzB6hJjSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to scrap Nasa climate research in crackdown on ‘politicized science’...will pursue space exploration instead. https://t.co/ziYElkCgAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pipkeane thanks pip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Along a fractured highway https://t.co/Ht2fYBjpv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAtwood Sadly Louise says you're not doing more media for the book. On behalf of your NZ fans please can I persuade you otherwise?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAtwood @HogarthBooks thank you! Will do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vit_Jedlicka Hello Vit keen to talk Liberland for @upthisway best email please? Thanks Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SundanceTV Hello! So keen to track down Ray McKinnon to see if he might be able to talk @Rectify for Radio NZ's @SaturdayRNZ, Please help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretAtwood Hello Margaret! Any chance of a chat with Radio NZ's Kim Hill @SaturdayRNZ about Hag-Seed sometime please? Thank you R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate Wes Anderson music playlist. https://t.co/Z6oJkucWr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news: the Barkers are delivering a public lecture in Dunedin on the health benefits of dogs, https://t.co/7SC6I3E3q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could this be the Holy Grail of audio editing...an automatic de-ummer?! https://t.co/CGbox2KMBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@broadinstitute Prof Aviv Regev @humancellatlas Like Google Maps for the human body https://t.co/t7GDwemTAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video of the most unsatisfying things in the world (via @kottke) https://t.co/ruyVCfyZof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click plate: how Instagram is changing the way we eat. https://t.co/OKEcWshl3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chamiltonjames Hi Charlie any chance of a talk with @upthisway in NZ about vultures sometime? Best email please? Cheers R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ShipMap generates gorgeous maps of global shipping routes. https://t.co/BXn313GYjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shortest-possible walking tour of the 27,000+ pubs of the UK. https://t.co/ICCVSTHNNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oasis snubbed Trainspotting soundtrack thinking film 'was about trainspotters'. https://t.co/GNgTv9l6vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We wait, miserably, for the dong shot." Taibbi skewers the Trump campaign. https://t.co/55scTggfjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US National Retail Federation estimates jump in Halloween-related sales: $8.4bn total with $3.1bn spent on costumes. [@readtedium]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take 26 balls of wool in 7 diff colours...BBC instructions from 80s on how to knit Tom Baker's Dr Who scarf https://t.co/LjTw81RVLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL teams recreate games with toys following league ban on highlights. https://t.co/CjZHtcja1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chamiltonjames Hi Charlie any chance of a talk with @upthisway in NZ about vultures sometime? Best email please? Cheers R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RorySmith Hi from NZ Rory! Would love to talk Football Manager/FIFA for @upthisway sometime next week if poss. Best email please? Thanks R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Shortcut, anyone can select a &lt;30 sec audio clip and immediately share to social media, where clip plays alon… https://t.co/nHEumR3sPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This American Life is making podcasts as shareable as GIFs. https://t.co/0TVItqJnLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A local shop for local people? Brexit could inspire the League of Gentlemen to return to TV https://t.co/f7ftdMZSOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srhbutts Hi Sarah Any chance of an interview with @upthisway re the @arguetron please? Thanks a lot Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicoleperlroth Hi Nicole super keen to chat Silicon Valley restaurants for @upthisway. Best email please? Thanks! R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Benguiat, the 'Stranger Things' font. https://t.co/CldQgeKmvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Twilight Zone for the digital age...' Black Mirror's back for season 3...here's a trailer. https://t.co/RQKIV91vg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Chopra and Naomi Mackinnon talk tactile astronomy on @JMulliganRNZ later 3:40pm today @BlindNZ… https://t.co/R7qpqe9wfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickMeier Hello Patrick! Very keen to chat with you for @upthisway. Best email please? thanks Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Simpsons marathon coming in November...600 Eps, 300 hours or 13 solid days. https://t.co/JHLsTojV3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmjakicic @PittSchoolofEd Wearables and weight loss: how well do they work? https://t.co/5gw4ddG1Ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GIMilner interviewed about Pinpoint:How #GPS is changing our world @wwnorton @GrantaBooks @allenandunwinnz https://t.co/XlvC7tLSOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple ‘in talks to buy supercar maker McLaren’ as it seeks to acquire tech to be used in driverless cars. https://t.co/CvpTXj9ccg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Users attempting to activate the iPhone 7 within a...sports armband will have to remove the smartphone to do so." https://t.co/2hwgT2zC6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardHardiman @upthisway No worries thanks Richard emailed you back with some times this week and next Cheers! R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From mall Santa to beer smuggler: tracking Homer Simpson’s 191(!) jobs and salaries. https://t.co/liOSdFbfUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasbychuck Done! thanks Chuck Cheers R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardHardiman Hi Richard Keen to talk about the Sea Shark for @upthisway best email please? Thanks Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonMudlark Hi there! Anyone (Lara Maiklem?) we can speak about mudlarking for @upthisway please? Thanks a lot R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasbychuck Hi Chuck Any chance of a chat for @upthisway sometime please? Thanks a lot Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonMudlark Hello there hoping to chat to Lara Maiklem for @upthisway best email please? Thanks a lot R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasbychuck Hey Chuck! After reading Rory Carroll's piece would love to chat for @upthisway in NZ. Best email please? Thanks R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avlskies Hi Ariel would love to chat ayahuasca for @upthisway best email please? thanks! R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Booker shortlist 2016: tiny Scottish imprint sees off publishing giants. https://t.co/T6yYoX1Rl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does shower gel seem to be designed to have the same physical properties as mercury?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianrausten thought that was  Essex in England for a mo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In AKL recording Monday 19th and Tuesday 20th September. Room for a few more cool stories. Please hit us with any ideas/pitches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleStock Hello there Kyle would love to speak Spam for @upthisway! best email please? Thanks R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s pop songs and yesterday’s classics have replaced the radio jingle https://t.co/rbmCxDaLTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of vintage base ball- using retro uniforms and the rules of the late 19th century! https://t.co/M61gF5kmG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAA expects 600,000 commercial #drones in US airspace within a year. https://t.co/xjF1rdoo0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no bad weather. Only inadequate clothing." (Finnish maxim) https://t.co/Cyuh1Ycpuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ek_obrien Word. Vape naysh yall. https://t.co/PwVXHGTSGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canines in court: therapy dogs making the wait for a verdict 'more human' https://t.co/vmeptLhajM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-cigarettes: do the benefits outweigh the risks? https://t.co/rPnvvQOy8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@minhealthnz @HaydenMcRobbie on #ecigarettes submissions and potential law change https://t.co/rPnvvQOy8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@otago e-cigarettes- the potential benefits and the risks with @ProfEdwardsNZ  @ASPIRE2025 @publichealthUOW  https://t.co/rnCeBHYUNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“My dad has suggested that I register for a donor card. He’s a man after my own heart.” Masai Graham https://t.co/22IJt6VPmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Apparently one in three Britons are conceived in an IKEA bed which is mad because those places are really well lit.” Mark Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is Henry’s wife covered in tooth marks? Because he’s Tudor.” Adele Cliff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Is it possible to mistake schizophrenia for telepathy, I hear you ask.” Jordan Brookes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The increasing prevalence of the Millennial Whoop, a repeating two-note motif in pop music. https://t.co/uv4Y9JBke7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Lebowski spin-off movie starring John Turturro's Jesus may be in production https://t.co/R9X5GZO9RL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Hitchcock cameo in 39 films (often near start so as not to distract the audience!) https://t.co/ABLsAV2vrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trained dogs able to act as an early warning system for epileptic seizures. https://t.co/4vANTZUJu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join MC MC on a trip into 1980's Wellington DJ and club culture. https://t.co/1qK0xZxewa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headline of the day: Christchurch man thinks burglar mistook father's ashes for drugs https://t.co/OHpj3V8Gf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NPR latest media org to ditch comments section. Looks for dialogue and 'engagement' with audience in other ways. https://t.co/cKBlLFxkdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman remember you/it well Sam! Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike share mapping creates beautiful portraits of London, NYC and Berlin. https://t.co/3rlKBg9zNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1994 pop group The KLF burned 1 million pounds. https://t.co/mjvdB8rBcw @claudiahammond discusses here: https://t.co/IBuQRyzUZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrBronKing Hello Bronwyn! We'd love to chat with you for @upthisway please. Best email? thanks RIchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DOMESTIPUPS Hello there keen to chat for @upthisway. Best email please? Cheers R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists in Tajikistan to face fines for using 'incomprehensible' words". https://t.co/bLQUHHhfZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book now: German readers get extra airline baggage allowance for holiday reading. https://t.co/xHVOAVgbgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sierra Leone is the roundest country in the world. https://t.co/s3rodcO2DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French media to stop publishing photos and names of terrorists. https://t.co/KK9SU9jKhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWConflict Hi Neil are you contactable in Botswana to talk about your project please for @upthisway? Cheers R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's largest seaplane unveiled by Chinese state company. https://t.co/x7QjHluqhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@budgeebot Hello I have tried emailing Wendy several times. Please let me know if you can speak about latest trolley tech for @upthisway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fo_Inspiration Hello I have tried emailing. Please let me know if you can speak to us about latest trolley tech for @upthisway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of all US food produce is thrown away, new research suggests. https://t.co/afiPmwlKPm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>