<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@D_Shariatmadari @shaunwalker7 I once had a fascinating conversation with a Soviet ambassador on that very point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandparis @FinancialTimes he may consider the West no loss. As apparently Trump does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LAustyanJulian @TheRickWilson i have been wondering quietly since 9/11 why such a movement has not emerged in force.  /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieBrender is that net good or Net relative?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee poor alternative candidates an ancillary factor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee According to a pollster friend that was also big factor in #RobFord mayoral success. Incl. among educated women. /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney ah. I'm using Galaxy note 5, the one that doesn't blow up. I like your low contrast textures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @thedailybeast This may prove to be a highly optimistic assessment depending on how far Bannon is prepared to go...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkGaleotti increase in repression in North Caucasus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anneapplebaum at what point do we conclude that the 'hundred monkeys' metaphor either does or does not apply to Trump utterings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GicAriana OTOH a demonstration that most talk show hosts still have no idea how to handle Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GicAriana Quite so. It's that he did it. And apparently entirely uncoached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinEph Thagomizers are key.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinEph No Trump in Far Side. In Vaughan Bode, maybe disguised as a Lizard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This trend has been building for about 20 years at a rough guess. SOF are now regulars. https://t.co/BKTsr2l7wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney ok i give in, what phone r u using?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne and at that we're probably safer then if any of that gang was in full control. But that is very relative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom i think in his case we can safely omit 'possibke']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerryGlavin @kinsellawarren I'm spending it reading The Handmaid's Tale for the first time. That may be more depressing I'm not sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenduca don't tell me its an Islamist Threat now??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne The Eagle of the Ninth paradigm: never send good reinforcements if you know you won't get them back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee certainly it won't be so innocent after Trump is done with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DancesWithTamis @living_marble @laurenduca We are all Post-Trump Syndrome Disorder carriers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmathen he has been looking haggard since before the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariedanielles that does it. I'm coming to the Dark Side!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobPulseNews @PressSec @greta duck and cover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @AmarAmarasingam Are you calling Your President a Malevolent and Incompetent Keystone Cop?? GOOD ON YA!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieBrender my ancestor Mellow N Frettingfellow III was CIA station chief behind the infamous #BowlingGreenMassacre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones that means we have four years of highly entertaining leaks doled out in driblets to look forward to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkGaleotti Or warlords more than usually incompetent...smoke 'em if you got 'em...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProdigalFailson @20committee Ulpian on the freedom of the Emperor from the laws. I suppose i shouldn't encourage h… https://t.co/nWIdPgHG6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee One assumes a Tweet of Attainder is not far behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieBrender I'm a mellow fretting fellow. Wait'll i get wound up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABarnardNYT @DrAmithaK and not a great deal different from the stuff that Spiro Agnew used to spout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perlineamvalli wasn't Morris Dancing head of MI VI for years? Codename Mater Peregrinorum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattmfm @amberlym Fine Guerrilla tactics. Can't suppress a protest over something that never happened because it's not happening either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perlineamvalli I suppose module 97 is permafrost and how to love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_marble but a marble one. Its the big difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly @20committee Is #TRex the new hashtag? Some theropods I know are going to bear a grudge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlogsofWar I've met some in both venues. That can be even odder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinapittaway PS: after a real ekpyrosis (or conflagratio) you had a municipal orgy and Horace got to write the hit number with virgins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinapittaway i had an ekpyrosis once after food at Rosa's. If he and Alexander 'Mad Monk' Dugin ever meet, the stench will be incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinapittaway Billy Shrugged?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perlineamvalli and if THATS what I need for a Classics degree I'm sticking to my Early Byzantine Sex Toys major.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HistoricalPics @RadioFreeTom meanwhile, only 1300 years earlier, at a small Roman fort somewhere in Caledonia... https://t.co/hapaqTe11q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlogsofWar It's really really hard to get to this but they've managed it in under two weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmathen you know, @20committee may be right after all. They ARE that incompetent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbritneff @stphnmaher judging by most of the billionaires I've met, I might  happily pay for a holiday anywhere but their place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cabbagetowner @TorontoStar cant we agree to go back to innocuous stories about cabbage worship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieBrender @nytimes we are in a great deal of trouble no matter who is PM. That would include O'Leary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee @wordpressdotcom what bothers me on the reread is that the US now looks like reaching a state of Mad Max before Europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanYeahMan @20committee  so actually its the kind of thing money CAN buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee nowadays you'd have to await admission by the International Olympic Committee. It's something money can't...oh wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmathen i'm with @cmathen. Undoubtedly more. Order in Council is practically unlimited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_marble I'm still grouchy about Arrival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_marble that could be a rad new fashion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumailn Seriously you need to see a superpower specialist about that :) #overspecialized]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougSaunders holy cow. Federal jurisdiction is starting to come apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even for the Kremlin, 'The Norwegian Threat' is a stretch. https://t.co/cL574KyoY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones how do you know it hasn't happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joanne_stocker that may suggest that they are behaving as they should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunKing @AlexSBurton Distracting them with fantasy may be the only safe thing to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markusoff @perreaux it's The Handmaid's Tale. Real life just caught up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anneapplebaum @nybooks I'm allowing myself a momentary flicker of schadenfreude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougSaunders you know for a system that was developed to keep a bunch of interbred princes from killing each other it hasn't had a bad run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastfurtivefox @holysmoke @edwardlucas @rashadzali1 @spectator I thought that was more Manichees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kinsellawarren @Mediaite I have a bad feeling that sides don't matter anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ipoliticsca @amandacconn That's one way of putting it I suppose. I still doubt that 'peacekeeping' in any robust sense will resurface.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsbie @derrickokeefe @CTVNews That proves it. Media attracted to toxicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney is levitating in Commerce Court West a Thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney you levitated?? How cool is THAT?? Right here in #Cabbagetown  too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones well I think we have explored all the logical avenues of this conversational gambit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney somebody in the returning office once complained that one of my trainers didn't wear shoes. I said she was a trainer already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones !! TMI !! But in my case it is mine brother Esau that is the Hairy Man, while I am the Smooth Msn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney I have a bad feeling his standard is somewhat at variance from yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandparis where have they posted his brother Horse Hockey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones I have always wondered what with ISIS and everything how beards manage to stay in fashion this side of the water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC @misscherryjones No way Trump wrote that statement with his own crayon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost @kinsellawarren He's 70. The grooves on his vinyl are worn too deep #skritch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MollyMcKew Have VVP and DJT decided who gets to use the barrel bombs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @blakehounshell @politico Actually coming up with a Jew-free Holocaust is something even Heydrich couldn't accomplish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pressprogress @acoyne I was once a Returning Officer for my sins. I came out convinced that the only important thing is a paper ballot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pressprogress @acoyne There is nothing like tradition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@APHClarkson clearly an Emergency Situation. Also known as a Double Reverse Yezhovshchina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misscherryjones @jtylerlovell and ignored ad nauseam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosieGray its... so hard to get to. Kind of like Australia come to think...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_marble Canadian law doesn't recognize citizen's curses. That's only in the USA and on TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andersostlund and doesn't care in the slightest. Luckily, Bad Emperors are rarer than we tend to imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndelpesco @AmarAmarasingam @ShaunKing can hardly disagree that Trump doesn't care!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndelpesco @AmarAmarasingam @ShaunKing Most of these things are avoidable. Obama was a very cautious President with 8 years experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmarAmarasingam @ShaunKing in other words, SpecOps quite capable of screwing up without help from WH (which does always wear consequences).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmarAmarasingam @ShaunKing Hard to know where to pin this one but doubtful it was entirely (or even majority) a Trump initiative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmarAmarasingam @ShaunKing Early Admin special ops screw-ups not actually unique (Bay of Pigs). OP Eagle Claw very late bloomer for Carter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_marble i was just thinking that life has again imitated art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinapittaway Mad Dog at least has a good pro rep as a soldier. Of course so did Guderian, Hindenburg, Gordon, Bonaparte, Cornwallis...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kinsellawarren or to be more precise, civil insurrection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickglavin oh that is not good at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandparis Mattis is likely to be the first out of a top-level revolving door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieBrender @RosieBarton @rolandparis @guardian Canada actually does hand counts. Even tabulators only count hand-marked ballots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandparis Which minister was tasked?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>