<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman So it was just antisemitic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twice a day I feed Philip &amp; Buster, neighborhood stray cats. Sometimes I stay out there watching them eat.  A warm, fine part of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, this guy is a horror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a few positives here.  For example, if you tweet, simply, "God, this guy is a horror," EVERYONE will know of whom you talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have an opening now.  We should call him the "so-called president."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes.  I only have a few minutes, though... https://t.co/XenVvImqEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies and gents, here is a peek into your old age.  It is 11:30 am.  I've been up since 6, am feeling tired. So I am going to take a nap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well, the problem is that yiddish is dead. https://t.co/JmwuLY7m29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimJGraham It's a strange place to be.  I understand that. But there is no precedent for this. The world will be saved by people like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimJGraham U r a smart man. U see what's happening. There's a point where people of conscience, whatever their politics, need to speak our.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimJGraham  There is no precedent for this situation. You cannot apply anything from before. It doesn't fit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders should just go ahead and make it official, and change the spelling of his name to Sandiz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim, you are watching an entire national narrative with a zombie plot.  And you are applauding. https://t.co/rwUWXn5Fiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, this is a forever lost part of comedy.  Go to 6:58 and watch the whole Old Man River schtick. https://t.co/Y0xmcyBJrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U buried the lede, &amp; it's good news. WH IS LEAKING LIKE AN INCONTINENT DIPSO. Also, it's not Christ on a cracker it… https://t.co/9d75w71piX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diarrhea, phlegm and pus. https://t.co/chwoXIwH9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redskins famous wideout Art Monk is first cousin (once removed) of jazz hall of fame pianist Thelonious Monk. #YouGetOnlyTheBestStuffHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please retweet this 9,858,902,877 times. https://t.co/ZQnPHWN2Bh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please retweet this seven million times.  Thanks. https://t.co/jsypE4Bmzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the most presidential person ever.  EVER! https://t.co/jRgipO44Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murphy, who is nearly 11, just cost me $400 in shots to prevent 4 illnesses she will never get, even without them.  I was happy to pay it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do we think the chances are that Trump knows what he is doing, and that it is basically good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before I go to the Apple store: Anyone know any fixes for my screen growing in width so I can't acces the right-side up-down bar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alert: Cats are strange animals.  They don't seem to understant affection, except when they do, and then it is weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hear it for cartoonists.  Seriously. https://t.co/wIf8eAmjFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear people named Audrey:  Your name rhymes with "tawdry."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowdsource poll: Are you familiar w/ the stereotype that Episcopalians spend much time talking civilly over coffee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robdelaney CNN did to the extent that Trump HATES them.  Tapper and Stelter were very tough.  I think this is a false narrative, honestly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robdelaney U don't think we've been doing that, Rob? The Wapo alone spent 2 years warning the public he'd destroy us. Horse to water, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fairflattaxnow HE invoked the millions who voted 4 him.  if they count, what about the millions MORE who saw him for exactly what he was?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanbirnholz No. The japanese were planning to defend the island to the deaths of millions.  Hirohito felt they could absorb 3 more nukes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanbirnholz  I do not think Truman had a choice, esp. with Hiroshima.  I don't fault him for that.  You do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! Only two presidents had names beginning with "Tru." The first one was pretty good, so maybe things will go swell.  #PieInSkyScenarios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hm.  But what about the 3 million more who voted, thunderously, to make you go away?   Do we just ignore them? https://t.co/SLvSx7TU9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap.  The craven GOP is scheduling the DeVos vote for 6:30 a.m. tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsympU  Yep.  Agreed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsympU  Ha.  I asked because it has been mostly women who express concern about Patty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsympU Thank you, and I know.  I was nervous.  Of course if it went badly, I could have told her immediately.  You are a woman, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snowgall We are talking about Milo here, are we not?  He is a total a-hole jackass, but they are just stupid objectionable words and ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsympU  I had no time.  We were at my stop.  I simply wouldn't have included her name.   To the pretty lady, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, who is "in danger" from speech?   That's the whole POINT of free speech.  It's about words. https://t.co/bPaoubxJIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petersagal Interesting.  I won't read it through till I re-see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the end Eva &amp; Cary are literally hanging by their fingertips, in full view, while Leo and the rescuers are standing around wisecracking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petersagal Don't recall that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is, indeed, one of the main weaknesses.  Also the Rushmore chase scene is kinda ... lame. https://t.co/Bp0vkkAotz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mm_young  I would not do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTerritory Modern standards.  It drags.  And the Rushmore chase scene is kinda lame!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham  Ah.  Well, even when Trump is right, he is wrong.  If you know what I mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North By Northwest is significantly overrated, I just discovered. Though Martin Landau is a wonderfully creepy villain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham  I'd like to hear a single direct quote from Milo that "badly needs saying" &amp; that no one less repulsive says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, this is interesting.  A distinct escalation. https://t.co/MLPcVx9pND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham   He's a total hateful a-hole.  I don't see a "but." What things does only he say that "badly need saying"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cringe whenever I find myself even partially agreeing with Trump.  Colleges, please stop cowering to ideology bullies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I deplore this stuff.  But I can definitely blame them. https://t.co/fXVrphR29f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear he's still doing some terrific work, getting raves. https://t.co/dEefY9lgWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google IM autocorrects Gorsuch to Grouch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the two hundredth time, I don't mansplain to you, Bethany.  If you were a man you would understand that. https://t.co/reZxuakjWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am beginning to think there might be something wrong with this list. https://t.co/fEYGkVJigU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it possible that the doorknob wasn't invented until 1878? https://t.co/royAxBtGnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I CAN ATTEST TO THIS.  THIS IS THE MOST LAW ABIDING MAN ON THE PLANET ESPECIALLY RE SPEED OR PARKING INFRACTIONS. https://t.co/mKGha0wUYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait.  Do we think that Spicer didn't actually know who Frederick Douglass was?  That's not possible, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeckyDMBR He is a Barnaby.  Basic black cat with white feet.  White whiskers.  Total a-hole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, it's weird.   It's like it's just a bolus of organs floating together inside a big condom.  #HoldingACat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does holding a cat feel like holding a sac of goo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done! https://t.co/L5anVSApiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TK9582 No, I meant "malign."  It is a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha. All Time Journalism Hall of Fame Typo Horror!    In my chat, I called Trump "malign."  Somehow it came out  "maligned."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intro is up!  Right here!   We start at noon sharp.   https://t.co/d404vJsgSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHAT TODAY AT NOON.  Take scary Trump poll.  Intro, in which I creepily harass a stranger lady, shd be out by 11.  https://t.co/d404vJsgSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawrence_s  I actually liked it.  Anything that delivers a real "aha" moment is worth a lot to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattbai @DebAmlen   Think about the full quote, not just the words excerpted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's NYT crossword puzzle took me 5 minutes to solve and 15 minutes more to figure out what the theme was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like it when cats become loafs.  They are loafing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a way he can be president? https://t.co/XrUnMl3cnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I still hate you, Paul. https://t.co/vQUmpH906K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q: What do you call a long onion with a gift for mischievous rhyme?  A:  A rap scallion.  #ComicGeniusAtWorkHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thescramble A lot like tiny fishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder:  No chat today.  It's tomorrow at noon.  All iconoclasm will transfer over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting! https://t.co/m2FLK7sVeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark  I know!  Weird, right?  it's because I am old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark  Understood, except.  Except you don't REALLY think that sounds good.  Fair use as rhetorical device, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know how to do an obit? Find a voice and don't abandon it.  This is as good as it gets. Seriously https://t.co/jIxykUShwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark Sorry.  Does not sound good in theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRAGEDY:  It looks as though my chat will be postponed 24 hours, to Wednesday at noon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reader questions my adectivej: Trump's "infantile" obsession with how many people saw his inaug. You got a better adjective? I'm all ears!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scocca Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning world events.  Which means we full chat tomorrow.  In the meantime, take your scary TRUMP POLL.  https://t.co/d404vJsgSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WE are the soul of our nation. Not Donald S---head Trump. Don't let this distinction be lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See, now this is a good idea. https://t.co/UWOopi28XY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to go further than that.  Working on it. https://t.co/BeQBf3Eg0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is not us. He is a perversion of us. We are way better than him.  We were in 1941, we are now. We can be our greatest generation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mere seven days in, we are pretty well at the point where we are at war with our own president for the soul of the nation. We will win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am thinking it might help to be immature.  Trump cannot take ridicule; it drives him nuts.  #BLOATUS  #IMPOTENTUS #DESPOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or poop.  I am out of the poop business for the foreseeable future.  We have work to do. https://t.co/4fHcZEjaMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it was deliberate. The president is an unapologetic Holocaust denier.  We have done this to ourselves.   https://t.co/VKxm8xxQnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham "Trump may be a maniac, but..." is a bad way to begin.  If he is a maniac, then we are in unprecedented terrifying straits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwrotesham Sorry, Steve. You are alone out there. It's completely pointless to engage you on this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free talking point for you, Tim: The evil media is ganging up on Trump, a fine man trying to help us out of a big m… https://t.co/hcqBr9O8Cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrisonchief  Thank you for being a newspaper delivery person.  That job is unsung heroism, and I honor your selfless service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The contempt you have for the people who voted for you is absolutely stunning. It's well-earned contempt, though.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>