<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber: the billion dollar loss-maker  https://t.co/4X7rQpAzvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt confirms hiring of Trump staffer https://t.co/ZzTh2idjgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US attorney-general defies Trump immigration order https://t.co/UAdbMV2r0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi to leave Doctor Who https://t.co/jxnGVmyf0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds So the advice is, kiss Trump's ring kiss it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted with only this Jean-Michel Jarre track
https://t.co/OcLj6UMjq1 https://t.co/g4mZg27vUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realpaulyoung #makesythesgreatagain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pencilsword: Creatures of the comments 
https://t.co/Se4PYUUxdl via @Thewirelessnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPalenski @Brycepearce @fineleg2fineleg @TheAVClub We'll know the shit got real when @depechemode make a statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @fineleg2fineleg @TheAVClub *plays GNR*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fineleg2fineleg @Brycepearce Yes #NorthShirestandswithMexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @NZNationalParty @PeterDunneMP seems to be a lower half country problem upper N island not enough rain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae asking a right wing extremist to own it once it's in the wild is probably too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae He gets paid for his political delusions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump snowflake in chief has to have aides control information th... https://t.co/NRUn1GSmP4 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jargon's creeping menace https://t.co/XbDhLITQjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REMIX! Alt-Right Leader Richard Spencer Gets Punched in the Face https://t.co/c5bQdGemJj via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire-Starting Child Tells Fox News: 'Screw Our President' https://t.co/zFk0F2nneg via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Dumber: George Bush or Donald Trump?; I voted Donald Trump, https://t.co/TDm2dJidw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland trials electric buses https://t.co/ZD5QHTe1K0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wyoming is trying to ban renewable energy https://t.co/lGP7BikBCV via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trump'sAmerica
'Nine Meals From Chaos' (future Ivan Noel film) 3min 'teaser' https://t.co/tt3dISIpff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does the trend for smaller nipples say about us?

https://t.co/hKdi5oiwsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of Auckland passengers face fare hikes https://t.co/jKipZeWJCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be old news but anyway https://t.co/jzwV0ngIEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the next three years because the nine after that well... #WhatIWouldITellA15YearOldMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This wasn t New Zealand last night, and it wasn t shared by an astronaut  - Yahoo New Zealand https://t.co/ELj0Yq3wa4 via @YahooNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TDB Summer Election Special: Why English is far more dangerous than Key ever was « The Daily Blog https://t.co/l57ElIvRRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does New Zealand really have a porn problem? https://t.co/MgsT6wRYwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down to two bags #aucklandimcominghome https://t.co/PIfoiBCsso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMcMullanNZ I think this guy wants to be a cult leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How two congressmen created the internet’s biggest names

https://t.co/LM92RBMMOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economic forecasts are hardwired to get things wrong

https://t.co/gXgVax5Blz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once the baby man was a figure to be mocked. Now, manfants such as Donald Trump are taking over

https://t.co/PaH9e0dXf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyBowie @alanhsmith should be able to drag onto Mac drive I had an external HD that was NTFS and did that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Bomber is happy now https://t.co/eWIJO4Sl2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek something gone wrong with the poll it reset on me showing me as the only voter so I don't know if it's gotten worse or better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeilaniTamu personally I think I've seen enough accounts to establish a pattern of behaviour on part of the Butcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima What about the Nines? Could they be to blame as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's walk a test of how well I applied the spray on sunscreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norway first to start switching off FM radio

https://t.co/NERNm9Z4FL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that glitters is not green: Costa Rica's renewables conceal dependence on oil

https://t.co/pexcq4Hu9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Hollywood ever end its love affair with guns?

https://t.co/fTL4AQAxt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mihi_Forbes It means he watches a lot of Fox news because I'm pretty sure it was O'Riley who used that term on regular basis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @lukechristensen @henderception the track was pretty poor 10-15 km/h speed restrictions in places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wheronui1 @DoctorJeph I didn't know Howick elected Bill O'Rily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatDudley @__catpower I guess the whole spent an hour defending you then do have a bf is a bit of give away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['China freight train' in first trip to Barking - https://t.co/27gT8orZqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso The tweet where he was triggered by Neoliberalism I must of been blocked by association]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Binge drinking happens. The problem is binge moralising on women

https://t.co/igW9Xv0zSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling I guess when it comes to positive news stories they make it into clickbate sadly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling makes coping and pasting easier for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving New Zealand's murder capital: 'We don't want to be defined by death'

https://t.co/fgRk8y2Z5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordantcarter @kimbakerwilson @TransportBlog @AklTransport @phil_goff @DarbyatCouncil  something something dark side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe that's the 1-0.1% remaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hippytech @jgmccl that's amazing you basically lost the equivalent of 1 me in 2 years 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geocaching: GPS treasure hunt on shifting ground as Australia changes coordinates

https://t.co/iJJQVJ3cPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally but do I deserve such an honour? https://t.co/0YAgwAhzWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashspeter @AklTransport if they didn't put back up on that is bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year twitter not so drunk by the radio I think 2017 is looking better already and #changethegovt2017 #theNatsareRats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember 7 pips to midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellClarkNZ Baywatch on Jones have a drink each time you see or hear David Hasselhoof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving your love for another Twitter account because this room is yours
https://t.co/1br1zgIoGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to do to 2016 https://t.co/jHmPzJxAeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl your waist line will thank you 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dewithiel Is Katherine Rich on the AT board too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl it's funny because it's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling seems to of stemed from a creepy video that thinks he's autistic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robyngallagher required because he wants that way 🎤👹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic bring back the Jesus they said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's gone https://t.co/3TCLByYpDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jarbury oh dear winter is coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @NewshubNZ 200 character limit I need MOAR words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling what a beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirWB @rnz_news @Mihi_Forbes 2016 take this man with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac @JJPalethorpe they need it to bring back Jesus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl railfans don't let other railfans stop themselves posting pictures to Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a Mr Whippy single flake it was gaytastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @bootstheory @Dovil Will English give the nod and wink or will he dance with Winston in the pale blue light]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downloading anything was a big deal no CD'S from the magazines required https://t.co/9KXFIIFxLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pcuser42 2002 was the year I got my last PC with a floppy disk drive a year before your cousin was born 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPalenski you get days of use before needing to recharge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phones had big buttons and small screens https://t.co/9KXFIIFxLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nostalgia was analogue and you couldn't delete it when you thought of something wittyer https://t.co/9KXFIIFxLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe wtf did I read most of that is European and most of us are well so misusing non European culture not quite the same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling I guessing the next question is was he drinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did end up shopping on boxing day wearing one of my buys now https://t.co/hQErIQUeyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMcMullanNZ I only checked wiki had no idea he was 60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMcMullanNZ Hopefully it's not a prediction he doesn't look he's going to drop off the planet anytime soon :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMcMullanNZ He is for now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce council call center always open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce hopefully I'll be sitting by the beach when I get this, maybe call them and see what they say about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @AklCouncil yes two public holidays in a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @AklCouncil they're on holiday won't get a reply until Wednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce I think there's a song pun in this, Get ourselves a night mayor ooo, oh a mayor for the night, get ourselves a night mayor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ's Israel resolution: Peacemakers seldom win friends https://t.co/62WANuQNS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoutriver going all right I think I slept off enough Xmas Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL I skipped Boxing Day last year I'll be doing the same this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas is the opiate of the masses in a world that’s mad « The Daily Blog https://t.co/UDpgWMX0yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae @ajthompson13 cute though]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>