<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That's DEAD she was the best TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why am I not going printworks opening?? WHY???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and a quick weekend to ibiza ðŸ•ºðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are , parklife and secret garden party are all a mustðŸ•´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What day for @wearefstvl ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrettFrench is it worth a bang...I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrettFrench if you sleep with her you'd have to either wifey or go into hiding #Clingy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrettFrench but hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum is a gent he clearly ain't on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnolucky7 and then what would we laugh at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chloe is TV gold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend consist of sleep and gym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pet hate is people talking who have a dry mouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieP__ I'm taking that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAN SAID CHICKEN LIVERED SHITS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got those mad eyes https://t.co/InwoMia8rT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was funny at first now it's awkward ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KICK THIS CUNT OUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim needs to be taken to a mad house ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim is crackers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to work on myself for the next 3 months ðŸ’ªðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnolucky7 oh she's hilarious such good tvðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnolucky7 she literally has NO clue she's the same in geordie shore ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had to pause the tv so I could rewind passed that awkwardnessðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's actually mad ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Kim talking about I'm wel confused ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually think Chloe has a banging figure ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruv I be the same as jasmine don't fucking touch me bro ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray z slept walked back to America ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Callum's best mum is a JAR ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be carful who you call ugly in high school https://t.co/QPaqntrrBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have a never seen a baby pigeon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argh its peak a big nose can ruin a girls whole face ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob Kardashian is actually a lump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 been fucked Prince , Bowie, Muhammad Ali , Gene Wilder, Alan Rickman and now George Micheal ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every fucking year I say I'll take it easy on xmas every fucking year I LIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners I said I was inside I was on one of the benchessssss u slag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do is check how much I got paid why are HSBC mugging my life off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah my throats fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is the word dyslexic so hard to spell and lisp so hard to say? You can't fucking catch a breakðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_AbotikalzZ @rybrennan20 aw don't you both scrub up wel ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGripz @rybrennan20 ðŸ™„ breaking my heart here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday ryyyyyyy love ya long time! Hope your recovered from the weekend ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/aSLyLtp04L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roll on 2pm Friday ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicolablake93 @SkyNews ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤”ðŸ™„ piss off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me so so happy â¤ï¸ https://t.co/iXqWPYEy1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plant earth is heartbreaking tonight ðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boohoo hi I returned a dress about 8 days ago and have heard nothing back my order number is 33643405]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a clue how to use my work phone ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for the Christmas seeeeeeesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerzMike come down Sunday's with no dominos NEVER ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerzMike ðŸ¤”ðŸ™„ would I risk dominos? I don't think it's worth the risk ðŸ˜¥ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerzMike shit cunts like you are the reason dominos have only just started delivering to my house ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rybrennan20 actually I change my mind I like her so I'll take it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking shit cunt @nationalexpress is NEVER on time stupid cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot express the feeling off passing your driving on the 8th time ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait till the 23rd, 9 days off ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting this fringe tomorrow shitting myself ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/GlIPwrur3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hollowed fucking WINNING mate ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners kmt don't break my heart my achey break heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners I hate you and your black soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners I fucking missed it  can you not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone bring me sheesh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jada_KissKissx anything cunt related I get tagged in ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My manager is so bless ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne bridge? #imacelebrity https://t.co/fAv4WEN7bG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 3 more people to buy presents for makes a change from two days before xmas ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rybrennan20 fuck sake your like the 10th person to say this ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If another person says I remind them of Scarlett out of I'm a celeb ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DEEPINTENTIONS1 I have tickets already thanks g ðŸ’ƒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people just look like they smell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cleaner at work fancies me and he has a head like angry kidðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people who film plant earth are beyond talented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to spice myself up tonight âœ¨ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@professorgreen worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk to you more on what's app than in real life welcome to 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phones are the worst thing to happen to relationships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly hate it when people tell me to smile FUCK OFF CUNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jada_KissKissx 100% of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does my life revolve around food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah mate it's the worst when you front camera flips on you and you see how truly butters you are ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally have a new job! 7grand pay rise don't mind if I doooooooo ðŸ’ƒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hollowed ah me and you both mate ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hollowed that's what I'm saying ðŸ‘‘âœ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for a messy egg night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DemiRoseMawby wrong Demi ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/U45eS8AI2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners I just your humour is stupid like mine ðŸ˜‚ I forgot how good vine was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeyhenners before I even clicked on the notification I knew it was you liking the Ines ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrettFrench bruhhh, please don't ðŸ‘º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarrettFrench better late than never ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished a series in 24 hours ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How have I only just watched peaky blinders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hollowed @Jada_KissKissx I want someone to carry me at all times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jada_KissKissx @P_Hollowed can we have them for free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jada_KissKissx @P_Hollowed you buying is ticket Paul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredlendon stick to single run free ðŸ‡ðŸ‡ðŸ‡ðŸ‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission of the month learn how to do eyeshadow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting Spanish in your insta bio don't make you Spanish baby girl just means you have the brain capacity to use googled translate ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lightskin girls who pretend to be be Latino are the worst ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>