<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why didn't @TigerWoods play the @WMPhoenixOpen ? The fans would of supported him and cheered him all the way to Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks had the perfect response to people protesting the chain's plan to hire refugees https://t.co/J3qqDltsAy via @BI_RetailNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want your best people to stay, you need to think carefully about how you treat them. While good employees are…https://t.co/CITm4s2K26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSSports Let's cut out the commercials every two minutes and enjoy @PGATOUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diversity is a source of strength and opportunity. https://t.co/m3vjlYn8WY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terry2shots You got your 5 sets! What a match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_heslin @filipemasetti Looking forward to seeing you again soon brother!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read @jlisterca ! Employees with soft skills are key to success. https://t.co/N0pWXTFPiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all meant to do incredible things with our time here, the only question is, will you? Thank you…https://t.co/xYjxkaJXO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journey to the end of the world: help in a hellscape https://t.co/rAvHWBHyFU via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should all kick these habits. https://t.co/s7zHXQqwvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....when we ask them, "Why would you do that? Why would you give your blood and sweat and tears for that person?" th…https://t.co/TYCO5BUDsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the best way to recruit sales people? by Mike Heslin https://t.co/ycpsNmIh7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you wanted a diploma from Harvard? https://t.co/5c3EXXP0OR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share the "why" https://t.co/kfXreltVzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question is not whether your company’s employees and leaders have the right skills; it’s whether they have the p…https://t.co/gKnS94zxIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats on whatever prior success got you the new gig…but don’t assume it means anything. https://t.co/5UVde9oAjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to make some changes in 2017 and join one of the fastest growing tech companies in Toronto? Email me…https://t.co/PF8v7Wj29Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE THIS-----&gt; "No one cares how much you know until they first know how much you care about them." https://t.co/TJB1WNLYWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great leaders have a way of unlocking the best in their people. https://t.co/Nbb7AlF1iR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicoleroannef I think I found your wallet on Spadina. Did you lose it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't agree more! Thanks for sharing @pamelamaeross https://t.co/Y85M9fDOsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great reminder for all the "bosses" out there who think they are leaders. https://t.co/dBQQUjmR3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before taking (or staying in) that job, consider carefully not only the product, pay, and purpose of the organizatio…https://t.co/lnEI2gi3na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be worth more than you cost. https://t.co/dAut5Vdszu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earn authority by respecting your direct reports and giving them a reason to trust you. https://t.co/n7b2MbtDB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing Ita O'Sullivan ! Biggest lesson here: Careers Are Journeys Not Final Destinations https://t.co/sE5vX4KWjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our success depends on how we choose to see our environment. https://t.co/hFAKYEit01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us as we look to make moves in the near future! https://t.co/oKRKIt26BO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For many companies that have SDRs, business would STOP if they all walked out the door."..... Great read. https://t.co/6xAcq5Ng7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone deserves a chance. https://t.co/qbRVHd18au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come join our mission! Best city + fastest growing start-ups= Truly a great experience. https://t.co/rQMIeNEGqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireneoytang @FlashStock Thanks! I will connect with you soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's this? A new opportunity to join our team? Yup! Message me if you are interested. https://t.co/NZLBOLyFXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day! Thank you @BrainStationTO for the opportunity, and thank you to everyone who attended. https://t.co/3zKPJUgAYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you tomorrow!The content is warping into something pretty unique. Come join me for an interactive conversation… https://t.co/THAtydzV06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting opportunity to join our team and work with our global network of photographers. https://t.co/nujCch4qJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting the finishing touches on the content I will be sharing and it's looking exciting! See you there. https://t.co/KaxvrmXxvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come join me next Thursday for some delicious lunch and a interesting conversation around building your personal bra…https://t.co/KaxvrmXxvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrainStationTO @FlashStock Looking forward to this in just over a week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Representing FlashStock at this years Incite Marketing Summit! Come by for a visit if you are in New York over the n…https://t.co/ftR3ydIyNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article by @gmunro123 on the importance of establishing your brand's visual identity. https://t.co/2pMzkMAzmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our opporutnities and I can chat with you about our purpose and values! https://t.co/lmxnVrz6fP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great insight. Thanks @myinstantCOACH for sharing. https://t.co/WXXOPa1nqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop by the MaRS Discovery District on Monday to meet some of the FlashStock team! https://t.co/PVuzFhI7eT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! Excited to be there.... See you guys soon. https://t.co/k2lNmUvyc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re currently a boss, is this how your employees would describe you? https://t.co/I8HA0sObyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawsonwhitfield I just used airmason. In need of your assistance immediately to finish a project. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PicklesPubOC You guys watching the Jays game tonight? #gojaysgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Culture is not about what you do. It's how you do it." https://t.co/3maW98w0dB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-promotion alert! Looking forward to having a informal discussion with you about advancing your career and worki…https://t.co/KaxvrmXxvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drum roll please.............. .FlashStock is #1! Reach out to me if you are interested in learning more about the o…https://t.co/cn6afjJ8nw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold Palmer will leave a lasting legacy for all he touched, on and off the golf course. You will be missed Mr.Palm…https://t.co/Tq78Eehz1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FlashStock team is ready for the  Startup Open House ! https://t.co/k4jVdCxdP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Canadian startups should foster a culture that allows employees to tackle tough problems, and work closely with col…https://t.co/nrpWrmETps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our doors will be open tomorrow! See you then. https://t.co/lXIy6pIFsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we recruit people, not through pieces of paper, but learning who they actually are...... https://t.co/evLhYLFMx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to shed light on a real issue. https://t.co/VlemDu75dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compassion: The most important thing in business and in life. https://t.co/STdhLWVrRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing everyone on Thursday! https://t.co/lefBEoQTrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealAlyshahn Welcome to 2016!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In summary, we're pretty awesome! Check out why our clients think so too..... https://t.co/gh8qFrY7t2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to school has never looked so exciting! Reach out to @jfield37 if you're interested. https://t.co/5YGgofsZNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring it to Toronto! Let's see this technology in action. https://t.co/lsP1k7Eo76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge, Learning, Coaching...Enough said. https://t.co/tXhypLqbrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity overload! https://t.co/DWoDJMgZA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big news for Toronto! https://t.co/M2UdADJsQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are growing our sales team right now! https://t.co/1ZhlLOND3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we want our startups to become grownups, we need to realize that the issue isn’t lack of creativity or technical…https://t.co/gm2yW98nRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law of reciprocity... https://t.co/nVM4532N9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CKLinOrg Thanks for writing and sharing. The title of this article got my attention! 
At the end of the day, "cultu…https://t.co/brN3m3FpMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us on September 1st with Simeng Zhu, VP Marketing at Flashstock. She will share the story of her career transit…https://t.co/7XpUfghpN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't just make the "safe" decisions when building your team. https://t.co/cTJozLhdUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great lessons here. https://t.co/vpnxq0g9f4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter a draw to win a Playing Spot in the RBC Canadian Open Pro-AM! https://t.co/qJwicVhY9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salespeople Are Burning Out Faster Than Ever -- Here's Why https://t.co/zY15Y8xgo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! More leaders should start doing this on a weekly basis with their team. https://t.co/OoRBjzOVic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite interview question! What have you learned in the last year? Expect this question and more as you make y…https://t.co/m8HsH1klIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the team Holly Tiessen . Looking forward to working with you! https://t.co/1DfDvn2Hyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the better articles I have read on sales recruiting! https://t.co/GnwuZmhmbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelex Gives Back - May 2016 Update - https://t.co/52l8LFrF8n https://t.co/52l8LFrF8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a great month giving back to society! https://t.co/DW01g0wJJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reid Hoffman's Top 10 Rules For Success https://t.co/X1p8Xrdpaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Message me to learn about the exciting career opportunities in sales that we are currently looking to fill. You coul…https://t.co/aNuXvukTFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join our growing team of Enterprise sales reps! https://t.co/SFWK4njM2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNL77 I probably wouldn't come back. I'd get lost somewhere between the 1st and 18th tee...... forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see! https://t.co/T88EKGlurX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't agree more! https://t.co/MTFPn7BcfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Building a culture of trust that encourages employees to have autonomy to do their jobs and the opportunity to lear…https://t.co/qlGLaYyDQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesKhabouth I have more than an "idea" that you may be interested in. We should connect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome day to be an Intelexian! https://t.co/DTY3EnrCd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this idea. https://t.co/6NcJMXs0Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We attract exceptional people and give them the runway to do incredible things” https://t.co/FYb0xpo89z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. https://t.co/ySfthDknNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the beginning. https://t.co/FtoQk3sbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Mid-Market team is growing! Reach out to me today. https://t.co/rYAycFQDgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news! The City of Chicago is officially part of the Intelex family. https://t.co/PRBzNtxori]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be you! We are seeking top Mid-Market account executives to join our team in Toronto. Please reach out to…https://t.co/e9wAKAJ5Jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot off the press! https://t.co/UJ7vQihKS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot off the press! If you are looking to join an awesome company in 2016, reach out to me and we'll chat. https://t.co/zCImCZ3mnB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>