<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The way the GOP has willfully succumbed to Trump's fascism is appalling. It's clear their priority is power, not policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bush was incompetent and socially backwards, yes, but he never seemed downright evil the way Trump does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuykeaExec yeah but she's got some pretty sophisticated interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My bowels are so messed up I got traveller's diarrhea just from watching Anthony Bourdain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyschumer how do I get to make out with Paul Giamatti?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never understood why Lisa enjoyed Itchy &amp; Scratchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Canucks were as good on the road as they are at home this season, they would have 6 Stanley Cups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peaceful protests aren't going to cut it. You have to break some eggs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only people who identify themselves as terrorists on their visa applications should be denied entry into the US. It's not that hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SadieVadnais Alien, Only Lovers Left Alive, Harry Potter, Snowpiercer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josueaparicio I know stranger things was big for her but honestly? You probably could be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citizens of Earth have won the Miss Universe pageant 64 years in a row. That's appalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A decade of bad movies followed by a pair of merely mediocre ones? Yeah, sure, Shyamalan's back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanBarnatt here's hoping it's Keith's new phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly scary stuff. Brilliant. https://t.co/TXmKDTxZVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My spirit animal is Leslie Nielsen from "Airplane!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,854 goals, 3,641 assists, +1,230. All at one table. https://t.co/uowszWAcYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless you're a female, person of colour, school age adolescent, LGBT… https://t.co/Ig1wslobtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMacDonnieMoj although he showed signs of it last year I would still say Baertschi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to tell someone. There's nothing "wrong" with you. There is a way. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy who punched that Nazi prick is more qualified for the presidency than Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When any film franchise gets to the point where there's an equal or greater amount of bad entries to good ones, it's time to pack it in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleading the Fifth, very smart. Or is it? @NancyGrace https://t.co/D6odtGfGnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ I love you and all but why can't you tell me where you were the night JonBenet Ramsay was murdered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New BuzzFeed quiz: Pick a Puppy to Euthanize and We'll Guess Your Favourite 'Big Bang Theory' Character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you remember a single song from La La Land? Apart from City of Stars? No, you don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ they called me to play today but I said no I have to work and honestly please take me off your calling list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My rockin' six-pack and I have long been a champion of alternative facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SadieVadnais not a podcast *per se* but have you seen Head of State? The Chris Rock joint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henrik Sedin -- one half of the greatest ambassadors this city has ever seen, in any field. Congrats on 1,000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Steelers win the Super Bowl Trump and Big Ben will have a lot to talk about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuykeaExec what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillSasso so when are you moving home?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a sense of humour that's always on means being in damage control mode almost constantly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superdeluxe my 9 year old is so over you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Witch (VVitch) is one of the best horror movies of the last like 30 years, no joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuykeaExec you know she's gonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more day of President Obama guys let's drink it in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evening stroll through the woods listening to Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he took this at @LasMargaritasBC https://t.co/0LeEUPgNby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthrax's new record is better than Metallica's. Leaner &amp; meaner with more replay value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before an important interview, it's a good idea to schedule a full body wax, because you never know what might happen. #careertip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuykeaExec too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMacDonnieMoj Eriksson's turned it around a bit but Gudbranson's got to be the most disappointing overall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening a movie review with a quote is pretentious and needs to stop, right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop star Aaliyah would've turned 57 today. Hard to believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that it matters but why isn't it the Kansas City Chieves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that woman who preached to dudes on Tinder the wise words of trailblazing feminist Taylor Swift? Wasn't she terrible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate Green Bay! I also hate Dallas. But my hatred of Green Bay is more pressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Packers win at Dallas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching The Office, and I realized -- we're supposed to relate to Jim and Pam, but they're just terrible people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @ovi8 on career point number 1,000! #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People talk about this rapper and that EDM band(?) at work and I'm like "the new Gorguts album rocks." And they walk away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iDennisCole what the Christ are they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFOXvan babies should only be allowed in the cargo hold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Wild Card weekend sucked. No game closer than 13.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How often do I feel like Michael Fassbender's character in Shame? Oh, man. Not very often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the playoffs started today Winnipeg would be the only Canadian team not going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kristen Stewart was always a talented performer. Always underrated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally swiped right on my cousin. At first it was really awkward but it's better now that we've been on a few dates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all set for Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ARizzo44 love the tee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand why people smile in photos. It's just so presumptuous. What's so great about your life? Why isn't mine better? Help me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My motto? Total commitment to the bit at all times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people get lost in the mountains? Can't they just ... walk down? Like if you're high up, maybe come down a bit? Where people live?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ I did learn it on the streets. On the ghetto, in fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WANTED: A Lady born from Freyja's cloth whom I may squire about town and boast merrily of past battles won. Asians preferred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passion of the Christ was not funny at ALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A single joke may fail, but if three out of ten land, you take that as a win every day of the week #keepjoking #neverstop #helpme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am without words. This is horrible. #RIPCarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ Christmas sucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superdeluxe Fallon should host !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like these Bears!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who? https://t.co/Z2Hvf202WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bucks are probably wishing they could play us every night #Bulls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Metallica at the end of Leper Messiah, someone says something in the background. Who is it? And what are they saying? #askmetallica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We laugh at our American neighbours because at least our narcissistic plutocrat is SEXY! #thatjawtho #notmypm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ not smart at ALL, Cotton!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattsekeres @TSN1040 god... a tie between C and D I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy hell the 'Hawks look heinous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got back from the German Christmas market. This year's theme is "Silent Night, Crystal Night"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loui Eriksson on the Laine own-goal: "beautiful shot. Top-corner. That's how it's done."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think about me when you masticate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your screaming toddler was your own poor choice, so why are the rest of us made to suffer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SABRiiNAOhh nowish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ oh yes there is. Oh yes there is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoldsGym the apostrophe is on the wrong side of the S in "Gold's" https://t.co/Ozk5oAYZRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonFinZ I got two the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportslogosnet any phantom merch for the Stampeders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ieatanddrink I can't remember how shorts work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll find out in January! https://t.co/uoj0pLR8x4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do I want to see Russell Westbrook take out the Warriors in the playoffs? Very much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care about much, but I do strongly believe in public health and education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh YEAH https://t.co/2HhjXYQikl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawks win 5-3 in overtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicBergerIV @superdeluxe but he wanted to be president??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's too emotionally draining to care about everything. Be a cheeky cynical bastard instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all these white folks pretending they ever gave a shit about Leonard Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairedotcomedy well, I hear they found water on Mars...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>