<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what some of the biggest US companies are saying about Donald Trump: https://t.co/R7EIs9erkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@theboysmithy's TED Talk, "Why you should love statistics", is out as a podcast:
https://t.co/rlOK39z6sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinKwong @_Kate_Allen @RobinWigg This is the best recent thing I've seen on when to use pie charts https://t.co/vOLIFJxyRk @theboysmithy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students: last chance! The deadline for the @ftdata summer internship is *today* at 23:59. Apply here: https://t.co/Rf2co7eOEq #ddj #dataviz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chadskelton @FT @chadskelton … and the idea of that page you found is to eventually be a web-based version of this… https://t.co/g2Xjl9feMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chadskelton @FT @chadskelton the greyed-out charts are ones that we have not yet made into reusable D3 templates.… https://t.co/w3p1EmZEKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, don't forget: The deadline for the @ftdata summer internship is *tomorrow*. Apply here: https://t.co/Rf2co7eOEq #ddj #dataviz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…and if you want to build stuff like this, we're hiring a developer https://t.co/ZXg9RD5Zqp and an intern:… https://t.co/UZi1nXjJwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NeilTMcIvor's striking new @ftpodcasts logos have been making their debut with this week's new episodes:… https://t.co/N7bO16KLFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @ftdata team is hiring a newsroom developer. Come talk to @callumlocke or me at #hhldn for more info https://t.co/eJqHtgwcL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dow Jones: a flawed measure but with a rich history #dow20k  https://t.co/RcHfI6N793]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students: only one week left to apply for the @ftdata summer internship. Find us at #hhldn tonight or apply here: https://t.co/Rf2co7eOEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students: only one week left to apply for the @ftdata summer internship #ddj #dataviz https://t.co/Rf2co7eOEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The emergence of the populist right in German elections since 1990— great new @morgenpost data project: https://t.co/JgNFT7a8Pk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to build stories like this one at the @ft? We're hiring. #ddj https://t.co/jt84Ys4UoN https://t.co/If6Pl1sI4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Trump speech annotator: Slick project by @GlynnPhillips, who's on loan to the newsroom from the FT website team… https://t.co/xwEBRxJnRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s inauguration day speech — annotated by @ft reporters https://t.co/Y9xw1HyIAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commuterjoy Change of ownership. Financial News bought FT, kept the brand but used their typography and design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jburnmurdoch @joshspero @JohnMurrayBrown @jburnmurdoch cue JMB and JCB stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jburnmurdoch @joshspero @jburnmurdoch People have also asked for @JohnMurrayBrown when looking for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Join the @ftdata team as a developer in our London newsroom. #ddj #dataviz https://t.co/xD5yxp0P9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job going for a #dataviz developer to work on the Flourish storytelling platform with @k_i_l_n https://t.co/sBjc9uC3ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ft readers can now follow the confirmation process by adding Trump's cabinet nomineees to MyFT: https://t.co/ABLWZ9yIFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT commenter on the immigration skills levy: "A tax on experts. I suppose it has a certain logic to it" https://t.co/ZCgSZaBsf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI, the @ft is hiring a developer for its data journalism / #dataviz team in London. Details here: https://t.co/jt84YrNjxf #ddj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pilhofer @albertocairo @dangillmor To be fair... https://t.co/6o5vgD1tma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're hiring a newsroom developer. Come work with us in the @ftdata team in London! #ddj #dataviz https://t.co/jt84YrNjxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lisaocarroll's coverage of the impact of Brexit on EU citizens in the UK has been excellent. Her latest:… https://t.co/6g8XaawVbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students— interested in quantitative research and a career in journalism? Apply for the @ft internship: https://t.co/YGqSPzXoW6 #qstep #ddj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students! Want to apply your knowledge of maps and #gis to news? We have a summer internship for you at the @FT: https://t.co/YGqSPzXoW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28 hours of recordings for a 17-minute story. How a @planetmoney episode gets made: https://t.co/3MiuhEN2KF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would requiring real names really improve behaviour in online comments? The evidence suggests not. https://t.co/w4GtJwW8Pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students! Interested in data journalism or #dataviz? Apply now for a summer internship at the @ft: https://t.co/YGqSPzXoW6 #ddj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rgdonohue @rgdonohue the beauty of the colour-your-own map is that you can fix this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating talk (in German) on how to discern a news org's Internal structure by scraping &amp; analysing its output:  https://t.co/nY86gUYI1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant, erm, interactive choropleth on this @TheEconomist story about the rise of colouring books. https://t.co/FQ5kpQyMnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news or not: can you tell what is real? https://t.co/9udlPcgEpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This new journalism grad scheme from the Telegraph sounds very impressive— inc training at @columbiajourn: https://t.co/o9mV91a3iX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbradshaw @paulbradshaw … but history of interactive (which you might mean) goes to 2005, as @robminto wrote ab… https://t.co/Ae9Kbr3DL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbradshaw There's officially no such team. It's a loose network of people formally in stats, graphics, interact… https://t.co/FTyZXzPJZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do some people misunderstand about the white working class? @JoanCWilliams  on Alphachat with @CardiffGarcia 
https://t.co/QG47vdxyfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rybina_Alla It's also available in Sweden, and other countries. https://t.co/nC0s6HqWZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What proportion the population is Muslim? People in many countries have no idea. Think you could do better? Quiz:… https://t.co/8wfkOdLpLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesarthur @charlesarthur Without a doubt there will be. @davidcblood and @aendrew have done great work making… https://t.co/qiia66G7aQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the @ft next summer as our @googlenewslab Fellow. #ddj Apply here: https://t.co/9VmMTPOHTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications are now open for the UK @googlenewslab Fellowship, including a place with the @ftdata team: https://t.co/KeKpg4nxPE #ddj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@david_donald was a great friend, teacher and mentor to many of us at the @ft. He will be greatly missed: https://t.co/zrxGzGpv0f #ddj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chart Doctor @theboysmithy shares his wishlist of #dataviz books: https://t.co/A8Qji7UKKb https://t.co/sInTZT1Bdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's #dataviz/#ddj must-read: @stdbrouw's "ode to the bar chart": https://t.co/ArHTWnrgsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's #datviz must-read: @stdbrouw's "ode to the bar chart": https://t.co/hi7ggVDTV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrishanretty all in the same area, so probably just one bad decision to be fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrishanretty and there's more: https://t.co/2tTvWRkJVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrishanretty not the only one today: https://t.co/7tH2Vt2A7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new editorial transparency blog from @zeitonline is a great idea. Explains decisions and corrections in public: https://t.co/kcz2vdjgeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big split in voting by gender and educational level in Austrian presidential election: https://t.co/4tbbRv504e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["56.1% of the UK population live in areas not served by a local daily. Rural areas are particularly poorly served…" https://t.co/KaRhpABCeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Over half of Parliamentary constituencies - 330 out of 650 - are not covered by a dedicated daily local newspaper" https://t.co/T4Dt5qX2zW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another story about that Tweet of a screenshot of a comment left on an @ft story back in August: https://t.co/GWeBA1dMQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@theboysmithy has been thinking about how to visualise uncertainty in official statistics #dataviz #ddj… https://t.co/MlvvAVrDWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student journalist, designer or developer? Want an internship with the @ft #ddj #dataviz team in 2017? Look here: https://t.co/Rf2co7eOEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtophercook Here it is: https://t.co/KhtjTSJA6k Will look for a more systematic fix to this. Thanks! @gadilahav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtophercook Oh, interesting. That's a new type of problem. Will fix. @gadilahav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtophercook Send it to me, and I can fix it within 30 seconds @gadilahav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xtophercook are you sure? have you checked any of the URLs you complained about recently? @gadilahav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gadilahav explains the development of the new @ft website on the Responsive Web Design Podcast: https://t.co/fBuiPVcSxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uedaxecker @TomWGvdMeer thanks; that set of tweets is a very useful critique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Across numerous countries…the percentage of people who say it is 'essential' to live in a democracy has plummeted…" https://t.co/YgrRkOBxBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student interested in news and looking for a #dataviz internship next summer? @ftdata has the thing for you:  https://t.co/8NfTbHSHkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student journalist or designer who is learning to code? Developer interested in journalism? Intern at @ftdata! #ddj  https://t.co/8NfTbHSHkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the first episode of our new emerging markets tech podcast, @billgates and @NandanNilekani
https://t.co/6uT1LZ0sCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jburnmurdoch @mattliddy Interesting case at the moment in Italy, where law imposes a 2-week poll reporting blackout pre-referendum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamjordann @progressivehere @lisacrost It would also highlight the distortion of total votes -&gt; electoral votes by state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dosima_org @williamjordann @MikeGapes @lisacrost Nevada is also very interesting on this point. https://t.co/HDGWNTqUI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williamjordann @progressivehere @lisacrost Might be better to make the the big bar proportional to total votes rather than electoral votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dosima_org @williamjordann @MikeGapes @lisacrost Yes, this approach works nicely at county level too. Here's a qui… https://t.co/Nt0Pf2W5kR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US election, unmapped: really like this proportional stacked bar by @lisacrost: https://t.co/m5EXFsYLVO #dataviz https://t.co/fBHbjnPEtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very nice European parliament cartogram to illustrate a strange counterfactual — what if the EU used the electoral… https://t.co/OyBX37HCmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news site operator from Georgia: “Are there any elections coming up in the U.K.?”  https://t.co/U4YKdZnyDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How UK retail shifted since 2010: great @markvdvd data analysis with #dataviz by @digitalcampbell &amp; @BillyEhrenberg… https://t.co/c9bMdDtCGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High streets' #blackfriday survival fight: great @markvdvd story with viz by @digitalcampbell &amp; @BillyEhrenberg… https://t.co/LGIvN8Ml5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarrieKehoe Having been in @LeilaHaddou's training session on the value of these records today, I see your point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarrieKehoe not this? https://t.co/MQiAEfmFof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As typhoid ravages remote villages in DR Congo, MSF doctors race to save lives. The @ft seasonal appeal:… https://t.co/cQCmj3CxZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #hhldn, we're hiring for a couple of data journalism roles at the @ft. Find me between sessions or at the end to find out more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the BBC parliamentary feed piped to FacebookLive largely for the live emoji reactions floating by Hammond. https://t.co/EatkyjbhFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modern news: Here's a story about a Tweet of a screenshot of a comment on an @FT story… from August. https://t.co/AUgOdLwIIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YemisiOgunleye @viewmagazine @eborgesrey @paulbradshaw I thought this conference was meant to be about local journalism in particular?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sallyeaves The background to this, by @theboysmithy is here: https://t.co/4iEQEStqkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Norwegian news agency NTB automates football match reports: https://t.co/rft4FFPfrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[… here's @nikkei's election results site: https://t.co/hZ0HxLgl7K https://t.co/BVj9jKAth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ftdata's been hosting our colleagues from @nikkei Visual Data this week. They showed us some impressive stuff #ddj https://t.co/369ZiUew8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisapplegate really tricky problem and useful design exercise. Been thinking about it all evening. May blog as 140 chars not enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisapplegate Basic choropleth shows "where". Extrusion attempts to adjusts for population, and I don't think it does that effectively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nicco_Cirone …the thing I object to is interactivity/exploration for its own sake or that abrogates responsibility for explanation/insight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nicco_Cirone I'm not against exploratory viz, even in data journalism. The best examples often combine explanatory and exploratory states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisapplegate height is just as problematic without a common axis. I'd stay away from maps altogether: https://t.co/i9k4eSujy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisapplegate I don't think extrusion solves the choropleth pop density problem. People are even worse at comparing volume than area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickStotz Two years. Midterms :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look, a spinning extruded county-level election choropleth. https://t.co/8WtPQvH60D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data journalist job: come work with us at the @ft #ddj https://t.co/NvROBr2I35]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>