<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh for fucks sake people this is not a game https://t.co/fLlV1GMPe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to only sub 30 degree day in weeks, going to be 30+ for next 7 days... What warming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single mums 'too lazy' to attract and hold a mate: One Nation candidate https://t.co/eJPQk2nQSK - via @abcnews
#DefundOneNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm *DO* something about this before you have more blood on your hands https://t.co/KEL1BqJ7U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looky here @TonyAbbottMHR and his alternative "facts" https://t.co/DF01ihAYCx can't get fresher bullshit from the back of a bull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@venkat_s You only store important information too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK will have to switch entirely to @GuardianAus from @abcnews as the puff pieces and Human Interest Stories take over the news #FuckGuthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what you need @aruizca https://t.co/2eFl6klOdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So crazy that in a democracy blatant corruption is not only contemplated but unsurprising. https://t.co/CMyilIlZQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting @usps it takes 1 day to get my package from LA to SYD but 4+ (and counting) days from SYD to CBR (a 3hr drive). what gives?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aruizca @java @groovylang spock for the win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FFS Barnaby Joyce won't rule out dumping Renewable Energy Target https://t.co/wZ7HJFVwCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ah good latest updates on #fedora25 seem to break lots of things, suspect wayland behind most of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't normally share facebook content, but this: https://t.co/p29x09Pekj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW REPORT: 2016 officially Earth's hottest year on record https://t.co/LYZvYbsbCO #hottestyear #climatechange via @climatecouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes me cynical? This: $1b spent on detention contracts without authorisation, audit finds https://t.co/8YASJpCphp - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@venkat_s is that your wishful thinking ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, I knew my PV's and battery would cause a wide spread power outage in Canberra, sorry. #canberra #storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked memo tells Centrelink staff not to process debt disputes https://t.co/t8tshRmXWX - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines: Stop plans to bring back executions https://t.co/7gO2NTqQL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trello Is Being Acquired By Atlassian https://t.co/JxoWKMJMkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happened when Centrelink called to review my false debt accusation | Michael Griffin https://t.co/QPRzI8RUwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now we have @realDonaldTrump /@TurnbullMalcolm govs there must be a gov conspiracy to make us believe climate change isn't real?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... there is this conspiracy, by big carbon, to make people believe there is a conspiracy to make people believe in climate change ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So *every* time you click a circle notification it *restarts* the app, taking minutes!!! even if the app is open #fail @meetcircle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[got a circle with Disney. The app is abysmally slow and the UI is, to me, un intuitive, and crashes. Apart from that it looks promising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have been used to detect disease before, we're catching up! https://t.co/uTeZuAzw06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please sign the climate emergency petition here https://t.co/QGkvz3aoKN we have to at least try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgdavies @michikokakutani I'm thinking if you're Pope you take that as read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M0les @TurnbullMalcolm @wolfcat so the theme is to use old "cheap" tech, like coal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That'll be a great insurance claim... Massive fur seal squashes car in Tasmanian driveway https://t.co/p4gOKBzp4T - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dethfrmabve @DoctorKarl not with a petrol mower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphene is the new black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haruki_zaemon @SkyNewsAust going all Trump on their ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richieaussie @ChristineMilne I can attest to solar working well on even a small scale, supplement with local wind power and storage...WIN!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale those were not the notifications you are looking for... Move along...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danveloper equivalent to substituting a manager for a web developer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, the LNP are much better at financial management... What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You guys should look up Joh Bjelkie-Peterson https://t.co/0TVH8IijXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cute3, and the puppies are nice too ;-) https://t.co/TB2qukarhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale with current dumbing down of everything and lack of education (everyone must be a tradie, doctor or lawyer) no cyber anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdoch is the evil Sith Lord trying to takeover the world. (Trump is only a deputy)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wilson parking machines in Canberra CRAP!!! just accidentally paid for someone else's ticket. Y U NEED LICENCE PLATE ANYWAY!!! #crappitycrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's fully charged, the eyes are green https://t.co/OLfdPRZgmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[suddenly it looks like we might be a game on a quantum computer ;-) https://t.co/qtvquZbbfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network time/clock inconsistencies maybe? can you rely on the timestamp from twitter? https://t.co/ORpbuuys78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M0les think the tradie from the libs ad during the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg @M0les indeed it's filter coffee, but they've got the right idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the latte sipping tradie (with gold watch and chain). Makita DCM500Z 18V Li-Ion Mobile LXT Coffee Maker https://t.co/3svzKJoiDE #ilikeit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor John Glen. The hope of his time, then dies as Trump comes in, must have wondered what was it all for...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale see, now that's complex English shit right there, but then you have people saying "but than you have people saying"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know English is shit, but, please learn the difference between then and than, it's one of the simpler things. #grumpyoldman #getoffmylawn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[they're short of cash this time of year... https://t.co/mTPsRxo0be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so @OfficeMaxAu schools has no feedback link so... while not the worst online store UX pretty bad. 1 kid at a time, re-enter all details :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure telcos send a command to your smartphone just before Xmas to make it muck up a bit, just as a hint... If not I've got the patent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg so like, dunno, about $400 with mealing them. Reno, somewhere north of $250k with me doing most of the work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale @piersg dude, you just don't get it. I was into vertical stairs before they were popular...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg what, for the stairs, or the whole "Reno"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aruizca floors being sanded and lacquered, we move in next week.. no kitchen sink yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barriecassidy @realDonaldTrump he's already started to grate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["rural, Christian, white American fundamentalists..." https://t.co/FM5GHk8Y46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, phone crashed, changed keyboards, and now thinks I'm  "Scott"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is what is at the bottom of the swap.... BTW swamps are environmentally important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record die-off of coral confirmed by scientists https://t.co/sC1jAY067w - via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bony_rabbit indeed, typing too quick :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Nation -&gt; Wrong Nation 100km off the money...
https://t.co/25GsVPMW8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danveloper ROFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale and self cocktail mixing, w/bed/kitchen/mobile work station.Then they don't even need to get to work, just drive around allday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg yeah, I dunno, try as I might I can't find batshit crazy people when I need them. (oh hang on, I should try the internet!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale it could be more American if the electric cars also had blue lights on them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just donated to @Wikipedia. Support free knowledge! #iloveWikipedia https://t.co/SkwqSSkGfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale if the gov could they would, you have to spin to have a health out come which both reduces cost and raises revenue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it when the morning sunshine gets poured into my (Tesla) battery :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale I suspect this isn't a nanny state thing, it's a this is costing us in health care, so tax to pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astounding how many people do not get the concept of "too much". Yes you can get too much of a good thing. Try too much water, or CO2...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DON'T fact check Trump, you know it's BS and he's misdirecting and wasting your time. Don't report what he says, but what he *does*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale 1: vote for some nutbag. 2: watch world go to hell 3: profit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the newest Guardian member https://t.co/JK6aQReBRg #guardianmembers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh 2016.... WTF?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that cleaver green on #730report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two die in 'thunderstorm asthma' emergency in Melbourne https://t.co/Ywuoq5qWlN via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg I had a pressing need...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making stairs. The laminating begins https://t.co/1Rco9bUF9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah how brown is Malcolm's nose!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't need a new word "post truth" for bullshit #730report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🎶 there'll be time enough for coding when the shaving's done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshbloch @KiahCollier isn't that what the second amendment was for? #ofcourseidontbelievethat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally. https://t.co/TMhGusK7oW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhysam that was the one speech he read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the birth of the Mexican wall https://t.co/6RPnjRUM7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigfis @abcnews @AntonyGreenABC @realDonaldTrump it's not that much better here with Abbott/Turnbull conga line of fwits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersg @michaelneale key ring bottle opener is the workaround]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelneale does chlorine go with beer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting a popular uprising against the IPA who's with me? People against think-tank fronts for pushing agenda's for bastards. #Pattffpafb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dark side of the graph https://t.co/a2WdDGxcXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ffs @730report she's saying TRY to stop these cases going to court. You may TRY but not succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit what just happened? https://t.co/z8CpNVZFWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would a Trump whitehouse look like? Orange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What! @ABCTV axing Catalyst!!! Faaark. Yep dumb down the nation, I blame the LNP directly.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>