<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain technology: how to remove the middle man in online security via @forbes https://t.co/c1ErSSlZsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa! this, in a whole special section of @sciencemagazine on prediction, data science, &amp; behaviour, via @dggoldst https://t.co/MOhdCLhaxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Hurt, so many fantastic movies. This from @guardianfilm: The making of Alien's chestburster scene https://t.co/pxsu890N2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paper w Ivo Vlaev @mollycrockett in CABN: Serotonin (citalopram) enhances impact of health info on food choice https://t.co/Laxax5eagy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Nov, @CBCQuirks w @DavidJuurlink "Your brain on fentanyl", useful primer for 101 addiction, neurotransmitters https://t.co/TNweyzCKpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clever article on luck: “As soon as the player becomes aware of any sort of pseudo-randomness, it undermines the jo… https://t.co/Cg1YZB60re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superstitious Chinese investors jittery as black swan sculpture appears in Beijing financial district https://t.co/xcbmEqa7Gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool: predicting explore vs exploit streaks in supermarket buys from 280k shoppers @DrLoveBC in… https://t.co/mggsp7yGdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Player skill, time pressure &amp; decision complexity in 200 million chess games, w @m_sendhil via @tilmanlesch https://t.co/wANSxehuRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathryn Cunningham talking @DMCBrainHealth neuro this am "Phenotypic &amp; Serotoninergic Targets for Therapeutics in Addictive Disorders"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my psyc 101 class... A behaviourist's guide to New Year's resolutions https://t.co/n9guc8mCkK via @MarkHaselgrove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @RuthJvanHolst I was hoping to do sobp but have a dates clash - how about HBM in Vancouver?? @neuro_tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new paper: cravings &amp; insula resp in problem gambling @neuro_tweet @stevesharman81 @ArtScienceDoc… https://t.co/jKW1PharOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female binge drinkers unfairly stigmatised by media, says study https://t.co/oFFAIue5u7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool @freakonomics podcast Why Are We Still Using Cash? feat 'reverse money laundering' https://t.co/YkHcUZ5Qo6 HT @neuro_tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E_Anahata @yinwu0407 that's a terrible sentence, but is your prob w the research or the press release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PFC theta stim modulates EEG resp to sexual rewards, imps for impulse control, w @marcoiacoboni via @SSA_Addiction https://t.co/ofOFP6bEsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Q&amp;A including modern slot machines, online gambling, neuroscience, gambling policy... feat. @smurchy… https://t.co/Bn56PbKLWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting weird: lower stakes on FOBTs or increase jackpots on grabbers! Via @vicrgf https://t.co/PNlPXp9hdS via @ThisIsMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paper Baskin-Sommers &amp; Buckholtz on regret counterfactual learning in psychopathy, in @PNASNews via @yinwu0407 https://t.co/YFLOvYn1JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day of term, big shout-out to my Psyc335 class for a term's worth of great, engaged questions on Gambling &amp; Decision-Making @UBCPsych]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @chuckkeeling1 &amp; thanks @BCGIA1 for inviting me - lots of great discussion and I appreciate your interest in @CGR_UBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent afternoon finalizing @CGR_UBC newsletter to take to talk to @BCGIA1 tomorrow... and left the copies on the printer, grrrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbloomatyale Agreed. On Cam Gamble Task, in 90% condn many Ps choose 10% option &gt;once. "Seriously- u think it's going to land THERE?!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thread by some people who haven't heard of Herrnstein's matching law (1961) https://t.co/XTAOo1HVyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @jtobiaswebb from @CGR_UBC for PhD submission "Relationships between gambling &amp; alcohol use: a cognitive perspective" ! @CambPsych]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many things I love about the 70s... golden age of cinema... p'raps not Cauliflower Surprise "70s Dinner Party food" https://t.co/IEkIayLtDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[clever qual study on alcohol intoxication &amp; social media use in young women, by @profhrs @pbhaatki in @ijdrugpolicy https://t.co/8COJGGKwFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontal connectivity predicts placebo effect in knee pain patients, Apkarian &amp; Baliki new paper in @PLOSBiology https://t.co/MnN2bYJq2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My undergrad class now bringing funky stuff like this to my attention: @Morewedge Man Sci ms on 'emotional hedging' https://t.co/OV6QlVSS5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pause in the rain @UBCPsych Cognitive Retreat in Squamish, great ideas &amp; discussion @CGR_UBC @smurchy @neuro_tweet https://t.co/gJlYSlTe6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wetherby1919 @smurchy @neuro_tweet that's why we focus on EGM features. But individuals still need help, &amp; there r individual risk factors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wetherby1919 @smurchy @neuro_tweet policy makers need to be able to separate opinion from knowledge. Much of Ka-Ching was opinion (sorry!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wetherby1919 @smurchy @neuro_tweet well I agree the machines are dangerous, but we don't understand how, or what can be done about them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Constructive peer-review relies on being devoid of jealousy" - primer for grads, pdocs by @belin_david &amp; Karadottir https://t.co/0VoCjIPOyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wetherby1919 @smurchy @neuro_tweet Yes, I have, but is Ka-Ching old hat or new hat? Has Australia solved the whole dilemma over pokies now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trial of new vasopressin drug for alcohol use disorders - promising in Ps with high stress, smokers @NIAAAnews https://t.co/EIgYTndeoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI, Hyde &amp; Perlis study in @NatureGenet: Large DNA study using 23andMe data finds 15 sites linked to depression https://t.co/Jm0s4agiHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@left_hemisphere is this neurosci's 1st quintuple dissociation @dr_stan?? I recall @Timothy_Bussey nailing a triple dissn, u've raised him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the @r2rnow team did a great job on our research on slot machine gambling &amp; addiction, feat @smurchy &amp; @neuro_tweet https://t.co/dnobZiEslj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulPcf22 @PhilCorlett1 sound like choice cuts! Our discussion was if addiction was inherently drug-related until eg 1980s. Whaddya think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Robert Palmer's Addicted to Love reflect a change in popular usage of the term "addiction" in the 20th century… https://t.co/mihmuECfZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aside from the whole striatal fmri = dopamine =
addictive, this IS a neat result https://t.co/o8eV8Lq7Gg #Wormhole via @Mark_A_Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFCamerer well, it's tv. I thought it conveyed the power of fmri (eg bet vs spin), but glad I didn't have to make sense of all those blobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain responses in a single case (@GamblingHurts) to electronic (FOBT) roulette: bet, spin, outcome @ProfDavidNutt https://t.co/G2tPsCfut4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline for the @UBCPsych hire in Cognitive Science (also hires in Clinical &amp; Health) is 1 Oct - come join us! https://t.co/bfQV4Szcmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrGBuckingham I had hoped for so much more, it just sounds like Fluttering Kite to me. But Chris does look quite menacing in the still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grant &amp; Chamberlain 2016: ICD-11 set to diverge from DSM5 in classifying "behavioural addictions" https://t.co/UFJFRDnTBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @UBCPsych course Gambling &amp; Decision-Making starts Wed: cog psych | neuro | addiction | public health https://t.co/zzZN6RFjXW @CGR_UBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asymmetry in confirmatory bias: new ms on climate change by @CassSunstein Tali Sharot @affectivebrain MT @davenuss79 https://t.co/BHpkzKtFyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psych / neuro labs, @CGR_UBC switched from email to #Slack for internal comms, here's why: 22 Handy Slack Hacks https://t.co/vdTmG2lWb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trading experience reduces endowment effect, regulated by insula: nice summary of Tong ms @PNASnews @UChi_Economics https://t.co/zdXnIKaX8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALE metaanalysis of 176 fMRI expts shows shared brain response in caudate/ ACC/ insula to drug &amp; natural reward cues https://t.co/6Frhzuaz4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[link to SCAN paper here https://t.co/rRKo9hI6Su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subjective feelings on #gambling decisions predict choice / loss aversion over &amp; above EV @caro_charp @jonroiser https://t.co/RUBwBIyMxn 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional faces prime loss aversion in low-anxious, linked to amyg-striatum conn, @caro_charp @jonroiser in SCAN 2/3 https://t.co/fq5AsxUer5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressed by 2 funky recent studies on psychological basis of Prospect Theory by @caro_charp @jonroiser at @UCL_ICN @affectivebrain 1/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@neuro_tweet 's talk at #SNE2016 "Behav &amp; neural correlates of gambler's fallacy in Gambling Disorder" Tues pm @SocforNeuroecon @CGR_UBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakthrough understanding links betw immune system &amp; depression w Ed Bullmore @psychiatry_ucam &amp; @ParianteSPILab https://t.co/DZ7oK3n1QB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crespi awarded SFU prize for theory that autism &amp; schizophrenia due to struggle betw parent's genes MT @BCPsychosis https://t.co/Rh4uHUSu63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pupil dilation to monetary incentives linked w apathy in Parkinson's | new paper in @Brain1878 by @MasudHusain lab https://t.co/pvTX8EpdhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zorroesque of course the insula also play key roles in crime, and punishment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesharman81 @DrMarkGriffiths surely Beckham example is upward not downward cft: regret, alternative better than reality? (like silver)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Olympic training/treatment devices are evidence-based? Very few says @CaulfieldTim Olympic debunk! : https://t.co/hvXdqiqXOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best media quote by an academic? "mate, if you don't eat soon, shit's about to go down" @zane_andrews1 https://t.co/LBiZjLlhFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If addiction is a learned response, then can it be unlearned? by Marc Lewis https://t.co/BdJvUjovFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V amusing Flight of the Conchords @fotc on child's mental representation of money (from 6:15) https://t.co/67QwBA9wV6 via @claudiahammond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats &amp; lovely figs tricky for this paper, big shout out to our statto mentors @neuro_tweet &amp; @mrfaitkendeakin https://t.co/7E9JkglFYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herzog on Pokemon Go: "When 2 persons in search of a pokémon clash at  Sunset and San Vicente is there violence?" https://t.co/fxLy94epMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confidence only predicts illusory control decisions when taking control costs money... Our new paper w @jtobiaswebb https://t.co/I0UT5FvDii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new paper on illusory control &amp; sense of agency in QJEP @jtobiaswebb @mrfaitkendeakin @NeuroCog @clairegillanTCD https://t.co/4nlYQbHBzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Additive effects of alcohol &amp; negative mood induction on cravings: new paper from Cyders https://t.co/NiNijqSp8V @jtobiaswebb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sensible look at difficulty separating excessive use vs addiction to smartphones "Hooked on handsets" via @BMH_Lab https://t.co/lGbingRInT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American undergrads are too WEIRD to stand for all humanity
 – https://t.co/cFgCOGVvw8 HT @mvugt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pnewall is that your thesis opener? Nice quote and congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pnewall hmm, Bernoulli generally credited w concave curve for gains - did he also know about loss aversion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out there was a good reason why @Allen_Institute showed mice Touch of Evil specifically https://t.co/GqFujvjOmB via @danielmabuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never met a Korbinian... Glasser &amp; vanEssen's multimodal imaging study uses machine learning to find 180 areas https://t.co/p9vdQ898Av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article on poss benefits of Pokémon Go on mental health, @kashmiragander w @ProfDFreeman @soozaphone https://t.co/hutvmWBGEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In London homeless, awareness of gambling tx services sig lower than services for drugs &amp; alcohol: @stevesharman81 https://t.co/fUkNdoI5Fp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pathways betw gambling and homelessness: 14 of 17 PGs experienced gambling probs b4 homelessness @stevesharman81 https://t.co/fUkNdoqugP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New study w @stevesharman81 @ArtScienceDoc confirms high prob gambling in London homeless https://t.co/fUkNdoqugP https://t.co/24nlAr8g9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physiological responses to near-misses on a Wheel of Fortune predict gambling problems: new from @Nat_A_Ul &amp; Hewig https://t.co/FwyqnbXR3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DocHosking yeah I liked it &amp; lot of clever nods to other Leonard stuff... Still not as good as JB but will put more soderbergh on my list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun list: having to rewatch Out of Sight as there's no way it can be better than Jackie Brown. Elmore Leonard Movies https://t.co/3miqWChGt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Am I going to check every statistic?" 9 point guide to spotting dodgy stats by @d_spiegel  https://t.co/8dV6XMz4aJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multimodal imaging in 1171 dementia cases shows blood flow &amp; cog early predictors of progression, in @NatureComms https://t.co/Kc7a9dMNe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given @R_Thaler comment in #misbehaving that scientists do their best work b4 40, I'm busting my chops to write 5 papers in 4 days #gameover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major methods review of difficulty separating "liking" &amp; "wanting" in humans, Pool &amp; Sander in NBBR @NCCRAffective https://t.co/3PlytMfRPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesharman81 crack cocaine check?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pun titles not associated with success" - the hours wasted! @mrfaitkendeakin @neuro_tweet @smurchy @jtobiaswebb https://t.co/VHhC4nhXzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funky new opto study in @NatureComms challenges dopamine D1 - D2 opponency for motivation https://t.co/muR8tFn4Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personalized medicine in the addictions: great chaps by LeFoll, Heilig &amp; Leggio in Progress in Brain Res new volume https://t.co/du6nWIzP9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which cog domains most relevant to addictions? Exec func, incentive salience, neg emotionality Kwako in @SOBP https://t.co/7ljxyuh2hx #RDoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effects of naltrexone on fMRI cue reactivity in methamphetamine users: connectivity changes w craving Courtney &amp; Ray https://t.co/z76Boda9Dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wondered why the media run so many stories about lottery winners?! w @DunnHappyLab @DanTGilbert https://t.co/q50Tq8uUhV @MaryseZeidler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Living_Lab hi, I have a beautiful live edge mirror from your store as a house warming present- what kind of wood are they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UBCPsych are hiring 3 x Assistant Profs across Cognitive, Clinical &amp; Health - come join us! https://t.co/5GK7CB6uSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zorroesque @stevesharman81 @SeanCowlishaw are you grumpy bear about something, @drgjdcam ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substituting gambling for Hearthstone - many interesting obs in candid 1st person account via @theNCRG https://t.co/G6xJVocNoE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>