<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tammy Abraham, Izzy Brown &amp; Kasey Palmer ripping up the Championship. PL loans or 1st team players next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yeah I know it's 2001*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irrelevant club trying to make headlines.
Lampard supposedly taking the piss in the airport in 2011 is still trigge… https://t.co/aWlqa626QO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father &amp; Son finally reunited.
Don't give up @Memphis you might find him some day https://t.co/OjTaT9UPT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic Pic To End This Thread. https://t.co/XgCS3y1hzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ThankYouSuperFrank for Everything.
Greatest Ever Chelsea Player.
We Love You Too💙💙💙 https://t.co/yrabTgaI9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOW THE.... WHAT THE.... WTF.... WTF....
(Garry Neville Goal-Gasm Worthy) https://t.co/mdGFmGmnrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spin &amp; shot against Bayern, AMAZING https://t.co/ewWzB9ZcNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous back-heel assist https://t.co/kIZdNOVFSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for some Magic now

Lobbing 6 players &amp; the GK with his weak foot https://t.co/Z56zzh213a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another beautiful flick assist https://t.co/w1xAn1rmyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delicate flick with his left foot to create a goal https://t.co/RVAVOZGx8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just seeing the pass but being able to pull it off too. Great Assist https://t.co/NcaFfA9VWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's some vision to show you how complete of a CM he was https://t.co/UJGk72CHx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not once but twice against Fulham https://t.co/NAbQeZBxja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That technique to always get it to land before the GK made it unstoppable https://t.co/SUrgUxtBwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devastating with a Dead Ball too

Destroying Spurs at Wembly https://t.co/bgVVci3JR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Precision strike against Everton https://t.co/OE2bnYMKJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next for some thunderbolts from the Main Man

Smashing one in against Newcastle https://t.co/SGkU1FGPCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamps Best Moments

Breaking the goals record for @ChelseaFC against Villa with a trademark late run into the box a… https://t.co/swLI7reQZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best PL CM of all time
Top 5 Goals &amp; Assists in PL history
Complete midfielder
#NeverBeforeNeverAgain
#LEGEND… https://t.co/rAXkDhp4GA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City's front 3 look electric without Aguero &amp; they're 22, 21 &amp; 19. Thank god they're mid, def &amp; GK are so shit that it holds them back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on West Ham, need a Utd v City scrap for 5th place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bertrand Traore v Mo Salah in the AFCON semi's rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol, debating over how poor our performances vs rivals have been triggered him hard.
Too many yer da's on here, SMH https://t.co/YMsq9RaEH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanovic was always reliable up &amp; down the right, popped up with big goals in big games. Chelsea LEGEND… https://t.co/1ueYuOffQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luizesque yep the goal too. Attacking between Azpi &amp; Moses. Might need to put Zouma RCB &amp; Azpi LCB, Alonso more defensive help with crosses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luizesque tactics feed into the players &amp; that all just sat back, forget the pen. Even after they equalized we should've won comfortably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDeller1 nowhere I mention of us winning every game by 10-0 or even questioning results. I mentioned performances, quite average]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luizesque ridiculous that they can't see with a few tactical changes would've rip part Liverpool tonight

But we got a point at Anfield!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Luizesque going back &amp; forth with 1 rn, telling me to take a break cauz I said we were shit against all our rivals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDeller1 by playing Cesc in a 3 to counter their press, Hazard closer to Costa &amp; not chasing clyne back, Pedro instead of Willian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDeller1 I get what you're saying, we're leading, got a good point tonight &amp; at other rivals but we could've made it so much easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to sit back &amp; relax with some AFTV https://t.co/hK8Ze9iXRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDeller1 how can you be happy with out performances against Liverpool, Tottenham &amp; City. Yes got a few points but we were really poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDeller1 it doesn't say I'm not happy about the result, it's the continuous shit performances against rivals I'm more worried about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cesc doesn't have to track back, Moses RM, Pedro LM, Kante &amp; Matic sit to protect the back 3. Great balance in both attack &amp; defence 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[them to create as they need win the ball back &amp; roll it to Cesc who can create. Hazard with Costa gives freedom to play off each other 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How may more dross performance does Conte needs to see to understand Cesc has to play ahead of Kante-Matic which takes pressure off 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down bid 40M+ for Dembele you retarded cunts @ChelseaFC push Tammy next season https://t.co/aaJfuNZxXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a bad TBH Arsenal Lost, Liverpool &amp; Tottenham drew so the gap stays as it is, Perfect day but we should've won this easily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kante easily MOTM, stopped so many counters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the cunts that wonder why Kante plays, immense pressing from the African midget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck it get Zouma or Chalobah on take the Fucking draw, we should've won this comfortably shit decisions making by Conte today TBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS Antonio play this formation &amp; team but with Hazard instead of Pedro in that SS role. Fuck your Workhorses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Fuck has Klopp been allowed to scream in the 4th officials face @FA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cesc for Willian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS that was such a shit pen &amp; Willian hits the 1st man again. Time to die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking get in, Costa pen please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF Antonio, play Hazard behind Costa in a free role 3-5-2 he's not a workhorse FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immense pressing from Kante in the last minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pedro or Cesc for Willian please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tammy still scoring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCK OFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmino bottled that. TBH he's probably on the bottle anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what Matic does you tactically incompetent Fuck boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cesc fan boys ripping Matic again Conte's plan is to sit &amp; counter &amp; it's working we all want Cesc but Matic's shielding the back 3 well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie G crying at HT about the freekick that led to the goal https://t.co/7TEFmrYnf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mane might've hurt himself getting warmed up. https://t.co/LCS54zwLOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btsportfootball how about some impartiality in your commentary. Stop licking Liverpool's arse, you shit cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That killed the crowd quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David "SideShow" Luiz
Bleeds Blue🚹
Heart On His Sleeve💙
Captain Status Needed🇨
Best CB in the PL💪
We Love You Too G… https://t.co/bVDH1nYm5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lool Arsenal 2-0 down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little early than I expected but time to mute the pro-Liverpool commentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS Antonio, sit back &amp; counter then. It's gonna be like City away but Liverpool will stop that with their pressing… https://t.co/DHrE9epMT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scenes when we beat Liverpool tonight &amp; Emenalo pulls A Rabbit out the Hat with Belloti in a Chelsea shirt or news… https://t.co/LirrTtlUhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaFC Biabiany being a Serie A cunt means we don't know if it's Emenalo or Conte. One likes to penny pinch other likes workshorses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know what's worse being rejected by the Djilobodji of attackers or actually going for him in the 1st place
Fucking Disgrace @ChelseaFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol we're being linked with the Djilobodji of attackers https://t.co/zckdr0SlFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wolves then, @chalobah to pocket Helder Costa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aids on the TL.
15yr old kids who never saw prime JT, Lamps &amp; Cech aren't legends but Ivanovic is cauz he popped up… https://t.co/HWUyNta5ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, this has been one dead-ass transfer window.
Fucking do something @ChelseaFC https://t.co/0Qou85IpuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck You Palm Tree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Grigg Time🔥🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/7IlN4vTqOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability should be quality, Lomachenko's movement is unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability soz my bad read that wrong, but still want everything I tweeted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability nah he's a Jr lightweight, Truman v Garcia, want Garcia v Brook. Did you mean Lomachenko v Mikey Garcia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability son of a legend, that's all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[115-113 Santa Cruz, 1-1 then. A 3rd at the Aviva Stadium please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7-4 Cruz, Carl needs a KO in the last round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6-4 Cruz, Carl needs the last 2 Rds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz second wind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4-4 Carl back in it, Santa Cruz looks gassed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability yep using his reach well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costability I gave 5th to Cruz &amp; 6th to Carl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-0 Santa Cruz, Carl looks lost needs to get in close &amp; bang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton Cruz picking up where they left off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG Mikey Garcia with a brutal KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mane missing the pen for Senegal in a shootout, another L for Liverpool

But he might be back to face us on Tuesday, so we're fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Southampton, KO another Cunty team out the cup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make that 1 in 9 after Tuesday, Klopp on the ropes https://t.co/OwY82sLlsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who believe Begovic is quality,  this was his 1st clean sheet this season &amp; he's only played in cup games against weaker opposition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really good performance by the squad today, 3-5-2 on Tuesday please Tony mate. Need Cesc to counter their press &amp; create for Costa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Fucking cunts https://t.co/1KW1xs4N3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put Akinfenwa in goal @wwfcofficial 
Just Hold On Lads, Hold On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seamless transitions from Ake not just to understand Conte's system but also going from LWB to LCB. Plz Antonio Ake, Luiz, Azpi vs Liverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michy taking responsibility with the pen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People hating on Michy. Willian &amp; RLC won't create for him. Never played with Eden &amp; Pedro around him, literally trying to do it by himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtois laughing at Costa struggling to find his top 😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatass with a goodbye goal #ThankYouBaranna]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>