<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Bill English is too casual ... running scared ... unable to handle the Trump issue." Patrick Gower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Creep, groper, psychopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm still open to the idea of Robert De Niro punching Trump in the face. https://t.co/oEBx8GONZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mocks people moved to tears. Incredible. https://t.co/C6YKbuekWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've heard of shitposting? That's something different. https://t.co/uGAWafDuAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyByrt @edmuzik The Trudeauvian People's Front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf Biggest thing to hit Taihape since gumboot throwing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyByrt @edmuzik You probably want to visit the US at some point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik I'm a similar idiot. I remember hearing all that stuff about checks and balances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CherylBernstein My brother went to that school and told horror stories about what happened to third-formers but I'm sure it's all changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack @beckeleven Your tweet was in Slovenian. You know who else speaks Slovenian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack @beckeleven Mosh pit at the NZSO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz The end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirLeslie Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CherylBernstein Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @SundaymagSST Must watch it again. My memory is it wouldn't even make my top five Mick Jagger or Emilio Estevez films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been shite since Tom Baker went anyway. https://t.co/oEMkO93Pgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WINONA FOREVER. https://t.co/ElmURmbpIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only Trump had read failing, losing, dishonest media magazine Vanity Fair ... https://t.co/MpYS0JcuxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Just think: what would Crean do? That's the test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Jandals are probably okay, but not pyjamas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American nightmare is back. We're going to create an environment for minorities like the world hasn't seen in s… https://t.co/C3SUxwckpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS I'm hoping some people in my bubble can see through the walls of the bubble to the world outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleDChurch I guess public opinion. I think you're right about moral misjudgment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjkmorris Name and shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Bill English misjudged the Trump ban or am I in a Twitter bubble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is a probable impending major crisis with North Korea – probably graver than anything in the Middle East." https://t.co/hCsVfFl9g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDUBreakfast I liked Audrey Young's description of him having all the urgency of a teenager with a tea towel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having seen THE EXORCIST, maybe this isn't so bad ... https://t.co/lZm6ilF6jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizenBomber It will be interesting to see. I'm less sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams But Cabaret Voltaire did say "Do right, always work, go to church, Respect authority."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this talk about "social investment", which he seems unable to communicate to the public. Surely he's temporary again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They talked about how much English has developed since 2002. But he looks like the same blank, ineffectual person we saw then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of those commentators who talked about Bill English's competence, intelligence, smarts, charm -- which we've seen none of so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a comfy spot on the fence. https://t.co/1w1q717rFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Crampton: Doing good, and  doing well as a consequence https://t.co/yMriJobCki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of us haven't evolved much since. https://t.co/U498vEn3OX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickCrewdson And nasty women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five year old bad dudes are peddling terror. https://t.co/TZWX2yZ9bH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget it Jake, it's Chachitown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frog of war. https://t.co/Z0VCcIHZz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Donnie Loves Chachi series is getting pretty dark. https://t.co/iiLmf1RsAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonathanKing @AJemaineClement We need the Fonz to mediate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they say poets never make the news (unless they're Colin Craig). https://t.co/jCsTXVSN5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorkPieMovie yes, reboot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure Winona was ready for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorkPieMovie Cheers, look forward to seeing the remake soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English criticises Donald Trump's Muslim ban as 'not the New Zealand way' https://t.co/aJEybloBVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go for second best. https://t.co/V8aT1pugqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know @ChristchurchLib has Mark Fisher's Ghosts of My Life. https://t.co/PjDWqz6q7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajhill_alan @PorkPieMovie @NZStuffEnt Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which I ask if GOODBYE PORK PIE was worth remaking as @PorkPieMovie. https://t.co/JhxgDcQ2uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven No, not the Spam .....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for your nightmares, @beckeleven. https://t.co/nm5xjk89cL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmnicholls When I interviewed him, he scoffed at method acting: "How should you prepare to play Caligula? Should you eat a foetus?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pno_nwa @SteveBraunias It's gone clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CnrJoe I've never watched that film. I've seen clips over the years but never the whole thing (similarly, I CLAUDIUS).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He could out-act everyone else wearing a bag on his head. Also: as Winston Smith and ageing blood-junkie Christophe… https://t.co/MUc8sTVKev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet there's a lot of soul-searching and deep-thinking going on for @pmbillenglish this morning.
Was @PorkPieMovie better than original?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's @SundaymagSST featured a kind of old-school Listener reunion: stories by me and Bianca Zander on PORK P… https://t.co/zTDjWX480A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kjrothwell @rachaelking70 Wait until Post-Cab press conference, about 4pm. He was observing Auckl holiday by not going on Morning Report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsrosieb @MacFinlay @pmbillenglish I'd like him to opinion about global issues man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has @pmbillenglish said anything about the Muslim ban?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a piece on GOODBYE PORK PIE and the old weird New Zealand in today's @SundaymagSST. Not online yet; print exclusive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would take too long to list all the films John Hurt was great in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt. I met him once, for an interview in the mid 90s. Utterly hilarious but he was really just charming the photographer. RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @PressNewsroom week in review: Trump, Orwell, marches, Ratana, Helen Clark. https://t.co/AkeoBWGvi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editorial in the @PressNewsroom on Trump, truth and journalism. https://t.co/dg0tLIznbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My interview with Gareth Morgan in the paper this morning. https://t.co/Y5Ji4gVY4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grenow Thanks for the nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to have a weekend without thinking of Donald Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you remember Test Dept's "F---Head" from the 80s, this is a suitably intense update. https://t.co/8XoBRCsBaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @fancylettuce "Donald Trump Has Balls" is not a good slogan if you're hoping for more women to show up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Pork Pie reboot looks better than they say. https://t.co/LalpLv4Guh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHubbard33 You should have put quotes around that sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven Without being Gareth Morgan, people feeding strays are the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that Sean Spicer is an IDM fan who tweets Autechre song titles. https://t.co/ek6ECW6uyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC says Trump claimed 2 were shot dead in Chicago during Obama’s speech. But it never happened. https://t.co/TePmT8XpGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJVita I'm too OCD to ever have just part of a song on one side of a tape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pr0gger @SmithiesGrant 
Like this, you mean? https://t.co/rzl7D2ERQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithiesGrant Holy crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oharris69 @publicaddress @dubber Kids these days have no idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home-taping memories: when you had to add up the times of songs in your head to see if you could squeeze an album o… https://t.co/3ZgpXCGSlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pr0gger @ChoiceBros Must try one sometime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSlack @robhosking Beer hall putz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@redroomrantings "Thank You" by Alanis Morissette is a magnificent song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking "Always drinking in the same bar".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not the side effects of the cocaine. I'm thinking that it must be lager." (Not actually one of the names, as far as I know.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Wellington bar where the beers are named for David Bowie songs. eg "Strung Out On Lasers, Raspberry &amp; Lime" https://t.co/U9YA1Yj6gH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brgibson11 She was on a Mission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goth banned from cemetery. https://t.co/BuJLutgco9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @mizjwilliams @cjsbishop @popbitch That is good. I was trying to do something with "red right hand".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russell_Baillie I've really enjoyed your reviews over the years Russell, even when you've been wrong, which isn't often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good analysis from @EricCrampton. How much of the Thiel kerfuffle is motivated by Trump hatred? https://t.co/WH2SxIucnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that he backed Hulk Hogan is good enough for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's worth subscribing to this podcast. https://t.co/i5EFmUas38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomInvisible I liked that too. I'm glad he's getting his moment again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best photo of a nun riding a bike in front of anarchist graffiti you will ever see. https://t.co/o3yTKatBul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To prepare for Shyamalan's SPLIT, I watched THE VISIT (2015) last night. An overlooked, small horror film with a terrifying central idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're only supposed to blow the bloody doors off. https://t.co/IHRV9pyWMO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>