<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[THANK YOU FOR WRITING.!! https://t.co/Y5Mw1prxz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True. The BC NDP can destroy itself without any help. https://t.co/35phsBxkWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick @IsaacRHolloway And which switchers. Red-blue or orange-blue? Or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsaacRHolloway @awudrick That'd be my worry. Or straight up breakaway movement. It's a tricky tent to keep up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's right: O'Leary can't even carry his own home. https://t.co/MnluFa5gq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catelli_NQU @awudrick Yeah, he's so good on some things. Then a head scratcher. CC: Ahem...Elizabeth May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmbutts Yeah, true. But the game was Civ 6. So, it counts as research. (In case my supervisor asks.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick Totally. O'Toole had some good moments, too (at least tonight).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick @paulisci Because he forgot how to count.

(Mostly kidding.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick Totally agree. It's nice to see a range of ideological types in the race, though. Healthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulisci @awudrick (with fewer votes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick Yeah, true. As a social scientist, I'd like to run 14 different elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smsaideman @arnonmishkin @VP I'll put $100 on over and I'll give good odds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick Totally. But I also think Chong could get at LPC support in a way others couldn't. Could be dangerous. If he keeps party united.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick I'd like to see this whittled down Bernier, Raitt, Chong, Scheer, and O'Toole...let them really get into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awudrick *Points to himself*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my defense, I was playing video games while watching. https://t.co/GDf58DqBfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heradasha every time I do that (by accident) I feel the exact same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. And Chong remains too beautiful for this world. https://t.co/ZgtPEpUt2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, I can't wait to see how the motivated reasoners who support Trump spin this one inside their heads. https://t.co/8vibEaPVmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heradasha Tough talk, but real talk. I'll close 40 of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee @TaylorVaisey Which made me think of this episode: "My name is Toby Ziegler. I work at the White House."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee @TaylorVaisey And here I am in Vancouver, like a sucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heradasha But...but...I made bourbon bread that one time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee @TheOfficePubTO Top-five episode. 

"Protuberance."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Browser tabs are either the best or worst thing that ever happened to me. I'll let you know which when I'm done opening hundreds of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee @TheOfficePubTO What if I'm busy leaf-peeping?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee @TheOfficePubTO I want to come to this so, so, so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't speak for UBC but I'll be advocating for a hard pass on that one. https://t.co/Ui2lbqmavu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the #CPCLdr moderator just speak in iambic pentameter for a second?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It puts the lotion on its skin, or else it doesn't get tax points transferred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think Erin O'Toole understands 'The Silence of the Lambs'. #CPCLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemieux: Money is spent in the economy. 

Thanks, you giant donkey. #CPCLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to Blaney: The opposite of a federation isn't a dictatorship, it's a unitary state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@journo_dale @kady Can we go back to the carbon tax?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Kellie Leitch is a surgeon? It's a good thing she let us know, finally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me, or is Peterson a sexist? #CPCLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are serious candidates: Chong, Scheer, Raitt, Bernier, O'Toole. The rest are a distraction and/or a joke. #CPCLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #CPCLdr debate is awful. Folks, figure it out, get down to a few serious candidates, and get serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Raitt panders like a pro after Alexander says silly things and then Obrhai makes a funny and I'm done with this debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again: O'Leary is unfit to lead. He isn't a serious politician. He's a walking advertisement of a human. He's empty. https://t.co/tZAyccnGy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marvin_Beatty I try to. But then I don't go too deep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marvin_Beatty Not anymore. Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BruinsRocknRule Info Wars isn't exactly a reliable source.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UrbanSlowLife @jonathanmcleod @StevenBlaneyPCC Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go ahead. Do it. Prove it to me. https://t.co/pC6Vk8jhTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, as now, ideology and philosophy mattered. But don't forget that politics and money are always at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevindueck65 What if Ernie is...all of us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very smart (long) read about how Nazi Germany operated -- it puts politics and economics front and centre. https://t.co/OCunwNTF2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heradasha Well now that's all I see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivated reasoning is often troubling -- but Bannon's mistaken commitment to this thesis is seriously troubling: https://t.co/b8WYoxJUB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question for @StevenBlaneyPCC: Why would I know Ernie? There are 36 million people in Canada. The country i… https://t.co/MLDpwWhiBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arpiem11 @bryanjack But you can both read those emails (and critique Clinton, Podesta, et al.) and still oppose DJT. It's not a binary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@journo_dale I was just about to rewatch Best of Enemies. But now I'm rewatching this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmMacfarlane @ElizabethMay It's the sort of thing that makes me want to walk away from being an advocate of PR. So lazy and so cynical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seceedercat Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithjs Oh, damn. Now I have to watch that all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithjs That's all I ever do. But I'm mostly a utilitarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithjs Totally. And when it happens to support an electoral system you prefer...🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thevinetwayway Looking like that more and more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be lazy. Don't be sloppy. Don't be craven. Don't be cynically opportunistic. We're living in serious times. Be serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a supporter of PR. But as long as supporters are using desparate, half-baked arguments and tactics, PR is a hopeless cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why share it? And it looks like an endorsement when you're a huge supporter of PR. https://t.co/aJefPf5vgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece is lazy and wrong. Shame on you for sharing it. If you think the electoral system changes this, look at… https://t.co/lTR4kiDroF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's worse than if she had a White House title. https://t.co/NO00fMT1dk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey man. We all had a talk. We decided it's cool if you just take the weekend off. Or a few weeks. Or if you just q… https://t.co/Jh6LRdNfCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, you're broken. Also, who watches TV with ads these days? https://t.co/lwYLayse27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srwhd Finally, a reprieve. But now just watching to see what's next...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@polisisti Oh? It was in reference to him attacking Maclean's and folks who'd just lost their job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RatFreeAlberta @BRusselsghost Oh, so much tonsay in response! (Both.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rymkrs That dude is the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bcbluecon Also, last message to you for tonight -- you're trolling, but if you want to do this, it'll be you who ends up blocking me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RatFreeAlberta Not even close! Hahaha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, you're a real champion of freedom of speech, huh? So much so that you're cheering for a magazine to fail? https://t.co/rW5mV8sMD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AvalonCarolAnne All the bourbon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieSweeney_1 @Arpiem11 So it's about reach? Also, fake news doesn't mean what a lot of people think it does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRusselsghost Exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious journalists and staff just lost their jobs. Human beings. And this blogger has this to say. Shame on you, m… https://t.co/vcxe1hZmJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I would have got away with it, too! But you caught me, Eyes Open. You might say, you really...opened my eyes.… https://t.co/0Uei0OKTuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieSweeney_1 @Arpiem11 But Breitbart and Info Wars? They're worse. By far. They're a different beast all together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arpiem11 @KatieSweeney_1 The interview was about Trump &amp; it was short. Plus Trump was elected and Clinton wasn't. My focus is on the winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arpiem11 @KatieSweeney_1 Yeah. I put a lot of responsibility for that on the Clinton administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: The United States is a country that still subscribes to constitutionalism and the rule of law. For the mome… https://t.co/5ln44t6GqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, Johnny H. Thanks for writing. You seem like you have a lot to teach me and others. Wanna hang out sometime? May… https://t.co/UHFubJVEKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieSweeney_1 Oh, way more stuff than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arpiem11 @KatieSweeney_1 I'm no fan of the Clintons. Bill Clinton is partly responsible for 2008 -- unforgivable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says the "president." https://t.co/eOTSlxPGuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieSweeney_1 Oh. Yeah. That's gonna be the title of my autobiography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auxonic oh, I want this to become a thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathan_sas Oh, I didn't doubt that he was for a second. I'll be watching closely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what Mike Pence does all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathan_sas Is that you, Mom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what I just got in the mail! Thanks for the reminder, @cathmckenna. Do it up, folks! https://t.co/7U2oA2Ft5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDicosa Will do! Thanks again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eutrapelia7 Could be if it gets picked up as part of a narrative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieSweeney_1 Oh, good. Close call. I was worried you'd found out that I'm a Chelsea fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janewordsmith Deal. But it's going to be a Ford Focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDicosa @joshvisser @jordanbpeterson Oh, I'd love to! I'm working on this book right now (and defending the dissertation in a month).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDicosa @joshvisser I do include those a bit, actually. Pops up in the psych lit all the time. I have more to do there, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDicosa @joshvisser Oh, yeah. Heuristics/shortcuts have been used for a long, long time. The problem is when they undercut democracy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>