<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Pushes Dark View of Islam to Center of U.S. Policy-Making, via @nytimes https://t.co/uPk8bFVTKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great piece even for experienced writers. https://t.co/odtbWH3kCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYTimes on WEF not getting global inequality. Davos Elite Fret About Inequality Over Vintage Wine and Canapés https://t.co/Zsdg7rqShm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whanbam1 @OECD_Social Agree. US shd be downweighted in regression. Expensive system, poor outcomes &amp; worse if Affordable Care repealed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s Anxious and Angry? The World on the Eve of Trump, via @nytimes https://t.co/0YTbPwwLlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cities of the Old - Learning from naturally occurring retirement communities.  https://t.co/4KCocfFkjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying 'fake news' is handy for politicians but toxic for democracy https://t.co/RIwveqHKUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UQ offers MicroMasters program in global development - UQ News - The University of Queensland, Australia https://t.co/05LDUSfX2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Long-Term Jobs Killer Is Not China. It’s Automation. https://t.co/B5NBJndRSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rage of 2016 https://t.co/u7Fg2K7aBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childhood forecasting of a small segment of the population with large economic burden : Nature Human Behaviour https://t.co/Q2eP8UTnI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research based on Dunedin Study. 'High social cost' adults can be predicted from as young as three https://t.co/gzN1bpOb1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substituting minutes for money. Mobile money and poverty alleviation. https://t.co/SZSU9nGiU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Equality of Opportunity Project https://t.co/inzjuEUvpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Dream, Quantified at Last, via @nytimes https://t.co/vyh5f19kjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding the four types of AI, from reactive robots to self-aware beings https://t.co/Yzyk14UrJH via @ConversationUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is doing computational social science. Sage report.  https://t.co/gOOSyjUcdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Big Data rich and the Big Data poor”: the new digital divide raises questions about future academic research https://t.co/E1tmFu5PWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Rorty’s 1998 Book Suggested Election 2016 Was Coming https://t.co/KDyrVkn8RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New UQ Master of Leadership in Global Development in 2018 https://t.co/b2iOrQTyde. Online edX entry pathway Jan 2017 https://t.co/0BbiqTN7az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phenomenal piece from before US election. https://t.co/J9rPLj8zoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was written before US election result and published late October. https://t.co/01AuIM4fXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSR's Baffour and Bon before US election result on uncertainty in polls - Does Donald Trump “defy all odds”? https://t.co/1j19FWxBqk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Academy ofSocial Sciences Symposium. @AcadSocSciences https://t.co/MXJude4Pc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to ISSR's Paco Perales - institute's newest DECRA. Congrats also to Michael Aird, D. Trigger, P. Memmott - Indig Disc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSR Staff and Student Forum panel session. What makes the institute distinctive? Didn't realize it was dress code. https://t.co/SUwkmgICku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to build high impact social  science teams? ISSR Group Leader jobs closing soon https://t.co/uS7CxSjkQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lifecourse centre at #NCLDconference2016. Strength in numbers. Great conference. Congrats to organizers. https://t.co/hI9pNEWliV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Couper, self described survey methodologist not survey mythologist, Eeyore not Tigger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Couper at #NCLDconference2016 https://t.co/HmD4whohsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive LSIC findings for the evidence base. https://t.co/7x3nRIi1ll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less smoking in the home. Tom Calma. https://t.co/d2ljB50ZKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous inequality - LSIC. #NCLDconference2016 https://t.co/pYxjIjW2XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Calma at #NCLDconference2016 https://t.co/BvKN3ImfYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Calma at #NCLDconference2016. NT Intervention not data based. Policy not always data driven. https://t.co/pxoPHVcWZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future of ABS. #NCLDconference2016 @ABSStats https://t.co/AkVWhHRpOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kalisch - like to get to integrated economic, social and environmental data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLADE - longitudinal business dataset incl ATO. LEED - employer-employee data. Significant new resources #NCLDconference2016 @ABSStats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Statistician David Kalisch at #NCLDconference2016. https://t.co/s3OerNDMhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rising inequality because of growth at top of distribution. Always thought this politically too hard to tackle. Int… https://t.co/BgxKnMcMsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good upcoming sessions at #NCLDconference2016 - policy impact, wealth, health, Ageing, analytics and diversity. ISSR and LCC in many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piketty challenges us to consider if we need to rein in wealth inequality https://t.co/SG9t7dgQwl via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training on Using the Global Terrorism Database: Introduction &amp; Module 1 | https://t.co/C4uyfdR2wI https://t.co/BVOXmwbZR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carter Butts on networks of interpersonal influence. Why I know but don't believe https://t.co/dutYRJzkE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New network model of belief dynamics. Network science on belief system dynamics under logic constraints https://t.co/oNp4sHg0Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How economic, humanitarian, and religious concerns shape European attitudes toward asylum seekers https://t.co/xroFDmGFSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We leave interpersonal dynamics to psychs and ethnomethodologists. https://t.co/Kpfbbq9zsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on metric data not reputation https://t.co/vdOAO7uZIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen King tells US to 'cool the clown hysteria' after wave of sightings https://t.co/knrfKCgUzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impact of training informal health care providers in India: A randomized controlled trial https://t.co/rmZlUaNlYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social norms as solutions https://t.co/Pvet8rwjRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. charges journal publisher with misleading authors https://t.co/ujEKJSEqNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read this first as "waterboarding research". Probably says a bit about how some current papers are going. https://t.co/F5fzPxLFBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PLOSONE: Early Father Involvement and Subsequent Child Behaviour at Ages 3, 5 and 7 Years: Prospective Analy ... https://t.co/Ank1c244rP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done this myself unknowingly for years. Heretical but good. Jamie Oliver's paella brings fractured Spain together.  https://t.co/sCzBuMiwh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PLOSONE paper with Wojtek Tomaszewski: Subjective Wellbeing, Objective Wellbeing and Inequality in Australia https://t.co/S7jmnuBhQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing pains for global monitoring of societal events https://t.co/mQcU2iSMxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unemployed people need money to live on.  https://t.co/3MN9QPyJtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The potential of big data and new technologies in human rights research https://t.co/3h7FdcLqgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding the maths is crucial for protecting privacy https://t.co/pqmKWp5rYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Data to Produce Useful Research Evidence https://t.co/RW40Phgsxm #wtgrantfoundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D tax incentive review still STEM focused. Advanced services &amp; manufacturing genuinely needs soc science too.  https://t.co/p6eqUcfJ3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UQ has a senior job in Society and Genomics. Please RT https://t.co/mYu29ORH7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intergenerational earnings elasticity in Australia. AJSI paper by Huang et al.  https://t.co/dl3a6fCGBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANZJ Public Health: Profiling the mobile-only population: insights from the Australian National Health Survey  https://t.co/KypXW3ov9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Journal of Official Statistics paper Weighting strategies for dual-frame telephone surveys available https://t.co/rY0XUBRLk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's meet in the middle on schools funding, not continue the trench warfare https://t.co/2ZuRcdhexn via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uqpharri we visited Marx's house in Trier on recent leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dollee_elle thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleBradyUQ thanks Bery much Michelle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for ABC #Lateline discussing investment approach to welfare. Tonight. https://t.co/Fve3HPxyDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobl opportunities in ISSR: Group Leader, Social Science https://t.co/QOFEtPHavV via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @MikeSav47032563 @LSEInequalities Sociology and class analysis in Nature. https://t.co/UvsOxuA5qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSR's new micro masters in global development. Building credit inch by inch https://t.co/ZDQomWW5HX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific piece by Suki Kim. It's tough to get identity when most of your subject positions are hegemonic. https://t.co/wpnSqt0OZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job opportunities for leading researchers: Please RT https://t.co/uS7CxSjkQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Minutes with Professor Gary King: Transformational power of big data lies, pure and simple, in its analytics https://t.co/ld9p3pdkLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research collaboration between universities and industry: Five practical principles to make it work. https://t.co/B6RMDnkePT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobs for exceptional research leaders to build work programs in high impact social science. ISSR, Uni Qld, Aust. https://t.co/uS7CxSjkQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andduer @ProfJanBeyers Science has more consensus on problem &amp; method, implies more consistent research practice &amp; reviewing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developing SocArXiv — a new open archive of the social sciences to challenge the outdated journal system. https://t.co/TPvhhSTbHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have @Qld_MHC as a partner. Thanks very much for coming to UQ awards tonight. https://t.co/CM31tg19QT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research that matters should matter beyond journals and the academy. Congratulations again @cameronparsell https://t.co/6sazdJPftN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @cameronparsell, winner of UQ Foundation Research Excellence Award. https://t.co/lekkgbwe72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSR's @CameronParsell's research helps reform policy on social housing https://t.co/X8vX4wPtIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New link. Postdoc Opportunities, ISSR, University of Queensland, Australia. Open field and mobility and inequality https://t.co/SsjLEzaqF8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postdoc opportunities, open and in inequality and mobility- ISSR - The University of Queensland, Australia https://t.co/EVY7Vm9tf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISSR is hiring postdoctoral researchers in inequality and mobility https://t.co/CRWF2njEpb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to completing #MyCensus and contributing to Australia's planning. ABS knows less about me than my bank and supermarket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pooling the polls: how we're tracking opinion polling for the Australian election https://t.co/cdRF5ku5Q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Brexit’ casts pall on future of U.K. science https://t.co/fn6sNXqdgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science and Brexit https://t.co/zWQE95wgQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repackaging research findings is not enough: Building partnerships for a practitioner-driven research agenda. https://t.co/utE0OJHe1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 Kanter Award to be announced today. Congrats to all finalists; good luck to ISSR Perales, Baxter and Tai https://t.co/b2YOrIkGng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid mounting political and social uncertainty, institutions must evolve to support evidence-based decision-making. https://t.co/0lgNhobeCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's first national ecosystem assessment | Science https://t.co/A5VlqPvS0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New online ecology of adversarial aggregates: ISIS and beyond | Science https://t.co/Ln9O6iX6Dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any justification for academic social science? https://t.co/RdLYmf2Gfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very nice piece. Good for anyone using statistical methods in research.  https://t.co/Gg9ypUpON4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High quality open access.  https://t.co/jeBPN8pc6v]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>