<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganhoang_ SO BEAUTIFUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg @YouTube currently watching my boyfriend shit himself while watching your resident evil series thanks joe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tsas87 yeah they're not as cool as us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tsas87 how's the first week of school? We're coming back to see you soon!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tsas87 PR and Advertising!! â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganhoang_ everyday!! Send me your timetable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't lie this is the best video of 2017 @kileab1 https://t.co/1EjgTOsCMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mayerstagram PR and Advertising!! Thank you so so much ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taaela happy birthday you absolute stunner! I hope you have such a wonderful day! Party hard! Love youuuu ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi I am, thank you my love!! I hope you're well ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally finalised my uni timetable, see you soon UNSW ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indielrh happy birthday princess ðŸ’– I hope you have such a wonderful day filled with so much love and happiness love you so so much ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swiftlykira CONGRATS KIRA IM SO HAPLY FOR YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baessari gotten everything right the biggest Ashleigh bayssari fan right here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg Vietnam! And back to Australia and actually explore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selzacat thank you so much selin â£ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenwolfsugg thank you Diana love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adoringjaspar thank you love you ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much to everyone, I'm feeling so so much better, my ankle is just sprained and I've got a few bruises but I'm all good now ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adoringoli thank you my love ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganhoang_ thank you Megan love u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purposejailey_ thank you my love ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wildfrantasy thank you â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdyonce thank you bianca love u ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi thank you my love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anaemicannabel so much love for you thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm currently thanking god that I am alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My anxiety has never been this bad and I'll probably never get on the road again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got into an accident in the road, please guys whatever you do on the road please please be careful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selzacat SELIN WE ARE ONE THOSE WERE MY LIFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to get home and find all my old Archie comics, they were all I read in year 6 and seeing the show come to life is incredible â˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg hello getting complaints from my bf that I spend too much time focusing on you and your videos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonahGreen so much love for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaSulewski honestly you can kill me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg hello what do you call a chicken staring at lettuce? Chicken sees a salad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Lunar New Year from Vietnam ðŸ’®â£ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karenxw_ this is such a me thing as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiesugg thank you bub!! Love you lots (It's actually lunar new because so many other countries also celebrate it) ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adoringjaspar congrats my anhel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg @YouTube good try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I CANT STOP WATCHING THIS! YOURE SO BEAUTIFUL I LOVE YOU SO MUCH ðŸ’– https://t.co/4Q8ybBlUSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maccas in Vietnam has a teriyaki burger? But I'm too scared to try it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you https://t.co/qQeZZR2WWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg you should be here!! Drinks all around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baessari stop that this is so beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colesprouse I've never been more excited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenwolfsugg OMG HOW DID I NOT EVEN MENTION THAT IN THE CHAT?! TW IS ONE OF MY FAVOURITE TV SHOWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selzacat thank you!! Ill try and find them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@selzacat omg where are your shoes from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg morning how was your sleep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@75beII @passionpoprince @colorstripped @BlTCHOLOGY so incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lauraflwr much love, happiness and doggy cuddles! ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lauraflwr happy birthday to one of the most special gems ever! Laura I love you so so much and I hope you have the best day filled with so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itstalecia happy birthday my love! I hope your day is filled with so much love, hugs and cake ðŸ’– miss you loadddds ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatsovivian WHAT THE WHERE DID THIS TWEET COME FROM BC I DIFNT TWEET THIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beenyouhayley HAPPY BIRTHDAY BEAUTIFUL! I HOPE YOU HAVE THE MOST INCREDIBLE DAY! I LOVE YOU SO MUCH ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg FUCK YOUVE BEEN UPLOADING SO MUCH ALREADY AS WELL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DESlRESUGG @Joe_Sugg Joe's won no competition needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is female ðŸ’– #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just watched the final episode of girl meets world and I actually can't believe that it was the final episode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fairlysugg @Joe_Sugg literally send help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi I LOVE YOU SO MUCH I DONT KNOW HOW IM MAKING YOU SO HAPPY BUT I HOPE I CAN CONTINUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg @YouTube STOP YOURE GIVING US SO MUCH THANK YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frantaspotify thank you my love ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adoringjaspar @Joe_Sugg I legit can't believe 13 seconds after I tweeted I'm in shock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg I can't believe you liked my tweet and it was because of my boyfriend I hate you why aren't you my boyfriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg got my boyfriend to start watching your videos congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I get into a taxi in Vietnam and reach for my seatbelt I get laughs from the driver IM SORRY I CARE ABOUT MY SAFETY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg @YouTube THANK YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rauhlaround best tweet from you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@troyesivan that was absolutely fucking incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi 20th of feb!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg @YouTube FUCK IM SO THANKFUL 2017 A RISE ON THIS CHANNEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ash_london @JacobWhitesides THANK U ANGEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to all my loves who got into their uni courses ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Vamps songs have been playing at this restaurant and baxter's cute little head keeps appearing in my head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiexanderson stop that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddisondaviss you'll love it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatchmylee THANK YOU LOVE U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yeahjaspar happy birthday my beautiful blessing, I love you so much and I hope you have the most incredible day ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DESlRESUGG I wish! I'm going to Vietnam with my family!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you all in 8 hours https://t.co/udgsHCS4jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leonbusty on flight to Vietnam today? That's eventful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi Omg okay I'm so happy you're still sending one love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I'm flying out tomorrow for a month I'm going to miss my friends so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe I'm not going to be in Australia for eesha and kira's birthday ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 WE LOVE U BBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voideesha honestly thought I was the only one that liked it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anyone who lives in the US can you buy me the sephora monopoly and I'll send you money ily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi stop that I love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_Sugg WELCOME BACK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@milliexpage happy birthday beautiful! ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaliciaxo cannot believe I missed this, this is beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtspotter HAPPY BIRTHDAY MY LOVE! I HOPE YOU HAVE A DAY FILLED WITH SO MUCH LOVE AND HAPPINESS ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rauhlaround thank you ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HAVE TWO BLISTERS ON MY FEET AND I CANT WALK PROPERLY FML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so me https://t.co/dyZk0XUrgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bree_sivan_levi I edited one! It's one with my friends I'll upload it tomorrow ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppysimp never been but apparently it's good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppysimp Janine and I are going if you wanted to come with? â˜º]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>