<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton The writer of the article under reference clearly knows little about #TPP !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More fallacy about #TPP - aimed at coherence not harmonisation.  And is a simple tariff agreement really possible i… https://t.co/IUfa1crFEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZHunterM @davidcapie As a French &amp; German linguist myself I agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oiwoods @davidcapie Thanks for the feedback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to school - Thoughts from me on importance of learning Chinese @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/msq49GFzby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @Mihi_Forbes @emmawehipeihana Also glad to see free trade + housing incl security for renters, Maori, art &amp; culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Republic now seems to have an Emperor and fiction appears as fact! https://t.co/uJbh7raAa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charles_finny if you follow the Robert Graves' theory Claudius put Nero on the throne to bring the Empire down &amp; restore the Republic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charles_finny @FT @FinancialTimes Can Trump play a fiddle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDCANZ Thanks for letting me know and congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong endorsement of free trade from Mayor @phil_goff at #CCNZ Charity Gala Dinner @nzchinacouncil  @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/YjGjGbOrdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ will remain open  - to trade, to investment and to people - @pmbillenglish to #CCNZ Charity Gala Dinner @nzchinacouncil @TradeWorksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM @pmbillenglish congratulates China Chamber for getting involved in the community through this Charity Gala Dinne… https://t.co/U5NXosMgK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ambassador Wang Lutong says NZ/China relationship is a model for the world @nzchinacouncil https://t.co/Fr8HYJJ94T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCNZ Chair David Wang addresses the New Year Charity Gala @nzchinacouncil https://t.co/mI9GDf0cXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to be at China Chamber of Commerce Chinese New Year Charity Gala @nzchinacouncil https://t.co/Xr4WVDNRhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ Warmest congratulations !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Tui ad - "They"ll know we are Christians by our love" https://t.co/8yqOVpx2Gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation about LGBT and sexuality not allowed at Festival One https://t.co/jpWSWtDOIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Godzone - Group 'forced' to leave Christian festival https://t.co/OmGZ0toFXC via @StMatthewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We cannot preach the centrality of love &amp; demand that people live without it" - hear this church and world… https://t.co/bitR2ak1lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful perspective from my friend Rod Oram @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/s53GRTTpGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewRiddell1 We don't see eye to eye on #TPP but I like those principles too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeting one racial group is more than poor comm'n but good that @PhilTwyford acknowledges this error… https://t.co/VTgQHsKwnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumper edition of #Mediawatch this morning @RNZSunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to have you back @wallacelchapman @RNZSunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers Weekly | https://t.co/FcmErIgdHR via @AgriHQ  @StirlingNigel @TradeworksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight @RevHelenJacobi @revhirini @clare_barrie " just how difficult and painful all this has been - FOR THE BISHOPS!" #dumpthepurple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight @petercarrell @revhirini @RevHelenJacobi Have we discussed structure &amp; governance since '92?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell @revhirini @gendidwight @RevHelenJacobi Not nec to agree, just be willing to discuss. Surely must see oblivion on horizon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @gendidwight @RevHelenJacobi The reason we can't move forward on same-sex etc is largely because our structures are stuffed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight @revhirini @RevHelenJacobi Hope other tweeps will join this conversation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @gendidwight @RevHelenJacobi Need this korero. My concern is if we keep going the way we are, we'll end up where we're headed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight @revhirini @RevHelenJacobi Reform electoral process, time limits on serving bishops, increase accountabilties - places to start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @gendidwight @RevHelenJacobi I pray so but at times I think we should start again #insurrection #dumpthepurple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gendidwight @revhirini @RevHelenJacobi Absurd statements of these English Bishops show why the church is losing its prophetic voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to working with new Dep Sec Trade at @MFATgovtNZ - lots to do ! @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/De0l0Y7It5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VangelisVNZ I see you are using your new title! Great ! We need you back here asap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith Cheers. I don't mind if people disagree with me but must Dave be so disagreeable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith He hates us both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell @revhirini Go on, you know you want to ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell @revhirini I have all my teeth, well most of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @petercarrell #insurrection is our calling! #rogueone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini @petercarrell There's a certain Anglican bishop - very pakeha if you know what I mean - who wants to sue me ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaltersPRnz That's very kind Jacquie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercarrell Go to the top of the class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@revhirini Kia ora brother!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you just love Twitter! This gem refers to me! https://t.co/brZRYQ23WF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward Thanks Bronwyn. I long ago muted Dave who prefers name-calling to genuine exchange of views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More "enlightened exporter" views on #TPP and what's next @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/S4B3Cx35DH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward I even talk to @BarryCoates and @DavidClarkNZ.  Conversations with @TabuteauNZFirst are cordial but short !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith It's a complicated picture because of the China-Japan-Korea-India nexus, but worth exploring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjsmellie Good to hear, just keep in line on #RCEP will you !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith Yes agree with you on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith Yes - but in #RCEP's case we don't see China acting to set the agenda as US did in #TPP. It might help if it did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward @1NRSmith Understood. My view is that those rights and values were safeguarded in #TPP but we disagree on that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith  #TPP didn't aim to supplant the #WTO &amp; #P4 was set up in such a way to encourage US &amp; others to join]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1NRSmith Thanks for this - very thoughtful.  Note #RCEP is not led by China but by #ASEAN 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin Thanks. Who knows but it seems to be more like GST rather than a tariff (not that I'm in favour!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Govt worth its salt can turn its back on seeking advantage for NZ - that's why we need to pursue all options pos… https://t.co/aniEWxBY94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping my friend @pjsmellie will cheer up soon: Enough already on TPPA https://t.co/2KlLcMiuPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward Please see my Spinoff article for an "enlightened exporter" view !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin Lot of vagueness here.  Seems to be talking about a tax rather than a tariff, applying to domestic goods as well as imports??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very pleased to meet with Dr Jian Yang MP today &amp; to congratulate him on his appt as PPS for Ethnic Affairs… https://t.co/RKiTlL21BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year of the Rooster to all Chinese friends !https://t.co/wKbFoDCX7h来自杰珂陛先生的新春祝福  @nzchinacouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @melissaleemp on your appointment as PPS for Ethnic Affairs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenClarkUNDP More mountains to climb! Best wishes from Aotearoa! @HelenClarkNZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to spend time with the best neighbours ever. Happy Australia Day! @AusHCNZ @NZAustralia @alijduncan https://t.co/cCmMIFRG2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryCoates @TheSpinoffTV Yes - but now you're the trade guy you have to come up with ideas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet more from me on the way forward on #TPP and trade with the USA @TradeWorksNZ @NZUSCouncil https://t.co/eVRjVz5zWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good job by @toddmcclaymp on @NZMorningReport - calmly assess the options - next step for NZ on trade &amp; #TPP  @TradeWorksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slightly more nuanced comment on Chile &amp; #TPP in this report https://t.co/NYMRo3Pgp6 @TradeworksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@toddmcclaymp has the best job, even if tough @NZMorningReport  @TradeWorksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward What sort of nation are we becoming when this happens?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin @davidcapie @smh Wouldn't have expected anything else at this stage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamienOConnorMP @nzherald @nzheraldbiz They must be the big corporates that some politicians go on about ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robellcampbin @BarryCoates Look forward to hearing some ideas about how to achieve these aims!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PolicyObsAUT Many thanks. Will review with interest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so surprising. Japan cannot repudiate its main ally. Meantime v positive Japan has ratified #TPP https://t.co/2AxzH7VQkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade Minister @toddmcclaymp on the case - NZ still in the business of trade @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/OT85aEuQOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US withdrawal from TPP expected to impact NZ economy, businesses https://t.co/foaOVIxzxL  @TradeworksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for you @ItanzIndia - India NZ FTA is part of this picture too https://t.co/UFYVIlYkrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin Defer to the expert on this but happy to accept the pineapple lumps when the time is right (may not be for some time)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philquin thought we only needed 51 as goes under TPA ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana @robhosking @BenRoss_AKL @charles_finny Keep the faith sister !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to talk with @KerreMcIvor &amp; Mark Dye on @NewstalkZB about #TPP - a bilateral deal with the US won't be easy! @TradeWorksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @robhosking @emmawehipeihana @charles_finny Happy to look at all opportunities for NZ to grow and prosper,  Ben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashmcgill not quite the way we do things eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @robhosking @emmawehipeihana @charles_finny I see another ten years of flogging ahead of us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prchovanec Some progressives have the same problem !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashmcgill @TradeWorksNZ Even Oz wanted to improve their FTA with TPP but let's see !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article below contains text of Presidential memorandum on trade #TPP @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/AFSXX54ViA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ likely to be offered one-on-one trade deal with United States https://t.co/BV20spQtwj  @TradeworksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNBR Thanks NBR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More from me on US withdrawal from #TPP @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/fBGcgjg42r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewRiddell1 @AndrewLittleMP @NZMorningReport @TradeWorksNZ Know better that TPP did not undermine sovereignty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protectionists of the world unite - you have nothing to lose but your livelihoods @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/H5PtouPYEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to talk to @SAINSO on @RadioLIVENZ about NZ's global friendships and #TPP just now @TradeWorksNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewRiddell1 @AndrewLittleMP @NZMorningReport @TradeWorksNZ I acknowledge the concerns but political leaders shoukd know better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid commentary from Charles Finny this morning @TradeWorksNZ https://t.co/uebNchEKxh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>