<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had a FedEx agent call me, "...my dear friend." #feelingthelove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently not a lot of practice time is spent on the 2 on 0 breakaway. #NHLAllStarGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charming, classy and funny. This'll be stuck in my head for a while. #RIPMTM https://t.co/UJTND5QZqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough morning commute. #westendtrafficjam https://t.co/Sg7VOIvNk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Meryl Streep is overrated," said no one, ever. Oh, wait...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanRobertBos ah, yes... big difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcamcole @jonmccarthySUN you had me at "Augusta house."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 observations from the #GoldenGlobe Awards: 4. Every man in Hollywood has a beard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 observations from the #GoldenGlobe Awards: 3. Kristen Wiig and Steve Carrell are comedy gold...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 observations from the #GoldenGlobe Awards: 2. A crybaby response from the Commander-in-Tweet elect was sadly predictable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 observations from the #GoldenGlobe Awards: 1. Meryl Streep is the bomb...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't often look like this. jojodas's photo https://t.co/AICNrUe8Xf #vancouversnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating to discover what the *hack* may really have been about. https://t.co/6tFIQy8oun https://t.co/ZttbmEXFRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the greats. https://t.co/alZ1FJuxjX #NormanLear #OneDayataTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next year I'll set the PVR to record for an extra hour after the #RoseBowl instead of 30 min. Wow, what a finish... apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @MariahCarey was truly a diva, she'd have gone all Christian Bale on the sound crew. https://t.co/y7IUrtccnf #nomonitor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to worry about when riding your horse to church this morning in Pasadena. #roseparade  https://t.co/oIFa9EVh25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why 2016 will last a little longer. Another reason being good at math is a prerequisite to work at Google.  https://t.co/AqsKMa89FD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fake news is a false problem" | Toronto Star. Indeed. Cue the National Enquirer. And Batboy.  https://t.co/RlhN1SVzNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I can't do it on my own': inmates in need of mentors face a long wait list
https://t.co/0cuWCboYit https://t.co/nSA4P3AUEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental solutions coupled with corporate innovation. What a concept! https://t.co/mgBzgJjxpS #bipartisansolutions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One might be tempted to stand beside him for perspective, but then... no. https://t.co/DuNwTmuItJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems ridiculous. Until last night's game of #Saboteur. https://t.co/K2qzJLwsQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyConway Exactly. If it's a choice between between dying young and running, I think we all know what the answer is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read this stat: people who run are 24% less likely to die. Like, ever...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cantstopwatching https://t.co/odGxx0nTN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's gonna be this damn cold, we might as well set a record, right @michaelkusswx? https://t.co/JnRa5lspSP #yvrcoldsnap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmontonTourism @CityofEdmonton would love to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing about flying over/into @CityofEdmonton - outdoor ice rinks everywhere. #hockeytown #YEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With fake news as rampant as it is, believe me, I've fact checked this one all over the place. https://t.co/k1kLNHR9Kw #headtransplant #wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This can't actually be real. Can it? (spoiler) it is. Trump to Remain EP on ‘Celebrity Apprentice’ https://t.co/UGeglc34LC @variety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay, we're hardy. We will overcome. #vancouversnow https://t.co/oli94Y62Hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Execs with the vision to trust talent and let something grow are rare and special. #RIP Grant Tinker https://t.co/WD2JR8wF06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amber Alert activated for 4-year-old from Vancouver
https://t.co/I6Tb7JDrMl https://t.co/SM5yI941AC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to hear the very lovely Florence Henderson passed away at 82.  https://t.co/s2AXpd3WAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best sports graphic of the week. Oh, and @ArethaFranklin can take as long as she damn wants.… https://t.co/enARkSzTDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many "All Aboard Breakfasts" is that? #BCFerries https://t.co/I5kev8DvWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to @PBS, Canada's immigration website has crashed. Actually. #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least tonight's #Oilers loss won't take 4 years to get over. C'mon America! #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AFM2016 in Santa Monica, where it's all about the sunsets, er, uh, scripts. #nofilter https://t.co/fOLyEFFtCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind of like Sunday morning church for filmmakers. #AFM2016 https://t.co/UxVza57PeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new video for @KidsUpFrontVan, who provide event tickets for underprivileged kids. https://t.co/pChoGCEEN7 https://t.co/vM67hBHuMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it's a good kind of madness. https://t.co/JkmNEbWr59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironically, last time I was there was for a bag of chips. #medicalmarijuana
https://t.co/NAP6A5Qycz https://t.co/cn3yueJiO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those criticizing @HillaryClinton for suggesting the need of varying public and private messages have apparently never posted on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@balikoff thanks Aussie Pete, appreciate the support! We're working on it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The closing line is gold. https://t.co/xak0NFogjX #NYTimes #boom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The concept of race lacks scientific support. -Harvard Prof. #WeAreAllOne  https://t.co/kMzLgHu2xV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get Wayne Gretzky to shake his head, you know you're doing something. #ConnorMcDavid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auston Matthews on pace for 328 goals. #NHL #OpeningNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gretz and Mess on the ice at the new rink. #chills #Oilers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird, it all feels so calm right now. #YVRstorm https://t.co/RVtWGLoO1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It doesn’t matter who won the debate: America has already lost" - The Globe and Mail https://t.co/XAWTg5vPKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite elements of technology is instant fact checking. #Debates2016  https://t.co/Csv2AJF8CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arnold Palmer was king, the greatest and an inspiration for countless golfers and gentlemen. #RIPArnie #sadday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Clooney's at a UN Leaders Summit re refugees and the story is about a celeb divorce? #prioritiesarefucked   https://t.co/7hOR2Eh5JT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winding down after a great shoot for @KidsUpFrontVan, a terrific organization, providing tix to events for kids in #Vancouver. #yvrshoots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because of our peripheral vision, something, something, something... https://t.co/WtwAACeKTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhonaR @SoundKitch ...times about 3 different deliveries each.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure, 256 gigs in a phone is pretty cool, but isn't the design pretty much the iPhone 3 without the chrome? #iPhone7launch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic scene, remembering the gentle comedic genius of Gene Wilder. https://t.co/2P1Onq9q9r #RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news. RIP Gene Wilder. So engaging and incredibly funny. Re-watching #StirCrazy may be on the agenda tonight. https://t.co/4Abw69tmEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tigerwoods &amp; @booweekley had never marked a 1 on a card prior to @Scott_Brown803. I've written it twice. #minitour https://t.co/AgATrsS7vM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RainbowFrancks gotta send you a link to our new web series. Hope you're going great! https://t.co/EXNjBCUWJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @rcamcole, if u have 10 min while covering golf, check out our new web pilot with @fredewanuick https://t.co/8wzy82lz81 thx!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be a part of this. Official launch at noon tomorrow. https://t.co/gDDdvjk1YC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sledgehammers and umbrellas w/ metal tips not allowed. Guns, however, perfectly fine. #RNC 
https://t.co/WhBTwa5Sdl https://t.co/4J0mZRpqnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In honour of Cleveland hosting the #RNC2016. What could possibly go wrong? https://t.co/WAt84ozyns #RNCinCLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather have #Chiarelli making deals than the fans. Gutsy move. Can't wait to see it play out. #Oilers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering the technology to actually fly airplanes, you'd think they could come up with a better sound system at the gates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lennon61 @goingforbroke16 when there are that many Les Pauls on the wall, a concussion incident is all too likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get the sentiment of #CarFreeDay, but is the automobile not one of the greatest innovations of our time? #perspective #babyandbathwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredEwanuick with @LorneCardinal, then between takes with @DavidACollette #funnywithouthardlyeventrying https://t.co/Tomrz5WvvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful to have had the opportunity to work with such an amazing cast and crew on @goingforbroke16! To the edit suite we go...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exciting to watch this come together! Shoot is wrapped - now the real coming together. #editing #storyhive https://t.co/dwtHIx230A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To meet him, Gordie Howe was rough, tough, kind and gentle, all at once. And the best handshake ever. #RIPMrHockey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcamcole @penguins looked like the all star game for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkusswx shooting our web pilot for @goingforbroke16 next Tuesday with @fredewanuick and others. Care to offer a weather prognosis...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still in shock about #MuhammadAli's death. He was supposed to live forever. This one will truly take a while. The Ultimate Zen athlete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long time since I hrd @Margaritaville until tonite in the store. 40 minutes later, I blew out a flip flop. Literaly https://t.co/dyRs0TIdQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course. Go UNDER the Alps. It's a no brainer.  https://t.co/ZYkIOnkQ1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's about right.  https://t.co/oYpCQL895x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's me, but an on-hold Muzak version of Black Eyed Peas "I've Gotta Feeling" does seem a bit odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great shleppin the bag for @THayGolf at #PGATourCanada q-school. Impressive game, solid T9 finish and, most important, a tour card!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After #Telus green lit the pretend version today, tomorrow it's the real thing - looping for @THayGolf at Q-school for the #PGATourCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to report that our team has been awarded a #Telus #Storyhive grant for @goingforbroke16 with @fredewanuick! Deets to come...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeJudge's film #Idiocracy should be required viewing for American's when they hit legal voting age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraJMcGuire Truth. And there are a lot of hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevedarling we're developing a golf comedy starring @fredewanuick Check it out, perhaps even cast a vote and/or RT https://t.co/CkCzSirqgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day to vote to help make the pilot for @goingforbroke16 with @fredewanuick. Your vote means a lot! https://t.co/CkCzSirqgb Thx!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneak peak at the pilot script @goingforbroke16 with @fredewanuick. Only 2 days to vote https://t.co/CkCzSirqgb https://t.co/MeYe3p48pD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to work with @fredewanuick on our new web series, @goingforbroke16. If you have a chance, cast a vote. https://t.co/CkCzSirqgb Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natvana @STORYHIVE @goingforbroke16 Thanks for the support, @natvana!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're trying to build votes for our webseries. Can u help by voting at https://t.co/CkCzSirqgb? Perhaps even a follow @goingforbroke16. Thx!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking and sad. Such a beautiful and inspiring spirit. #RIPPrince https://t.co/joMs6kUHjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one "holiday" of the year with a distinct smell in #YVR. Putting the wrap on #4/20. https://t.co/ASapISU6p5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALMURDOCH Thanks, Al. Greatly appreciated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #storyhive project is a #webseries about #golf that actually isn't at all about golf. Starring @fredewanuick https://t.co/8wzy82lz81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks also to @THayGolf for the guest starring role our #storyhive demo... https://t.co/HLaeLzOl3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be part of #Storyhive with 'Going for Broke' starring @fredewanuick. Thanks as well to @vancouvergolf https://t.co/HLaeLzOl3K]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>