<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@semajsenrab72 Pride of the fleet 2 https://t.co/wzAMKZeSHi via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commander Joint Task Force 633, Air Vice - Marshal Tim Innes, CSC, prepares to board a helicopter in Kabul, https://t.co/ysTQVw1wjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leading Seaman Maritime Logistics - Personnel Abbey Johnson is presented an Australia Day Medallion and Certificate. https://t.co/KHVjGSTYmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Arunta on patrol in the Middle East region. https://t.co/mafLlqRlM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating 53 years of service in a ceremony held aboard HMAS Adelaide. https://t.co/AyzQQUp6Gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crew stand on the Casing of HMAS Farncomb alongside Diamantina Pier, Fleet Base West. https://t.co/sbEBbnPvrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crew stand on the Casing of HMAS Sheean alongside Diamantina Pier, Fleet Base West. https://t.co/BdREa1G41V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crew stand on the Casing of HMAS Dechaineux alongside Diamantina Pier, Fleet Base West. https://t.co/oi1WvhoRNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGTheMess Cool, impressive, any ventures in the civilian realm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGTheMess I'm living the dream and nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders versus Managers: Spot the Difference https://t.co/7CdNJe5WrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did the Trident test fail? https://t.co/gw2EMIPnlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirNasaRoyal well now you ask, I'm second guesssing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naval Shipbuilding Board gets down to work https://t.co/04VwlNq62q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirNasaRoyal Windy and sleepless Melbourne night, neighbours thoughtful placement of wind-chimes on the perimeter not compensating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Norwegian F-16 fighter from Bodø Air base https://t.co/QqDbhATKrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABH0147 @semajsenrab72  Hello ABH I'll be there + 1, but Barnes isn't coming, look forward to having a cold one with you :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commodore and COMSNMG1 Ole Martin Sandquist onboard HNoMS Roald Amundsen in Oslo harbour https://t.co/lEC16mmQWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HNoMS Roald Amundsen underway to join NATO Maritime Group 1 (SNMG1) as the command vessel for the first 6 months of… https://t.co/zQWknDhFXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[business backs PM’s Veterans’ Employment Program https://t.co/cTsyao44YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Participants at the Norweigan armed forces recruitment &amp; selection trials for winter 2017 are the first to undergo… https://t.co/ecQv0J1led]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blood freezer is loaded onto a C-130J Hercules aircraft during a trial demonstration at RAAF Base Richmond. https://t.co/fNIU8EISYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hydrographic Survey Ship HMAS Leeuwin sails into Sydney Harbour. https://t.co/NIIdmoqpws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An F/A-18 from 77 Squadron Royal Australian Air Force flies over Docklands.

FA/18 Hornet from 77Squadron over MCG https://t.co/AsCsXnfJg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch U.S. F/A-18 Hornets Unleash Swarm of Mini-Drones in First Test https://t.co/rIc7FbKjbK via @theaviationist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraqi soldiers undertake urban operations training under the guidance of Australian &amp; New Zealand soldiers. https://t.co/7D1VXItdfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian soldier from Task Group Taji 4 instructs Iraqi soldiers in urban operations at Taji Military Complex,Iraq.https://t.co/zsTfL96syF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Arunta &amp; Pakistani Naval Ship Shamsheer conduct a RAS with United States Naval Ship Walter S Diehl in the MER https://t.co/9CgQuiaoUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Arunta prepares to conduct a replenishment at sea with USN Ship Walter S Diehl during a patrol in the MER https://t.co/xMNse7oWrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Arunta's Rigid Hull Inflatable Boat returns from a transfer with Pakistani Naval Ship Shamsheer in the MER https://t.co/PLjICkk5qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagery Scanned from Navy Historic Archive

HMAS Cerberus Bulldog Mascot 1940 https://t.co/D7Ec4ioPbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagery Scanned from Navy Historic Archive

AE 1 https://t.co/u7x4cvjmPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS MELBOURNE II with HMAS QUICKMATCH

NIUW_HIST_1180_001 https://t.co/ojWl3ZsgLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RAN aircraft carrier HMAS Melbourne in formation with a RNZN Leander class frigate &amp; HMAS Brisbane.
https://t.co/9CIuVhKVrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A RAAF F/A-18A Hornet from the Air Task Group Strike Element alongside a KC-30A MRTT during a mission in the MER https://t.co/lcKExOmoxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief of Navy Christmas message - Defence Video Portal https://t.co/LnJsbBIkrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dux of the Submarine Warfare Officers Course 2016, Lieutenant Jack Abbott at HMAS Stirling. https://t.co/I2i2mOrV5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Norwegian frigate HNoMS Roald Amundsen firing the 76mm canon during Flotex 2016. https://t.co/BzvJSQDnGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operation Christmas Drop 16 - Defence Video Portal https://t.co/oatHtDzOZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whitedingo001 Well it is full of Seamen :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Sheean's berthing party as the submarine approaches Fleet Base West. https://t.co/rVOvNbw4nR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collins Class Submarine, HMAS Sheean, in Cockburn Sound, Western Australia. https://t.co/Nc0sDkO1lA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aircraft A21-101 and A21-32 get a water canon farewell https://t.co/zBz0bi5SrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royal Australian Air Force puppies get into the Christmas cheer at RAAF Base Amberley. https://t.co/FkaVofQK9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirNasaRoyal @60006717 My money's on the kids/recruits from the western suburbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirNasaRoyal @60006717 interested in sunagimo6000's take on that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Gun Directional Platform of HMAS Ballarat. https://t.co/JXpLwA1Boc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two C-130J Hercules aircraft dispence flares over RAAF Base Richmond during an Airborne Operations Training Course. https://t.co/yoLH6wuxSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Royal Military College Duntroon full time General Service Officer Graduation parade.

 https://t.co/1xMkG6c2mv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of No. 35 Squadron on the flight line with four C-27J Spartan battlefield air lifters at RAAF Base Richmond. https://t.co/RodB2E2nMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medal ceremony, presented for the United Nations Multidimensional Integrated Stabilisation Mission in Mali held at… https://t.co/uLIwkgzEgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The annual Church parade in Sortland Church for the Norwegian Coastguard. https://t.co/9s7PuzsI1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An F/A-18A Hornet prepares to depart on another mission from Australia's main operating air base in the MER https://t.co/jmX79OQy11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Graduation Ceremony of General Entry 348 Taylor Division at Recruit School of HMAS Cerberus, Victoria. https://t.co/LWsvLSXMNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney and Tobruk replenishing at sea during their deployment to Gallipoli. https://t.co/feEPIE1x1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His Excellency Sir Peter Cosgrove AK, MC presents MIDN Kate Milward with the Commander-in-Chief Medal. https://t.co/6rEldWdgkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The class of 2016 throw their hats into the air on completion of three years military training &amp; academic studies https://t.co/FAeyE6zQSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise at the AN/TPS-77 Tactical Air Defence Radar System situated on a ridge near Gunnedah, New South Wales. https://t.co/l3ekR3f0Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Canberra during a series of trials at Fleet Base East in Sydney on 6 December 2016. https://t.co/t7f1MTWU9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Ararat conducts a boarding exercise on Discovery III as part of their MRE, off the coast of Darwin, NT. https://t.co/5Y1222b1vS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Maryborough departs the attack wharf at HMAS Coonawarra, Northern Territory. https://t.co/CRqwc2nR2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMA Ships sail into Jervis Bay in formation at the completion of Exercise OCEAN RAIDER. https://t.co/wfatnIPcMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Ballarat's MH-60R 'Gold Digger' landing during flying operations in the North West Shelf of Australia. https://t.co/GZ7FfEdDfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Ballarat patrolling the North West Shelf of Australia. https://t.co/cn8gkzcPxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Ballarat's MH-60R Seahawk 'Gold Digger', during flying operations in the North West Shelf area of operation. https://t.co/EngsdDDkO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScaredyCat44 @Australian_Navy Pride in your uniform is very important, there are lots of tricks &amp; products like white vinegar, bicarb soda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A C-130J Hercules from No 37 Squadron flies over Lake George during a training exercise. https://t.co/fa4Zx56c8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A C-130J Hercules from No 37 Squadron flies over Lake George during a training exercise. https://t.co/jfPfv3aAVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The graduating New Entry Officers Course 55 conduct a ceremonial sunset at HMAS Creswell for their friends &amp; family https://t.co/GSQHpKog9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManfromMosman "John Sore Penis" in Australia https://t.co/k8hWYUgtVJ otherwise Johnny Reb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManfromMosman @StarAdvertiser Boomer, do you already know the answer but just want it spelled out for LOL's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A RAAF KC-30A MRTT, F/A-18F Super Hornet, F/A-18A Hornet &amp; an A27 Hawk 127 over Lake George in the ACT https://t.co/LtuFbkl1UJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Royal Guard &amp; Commanding Officer HMAS Cerberus, Captain Stephen Bowater, OAM, RAN, presenting a Royal Salute https://t.co/1sgKOVVi5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air-to-air refuelling trials between the KC-30A Multi-Role Tanker Transport and United States Air Force B-1B Lancer. https://t.co/YX6scdCmZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@margotdate @OMGTheMess Yeah it's summer they're everywhere :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Albatross Divisions as held on the A Hanger hardstand. https://t.co/ufJpy3PAu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RAAF’s first P-8A Poseidon, A47-001 fly’s in formation with a AP-3C Orion RAAF Base Edinburgh in South Australia https://t.co/K6rmRnyJ8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RAAF’s first P-8A Poseidon fly’s down the St Vincent Gulf coastline near Adelaide in South Australia. https://t.co/Ax2ApWrxoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sailors take turns launching capsicum spray grenades off HMAS Ararat during a firing serial off the coast of Darwin. https://t.co/xRSm31aDAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Ararat sails off the coast off Darwin during their Mission Readiness Evaluation. https://t.co/U37jJUbDii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@demens26 Thinking SSK too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMA Ships Melbourne, Newcastle and Parramatta depart Sydney Harbour in formation to participate in Exercise Ocean R… https://t.co/xU0UpOmHic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norwegian C-130 cockpit https://t.co/HXyDCTtQds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SKJOLD-CLASS Corvette, firing 76mm gun during Flotex 2016 https://t.co/sdnkMrjtit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crew members of HMAS Gascoyne launch a Double Eagle Mine Disposal Vehicle during Exercise OCEAN RAIDER. https://t.co/9igzqr3E1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Parramatta ready to take part in Exercise OCEAN RAIDER, one of the RAN's largest maritime warfare activities. https://t.co/IQk64P8ZF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief of Air Force, Air Marshal Leo Davies, AO, CSC and guests at the F-111 unveiling ceremony at RAAF Base Wagga. https://t.co/uW4PystGwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A C-130J Hercules aircraft performs a 'fly-past' as part of the RAAF School of Technical Training Graduation Parade. https://t.co/dw2UPddt0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Cerberus, Victoria. https://t.co/306OjxLeU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@semajsenrab72 @DeptDefence Only the scale differs :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KNm Hinnøy during exercise Flotex 2016 https://t.co/NUKM71yiwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An A27 Hawk 127 operated by No 76 Squadron participates in a training activity over Lake George in the ACT. https://t.co/m2TQQgeLOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pair of F/A-18A Hornets from Air Task Group 630 Strike Element flying in the MER during an Operation Okra mission. https://t.co/Xa4oEt5eSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pair of F/A-18A Hornets from Air Task Group 630 Strike Element flying in the MER during an Operation Okra mission. https://t.co/jvZFfUT0aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMA Ships Melbourne, Newcastle, Parramatta, Gascoyne and Huon leave Sydney Harbour for Exercise OCEAN RAIDER, https://t.co/UgpTOgahtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thales to design Collins sonar system upgrade https://t.co/uatmrB1wkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shortfin Barracuda briefings commence https://t.co/xBpJVVwadd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Warramunga passes a John Brookes Gas Installation while operating in the Gorgon Basin of the North West Shelf. https://t.co/LmwLVekyvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A RAN Bell 429 helicopter flies in front of the Sydney Opera House proudly displaying a White Ribbon flag below. https://t.co/owNuTNfXrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HNoMS Roald Amundsen transiting through Ofotfjorden during Flotex 2016 https://t.co/TPCmkJlqgh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>