<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Americans We Need https://t.co/KiCoLhACfK via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Trump is violating the Constitution https://t.co/QXkMKYKyoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Trump's sinister choice of blacklisted countries. https://t.co/fEofVANXDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Sabotaging democracy https://t.co/fDcROHvoGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: George Orwell's dystopia classic zooming in sales https://t.co/tYpsfmWzw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Sabotaging democracy https://t.co/fDcROHvoGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: American billionaires buying boltholes in New Zeal... https://t.co/OC9zfMbgia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Amazon launches 20,000-pound Indie prize https://t.co/teyGlimi6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Trump repeats a lie https://t.co/8iQY6aYymS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Trumpism predicted in classic novel https://t.co/x0zwuxuk2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Most borrowed books, January 2017 https://t.co/M0gPSziYxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Refugee in bid for a seat in the New Zealand Parli... https://t.co/JBZYYPHRYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: A Trump prediction from 1987 https://t.co/LAA81eymz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Write a bestseller and still be broke https://t.co/oSUIjKawbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Style tips for 2017 from my favorite designer https://t.co/LM9iAljTyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Sail of the century https://t.co/WEwhqrEOWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Whales that have lost their prey https://t.co/ZW3f8tUdpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: New Zealand and Israel -- the threats and repercus... https://t.co/JPSkyCcHnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Alaric Bond's Latest https://t.co/A6SskhiVU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Frederick Douglass, the most photographed American... https://t.co/kwYHXHLe6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Author of To Sir, With Love dies at 104 https://t.co/Sbp58yqG3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Happy Birthday Maritime History Discussion List https://t.co/iFAhIGbdGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Controversial Poldark https://t.co/LxUXwKIUGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Trump, We Can’t Just Get Along https://t.co/DgS1FOZeAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Scotland, Trump Built a Wall. Then He Sent Residents the Bill. https://t.co/IjRZz24GXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The original cliffhanger https://t.co/729A3RAlpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: New Zealand's PM finally talks to Trump https://t.co/VAAQFm1dxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Navy evacuates earthquake refugees https://t.co/z3lAU7nKO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Hear, hear https://t.co/xkBqPL4P7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: NZ Prime Minister fails to pick up when Trump call... https://t.co/kElknvHOp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: NZ writers penalized for publishing overseas https://t.co/00yKnc7HFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Captured twice by pirates https://t.co/2VoItAH5se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Latest Quarterdeck https://t.co/cxaoGOK6se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Is your book in a French library? https://t.co/KyCFjeMqZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The presidential election: America’s best hope https://t.co/0QKhgZSfhQ via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: from the island of Martha's Vineyard https://t.co/ATBE9LyVyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Unusual ship visit to Wellington https://t.co/4SALtdTeLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Rest in Peace - KEN SCADDEN https://t.co/kN0qxQbmpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Cruisers have a more exciting holiday than expecte... https://t.co/OuLaiJrYUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Maritime Murder Mystery in the Making https://t.co/skaKqFe7sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: ISLAND OF THE LOST -- the 400th review https://t.co/36GYpvbCCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: New Zealand a big cruise destination this summer https://t.co/smyNjzw5Zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Island of the Lost -- a belated book review https://t.co/eCtOtfw7wN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsiders with Gerard Hindmarsh https://t.co/0QcoF7mTRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: A Promise of Gold Countdown https://t.co/bsIydpIabN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Latest newsletter from McBooks Press https://t.co/M0W7H12HEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Life in a lighthouse https://t.co/6faI5Rdpey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The meaning of "Bully" https://t.co/d1Cw0q4plH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: EMAIL FROM THE UNDERWORLD https://t.co/jYwMV551ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: BLACKBIRDING AND THE BULLY https://t.co/DEtmQbNEiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Kiwi Dads not interested in Father's Day? https://t.co/FPHvK3Kw9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: whale skeleton on display again https://t.co/jED990Qc51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Book launch: the Notorious Captain Hayes https://t.co/1FCDJlQHRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Tsunami and Tupaia https://t.co/cHMfPiRlkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Bully Hayes - the radio interview https://t.co/VEma6ANo8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Parking problems https://t.co/ntUzxTgyNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: the philosophy that has given us Donald Trump https://t.co/FDq2zYyQg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Review of The Notorious Captain Hayes https://t.co/bn7DVVWDVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Constitution #2 on Amazon https://t.co/EZ3HY2BkC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Working on a cruise ship https://t.co/YISNEUOqcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: TENACIOUS in Tahiti https://t.co/MGm6w5yHJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Tupaia a Tahitian bestseller https://t.co/IW7WeNkRTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Mutiny on the Harmony https://t.co/xXuBaXf0zN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Island of the Lost -- a view from the top https://t.co/sRq3TmMESs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Is Kindle Unlimited killing Indie publishing? https://t.co/LM1mveRyZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The unspeakable Trump https://t.co/ndXvifblsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Nebula Award winners 2016 https://t.co/EOFKi0I5uM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Nielson confirms slump in eBook sales https://t.co/49ujMEkMCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: History of the White House Women https://t.co/yag5bLUGZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: 007 wins https://t.co/h7J7c3Ngur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The Trump disaster https://t.co/ROm8SbZKHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraDuncombe1 Thank you!  That is very good to hear. And good luck with the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Rare TITANIC poster found in attic https://t.co/dOzlIuYXJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Sailing the seas again https://t.co/7tPKC971yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The Rubbish Truck guy https://t.co/w0pNOqF7bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Indie bestsellers April https://t.co/dnqVqbwwqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Erotic Stories for Punjabi Widows bought by Harper... https://t.co/KBlytjN34l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: HMS Pinafore https://t.co/v0nAsBTrev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: What did Bully Hayes look like? https://t.co/INDYovJYhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Japanese pancakes ...  okonomiyaki https://t.co/rfkvVT5hJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: THE NOTORIOUS CAPTAIN HAYES -- the jacket https://t.co/ZXw4VavK8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The port of Rotterdam an indicator of the world ec... https://t.co/MlieNHKsYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Culture clash in Korea https://t.co/sLkuEyf4Xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Is digital reading on the decline? https://t.co/UWe0tbj5hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Sex and the sea https://t.co/uDd0ihqidR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Late mail delivery https://t.co/xQuElDC2OP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Wow, how sneaky is that? https://t.co/4hKpktPbh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Publishing opportunities for historians https://t.co/QO2zx3pgVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Underwater restaurant https://t.co/pkglN24vzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: More journalists slaughtered https://t.co/rV4QlwpyvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Travel scams https://t.co/foNQDCME44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Death Toll https://t.co/bqjbsLG7ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Save the Channel hovercraft! https://t.co/5KZ0x9egIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: The future for Peking https://t.co/iaoBdLUEHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: A new Beatrix Potter book! https://t.co/RLHN3dpMlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Preserved food for seamen and soldiers https://t.co/B4bhMNNerC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Second 19th century shipwreck located off W. Austr... https://t.co/RMwnsUIE7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Goodbye to a Wellington icon https://t.co/mEMrofnNqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: First Quarterdeck for 2016 https://t.co/iQZnFyjrT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World of the Written Word: Britannia's Spartan https://t.co/ctgkMFBeLH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>