<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimist people are not just cheerful people, they have better relationships and have to deal with less anxiety, stress &amp; depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot solve our problems with the same thinking we used when we created them. - Albert Einstein https://t.co/mQ6MHZmSYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our biggest fear is not failure, rejection or death but being ourselves. Let go of all the masks and just BE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give Back Thursday
Find ways to give back to others today- could be buying a coffee, donating old clothes or a smil… https://t.co/P3qe56g20E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about what others think of you. Just BE! https://t.co/8YHF7WBnuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From passion &amp; love, everything is possible. https://t.co/VJPyP1tmvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment. - Buddha https://t.co/nr1uDN4NPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about making mistakes or taking risks. Have the courage to say "yes" to life". https://t.co/54LkDj7pA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking: the talking of the soul with itself. - Plato https://t.co/SwhLBmL7zR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very little is needed to make a happy life; it is all within yourself, in your way of thinking. - Marcus Aurelius https://t.co/eACkPhZ7Wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give Back Thursday
Find ways to give back to others today- could be buying a coffee, donating old clothes or a smil… https://t.co/qOpiYlSfQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot solve our problems with the same thinking we used when we created them.
Albert Einstein https://t.co/in2HjNtjIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be impeccable with your words, not just what you say to others but ALSO what you say to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead. - Oscar Wilde https://t.co/4KTicJrQ9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you 100% believe that you will achieve your dream? Can you imagine living that future 'dream' of yours NOW? https://t.co/5Fqf0gqPbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give Back Thursday
Find ways to give back to others today- could be buying a coffee, donating old clothes or a smil… https://t.co/IK3OItmlR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world you see is the result of your perceptions. https://t.co/SlbL2qMElM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not take success or failure personally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one happiness in this life, to love and be loved. - George Sand https://t.co/sYw1OxTJv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our biggest fear is not failure, rejection or death but being ourselves. Let go of all the masks and just BE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimist people are not just cheerful people, they have better relationships and have to deal with less anxiety, stress &amp; depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle https://t.co/bRrBSyEo3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness. - Euripides https://t.co/MAgu4zKEBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment. - Buddha https://t.co/YnRM9fxMu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’ve struggled to follow through with your goals in past, you may find it helpful to answer these questions: https://t.co/LaELQwPQ7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to make 2017 Your Year? Then answer these questions: https://t.co/GjKPN4t1hX https://t.co/mSx02fBnbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is a journey where you grow daily as a person and give your best to every single moment. https://t.co/s0ERC2TLN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check this out before planning your 2017 goals. https://t.co/ERYWONPVLz
Happy goal setting. https://t.co/T6Jf1gCGQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot have a positive life and a negative mind. - Joyce Meyer https://t.co/z5x7AAB6BE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your intellect may be confused, but your emotions will never lie to you. - Roger Ebert https://t.co/DLf29AnuBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimist people are not just cheerful people, they have better relationships and have to deal with less anxiety, stress &amp; depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead. - Oscar Wilde https://t.co/9Fm0z6giKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle https://t.co/xSgS8dKJ45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mind is the fertile ground for the beliefs and ideas so avoid giving it negativity and fear based ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take responsibility for your actions instead of judging or blaming yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up every single morning and give your best in all you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best competition I have is against myself to become better."  - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make each day your very best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give the gift of growth to your loved ones this Xmas- a 90 mins coaching session to make 2017 their Best Year Ever.… https://t.co/2hv21DIZhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out John Wooden's ten pearls of wisdom here. https://t.co/BS0paYfUHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still looking for Christmas presents for your loved ones? Give the gift of growth this holiday season. https://t.co/q0TIqYRWR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be impeccable with your words, not just what you say to others but ALSO what you say to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our biggest fear is not failure, rejection or death but being ourselves. Let go of all the masks and just BE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment. - Buddha https://t.co/Tb5BjJ37GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your words heal rather than wound. Louise Hay https://t.co/iahOMY5wyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting on your shoulders is the most complicated object in the known universe. - Michio Kaku https://t.co/YGyNNBdM1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The eternal, blissful and natural state has been smothered by this life of ignorance.” - Sri Ramana Maharshi https://t.co/rKSaCPeQwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Abandon your belief in deprivation." - A Course in Miracles https://t.co/EllwjHpGss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends show their love in times of trouble, not in happiness. - Euripides https://t.co/NAPkG7tlPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one happiness in this life, to love and be loved. - George Sand https://t.co/Ke4iiQinEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid of happiness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is a journey where you grow daily as a person and give your best to every single moment. https://t.co/C42ARoDhMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you do in life, surround yourself with smart people who will argue with you." - John Wooden https://t.co/pQ4mMdKMSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay present when around family and friends. https://t.co/aPJqiei9h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't make/force others to think positive but you can always plant a seed of positive thought for those around… https://t.co/9sQwqBCNuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is on their own path and it is not your responsibility to change them. So let go and just be! https://t.co/Y7sNflRejT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimist people are not just cheerful people, they have better relationships and have to deal with less anxiety, stress &amp; depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not allow yourself to get lost in past or what yet to come. https://t.co/I8fUjsV6yA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flowers are restful to look at. They have neither emotions nor conflicts. - Sigmund Freud https://t.co/2PKQKL1zGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead. - Oscar Wilde https://t.co/Qb3YDpxqO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your intellect may be confused, but your emotions will never lie to you. - Roger Ebert https://t.co/OeL42Cf4p0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle https://t.co/yTmvWVZB5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the heart sees what is invisible to the eye. - H. Jackson Brown, Jr. https://t.co/z9x9g2CWjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure offers the opportunity to grow and path to the next level. Allow yourself to fail and let failure take you to success &amp; fulfilment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot have a positive life and a negative mind. - Joyce Meyer https://t.co/AJKJXStQNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put your heart, mind, and soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success. - Swami Sivananda https://t.co/ZfT5LG19HP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment. - Buddha https://t.co/57qgkQEbN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect and honour every single moment of your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting on your shoulders is the most complicated object in the known universe. - Michio Kaku https://t.co/px6suwxaiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is simple. Do what's right, the right way, at the right time. - Arnold H. Glasow https://t.co/hSu6fVDGTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your words heal rather than wound. Louise Hay https://t.co/0lopYiP3zW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aim for progress not perfection. https://t.co/pLprZ2iEaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no limitations to the self except those you believe in. – Jane Roberts https://t.co/8yrECKToRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I listen with my heart and hear myself. - Alan Cohen https://t.co/trfKGbuwLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a conscious vessel for the life force that is always flowing through you. - Christiane Northrup https://t.co/I56YWsBcXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are meant to shine! https://t.co/soaMO12Sbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I step out beyond the known to claim the riches of my true potential. - Alan Cohen https://t.co/nBSbI625iX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Own your true self. https://t.co/A8Sh4lNMFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the tomorrow that you have been waiting for to ……………………..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know what 2017 will look like? https://t.co/gXllGuLkJT https://t.co/s6uphlkbSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What have your beliefs created in your life so far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give yourself the permission to move out of the past and live in present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you mostly doubt  the positive and not the negative?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us always meet each other with smile, for the smile is the beginning of love. - Mother Teresa https://t.co/rh1TrQLmGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your words heal rather than wound. Louise Hay https://t.co/9SDBRSFPGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each relationship has at its heart, a holy purpose. - Doreen Virtue https://t.co/J684Tfdb80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignore the end result, and make the process your goal. https://t.co/TCkPGcRPh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness lies within you. Don't waste time and effort looking for it in the outside world. https://t.co/rdTfk8LfiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop playing small to please the people around you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big dream requires big action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are waiting for perfect timing to start something, you are always going to be waiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you love! https://t.co/xIsZyCwA5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose to enjoy living the life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about the choices you make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Stay hungry. Stay foolish.” - Steve Jobs https://t.co/RYLsMGkFVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To live a life that’s true to yourself, you need to live your values &amp; follow your dreams even when your choices ar… https://t.co/UZAmeEdgNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the most of your mornings. https://t.co/5HOlDm6r3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 things happy and success people don't do. https://t.co/B37DzppJrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are powerfully imprisoned by the terms in which we have been conducted to think. - Buckminster Fuller https://t.co/sXF4HgoCVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step. Think only about your first step, the rest will come. https://t.co/ik4XsjXXp0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>