<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to Lismore @ResearchSCU and looking forward to running #Turbocharge Publications and Thesis and orientation for new PhDs #phdchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to time with UTS teaching intensive staff talking about fitting writing into a busy day @utsnewsroom #ecrchat #turbocharge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@small_reynolds this was the tweet https://t.co/z0CGrQkNzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SleepGutsHealth I think this is the best way to write grants. A bit of Buzz and Elsa is always a good thing for the creative juices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DavidHobbs08 so only robots with no children and/or friends can be top scientists? Not in my experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSachaSB @UNSW @FranklinWomen great job Sacha. So glad you got on it and got it done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DavidHobbs08 @WriteThatPhD @PhDForum @PHDcomics @Dissertating @elfriesen @TiaCummins1 @AcademicPain love it and agree with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NataliaVeles excellent! We will be back at JCU in July and Nov 17. And they like your idea of a masterclass for previous  attendees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NataliaVeles at least it is a beautiful garden. May you PhD be so beautiful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClementJessicaH in Australia I would say a manuscript ready to be submitted for publication]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to our wonderful New Zealand friends https://t.co/Xt9drnzKA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kate_hayward_ @UBC @ithinkwellHugh we would love to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrScienceLover @sahmriAU yes great to talk about research and researchers. U can't have a coffee with us but u can watch us enjoying ours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AmyMilka great. And don't forget to park on the hill so you are ready to go next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrScienceLover love it. Wish I wasn't rushing around so much that I could think up something witty to write.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I agree completely. Or as I would put it - write a story for a 10 yr old, then write, read, write, read etc https://t.co/zOSwq1v1DD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Bull was so very generous with early career researchers. Such a kind and genuine person. I was terribly sadden… https://t.co/10LEjfGreV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hypocaffeinic great to hear. Keep it up and let me know how you get on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ithinkwellHugh and I very happy to sponsor the People's Choice award for the 5 minute research pitch #5RP won by… https://t.co/Mytud1zFRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Lizzie_Towl I promise to pay more attention in your drop, cover hold demos in future and to never call it drop, stop and rock ever again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to be on the other end for a change. Off to @Swinburne for @TheOtherKellyM PhD confirmation #proudsupervisor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, I agree with the FBI. So you know what this means - writing comes before emails each day! #acwri #ecrchat https://t.co/bN2QJR2qSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillianSGould I usually say go  next one down. But if feedback from reviewers is constructive &amp; u can make the changes u could try hi again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just reading PhD student evals of defeating #selfsabotage workshop and found this lovely comment. Nice to be promis… https://t.co/VT7b3BmWAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrRussellBrewer fantastic news and well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is hard. So yes regular short sessions make it easier https://t.co/oVUA11G1nd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A week of workshops for PhDs @MonashUni. See grad research website. All the top hits #7Secrets #turbochargewriting… https://t.co/lmNaAfEnmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many  in this group experienced #impostersyndrome Based on my experience with high performers- probabl… https://t.co/oYw1vigopl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic news Gillian - very excited for you https://t.co/zhPyeZQf5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fabulous visit to @ResearchSCU and special thanks to the fabulous Margie from @SCULibrary.  Such an asset to SCU staff @Geraldine_Mac16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Buffy! I love Trisha and her work https://t.co/Vy0Td2MLxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to be back @ResearchSCU with a full week of workshops https://t.co/syrKSiI1Yq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOtherKellyM this looks interesting https://t.co/aQTfrXPJ4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big congratulations Gillian. Very well deserved https://t.co/HsudVSaNcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cystic fibrosis. A terrible disease and so glad we have great researchers working on it. https://t.co/KNqUHvCibu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mentor, supervisor, co-author, person who taught me to write for publication and be a better researcher. Most of… https://t.co/zXkLLIyHDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BronwynHemsley not in my opinion. Law of diminishing returns. Take time off and reprioritise when recovered -ie jettison less impt stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howlingdingo I'll let you know how it goes. I only want it for my scientifically sanctioned napping and sleep monitoring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howlingdingo vibrates and wakes u up when u fall asleep so u learn to fall asleep. Do for 1hr for 5 nights Torture but works apparently2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howlingdingo I signed up for the info and they sent me a pretty detailed email. It is sleep retraining. The little device on your finger1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just took part in my first crowd funding campaign for a product. https://t.co/GTED4PvCDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great workshops coming up @CDUni Check out Cognitive Behavioural Coaching for High Performers Tue 9am Red9.1.45 https://t.co/3WxkHjilte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@reef_scientist @Alharborne very normal to feel that on your first day. Just remember that feelings are not facts-evidence is on your side!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a lift on a Monday morning and expose yourself to some culture at the same time https://t.co/ujLKSc0aol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LareenNewman @unisaresearch @UniversitySA @DrSiobhanBanks wow that stat is going straight into our Shameless Self Promotion workshop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@.joelrmcgregor that is awesome. Keep in touch and let me know how you go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@reef_scientist  it is a work in progress. See how you go tomorrow. This is experimental stage to see if morning or afternoon works best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be productive and then knock off instead of starting the day with email and then dragging out the day to catch up  https://t.co/cXm6ZwKWEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@reef_scientist @GriffithARI awesome. Sure Bella is very grateful. Let me know how you go (ps wear sunnies in the late pm - sleep better)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have gone on a bit long with my narrative 2/2 https://t.co/i0zBDDfNsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get stuck with your narrative speak it aloud. Kent the Aus Cattle Dog doing a great job listening 1/2 https://t.co/0VKVEwhbeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HDRs and ECRs @UON_research come and find out how the secret to high quality research lies in the narrative 2pm Tue https://t.co/MQvrOOvdgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hashtag research @DrScienceLover @wessidepraxis by some great researchers  https://t.co/aZSoPWUsMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much enjoying working with this wonderful group of future research leaders @FU_Research  https://t.co/5WEOdo5Tpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DHLangbecker hating emails is another good reason to leave them until last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to running Positioning yourself for Creative Funding @waiteresearch @tinabianco 9.30am Tuesday https://t.co/Ie66RHzDU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for an innovative PhD and a way to make a difference? https://t.co/hWYeCRdcgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronwynHemsley great to hear and looking forward to talking soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BronwynHemsley learning not to say yes while analysing frittata. Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SuEgan4 great to hear. Stay in touch and let me know how it goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@moninya @ @SuEgan4 @UNSWScience great let me know how it goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to @CQUni @appleton_CQU to work with amazing ECRs. Writing is on today-narrative is what  improves quality! https://t.co/ABCD1l6BgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes @reef_scientist @GriffithARI it's not how long you sit at the desk or spend in the lab. It's the output that matters #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Karen_P_Best yep and the jumbo jet closest to landing is as good as any #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Nadine_Painter @GriffithARI lets get the tube &amp; balls working right so we can fit a life in too #ecrchat #phdchat https://t.co/ByxlngQ6Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to talking to the Women in Research Network @UNSWnews @SuEgan4.  120 registered! 10am Wed https://t.co/vswO97kyyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IvankaPrichard great. How did it go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope to see lots of new HDR students @VicUniWgtn on Tuesday. Always a fab event run by the wonderful @Lizzie_Towl https://t.co/1va1Nmq6aL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PhD supervisors @UnitecNZ Auckland 9.30 Mon Let's see if we can take some of the lows out of the ride-for them &amp; you https://t.co/oT7wIYZhGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@donnelley  best tip is to pick one new strategy that really appeals and give it a red hot go. Don't try everything at once #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrScienceLover @JamesTamplin halve the number of meetings, do your work first and whatever time is left do emails (as a treat!)  #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DavidHobbs08 @ithinkwellHugh @FlindersCSEM @FU_Research @Flinders @FlindersLib @ScienceChiefAu Agree. I think is our job to promote this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencechloe I am sure it is the latter 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand new workshop @unisaresearch @UniSAnewsroom Wed 1.30 Positioning yourself for Non-Traditional Funding #ecrchat https://t.co/M5uSlo7Smo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A double header @unisaresearch @UniSAnewsroom this Wed. 9.00am Cognitive Behavioural Coaching for High Performers https://t.co/nSUQWhtOLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LareenNewman I can absolutely believe this. It is the model we use in our coaching. It provided motivation and accountability #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know  https://t.co/dwO1yaDrXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julesette thanks. I will have a look at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LareenNewman. I would like to promote it to my workshop participants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LareenNewman when are you running this? Goes with the one I am running at unisa next week positioning yourself for non traditional funding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LareenNewman @TheTattooedProf I call it reporting to the shareholders #ecrchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LareenNewman @TheTattooedProf I strongly encourage ECRs to promote their work. I see it that the taxpayer paid for it so get it out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencechloe never mind. I will be back a couple of times next year as well as at a lot of other unis. Am sure we'll catch up at some stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencechloe congrats on being so close - very exciting Staying at Jesmond. Waiting for final program - will let u no. Hugh running SSP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sciencechloe you're at UoN aren't you? If so I'll be there running Turbocharge your Writing on Tues Sept 13th 2pm. Be good to see you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidHobbs08 very sad to read this. Not the sort of life anyone wants to lead. Postdoc life is very hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NataliaVeles yes writing it down is better but it can feel yuck because now everyone can see how "bad" your are. Feelings are not facts!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@bluecology @GriffithARI great to hear Chris. Can't wait to see how everyone has gone when I come back in a month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@simonrogersNZ @ResearchSCU @SCULibrary @SCUonline thanks Simon. Yes it truly does work for most people. Good luck and let me know how u go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrScienceLover thanks for your wise and soothing words. All sorted. Nana times ahead! https://t.co/WSc8HbfwWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrKirrilly I agree completely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@geochemista thanks Ellen. It was a lovely group to work with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kirstenbenkend @ResearchSCU lovely to see you today Kirsten after all these years and chuffed that I am the subject of your first tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A room full of supervisors waiting to hear the #7secrets of highly successful RHD students @ResearchSCU https://t.co/jVk71Di3Qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LareenNewman @DeanHristov this agrees very much with my exp. Similar for ECRs who also need to publish early in their career #ECRchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrNatOsborne give it a go and see what happens. Very unlikely anyone will email you and say "hey, I don't like you doing that"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard it from @appleton_CQU, but not sure where it originally came from  https://t.co/3Ved8Oxz8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomenSTEM session on Shameless Self Promotion or as I call it Reporting to the Shareholders Wed 9.30 @Griffith_Uni https://t.co/V5G0KE9xQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@reef_scientist  the answer for tardy admin is "I'm working on papers". Make sure you still do impt admin. Just leave the less impt stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reef_scientist @GriffithARI excellent Emma. Clearing the skies in reef research!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>