<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May, demand an end to Trump’s Muslim ban https://t.co/P5sg2g6Hun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back #AMillionDecisions. #NHS &amp; #healthcare needs librarians with the knowhow to get the right evidence #HEELKS https://t.co/1kPyVgjyrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @Opodo_UK so much. App tells me booking's failed, takes money off anyway &amp; then they  tell me 30 days to get a refund. #lostcustomer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget Nineteen Eighty-Four. These five dystopias better reflect Trump’s US

https://t.co/01IvIkGjRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember as a kid in the 60s hearing sirens &amp; thinking the bomb had dropped. Think this is most concerned for future I've been since then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. https://t.co/P0uPbaF1Om

Seems justified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand safety of White Helmet rescue worker abducted during Aleppo evacuation https://t.co/Tzk8mbgD9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good &amp; relevant article.

https://t.co/LOjFYljJ67

Thanks to @lizmcgettigan for sharing. #librariesmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These seem to be well received. https://t.co/ZojLY2qSqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to seem unduly optimistic https://t.co/fqVZIITKIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franco could be deported because Sweden says he couldn’t "prove" he's gay. Here's how you can help:  https://t.co/MCxTwEPgiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COSLA plans social media drive to show 'real budgets' https://t.co/uS1sLt2QfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not waste an opportunity. Help us call on Shona Robison MSP to invest in neonatal services #babyreportscotland https://t.co/ZD8TWGLsn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bertrand Russell

"Dogmatism is an enemy to peace, and an insuperable barrier to democracy 

https://t.co/h1o5uRgE59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He just looks like a really bad actor trying to play the President. https://t.co/QztYptLjcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A (redacted) poem for the torture report

https://t.co/8J1FsVc6cS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really interesting and timely paper. https://t.co/yZKs3U1PN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dLpA1vIS6v

So I finish reading transcript of a Trump interview and then find this. Enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Howling Wolf then?

Dogs 'prefer reggae and soft rock' to other music genres, research suggests - https://t.co/1mQalCrKMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizmcgettigan no argument with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizmcgettigan not diminishing importance of staff at all, just that bringing in others' skills to complement  can make better libraries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 went AWOL. Would argue that success of libraries calls for potent mix of skills, librarians working with others. https://t.co/g7W6FwvQzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vanishing point: the rise of the invisible computer

https://t.co/MSERgXQSxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth sharing this again #librariesmatter

John Bird slams absence of library funding in autumn statement

https://t.co/Tp4GumBJSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen this quoted. Powerful &amp; true

Bobby Kennedy on GDP: 'measures everything except that which is worthwhile'

https://t.co/Ssfgo4t2sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health of children in Scotland 'among worst in Europe' - https://t.co/SoHyDdHPCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CILIPScotland Slightly tardy but massive congratulations on getting this level of coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really, really good discussion at the @SLIC1991 Board away day. Challenging, constructive, creative &amp; relevant. #headfullofideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irvine Welsh backs campaign against Scottish library cuts https://t.co/mWfo1J3jdK via @thebookseller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just supported #amilliondecisions  on @ThunderclapIt // @CILIPinfo https://t.co/BC7SldUIC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizmcgettigan  can I take issue with the quote? Libraries are totality of experiences they offer, in and through outreach from, them. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An afternoon's hard thinking in Dundee at the @SLIC1991 board away day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought this would be of interest to you @kennyhay564 https://t.co/TAud86eHPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought this would be relevant for you @FletcherEastRen https://t.co/TAud86eHPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen this? @lizmcgettigan 

Scottish firm creates 'digital classroom' for refugees - https://t.co/vEfuAgZxHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought this might be of interest. @Cllr_Mary https://t.co/TAud86eHPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/DlK5zPPZoD

Setting out the powerful and persuasive case for libraries ahead of May's local government elections in Scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 in a row at @ccfest. Calexico, Aziza Brahim &amp; Piers Faccini and, especially, Derek Gripper, all very good. Next up Orchestra Baobab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "Future Days" by CAN on @Sonos

Sad to see their drummer, Jaki Liebezeit, has died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkable music from @derekgripper at #CelticConnections tonight. A delight to listen to and a marvel to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "Make Me a Pallet on Your Floor" by Piers Faccini on @Sonos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "Quicksilver Daydreams of Maria" by Piers Faccini on @Sonos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard horror stories about @Opodo_UK but never had any problems - until now. Caught up all in one go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd time round on the @Opodo_UK call holding music and counting.

AAAAAARRRRRRRGGGGHHHHHH!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you stand up for human rights, President Trump? Take action now https://t.co/33wLulHXdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed your set. Thank you. https://t.co/FUG752tGLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the secret to productivity isn’t longer hours

https://t.co/REWrPkyFMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0b3R2p05i1

As worn by @camilolara at @ccfest last night. Hard to argue with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And very good it was. https://t.co/SSfM7boday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please look at this - https://t.co/YEXxxh1UBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On 17.33 to East Kilbride, automated announcement says we are now approaching Giffnock. Erm no, just left there this is actually Clarkston.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All good &amp; true but not just about libraries remaining popular, it's about their potential. Not where they are now… https://t.co/B3E1tmcQyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good. https://t.co/w1vO9PZksc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundance: Grateful Dead Doc 'Long Strange Trip' Goes to Amazon https://t.co/W6BbKxKwSS

Date's in the diary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Paris jazz clubs – chosen by musicians and experts

https://t.co/crV4QWShE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children unnecessarily removed from parents, report claims

https://t.co/phbr9MsFle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the NHS is performing miracles - https://t.co/gIBk6hJRTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're 'Ordering' GPs Are You, Mrs May? https://t.co/DqpDP5WeYC via @HuffPostUKPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is very hard to improve your swimming technique if you are struggling to keep your head above water"

https://t.co/GMNf9wkmkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHScotland  And very good it was too. One down, six to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Council job cuts have finally caught up with me – but I'm relieved

https://t.co/0HN9YGiSiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to share in new @CHScotland panel members pre service training in Clydebank today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles, lovers and light: David Hockney at 80

https://t.co/bol3h6p7uG

Really do want to get to this, preferably more than once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@walkyouhome  Also interesting distinction in the article between children and "regular users".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe everyone should be on the organ register automatically. Sign the petition here: https://t.co/pB7802PfFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is Scottish Premiership faring in latest Uefa benchmarking report? - https://t.co/JYe2EiZ2bO

Not cheerful reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relevant and thought-provoking, including some #libraries type thoughts. https://t.co/NgTgd0XdeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to disagree though many of the comments are just bloody depressing. https://t.co/iQvDuHTU8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "It Hurts Me Too" by Elmore James on @Sonos

How good is this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will give it a go. https://t.co/peQwHM8mX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to all of them. https://t.co/hVMBhmVBRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Farren: The Titanic Sails at Dawn – a classic feature from the vaults.

It's 40 years old but worth a read.

https://t.co/aJF9OfcBX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zlY7HcyQKT

And some catching up to do ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cZcdFsAKQy

Looking like a good year ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "Botyiaki ntembe" by Wendo Kolosoy on @Sonos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lot of food for thought here, including implications for #libraries 

https://t.co/jv6TrINhvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant boards: how to create the best voluntary sector set of trustees

https://t.co/jJT44vL8SY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordering from @waitrose, enter my email address, get told have used prohibited characters and services have detected may be malicious. Que?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing vinyl for first time in years and having to adapt to how short an LP's sides last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumpers https://t.co/LmnQGoWZ3Z 

Just got this on vinyl from Ebay. Listening to it, it has its moments but much is just bloody ponderous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A: Scotland's 2017 council elections - https://t.co/F4Ryi1dZPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists say your “mind” isn’t confined to your brain, or even your body https://t.co/9lLSwcmNzs via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repeat after me, it's not a library. Lovely wee idea but a library it ain't. The perception  that it is accounts fo… https://t.co/KcHGS6FxXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[' @oxfamgb  Supports VG cause, just doesn't help achieve freeing up space objective. Old Penguin HG Wells short stories, originally 3/6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering why @EastRenCouncil is allowing a banner from a competitor gym to be on the railings at Williamwood HS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairly sure that when you give books to Oxfam buying more from their stock isn't the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just supported Fiona Ferguson on BT MyDonate https://t.co/f8Ef3yWg8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are at any risk of feeling optimistic, read this set of tweets. https://t.co/rCg5hpBn2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bNkzswYw81

Just caught up with this, it is so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting worried. Finding this filing malarkey quite satisfying and (almost) enjoyable. Maybe an age thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope this is as good as it looks. https://t.co/JgqZvKReDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best or worst of a series this morning, depending on your taste in puns. https://t.co/g5S9QwE49M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhallsworth  I don't know but I suspect mix of genuine desire to be universal plus political/PR concern over anything that wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to start on filing. This could take some time. I hate filing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universal basic income trials being considered in Scotland

https://t.co/R41l70eVfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine in 10 elite Scotland athletes from 'middle class' background - https://t.co/QwzhDPEx7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent @indy100  Powerful story but I doubt she wanted to study *astrology* at Princeton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying "Ayo Ayo Nene" by Mor Thiam on @Sonos

Musical start to the year - From @Soundway playlist. Rather good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we heading towards a 'post human rights world'? - https://t.co/1tOCCLQN7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Argument also goes: if they haven't actually done that, they've probably done  something else, so it all balan… https://t.co/5mqvoQFnhl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>