<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@slaithwaitecc great knock from Cameron Cross today playing first grade at Naenae 128 from the little Maori fella ðŸ‘ðŸ’ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shows people have a sense of humour on here, mention a joke to @TrentWoodhill and he laughs. Same @markmywordsAM who blocks ya #warnie ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrentWoodhill @zamps63  Sorry your wrong @Redman108 once got interviewed at Kirkburton by Greavsy back in 2000 with Austin Powers teeth ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsAM Warney didn't need to practisssss, you did, get over it. Good average though what was it again #canyouremember ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz @lukewright204 @evangulbis great 2 c banter from 3 Naenae players. Magic,Mr Wright for the seniors, Mr Gulbis for the 3rds ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deita looks like the firebirds have a similar victory song as the Stingrays ? Well done @grantelliottnz and @wgtnfirebirds ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW @nzherald Shane Warne can pull off shark togs, you can't ðŸ¦ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaz_Cocks wouldn't of beaten me or you at the Petone flat, he would though @whites29. #hairyears #eggsarnis #goodtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancook85 how's it going bud? Who scored.... Delroy ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan Alistair Cooks birthday today, what slag off lines have u got for him Quiers? KP is waiting? #hbcaptaincook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW Shane Warnes got black swans in his pool, which is bigger than that ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsy100 @kirkburtoncc @HolmbridgeCC @DenbyCricketClu remember playing at Denny years back and overdosed on protein wi alt midges ðŸœðŸœðŸœ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW Shane Warne does not need to worry he's got a personal Barista #mojo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW Shane Warne has been conducting rowing lessons of Rob Waddell FYI ðŸ’ªðŸ‘€ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW Shane Warne could eat that quicker than youðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaz_Cocks my old man n bro are there pal #intheleftsideoverhere #normanwhiteside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished an episode of GOT with @IAMLenaHeadey , turn over and see Jodie Whittaker in Broadchurch, a night of #shelleyhightalent in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW Shane Warne would smash his Brekky quicker than you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whites29 they won 3-0 stop moaning and update the weather #michaelfish x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@breaking80nz coming for a pint lad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@breaking80nz when u playing there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz @garyplayer on par with @GeoffreyBoycott that lad #fatherfigure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliansavea7 had some moves today roboting to the street drummer #slick #fastfeet https://t.co/JtmKyr4CFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilesDavisLive I'm in Chicago Friday Miles..... #tinkle #nobcc #gocubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johntraceyjack cheers Rooley, was great to see you and remember Tom is always welcome at Naenae. #bensonhedge #creamflow #trousers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheardypants @htafcdotcom thanks Sheardy, good bumping into you and UTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveLarder thanks Dids and likewise. Was great to see you and the family. Till next time bud and look forward to one day seein u down under]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeSchlemmer congrats on the debut Romeo, keep up the good work #romancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mattwood100 haha good stories Ron, great to see ya last night pal and will give your regards to your colleagues at Upper Hutt #baison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adollive be at grove in 15 if ya coming for a pint lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htafcdotcom @johnsmithstadia will do, if you need a left winger can borrow some boots and be available. Ps I've still got wheels ðŸ‘ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adollive @HuwElvis after work pal for normal people about 5.30 ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@htafcdotcom not many flying from NZ to watch the mighty Terriers this wknd #UTT #maskellncecerestillupfront? https://t.co/EOtJB9YsdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis @adollive I'm not pal I'm afraid. Maybe next Sunday can pop up to yours or quick pint at the bull?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis @adollive I here #huwcam is live aye @DGlover86 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #huwsgotfans #famous #cymru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis fancy a beer next Thurs after work you big oaf? @adollive u keen? Going to GroveðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gangster @LukeSchlemmer  Cam says wuss up https://t.co/yckZEpPDwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CellyWratt @LukeSchlemmer nah mate, he will be out doing coffee and writing poems with 30 mins of throw dens squeezedin #romeo #ladiesman ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flintoff11 u commentating down under this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HitchmanKyle @CWCCJuniors @CWCC_cricket Huddersfield is a great place to play cricket. Is the WG Grace back left? C u when u get back ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wrk04 @SkyNews all good man I didn't feel it I am in Auk on business and was when I was asleep pal ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz haha u should come out for a hit with me n block mate over summer when you are free #300onthefly maybe even get Woodytoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz Sky Sports 3 now a game u did quite well in 2015. Karori vs NobCC at Ben Burn ðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜ŽðŸ˜œ #guatengshuffle #proudboycs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deancalcutt @GRoy28 @digger_bar @CFletcher89 @sargeyboy24 @Newsy100 average age that lot don't look like Carlton drinkrs. #64yroldinyellowðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deancalcutt @GRoy28 @digger_bar @CFletcher89 @sargeyboy24 @Newsy100 when's pub n club happening lads? Not seen any news ðŸ‘ #MOMfordiggaagain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis @DGlover86 could of done with that today mate in the GC they were everywre. Mal sure u keep working on those quads like DG #masive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis see your style has got better with your watermelon hat ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚, still enjoying #huwcam @DGlover86 #cymru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevo208 like a fine wine pal, well batted #gobig ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilesDavisLive you having laugh Miles, Yorkies are the backbone #tinkle #nobcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KP24 @DGoughie a man from Barnsley drinking that #neyseeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeSchlemmer hope ya well Don Whaun de Marco ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad enough seeing your big sweaty head on cam @HuwElvis never mind other sweaty parts aye @DGlover86 #Sweatyarse #huwcam #daftasabrush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whites29 just go and have a pint ya dick or sorry #halfanewcybrown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HB big man look forward to some golf this summer â›³ï¸ðŸŒðŸŽ‚ðŸ‘ https://t.co/jcmnWZEtbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate these things ðŸ˜³ https://t.co/FEMD0qMo2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U can have more or less anything u want, something that u don't have though is dignity @LewisHamilton and that's why your a ðŸ””ðŸ”š IMO. #noclass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@root66 is all class when ya down in NZ next a pint is on me..... #wawaw #ahseh https://t.co/pdpdwzE1Fo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan build a bridge ya ðŸ””ðŸ”š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanSidebottom used be part of the Longley Park GC massive those two ðŸ‘€ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan second half was different though #canesno1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeSchlemmer @cricketwgtn @wgtnfirebirds @BLACKCAPS congrats those concerned, I know someone else who should have one #romeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deancalcutt @moice82 only thing he does in his pocket now is billiards ðŸ‘ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moice82 spot on pal, hope u and fam bam are well ðŸ‘ðŸ’ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkburtoncc @HoylandswaineCC @moice82 He would of been waiting for David Lockwood with his hotter at the ready ðŸ‘ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz good luck mate will be cheering the @ZouksOfficial on in the coming weeks. @GeoffreyBoycott will be proud ðŸ‘ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirkburtoncc @Golcarcc miss the drakes league cricket but not the weather ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moice82 Nortonthorpe or Naenae but result isn't in yet. Butter 91no @DGlover86  1 for 106 of 3 and I'm 12* off 81 balls ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis looks like @DGlover86  needs to get tut gym and work of his sausage n hash brown sarnis. #stupidgrintwinsx https://t.co/qFaC37vSgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyNeesh bit more than green island vs uni grange Jimmy ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianbrown in Beunos Aries where is the classic #addidasstore help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alphaclee11 congrats to u and fam bam big lad ðŸ‘ hope alls well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wrk04 @BunnyOnions @Stevo208 He once yorked me at 90mph in NZ but I still beat him at golf ðŸ‘ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DijaRyder great knock mate #turnofpace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucybaby81 u working for the Welsh now Chris lad? Keep up the good week youngun ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DijaRyder Roosters still a chance #lookforthechook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAMLenaHeadey Miss Headey, coming to LA in January, u around for a coffee? Or will S or J be there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgianaLuissa what's needle doing in Town ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgianaLuissa I get it all the time don't stress ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class where's Sticks? https://t.co/1oHcRH2Iek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DijaRyder come on the Eagles get up #zaidijenkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CellyWratt @Youngerweireld @premierleague maybe will have to see....... Tough gig for anyone #haymoiskeen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CellyWratt @Youngerweireld @premierleague The horse has bolted on the league, Sums Evertons season up #alwaysnxtyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CellyWratt @Youngerweireld @premierleague so they should too Marcel. I lived n breathed football all my life and seen nothing like this b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Youngerweireld @CellyWratt @premierleague jealousy gets you no where in this world congrats Leicester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@korulounges what is it with the food in Domestic Koru lounge in Auk it is terrible. Wellington and Chch are top notch #needssorting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaz_Cocks @yorkcityfc Listen to Cocker York City he knows his shit, drinks classy top shelf, smokes gars and is a power dresser #highflyerðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGlover86 @ollidavidson Burks getting ready for weekends cricket wi our Kes ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¾ https://t.co/7NpiIJPPNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialDHCL @johntraceyjack Hope Sir Ron Tindal is providing thee wi Wooly hats, mittens n crampons rooley fut wknd #beinswimersatmarsden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGlover86 @ShepleyCricket Ask Burks why we called him Russell all day then he found out @gordontinsel had put a crow in his bag.. ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGlover86 @GRoy28 @ShepleyCricket @kirkburtoncc if I wa playing ad still be batting now esp if Glover n Burks wa bowling #creamflow ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DijaRyder @EAG_Kia great work bro hope alls well and watch out for #brucey popping up somewhere #multi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samtomkins1 come back to the NRL Sam, SL is awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TennantCompany great day at the opening of Tennant Australia with your president CK #greatwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DGlover86 @HuwElvis pair en yams got nowt on there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwElvis @DGlover86 bit of a belly coming on there pal.....bit more cardio and you will look like your hero #huwcam #hooellllis #liiiigend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ollidavidson thought the same #johngill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantelliottnz congrats on your ODI career buddy #geoffisproud #magicloveshisvegetables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whites29 @Wadderz1 only thing you've ever killed is Becky buckets Tash when ya breathed on her #turnip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainobrien @LegBreakGoogly1 Absolute clown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wadderz1 Haha Mustard once bowled me out on Mokis first ball however there's always watching @whites29 playing pool to laugh at #terrible]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>