<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Executive Order on Immigration — Detrimental Effects on Medical Training and Health Care — NEJM https://t.co/FWOW2A7a4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of stem cells: tackling hype versus hope https://t.co/Wr1Ou6xeml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic fetal monitoring, cerebral palsy, and caesarean section: assumptions versus evidence | The BMJ https://t.co/F4eWC7ncNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Efficacy of paracetamol for spinal pain &amp; OA: systematic review. Time to move out of the Aus top 10 prescriptions? https://t.co/bZHozXwiHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 drugs 2015–16 Australian Prescriber - prescribed paracetamol still in the top 10 https://t.co/mEmXMM5LkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EBM and the gap between humanism and scientific evidence: an essay by Iona Heath https://t.co/gPAS0MzB1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another reason you need to be able to speak fluent EBM: Cancer drugs, survival, and ethics https://t.co/CqE48PWx4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting perspective on recent events: Path dependency—Trump, Brexit, and the future Europe - https://t.co/NtZ97wXKk5 via @Shareaholic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A British perspective: should healthy people take a vitamin D supplement in winter months? https://t.co/y2Wd1axNYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treatment of ‘Lyme disease’ - WA Tribunal reprimands and fines GP following unprofessional conduct https://t.co/Nr57eMKeqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cranberry still just a fruit, not a medicine - Cranberry Capsules’ Effect on Bacteriuria and Pyuria https://t.co/O1DfewUJFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite number - the number needed to treat...Statins for Primary Prevention https://t.co/8Fz6TV3p5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPIs and community acquired pneumonia - increased risk of pneumonia appears to precede PPI use https://t.co/S5JBEYnWdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do women with recurrent genital herpes at time of delivery need a cesarean section? https://t.co/SRUvjafhcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future just arrived. Fully Implanted Brain–Computer Interface in a Locked-In Patient with ALS — NEJM https://t.co/j7CYDrpnbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-medical people may ask why an RCT to improve hand hygiene is even needed! Measuring hand hygiene when it matters https://t.co/mpaXXsL0mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does antimalarial mass drug administration increase or decrease the risk of resistance? https://t.co/WWQPfegmkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer is NO by the way... https://t.co/amX9foP7y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vitamin D Deficiency — Is There Really a Pandemic? — NEJM https://t.co/0zm6xl8WBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickrolyat I was just taking the opportunity for a dreadful pun! In truth (for certain) I believe uncertainty is central to all medicine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No benefit of steroids in septic shock- Hydrocortisone and Septic Shock in Patients With Severe Sepsis JAMA https://t.co/3WIiggWHrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not sure that I agree with this…Tolerating Uncertainty — The Next Medical Revolution? — NEJM https://t.co/uVROqo3uFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrible reminder of the inherent risks of drug development -  NEJM https://t.co/G4p81gtJQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron @sanj971 Cultures of abscesses essential in a rapidly changing resistance environment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron @sanj971 In ACT GP sourced isolates of S.aureus 97% cotrimoxazole sens, 92% fluclox, 85% clindamycin, 95% doxycycline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron @sanj971 This is best study that I know of wrt ABs and small abscesses. Local resistance will determine AB choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early report but exciting: Remission of Follicular Lymphoma after Treatment for Hepatitis C Virus Infection — NEJM https://t.co/d4PIDdw1rR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No difference in the five-Year Outcomes after Off-Pump or On-Pump Coronary-Artery Bypass Grafting — NEJM https://t.co/ZHzDjBktV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEJM invited Clinton and Trump to submit a piece on their respective health policies. Surprise! Only HC responded https://t.co/QNTocbqZS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes my breath away (or not): Randomized Trial of Long-Term Oxygen for COPD with Moderate Desaturation — NEJM https://t.co/HNqcJb2odb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More disappointment in the sepsis trials world:Levosimendan for prevention of Acute Organ Dysfunction in Sepsis NEJM https://t.co/fVLcSKQb3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good summary of the recent NEJM paper on mammography:  https://t.co/6MpLi2AdeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patient-Reported Outcomes after Monitoring, Surgery, or Radiotherapy for Prostate Cancer — NEJM https://t.co/ejTHogFCdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Year Outcomes after Monitoring, Surgery, or Radiotherapy for Localized Prostate Cancer — NEJM https://t.co/RHE66U5LZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breast-Cancer Tumor Size, Overdiagnosis, and Mammography Screening Effectiveness — NEJM https://t.co/RJqjC5Hjq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Surgeon Is Probably a Republican, Your Psychiatrist Probably a Democrat, via @nytimes https://t.co/nQEyI629rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less,sometimes, really is more https://t.co/OAlIlgZYOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central crushing chest pain? Quick,open the cath lab.Fever, rigors,bacteraemia?Let's have a think about that... https://t.co/r1oe0GYOKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The precision paradox? https://t.co/Da9bvCL14e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worldwide Thyroid-Cancer Epidemic? The Increasing Impact of Overdiagnosis — NEJM https://t.co/oAPILsCM8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brother Michael writing on Don Dale and the failure of arntarnte-areme - Eureka Street https://t.co/VUVo9QtbuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ‘Useless’ Surgery Is Still Popular https://t.co/T8JjOECVf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning Will Robinson!Similar early outcomes in Australian RCT of robot v open prostatectomy https://t.co/qNVTpRbH42 https://t.co/HVMXbc0D5x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another ripper from Michael Li for HOC fans. House of Canberra https://t.co/pcwk7NPZHf via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing animation from ANU medical student Michael Li for GOT fans Game of Canberra https://t.co/CpGxnaRSAH via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about One Disease’s achievements in controlling scabies in the Northern Territory over the past year https://t.co/w08xx8Orj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must read for anyone treating children with serious infections: The Lancet Infectious Diseases https://t.co/Z4q4Noo0Tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great editorial on costly drugs - especially the suggestions how non-Pharma groups could change PBS indications. https://t.co/JPRoPhc2dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IV NSAID may be better than morphine: Non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs for renal colic - The Lancet https://t.co/t936A0MPTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer seems to be no! 
Does paracetamol still have a future in osteoarthritis? - The Lancet https://t.co/hHoulg3WU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antidepressants may not be as effective as thought &amp; shouldn't be only treatment for depression https://t.co/9YNF1vJqkg via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richmond's amazing win tonight actually overshadowed by Jack Riewoldt's eloquent post match support for Alannah and Madeline foundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compare Australian guidelines to US Preventive Services Task Force which recommend against PSA -with a Capital D https://t.co/C3bG3r08rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust Cancer Council recommendations for prostate cancer screening and treatment-still includes PSA screening option https://t.co/5jlP2wxaUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caroline_J @FJB1923 @WWeno7 Thank you Caroline.  it was a great program and Mark's compassion and humility shown throughout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Dr Mark Wenitong on Australian Story on the ABC. Great, humble, wise man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAMA review of Lyme Disease, Human Granulocytic Anaplasmosis, and Babesiosis https://t.co/wTHwGqToCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trentyarwood I have an awesome daughter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter made this for the launch of ‘Infectious’ - everyone ate it despite the warning! It was delicious. https://t.co/04tkR15HVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The overwhelming power of personal experience: Anti-vax mum gets whooping cough https://t.co/r7i55Qcy2L via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No benefit of Longer-Term antibiotic Therapy for Symptoms Attributed to Lyme Disease — NEJM https://t.co/BB5NsmStKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it is a special April date but my new book is released today...(seriously!) https://t.co/1IFWBl0yto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NBA v DVTs! https://t.co/ItWW77582I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron purulent discharge and definite surrounding cellulitis would justify a short course of cotrim but otherwise  better to avoid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron If it was infection and not just colonisation cotrim is appropriate in light of the options available]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron Trimethoprim alone is safer but depends on the condition. UTIs  sensitive in 70-80% of cases of uncomplicated UTI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbetron it's really just an update of the evidence (which remains scanty) and highlights need for more interventional studies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New US guidelines for Screening for Gonorrhea, Chlamydia, and Hepatitis B https://t.co/0ucww7Gnf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAMA Viewpoint: Pregnancy in the Time of Zika https://t.co/x4ayBAsuFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Hospitals Prepare for Penis Transplants - it's in JAMA too!  https://t.co/GT87UCsX3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAMA study that IV antibiotic exposure in early infancy does not produce excessive weight gain during childhood https://t.co/rzqhQ5I7Tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquieGS @FJB1923 and nice to e-meet you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Causes of Outbreaks of Vaccine-Preventable Diseases in the United States https://t.co/y826qOgHID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does paracetamol still have a future in osteoarthritis? - The Lancet https://t.co/SGPEXYAZoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must read for all prescribers: Reducing the Risks of Relief — The CDC Opioid-Prescribing Guideline — NEJM https://t.co/jEeJoy3Am9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You're putting my child at risk': Adam Bandt's plea to anti-vaxxers -  https://t.co/seMVxKZUfv via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red spot specials: the fall and rise of Australian measles • Inside Story https://t.co/eupFO2qPUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modelling suggesting Zika virus effects in pregnancy will recede quickly as population wide immunity rises https://t.co/5xmOT72csC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C.D.C. Investigating 14 New Reports of Zika Transmission Through Sex https://t.co/xzx0rx6XYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and public health in the US - strange bedfellows indeed. https://t.co/lY33HeZLNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and the brand name is usually easier to pronounce than the generic name... https://t.co/iPzXyiyhKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful news for the (largely) iatrogenic Egyptian Hepatitis C epidemic https://t.co/tDth0yvowf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important study of mass treatment of scabies in Fiji with implications for Australia - see https://t.co/zv9IVv7b2S https://t.co/eKvKnqlfLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It all depends on how you define 'good':
Are Good Doctors Bad for Your Health? https://t.co/9edyy2fdZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will trend for 'active surveillance' of prostate cancer(ie yrly biopsy) mean more infectious deaths than 1-off biopsy &amp; prostatectomy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A year old but relevant to my last tweet. Still need to see good data on transperineal biopsy &amp; infection https://t.co/hEjAiuvFFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early Prostate Cancer Cases Fall Along With Screening https://t.co/B93f4HoF6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Efforts to limit antimicrobial resistance are threatened by lack of evidenced control policies, review warns https://t.co/bgtG0SDuMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editorial to go with the paper from my previous tweet. Nosocomial transmission of avian influenza virus A (H7N9) https://t.co/3Ui0Zsnmcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who really discovered antibiotics? https://t.co/IAPSbGdK9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disseminated methicillin-sensitive Staph aureus infection resulting from a paracervical abscess after acupuncture
 https://t.co/2z3XAGJvyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old truism reiterated: https://t.co/nyiJ4SvXmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long-term Effects of Fecal Transplants Questioned https://t.co/bFuqL6Ul0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very balanced piece about the arguments regarding euthanasia  https://t.co/rKnEaTYYfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See! Everything is an infection...(OK, it's just one study) https://t.co/hw64ggMbGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to keep the issue on the front burner -Abolishing Mammography Screening Programs? View from Swiss Medical Board https://t.co/1OZZznDfFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tea and Consent https://t.co/Lp56v5jY9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Prevent Malaria in Humans, Scientists Try Protecting Pigs https://t.co/uwVD4MXNxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ranjit Chandra: how reputation bamboozled the scientific community https://t.co/U6rYT2IFCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MERS—an uncertain future - The Lancet Infectious Diseases https://t.co/Qbwvv549hG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>