<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Two white-haired couples on a double date in Timothy's are having a heated debate about what shows and movies can be considered #improv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regarding the d20: a) Finnick is perhaps the most meta of our characters, b) it's a metaphor for luck, his defining… https://t.co/fegrTv1RaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoannaHaughton @agmours @CavernsPod Oh, murderhobo is a VERB. J'ai compris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for listening, JW! And for the feedback. Be sure to get in on our next contest! https://t.co/uVNz1O9QXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GKyleScott @MaddoxCampbell the red under your eyes was that much more foreboding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod I really want to know who wrote this. Are there any "good accents" in C&amp;C?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A much older @camalgie is carelessly eating Cheetos and very gently trying to make eye contact or conversation with uninterested TTC riders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for coming Elizabeth! We had a blast. See you next next month at #PotterProv if not before! https://t.co/C7m3gQM2pT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's so much wrong w/ this tweet, but there's NOTHING WRONG w/ MACRO NEATO! This delightfully directed improv sh… https://t.co/0NQDCT7C0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This streetcar driver sure knows the appropriate time and place for these dead animal jokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanie_malek Have you seen the end of Philisopher's Stone? Dumbledore straight up plays favourites &amp; breaks the rules to steal your win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't care about your happiness." - how everyone feels toward Draco Malfoy https://t.co/S7MH3hB1pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TONIGHT I am the boy who lived. I can live through anything! I AM A GOD! PotterProv - 8pm @comedybar #improv… https://t.co/eiK7gyvZWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how @JamieOComic ends conversations. https://t.co/imWLODUrer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out Of Appalachia #RedneckAMovie @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Men Who Stare At Pigs ...Longingly #RedneckAMovie @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @agmours Those sneaky Pauper Wizards and their tasteless pranks. THROW DOWN THE CARDBOARD! ...glad you're okay, bud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jom doesn't have a personality. @JoannaHaughton @GKyleScott @CavernsPod https://t.co/L2UDMTP9tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finnick says ALL THE CATCHPHRASES! Also, we meet Hank. He's a dick. #CavernsPod #CatchFinnick #dnd #improv #comedy… https://t.co/LrUkRKnPOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod A murder / phenomena investigation in a centaur village.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatting comedy w/ Luke Peters in Freshman at Night, tonight 8pm @comedybar. #improv #comedy #talkshow #Toronto… https://t.co/lqtMuudxSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you miss Brittany destroying Steven for losing her dress, or Lance on an endless waterslide? Don't miss tonight… https://t.co/lztmlGIq4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, you gonna wanna see dis. #HatTrickTO https://t.co/MfytQlqAeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parker Positronic #TechCelebs @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Cyborg #TechCelebs @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[phpBB King #TechCelebs @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fred ArMSN #TechCelebs @midnight #PointsMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SONNYBOGGS Haha, thanks Alex. Glad to be a part of your compliment rampage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Askren As long as it's normal. I guess I'll lay off @GKyleScott a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @MaddoxCampbell @Askren @GKyleScott Is a DM normally supposed to be a walking conflict of interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FANTOMA prat falls across the stage until everyone joins in TONIGHT in H - an evening with Harold. 9:30pm… https://t.co/S028OpJyyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @theRealVenger I like that there are little upside down servants quarters at the bottom. Because evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @theRealVenger New bot from @moniqueamarion for calling out passive-aggressive subtweets. Just trying it out. #subtweetsubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What song do you think Sophie Grégoire Trudeau has planned for today? #MLKday #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moniqueamarion Wowzers, shade much? #SubTweetSubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thiuma why hello, #1000!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @dndlawyer It certainly starts clicking along a little smoother in Ep4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep. Don't know if it's the great classic rom com I just watched or the 1/3 can of Red Bull I drank 8 hours ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon Twitter, you're teasing me. #1kClub https://t.co/bV0hswrsUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A painful reminder of the one you just couldn't save On A Shelf #RuinAToy @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickle Me Ernest P. Worrell #RuinAToy @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Wake Daddy ...or you get the strap #RuinAToy @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerplunk: Mafia Edition - How do you get rid of snitches? #RuinAToy @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brats - like Bratz, but actual kids! #RuinAToy @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be honest, I had some pretty ace material to work with. #CatchFinnick #CavernsPod https://t.co/rbenXchKwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at 8pm we ask the question: WHAT IF @EricMiinch had made one different life-changing choice? #improv… https://t.co/Vb2fV4BeUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neither can I! #improv #CatchFinnick #breaktheinternet #dnd #podcast https://t.co/j9KpPozdGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you wear a T-shirt that says "Watch out - I've got sticky feet"? @coconutphone77 @CavernsPod @JosefAdd… https://t.co/OUxX4SDeiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening Night of the new Second City HouseCo was a blast! Shows every Friday @ 8pm! #Toronto #improv #sketch #comedy https://t.co/YntooW0US1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giuliviane @CavernsPod Haha, you're doing just fine on Twitter. ciao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giuliviane @CavernsPod Haha, I blame it on Bing. Online translators are the worst. Thank you for accidentally submitting to our contest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GKyleScott @CavernsPod I won't like this, because I don't like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest submission to #CatchFinnick all the way from Italy: Picture a Halfling Rogue saying "But that man is Fin… https://t.co/PmRnQQdLPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're allergic to tuna don't get the teriyaki chicken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periodicallypod @CavernsPod @MaddoxCampbell It was drawn by Mawldar, what did you expect?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaddoxCampbell @periodicallypod @CavernsPod Wrong account, Santa! Now we know you've been Maddox all along!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm loving all of these, but the need for more catchphrases is dire! Finnick risks being forever unquotable, thus f… https://t.co/IviX0GAHEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @JoannaHaughton @MaddoxCampbell @periodicallypod @GKyleScott This is... ominous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod I never knew "That's hot" came from her. I've used it extensively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy's a champ. #uspoli @SenSanders https://t.co/OLtZvCmx0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastical variations on any of these would suffice. #CatchFinnick https://t.co/yr6kJvuPRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod @periodicallypod Wrong account, buddy! Now we know it's been Scott all along!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periodicallypod @CavernsPod Oo burn. How's that memory schtick holding up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like an iteration of this has already been said, thus it is a defo contender. Trying it! https://t.co/xZ5QJ0zNcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's gonna be reeeal sarcastic with Kony. https://t.co/F9vL4GwT0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will definitely be taken out of context. https://t.co/dzBJgrrIwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not in Finnick's universe it hasn't. Thanks, Balgor! https://t.co/ww8SyyHCcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll take it into consideration. #CatchFinnick https://t.co/bq5mpmFo3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time Finnick puts on his Slippers of Spider Climbing... https://t.co/3FAPKPiuLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteDeCourcy @GreasyLeesy I do too, but they changed the name to something that won't ever ring for you. #Bell #NoWingsForAngelPete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a used bookstore." "Yeah, but who's been using it?" - @katequickening &amp; @TwitZohaib in Seven Ages last night @TheSoCap #improv #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periodicallypod @CavernsPod I am for sure not trying this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CavernsPod I'm gonna be so quotable after this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finnick needs a catchphrase! Tweet your best ones for a lucky Halfling Rogue @CavernsPod #CatchFinnick &amp; he'll try… https://t.co/KpPOQxa3xM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreasyLeesy Wowzers, k, well I bet yours is something that you'll never have a good one of on life. #outlook #glasshalfPWNpty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreasyLeesy You'd rather it sound like a pun from the Fresh Prince internet episode? #gmail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waltz with Zephir #MonkeyMovies @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilled Monkey Brainspotting #MonkeyMovies @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven Ages, a night of improvised theatre, happens TONIGHT 9pm @TheSoCap! Perfect show for my first of 2017. #improv https://t.co/dLWnqjZKa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man on the subway has a stroller. Strapped into the stroller is a puffy snowsuit. The snowsuit is empty. I have seen the husk of a baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Bud showed up in my Netflix 'Watch It Again' recommendations. Thanks @Netflix_CA, I think I will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!! Can't wait to add #MUTHA to my daily soundtrack! https://t.co/UrUHS44DUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pure class, this fella. https://t.co/7lMiPKzHj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so lucky to know the people I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Finger Chef Kiss is my new improv troupe. https://t.co/6AqbFjbKKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for breakfast. #aptsocks https://t.co/qRsjAm52qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkhartprov Let us never repeat the mistakes that led to the atrocities of forts of 09.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkhartprov I, the Mayor of pillow city, extend my hand in friendship. Hi hello!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG! The Caverns &amp; Comedians Christmas episode!! I loved recording this so much. #CavernsPod #DnD #rpg #podcast https://t.co/hSst2Rg5le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jplarocque true stuff. *SPOILERS* Now he's got no parents to redeem himself to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, @MessingSusan! Just listened to the very first episode of @Improv_Nerd &amp; it made me wish I could train with you more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my second time watching Elf this year. There is no new information. I'm still crying at everything. Hormones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas movies are making me cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upon further inspection this is not a spelling error but an odd and maddening coincidence. https://t.co/FwTx00GmOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mkhartprov this series is A+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix ran out of Garfunkel &amp; Oates episodes much too quickly. @garfunkeloates https://t.co/vRdWrrLNvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And one to which I await your response, @MariahCarey. https://t.co/nwn5BViUWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Mariah Carey such a dick to the presence underneath the Christmas tree?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm worried that I might be a hypochondriac.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this hockey game a reality show? #Toronto #MapleLeafs #NHL #sports]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>