<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP @HollyShulman now we know why he is an "expert"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Week 1
Muslim ban
Climate science ban
Fight w/ Mexico over wall
Fake voter fraud investigation 
Global outrage
Nationwide protests
Week 2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My grandfather was denied asylum from various countries and eventually made it to the U.S. from Germany in the late… https://t.co/duf2kemn6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyEinzig Well, you rest assured that it wouldn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about this: no unanimous consent until the ban / EO is reversed by Congress #NoBanOnRefugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mucinex in fact we have seen Sean Spicer regularly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are not marching about green card holders, they are marching about the whole shebang. Some are totally missing the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @TheDemocrats were looking for an excuse to eat up Senate floor time, they can spend it debating the constitutionality of the #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packed mass chants "shame" at @realdonaldtrump outside the White House https://t.co/czusP2IimL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonkarl @realDonaldTrump Of course they are, they can't wait to change the subject!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most popular chants at today's #muslimban #protests? "Paul Ryan Sucks! Paul Ryan Sucks!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd outside White House breaks out in charge of "Fire Bannon"! #muslimban https://t.co/5ydUomz9Hd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias who says it was a mistake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit... https://t.co/rbW1oel2Eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anniekarni @CNNPolitics that's what is otherwise known as bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed up to be a monthly @ACLU donor and a few minutes later that decision was validated! #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible https://t.co/SjLoDNDOe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePlumLineGS What an embarrassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the hell are the others! https://t.co/4PNR5m2K1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan is a pathetic enabler and is more culpable than Trump himself for this disgusting display of ignorance https://t.co/pDdchpu21S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did PM @Theresa_May press @realDonaldTrump on U.S. climate action and the Paris agreement today? https://t.co/tuQ55GdcYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that the entire world is ready to believe it is the real problem at this point https://t.co/kXK2Q50tCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on, really? https://t.co/JskoFzBZnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cinerina @SierraClub April 29th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zcolman H2O is also necessary for life but too much and - woops! - you're drowned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is called a distraction. Don't take the bait this time guys https://t.co/mNSZtUTnKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFFriedman @EPA interesting like he's a climate science denier basically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikaylaLynneA @SierraClub 100th day of Trump administration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must resist Trump and his attacks on climate action and science. Join us on April 29 for the #PeoplesClimateMarch https://t.co/ecTR9or6TF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you doing after the #WomensMarch? Join the #PeoplesClimateMarch on April 29 in DC and across the nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hint: Trump is the opposite of an environmentalist https://t.co/7D3SS9NDRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arthurbrooks @CapehartJ You missed the main point though. This administration is the dignity crisis -- lacks it entirely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood what a precious snowflake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer: Trump demoralized on first working day as POTUS due to tweets about crowd size]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephensWSJ um, have you followed the campaign at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who hacked his account? https://t.co/8u2WaXINWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone was ever wondering what it might look like if someone like Donald Trump became president, we have your answer today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately a few months late on this one https://t.co/RhGuF1K8OO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More of this, please https://t.co/MBzZnBVcN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Langer it's polluting my feed and warranted some peer review]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCAppelbaum @Nate_Cohn would have been really cool if news media had focused on that possibility ahead of the election and not BS emails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Langer let it be said that this was an extremely stupid promoted tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging out with fake America in the neighborhood next door #WomensMarchOnWashington https://t.co/Z5pe6KOgYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnout pretty similar to yesterday #WomensMarchOnWashington #Inauguration https://t.co/hTyJky8VVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Trump, #HandsOff https://t.co/4nawADMpxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live commentary from @POTUS on the #WomensMarch https://t.co/ypXoHLZMHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec @JohnJHarwood @ZekeJMiller hey you should mention that to the new @potus maybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieFord @ngeiling right, that's his way of getting back at all the artists who wouldn't show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cd_hooks @DavidKlion you saying we're going to have pence for a full seven years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he know the price of a gallon of milk? https://t.co/Tzrukaap8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean air and water advocates swarmed the U.S. Senate yesterday to "Stop Pruitt" https://t.co/LhTKQc4akW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POLITICO_Steve @hillhulse what's interesting is that any member of the Senate would consider voting for them to begin with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bartonswaim Interesting theoretical exercise, if you ignore nearly every policy decision he has articulated to date https://t.co/NsYVMJY2mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must #stopPruitt - protest outside the capitol  https://t.co/QAfhRAwLgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time when you realize you have four of a product you never use, and are not actually sure what function it is… https://t.co/8zg0D3oTbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just dropped off a Pruitt Survivial Kit for @JeffFlake - includes clean water, but may not last four full years… https://t.co/sKAwhqgj68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he realize he is risking twitter feed burnout? https://t.co/ZTGEH4RdL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iChooseLiberty least exciting tweet of the day, why the fake exclamation point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cvonka by far the most efficient way to get around DC. Next stop Mass Ave bike lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump picking Scott Pruitt to run the EPA is like having an arsonist run the fire department. #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/NsYVMJY2mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's EPA pick fought mercury protections, did oil industry's bidding, denies scientific consensus on climate https://t.co/NsYVMJY2mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump picking Scott Pruitt to run the EPA is like having an arsonist run the fire department. Dangerous and absurd. https://t.co/NsYVMJY2mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsaacDovere least shocking thing about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like the 5th denial tweet in a row. Protest too much? https://t.co/DmBmFN0kJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best point... https://t.co/sgw06EKSzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the fake news stories are being spread by people ... (presumably?) https://t.co/XzOy3ucbOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimAlberta @BuzzFeedBen @DavidMDrucker so sad he can't gut health care for seniors unilaterally...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Sierra Club's Bill Price in West Virginia on Senator Manchin's Comments about Scott Pruitt for @EPA.… https://t.co/p3rOTd5CW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Sucks that it's news when someone gets pressed to answer a question in public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shearm @realDonaldTrump he's trying to distract from everything else, duh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jendlouhyhc @emilyhholden not sure that "the fossil fuel industry" and the Koch brothers are really that obscure guys. Many heads, 1 hydra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanCBS @CoachMotto Trump can help with that part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craziest headline ever but, incredibly, accurate. https://t.co/vsrEZrPUPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump your shtick has gotten really old and we haven't even gotten through the inauguration yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs @thomaswburr @RepChrisStewart how did he mean it tho?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktumulty FOX been doing their thing for a while and finally got trumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktumulty um, like about a year ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katherinemiller @Kyle_Feldscher Right, it's unusual and weird in the context of nominating him to run US foreign policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecketAdams This sort of by definition means its true, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the Trump administration planning a climate purge of the federal government? https://t.co/LzRtNAXmAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vote to confirm Pruitt is a vote against the planet -- period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytpolitics @nytimes really? Which ones exactly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eilperin @WhiteHouseCEQ @EPA @ktumulty @algore @IvankaTrump Ebell still running EPA transition team. Groves at state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur Maybe they should just stick with this nifty thing called "obamacare" which does all of this already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @EricLiptonNYT the point is no arugala, therefore not elitist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink @Reince @realDonaldTrump finally some actual draining of the swamp with the frog legs. Not so much on treasury secretary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drain the swamp guy just nominated a Goldman Sachs exec to be treasury secretary #TrumpTransition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time every two weeks when @Handy keeps having people show up despite having cancelled their service. #handy App does not work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It will be as exciting as the 1930s" -Stephen Bannon. 
I wonder if he has any idea what happened then, or afterward...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emma_Dumain I assume there are many people he has not met in his life, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattVas weed now legal in many places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing alot of this from folks https://t.co/H7CUh41Y6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @ChrisCuomo for fact checking Donald #Trump on his #climate change change denial. #ClimateVoter https://t.co/XxNghrR4dL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice summary https://t.co/XxNghrR4dL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible piece from a Republican, former Bush speechwriter https://t.co/FF7Q26uu3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP Biden was asked about Trump's climate denial today. His response: "I'm not even sure he thinks there's gravity" https://t.co/d086NDEqUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@speechboy71 Funny how environmentalists disagree: https://t.co/4wmh4LuUQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SchreckReports That's funny. America's largest enviro organization disagrees: https://t.co/4wmh4LMweU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYTnickc Nick, Trump's climate denial is the scariest thing this Halloween: https://t.co/4wmh4LMweU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothypmurphy THIS ELECTION: https://t.co/4wmh4LMweU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>