<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9UMrnBuj4m. Hundreds USA citizens killed every year as little gun control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LidnaStitt like Fuda but don't agree with this. Sounds too heroic for me. Good debate though. Does culture shape u… https://t.co/xctdlxUIP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterFuda quite a statement - historical, political, social, economic context shape leadership in my view not other way round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LidnaStitt @PapaSawsage A Taupin classic (Elton must have said..,eh you're all right). Don't forget Marconi plays the mamba. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Great Scottish Run half-marathon course found to be short https://t.co/nywW2NU2J1  Boooooooooooooooooooooooooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbc5live @CharlieSeaWolf Stop calling Trump leader of free world. Who elected him to that? He ain't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I hear Tim Farron say he would not sign petition to stop Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is astonishing - the audacity of these people is mind boggling. https://t.co/dVKXabDgGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. - Petitions https://t.co/sTk0sfZwo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to sign.  https://t.co/rLoDfsBgjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we are intended to give Trump a state visit. No way should that happen. https://t.co/kVs0h5x5EJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3zQcRDBkTl. Read this by Sir Mo about the ignorance of Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requires focused attention - 'Shifting the curve' report suggests series of things - in work poverty issue alongsid… https://t.co/SVF12qZZ9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeidreBrock @IanMurrayMP @DavidMundellDCT Donald Trump should not be welcomed to UK - its symbolism counts either… https://t.co/zJk4Wt72ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Parliament is sovereign it should be debating that there should be no state visit by Donald Trump - it would be rewarding actions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MizanRahman64 Enjoy the event. We should catch up on return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would control of guns in USA not make that country safer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference is stark to the views of Trump. Well said Prime Minister. https://t.co/ztTDnOFDvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Trump apologist on radio 5 about the Muslim ban she quoted Orlando as example- eh was he not born in New York?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating read in @runnersworlduk about Longyearbyen (part archipelago Svalbard - Norway) closer to North Pole than Oslo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCAlLamont @BBCSportsound Hopeful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or alternative facts. Wonder what Kafka would make of President Trump - he wrote about absurdity which seems releva… https://t.co/YkQlDtdBcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sitting on Ferry Rd opposite Eagle Lodge been there over a week. On marked cycle lane. @EdinburghPolice @Edinburgh_CC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so it starts. Desperate stuff. https://t.co/a0OISqWqbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #chinesenewyear #yearoftherooster from all @GrantonYouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverEscobar got some intel could send you on this. Would be great to have 30 mins of your time over coffee. How best arrange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverEscobar See City Edinburgh going ahead with Participatory Budget for youth work. Read your Report. Have concerns. Advice welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docandrewmurray @Sandbaggers1 @MerrellUK Congratulations to you. I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edinburgh_CC @north_team Yes, Here is photo taken now. https://t.co/qRqn1Fpg9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edinburgh_CC @north_team As you drive into West Ferryfield estate follow road to far end the bins are here. Dead a… https://t.co/zE6k5wjR7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edinburgh_CC @north_team Glass communal bin overflowing WEST FERRYFIELD. No go to use on line reporting as NO 'blue dot' on location map]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen of the South directors oppose fans' board bid - BBC News - Why not give fans at least seat with voting rights? https://t.co/JSqhc7Zl3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off on the bike this morning. Wimpish at 2 degrees compared to @docandrewmurray https://t.co/OTd05opqkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelbagshaw different argument altogether. I get your point about APT but there is no links to the argument on bus passes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could be eligible for bus pass pass in 2 years whilst potentially being in full time work for next 7-10 years. Ne… https://t.co/tNX9juMsMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative facts sounds Orwellian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump inauguration: President disputes crowd photos https://t.co/Ny6KZKR5ms. He can't dispute he lost popular vote by 2 million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House press secretary attacks media for accurately reporting inauguration crowds  - CNNMoney https://t.co/WCarQVMvSO. Just the start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a consistency in Lee Clarke's post match comments over last two months, with no change in positive results… https://t.co/EajoXCVzLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on 'Secrets of Orkney' - absolutely fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LidnaStitt ouch can relate after visit to sports Injury Clinic and my foot but I ain't 4 brave wee one unlike me..,wimp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexmassie @Martin_Veart what's all this voting lark all about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docandrewmurray thank you for advice and support today. First steps made towards start line at Stirling marathon. X-ray done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MerlinMMF indeed- just read his ban on @GlenfiddichSMW a bottle I will go out and buy this afternoon in support of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenfiddichSMW I would follow you but apparently at 57 I ain't old enough haha. I do this as if you have annoyed Pres Trump good judgment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenfiddichSMW would love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I watch the news that there will be a President Trump am I alone with this surreal feeling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having read mags over this weekend iam struck by how little international news there is across mainstream broadcasters in UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cllrcammyday @VickiRedpath @BenMacpherson @DeidreBrock  This issue impacts negative perceptions within our communi… https://t.co/cpg2G7zYQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out run Ferry Rd cycle path - so litter strewn. Granton Access similar and sofa dumped on Marine Drive. @KSBScotland @north_team @GrantonCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djmakin @NetflixUK @charltonbrooker Saw 1st one last night 1 of 1 (PM &amp; pig. seeking to be too clever that it's just daft - no sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acgrayling where does it say that in our constitution or is this making it up as you go along - you risk a backlash I voted remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatherineHMHart they packed it in box away from me. I anticipated when they said the amount it would be a slab of cake not so miserly one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£4.75 for this from Hendersons Edinburgh is surely over the top? https://t.co/nG4yIxVFhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HendersonsofEdi I just opened my carrot cake box and this cost £4.75 - expected bit more for that amount? https://t.co/cda1CQOaLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Barack Obama yesterday and compare that with what Trump said at his press conference- boy the bar has fallen to all time low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Cup: Gianni Infantino defends tournament expansion to 48 teams - BBC Sport not money making he says hahahahaha https://t.co/cIhmhmrOhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LidnaStitt  what is more amazing is that the blogger runs in same area as me and my wife is Michele. Great read thanks for sharing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captivating programme on 'Secrets of Orkney'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jinnapp maybe you should insist your couriers have cycle lights. Edinburgh refers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something oddly paradoxical seeing guy walking carrying his football boots whilst smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's fine but what about the 'missing streets' - Blandfield, West Ferryfield - flats? https://t.co/1Q9gSloMAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who made this up but I will do my best to support it with appropriate amounts left over from Hogmanay. https://t.co/AQdm1KZrw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people on TV who do 'high 5s' then use hand-gel? Saw Robbie Williams and now 1 show hosts do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillieFC at match with someone who  had not seen us play before and he said team looked like they never played together ever. Yep Shambles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialKillie that performance was as horrific as I've seen at tynecastle in many years going]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialKillie will there be tickets on sale today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillieFC you know if shop open for hearts tickets. Ringing out &amp; cannot get down as live in edinburgh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael I was a fan and will miss you. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how it should be. https://t.co/SCKtQLOd3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinDewar dream on mr dewar. Seriously big match for both clubs I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football player getting £400,000 per week for kicking a ball. We have lost all sense of perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if let's see how awkward and difficult we can make it for the fans. Disgraceful but not surprised. https://t.co/zc9GqDqt3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spfl @BBCRadioScot how does fixture that see Partick go to Dingwall Saints go to killie = home after midnight family friendly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen BBC weather and wondering about sense of Patrick thistle fans heading to Dingwall for Ross County match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantonYouth free Xmas community lunch. Over 100 served 3 courses all trimmings. Plus Santa. Amazing effort by sta… https://t.co/e6WeTJmSIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverEscobar @DeidreBrock @cllrcammyday @BigLotteryFund @GrantonParish Organised in collaboration with young mum… https://t.co/qdElZUngwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantonYouth Xmas free community lunch. The staff &amp; volunteers served over 100. Amazing effort &amp; true community sp… https://t.co/4mcPJGpsIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Menu for @GrantonYouth Christmas community lunch. @IMcLaughlan @BenMacpherson @PermSecScot https://t.co/3J8lmITXr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BigThankYou to all volunteers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alistairkgrant good job. As an added gift allow me to invite you to @GrantonYouth community xmas lunch. If free I'll send u details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life chances for all. @GrantonYouth supporting young people &amp; reaching out a message of solidarity.  https://t.co/rfwEorEk7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[florence magic roundabout - Google Search https://t.co/dcmeuFkdif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great evening to kick start the weekend with @tyaymusic. Loving Little Sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fife bound to see @tyaymusic. Nice way to start weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what community spirit is all about - great job @GrantonYouth https://t.co/ZBUlxFwN3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sl9SlVdqWS
Like our FB page and help us spread the word on the work of @GrantonYouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MizanRahman64 Good to connect up again this evening. Great you are involved in the community council.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMcLaughlan @GrantonParish It was a great event - bringing people together. What it is all about.  Great to see you too Ian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At lightning of @GrantonParish tree. First mince pie of season &amp; mulled wine. https://t.co/RyEpJY0lWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Spartans u15s in win against AC Irvine in Scottish cup tie at Ainslie Park. Great football on display.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics of Resentment by Katherine Cramer - focus on Wisconsin as case study. Interviewed people 8 years ago very negative view of Hillary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChakaKhan you coming over to uk in 2017?  Please. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private train company causes misery to passengers. UK government to pay out compensation i.e. tax payers.  What? Free market?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why the work @GrantonYouth is so vital
https://t.co/aPrAogBEoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRobb22 best wishes on new challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President elect Trump. Please tell me it's all a bad dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktmcnl jeez that's terrifying hope all well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing amazing work in North Edinburgh. https://t.co/BE6jv8vhOG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>