<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kodaxx7 I'm very proud of local private sponsors who have done so much to sponsor refugee families - they deserve a tonne of credit! (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kodaxx7 Canada will accept 25,000 refugees this year. To accept more, there must be adequate housing, lang/skills training, etc (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canesbian I unreservedly oppose the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joyohbliss I unreservedly oppose the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Family Literacy Day! Take some time and visit one of our great libraries in PW #familyliteracyday https://t.co/yJZHEqTwrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental health will affect all of us either directly or indirectly. Let's end the stigma and keep the conversation going. #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgorama - I hadn't heard it was happening until after it was already over.  Read that there was a good turnout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning @RI_Stratford &amp; @globalmedicdmgf made 700 aquaboxes! Thank you for all you do to provide clean water t… https://t.co/9dGg1eh5GX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beefwel My pleasure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pleasure to attend the Wellington County Cattlemen's Association AGM tonight in Alma @MapletonTwp #ontag https://t.co/24n0cMEJig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to be back at @UTEschool this morning to talk with the Grade 5/6s about the House of Commons and the role as… https://t.co/UhufplWw5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun for the whole family at the 2017 @StratfordON Winterfest! Thank you to all the volunteers! @StratWinter https://t.co/BpodvOD7ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbbkay99 Drayton is great. Was honoured to be there for Remembrance Day this year. We will let you know next time we host an event there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow (January 14th) for a free Family Skate in Arthur. Skating is from 11:00 a.m. to 1:00 p.m. at the A… https://t.co/tAchzjGxFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I enjoyed speaking with members of the Aktion Club of @StratfordON this afternoon - they had some great questions! https://t.co/NSKzs3uyh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet with @TrilliumMutual President/CEO @joe_jdietrich this morning. Great chat about insurance industry,… https://t.co/P4cPj0yXQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneInAction Hi Anne - thank you for sharing your views on this. I will carefully consider any proposals brought forward on this matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonBrodhagen Many more times! At least enough times to finally spell it and pronounce it correctly on the first try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to join the community in celebrating Canada's Sesquicentennial year. https://t.co/EO0HS1rqxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to attend @WestPerth1 Mayor Walter McKenzie's New Year's Levee honouring Canada's 150th! https://t.co/nDp9uskSDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@511Ontario These three tweets are confusing, misleading and dangerous to motorists. Hwy 23 remains *closed* from… https://t.co/o291rSGicc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently today is National Spaghetti Day!  Ainsley is more than happy to celebrate! #NationalSpaghettiDay https://t.co/6fX4gY4XnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of fun at our Family Skate in Mitchell @WestPerth1.  Thanks to everyone who came out! #HAPPYNEWYEAR https://t.co/RXqTGrSeQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My year-end interview with @thebeaconherald! https://t.co/vfWoTjS0sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TanyaCr13855628 Hope everyone had fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy baking cookies for tomorrow's free family skate! Join us on Jan 2nd at the Mitchell Arena: 1:30-3:30 pm! #2017 https://t.co/Q2Yolg3jMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's more Canadian than roasting marshmallows for s'mores over a Sesquicentennial Fire Pit in the snow! https://t.co/QPsMH7UrGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of fun tonight at the @TownofMinto Fire &amp; Ice Family New Year's Party! Skating, s'mores and fireworks! https://t.co/nHjU5NMsQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From our family to yours, Merry Christmas! #christmas https://t.co/T8FujFyzB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Gail at the Salvation Army Kettle. Please give as you are able. #MerryChristmas https://t.co/7thZQb3q0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful Christmas sing-along today at @RI_Stratford led by Steve Rae on guitar!  #MerryChristmas https://t.co/RIyMxs3G0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa dropped by the Office today for help with his Passport Application! #MerryChristmas https://t.co/EyIsmo7Dq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at the Independent Grocer in @townofstmarys this afternoon with my little helper volunteering with the Salvat… https://t.co/8v7e8gR3LT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recognized @TownofMinto employee Mark Hill for his lifesaving actions and showing true "Minto Mettle"! A reminder o… https://t.co/3ExET1kjLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWVoll Unfortunately, it would fall under provincial jurisdiction to implement - like Quebec has done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview with @AmandaBrodhagen about women in Ag. You are a role model for many young women in PW and Canada https://t.co/bXBXRfTeHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to join @TaraSlone on stage at Rogers #HometownHockey for a Thank You to @StratfordON presentation #FanHubHTH https://t.co/nBk5GcsAJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to chat with hockey icon Lanny McDonald today at Rogers #HometownHockey #FanHubHTH in @cityofstratford https://t.co/Z4EnBvuhAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @RonMacLeanHTH for chatting with our friend Emerson today in @cityofstratford! #hometownhockey https://t.co/TudCJu0v30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @887theriver on your first year on the airwaves! https://t.co/UIuZQdfexk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is National Day of Remembrance and Action on Violence Against Women. We all have a role in ending violence ag… https://t.co/2g1ou1JbWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful meal and fellowship tonight at the Stratford Legion's Annual Christmas Fare Dinner! #MerryChristmas https://t.co/gwO9F8Xd6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to roll at the Palmerston Santa Claus Parade! #MerryChristmas @TownofMinto https://t.co/vigrLgbwMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Habitat for Humanity and @CLNorthPerth on the new home in Listowel @NorthPerth1 #HandUp https://t.co/fLU3drqQzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Teri for decking out the office for the Harriston Curling Club's Christmas Rocks House Tour! @TownofMinto https://t.co/XJIQioZLET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damp and cold night, but warm and friendly spirits at the Mitchell Santa Claus Parade! #MerryChristmas @WestPerth1 https://t.co/bwj4Fn2KlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Mert Schneider on his 2nd Term as Perth County Warden! A strong voice for Perth County! https://t.co/gLVLrBaHBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see so many people out at the Santa Claus Parade tonight in @StratfordON https://t.co/Zluixer6g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ainsley at last night's "Bethlehem Live" hosted by Upper Thames Church and Thamesview United. On again tonight! https://t.co/e25s3Uzk5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is #NationalChildDay. It falls to all of us to make this world a better place for those that will come after… https://t.co/kwJQjA6zWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @perth_gala on their successful 2nd Annual Gala! Special congratulations @slitsdairyfarms on winning PC… https://t.co/4VZdZ7KAiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CZonny Hi Chris.  The courts have been clear on this in their rulings.  I believe the Bill should pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in the House I paid tribute to the volunteers of the Canadian @Foodgrains Bank. https://t.co/Q7b8NL5R45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ainsley and I read her new book tonight at bedtime: "The Darkest Dark" signed by @Cmdr_Hadfield himself! https://t.co/Yn67VkUHqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas!" Great turnout at the Christmas Craft Show in @StratfordON https://t.co/RoIOFrvMnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to the Listowel Legion for inviting me to this evening's Remembrance Day dinner #LestWeForget https://t.co/MFv8qWLY7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured to join Veterans and Legion Members in Drayton this afternoon. @MapletonTwp #LestWeForget https://t.co/l0xvFV7GaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to @Rae_Matt for representing me at the Palmerston Remembrance Day Service #LestWeForget https://t.co/w26T0i33fX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honour to pay tribute to our Veterans at the Mount Forest Remembrance Day Service.  #LestWeForget https://t.co/fAkwoJploi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to my wife, Justine and son, Bennett for laying the Dominion of Canada wreath in Mitchell #LestWeForget https://t.co/X2Ffmowaru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@44scottEdward Terrible situation - especially for Children. Canada must step up and provide immediate aid, but also long-term support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to the students in Grades 5 &amp; 6 at @LittleFallsPS for a fun afternoon of questions and answers! https://t.co/x6Q8BLsNQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A moving Remembrance Day Assembly this morning at @MitchellDHS - thank you to all our veterans for their service!… https://t.co/4Svc9yQt9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed chatting with students at @ShakespearePS this afternoon in Stratford. Smart questions from an engaged group! https://t.co/BlgrkfU7Un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@masonsherry we've got 12 great candidates - I look forward to hearing all their ideas &amp; policies and making a decision when the time comes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the Fawcett Family for organizing tonight's walk for @WoundWarriorCA - great walk for a great cause! https://t.co/6GR6NBbwD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to the students at Stratford Northwestern SS for calling us to remember at their Remembrance Day Assembly. https://t.co/p2Mtp1SkAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gavin07411658 Thanks Gavin - great ideas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylahorton8B Thanks Kyla - your class had great ideas and opinions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chaffey0016 Thanks Curtis!  Great ideas from the class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emily_haefling Thanks Emily - great ideas from the class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malia_glanville Thanks Malia - my pleasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grace_m19 Thanks Grace - I enjoyed the conversation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gektoid Thanks Aidan - it was an important discussion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0ZoeDietz0 Thanks Zoe - it was my pleasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edit_josh Thanks Josh - it was a great discussion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for having me! https://t.co/36Vam2KFfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoganHarmer Thanks Logan - it was fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @CFIA_Canada representatives for coming to Listowel today to talk with livestock producers and transporte… https://t.co/dsXpbxscXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress on the bell at @theoldpostca! A beautiful landmark in Harriston @TownofMinto https://t.co/1UudWVIGu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honour to lay a wreath this afternoon at the Atwood/Elma Township Remembrance Day Service #LestWeForget https://t.co/FEt7GlHy2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helped to kick off Random Act of Kindness Day this morning at Walkom's Valu-Mart! https://t.co/GGJ4fracur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pleasure to be back on the @queensu campus to speak to the
MPA 800 @QueensSPS class! https://t.co/0ZQg2sjf86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Take-Your-Kids-to-Work Day! I'm blessed to have such a supportive family in public life! https://t.co/Uh2grVHEjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Fair today at the Stratford Rotary Complex. Lots of Small businesses are hiring! @SPCFB @StratfordON https://t.co/Zdg08e01fo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ainsley and Bennett popped into the Opposition Lobby today to drop off Halloween Cupcakes for @CPC_HQ MPs and Staff! https://t.co/X7gHpkR2dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mickey &amp; Minnie/Ainsley &amp; Bennett went "reverse" Trick-or-Treating at a Retirement Home today in @StratfordON https://t.co/XSPaem3YD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great story from the @WellyAdvertiser on @theoldpostca clock tower! Pop in and see it in Harriston @TownofMinto https://t.co/6qWY8lBjJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWVoll Should be fixed now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWVoll Hi Ryan - DM me your email address and we can meet for coffee and chat about volunteering. -John]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneInAction I will be voting in favour of today's motion on care for First Nations children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to welcome constituents Kathy, Mary, Pauline and Liz to Ottawa for a tour of Parliament! https://t.co/7TpoJh6sY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations and welcome to our newest @CPC_HQ MP from Medicine Hat-Cardston-Warner @GlenMotz!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to 19 Squadron (@StratfordON) Royal Canadian Air Cadets on 75 years of service to community and cou… https://t.co/fnwoVYAo7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to attend the @WellFedAg AGM in Fergus. Former CKCO Ag Reporter @jdavidimrie is here as Guest Speaker. https://t.co/BT7RWQbS4E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #SmallBusinessWeek in Canada. Small businesses drive the economy - we need to support them. https://t.co/jIyipkxEXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pleasure to attend the Perth County Federation of Agriculture AGM tonight at the @MitchellGCC #ontag https://t.co/Rkp46U0dci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to learn about the Ontario Student Nutrition Program's pilot project at area schools. Thanks to the staff and… https://t.co/519sT60ZcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@modernfarmer Thanks Stewart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Fire Prevention Week! Check the batteries in your smoke detectors! #DontWaitCheckTheDate @WestPerth1 https://t.co/M974cPAM9o]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>