<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Such brave families speaking about their loved ones killed in Tunisia beach attack. Everyone of them a hero and missed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram will soon let you share multiple photos in one post - The Verge https://t.co/uvdHoGfsxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible, moving portraits at the Tunisia Inquests. Suzy Evans reading powerful tributes to her dad, brother and son killed in the attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump voters say US president is 'doing a fabulous job' https://t.co/GN43cPu1xG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callummay I dont think Duolingo teaches you "the Six has dropped us"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So doesn't this discredit his own victory too or did the fraudsters only vote for Clinton? https://t.co/a3il7zzokY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callummay I'm trying to learn. The Italian husband is insisting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daily Mail proves again that it is a newspaper apart from all others - the guardian https://t.co/1uk5weg2Gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Badlands on Twitter: US park climate change tweets deleted - BBC News https://t.co/DCh6pYTZGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Won’t Back Down From His Voting Fraud Lie. Here Are the Facts., via @nytimes https://t.co/uQcsQh8Pe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump believes millions voted illegally, WH says -- but provides no proof - CNN https://t.co/ZW7ZNym4qR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A call to action for the media dealing with President Trump and Spicer https://t.co/AJ7wrNmN4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Repeats Lie About Popular Vote in Meeting With Lawmakers, via @nytimes https://t.co/cEqmE8xgoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the media imagined that last performance then? https://t.co/UTINO3Gqg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Pushes ‘Alternative Facts.’ Here Are the Real Ones. https://t.co/SKhJzm3Fpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So huge. The biggest. The best. #InaugurationDay #blamethemedia #lies #killtruth https://t.co/QoI2Em5noi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more Facebook lives, producers!!! Back to just just thinking about the #Ten then. https://t.co/S32OggDEyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the middle of Arctic Circle and 3G signal better than London can be. @ThreeUK I have to say, Feel at Home is brilliant #showingoffpics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@godsavethepoint @GaryBuchanan5 even airlines like Delta and American, hardly known for being generous give free tea! #budgetBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After hours: capturing the journey home from New York City's gay nightclubs - the guardian https://t.co/Pf2haeuZWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry #BBCOne put the bloody #bbcnews at Ten on. Today of all days is no day for News at When.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJohnSudworth @BBCNews you #bbcbeauties I wonder if Mr T is spitting feathers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any connection to Wintour's NY's Damehood? May to become first PM on the cover of American Vogue https://t.co/ypXhc6y1Ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was waiting for @TheJohnSudworth to use the words "inflatable cock" but he chickened out. Great piece. @bbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being back on Home News soil has its advantages when you don't have to watch and pray as the piece creeps its way to London #hellonewsdesk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gosefjord @bealejonathan @British_Airways and £6 for a g+t! #livid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "beauty" of BBC News explains the Trump 'compromising' claims: How and why did we get here? https://t.co/RnPi1ouKIU #trumpsaysimabeauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the White House corr for CNN was actually threatened with being thrown out of the Trump presser. #goodluckamerica https://t.co/yteKKstx1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody who told you don't vote for Hillary Clinton because, "Look! Goldman Sachs!".Yeah, you got suckered. https://t.co/QAawaHSS4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists should've stuck up for CNN and refused to play Trump's game. We are all on the same side https://t.co/po2qkKrHHH via @cjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cory Booker Shattered Illusions About Racism in the Sessions Hearing - Slate https://t.co/4XoOtwwGMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those that voted for Trump will be cheering at that press conference, those who didn't, holding their head in their hands. #WelldoneUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I hope the American media dispense with their odd tradition of standing up when the President walks into the r… https://t.co/m2gUWTUlPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomprobert @British_Airways if it's they have just lost the loyalty of those who'll pay for full service. Easyjet now. No difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomprobert @British_Airways cabin crew on a flight this week told me passengers need to complain. They aren't happy either. BA is losing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final call for a free G&amp;T: @British_Airways starts charging for food and drink in short-haul economy tomorrow #shit  https://t.co/zsjVwySBIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebekahLeiigh fair enough, understand. Thanks for replying though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebekahLeiigh Hi Rebekah, can you DM me , please. Would like to talk about Tunisia. Tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enough With the Tweets, China’s State Media Tells Trump, via @nytimes https://t.co/nxnAaaoYD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellen DeGeneres bans Kim Burrell after she says god hates the homos.   https://t.co/nVFrGSUxPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe we should all do the same.. "It is unusable for anyone but trolls, robots and dictators" | Lindy West https://t.co/9K1OluLO86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyScottItv @British_Airways yup but that's what's wrong with the idea of economy £ for a mid-flight tipple. #wrongBA #easyBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days of a free @British_Airways g&amp;t are numbered. Might as well fly budget in future. No frills comes to the flag carrier #shame #easyBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the Danish Queen gives a very different speech to the British Queen. Much more of a message. No autocue though… https://t.co/eX5XsXncBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add this to the list of obits:
The Death of Clintonism - POLITICO https://t.co/5DM8unRznh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden gay British histories take centre stage 50 years after decriminalisation https://t.co/t130B3ivAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Hamill Posted This Moving Tribute To Carrie Fisher... https://t.co/pXDnx16JUN via @thoughtcatalog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he needs a better producer! https://t.co/8Pbm2UH4Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dutch woman with two British children told to leave UK after 24 years - the guardian https://t.co/jJSwnmcGPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know a correspondent or two who might agree with this plea. https://t.co/GmgJlJYzMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Border Security Now Asking Foreign Travelers for Social Media Accounts - Condé Nast Traveler https://t.co/FdevjuVBEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginTrains on such a busy travel day more trains are needed clearly. It's a pricey trip to stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginTrains nope. The mess of seat swapping because of reserved seats almost seems to make matters worse tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginTrains standing room only on a £100 ticket. Liverpool 0847 &gt; London. #nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man achieves the perfect drive through New York City traffic - Clotheshorse https://t.co/uKZLJVjLig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So The Times irony between these two stories? Growth beats those Brexit predictions yet £ crash means India now big… https://t.co/jWKNoNefFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do some people find it so difficult getting on a train? Despite the odd idiot Euston is strangely calm for Xmas Eve #notravelchaos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichPreston depends what you want to use the miles for? BA is perfect for redeeming for European short haul flights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second attempt at calling @British_Airways, now been on hold for 20mins. Fog not their fault but crap customer service is #humph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Matt Frei found the words I don't know. It's crushing and harrowing. Imagine the horrors they've endured. #syria https://t.co/Bp7ytDC8OR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunPictureDesk haha BBC journo on the The Sun website. Yes you can. Do you want the original?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight after flight being cancelled at London City today because of fog #xmasjoy #travelmisery https://t.co/v4WZKf0Dz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of vocal support and horn honking and cheers as Mrs Blackman arrived at High Court for husband's bail hearing https://t.co/UVsr78uiAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd collision of previous defence job and my first Home News gig since coming back from US #hellonewsdesk #hometurf https://t.co/xMJhs4PRMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sgt Blackman supporters arrive at the High Court. Full of optimism he'll get bail today. #MarineA #hellonewsdesk https://t.co/ID8ugbAfEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading for High Court for Marine A bail  hearing and a Chinook flies overhead. Chances are Sgt Blackman flew in it at some point (perhaps)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “This man loves dancing to the BBC News theme”

https://t.co/6ziK6icZXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCwestcott we saw the Pittsburgh cars in the summer - apparently having problems with pigeons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is more than one truth to tell in the terrible story of Aleppo https://t.co/CGEmg6EEZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's twelve mins of Syria reality check to those "commuters who faced a day of frustration". Awkward change of story there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakubKrupa @BBCNews I've done similar dancing waiting for a package to feed as that tune plays in our ears for real! #hellonewsdesk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not just a Christmas ad – it’s a Polish grandpa’s heartbreaking gift to Britain | Jakub Krupa https://t.co/SeOcgfh5lG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpfanBucksPA Trump aide Michael Flynn Jnr out after 'Pizzagate' tweets
https://t.co/qZyArhdTCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Real Subject of Obama’s Final National Security Speech Was the Man He Wouldn’t Name - Slate https://t.co/2IjeNXOKeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavincampbelltv I know. Ten of them at least to rank. Where is Nigel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ten Worst Homophobes In Trump’s Administration - Queerty https://t.co/8fJ6XbAEH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has the BBC?
https://t.co/gLWmuGjrBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Clinton won the popular vote, but still didn't beat Obama's count from 2012: https://t.co/eRU9yWoQOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM's message to #betterthanthat contrasts with leaks over illegal immigrant children plans she was backing over school places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go home and join isis" British victims of hate crime post-Brexit tell their stories at #betterthanthat launch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take the piss out of yourself before they can" says @Rubywax at #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are the creator of our own bubbles" turn on the feeds of people we don't agree with #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It would be amazing if Trump was impeached. It would be boring if he just settled down into the job" #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There seemed to be a huge amount of optimism with tech but when it comes to politics in UK or US a more downbeat feeling #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune in and understand your tipping point says @Rubywax at #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Care about mental health" I could listen to @Rubywax all day #EdelmanCB https://t.co/liCM20nAdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never had a voice that says you're making a wonderful decision and you're beautiful says @Rubywax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'll be cool to be mentally ill @Rubywax Three cheers to that!! #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the Future.. the return of Tony Blair. A vacuum in the centre. May not be back in the Commons but will make a come back #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The return of Ed Ballas and Corbyn's days are numbered. Politics 2017 #EdelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Brexit will still mean Brexit and we still won't have a clue what that means" #edelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah someone finally mentioned Brexit. Price rises and how we deal with that will be a 2017 challenge #edelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shrinking chocolate. This sounds absolutely awful #edelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is the first prediction for 2017. Maybe the chips will have better luck than the human did this year #edelmanCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defending press freedom in America of all places  https://t.co/vUsPbeDTpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off-duty heading to #EdelmanCB trying to stupidly predict 2017 then to Parliament for #betterthanthat anti-hate crime campaign launch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National anti-hate crime campaign to launch after spike in incidents https://t.co/UUm3qw4MdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Msm and proud! https://t.co/RLpnkp9Xsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes reminds the world about fact-based journalism. #echochamber https://t.co/0X9e7YCvJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleaford's Brexit byelection: a people united by fear for the future - the guardian https://t.co/ztIQ1QC4kp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>