<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @BHHooker The 2013 series was poor to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BHHooker @threeredkings If you save the pennies to go to NZ/Oz/SA I'm sure the tour itself is mad craic for fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BHHooker @threeredkings It's difficult for it to have a place in the pro era but everyone makes money from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Overthehillprop @threeredkings I can't see Munster keeping him now. Maybe Ulster?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Still young too so hasn't reached his ceiling. His move to France worked out brilliantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup SK downloads of retro episodes not working for me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvalDigest It's terrible. I was planning on going to both. Now it's Limerick only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Any Conor McFootball parody accounts appear yet? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Office_Zombie Their players will be wrecked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't expect 5 consecutive weeks of play. In the RWC teams are rotated in the pool stages. Bye weeks in 6N are… https://t.co/YLNtlNRz9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @lemonsrbitter In 2012/2013 Treviso finished only 4 points behind Munster in the league. Pity indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @lemonsrbitter And at some stage you have to prioritise the integrity/competitiveness of the competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May not agree on project players but how about this? @threeredkings @lemonsrbitter https://t.co/JjvTv1A0kZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm a Treviso or Zebre fan I'd rather go to Challenge Cup games that are competitive than watch my team get regularly routed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The growing the game argument (which has merit) falls flat when the Six Nations is a closed shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 win in the last 30 for Treviso and Zebre combined in the top tier in Europe. At some stage you have to make a change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner People love to be 'outraged'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug @WalesRugby I think it's fair. I think teams with an away QF and SF are on a hiding to nothing. Though understand frustration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug @WalesRugby I don't see the issue. It lessens the effect of a lop sided pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Option to buy through associate membership. Nice one @MRSC16 .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughcahill7 It's to keep players from moving abroad. This isn't a surprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Still better than the former referee who never called any review correctly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings And my problem has nothing to do with players who have to maximise their income from a potentially short career.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Yes they are. The project player quota is basically that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings That's fine. Just don't have the union buy them in to play international.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings ...and not compete with them for spots with Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings I think foreign players here should help to bring through Irish players to international level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings So I'd like to see the increase to 5 years happen. Focus the minds on developing indigenous players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings I hate unions buying in players to play for Ireland. I have nothing against the players who want to maximise income.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Where do you stand on residency players? Love for Stander aside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinDeeganEsq @EmeraldRugby The long term goal should be promotion-relegation with ENC. The 6N is great but it's a closed shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MEGhAnnMix @threeredkings  Sounds interesting, will give it a listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rugby_ie Ye couldn't get a more recent photo? :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam @Cianaf Yeah exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @shelflife68 @salmsonconnacht I'd wait for the result of the EPCR investigation before discussing this to be honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the NFL Skip B*****s makes the troll rugby pundits look tame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam @Cianaf If Jets draft an early round QB is it an admission by FO that Hackenberg last year was a mistake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoelRock Get this done Noel. We don't want a situation akin to the US where tickets are bought and sold like commodities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MallowNews @threeredkings Forget that Trumpt is an arse. They want to "bring down" someone who was democratically elected. Moronic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Positivity. I like it. Now if Welsh teams can benefit from being in the Challenge Cup, both Italian teams can too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's great to see SOLD-OUT tweets from Munster again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second man in is just ridiculous there. https://t.co/u6DCiYxzWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurphyPaul10 Brilliant. Up there with Packers @ Cardinals last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Cowboys didn't spike the ball on 1st down....fantastic game! #DALvsGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game this is. Fantastic. #DALvsGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSPSMSB_Screenr @JoeNumbas If JJ Watt can come back that D is going to be ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencoles_ NFC South is not short of great QBs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencoles_ He's fantastic. However he goes up against my team (Bears) every year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencoles_ He's been astounding since promising to "run the table" in mid-season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Belichick and Patricia planning to call plays against this Aaron Rodgers would be fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Siffror @brianmoore666 I'm told the defense adjusts depending on who is in the huddle. Stops teams playing silly buggers I suppose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvertimeIreland What's the idea of it? To allow the defence time to scan who will be involved in the play?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas I feel bad for the Texans D. They're elite and let down by the offense. If Texans had a Big Ben / Rodgers / Brees they'd be A1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Brock Osweiler is the greatest paid job guy ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Murray HIA etc being looked into. Inevitable and correct following the North incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper Thanks that narrows it down! All the best for 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper Hey Jon, when did you make your Soup debut? I'm searching the archives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falcons on fire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Broonjunior @threeredkings One gobshite doesn't reflect a fanbase and anyone with a brain knows that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @Broonjunior @threeredkings Exactly. One of my Leinster friends got a dickish PM on FB from a Munster 'fan' after Stephens Day win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc @paddylogan13 The Italians have no incentive to be better. Shouldn't be given free pass only to get hammered in every game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam @Cianaf Cheers Sam. If Bears can find a solution at QB then there's grounds for optimism. I have faith in GM Ryan Pace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @PFF_Sam Just curious how Bears 2016 draft class graded vs other teams? Jordan Howard stands out of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmODonoghue @AdamSchefter @PFF_Sam Thanks the one. I'm educated by the PFF pod.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamSchefter Not all about sacks though right? @PFF_Sam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeilHarder Ah you're blocked? One sec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Sam Arnold. Out again for 2 months when he might have played during the Six Nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeilHarder On the link posted 12th Jan 20:35...nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeilHarder Exactly. This could be easily verified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeilHarder Take a look at the profiles of the Facebook comments on the victim video just posted by Liberal. Something doesn't add up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc CC I'd say. Escalate to TD if necessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCarthyMick Your NFL pod is out though. It's all good!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[De Trumpt conference sounds equally horrifying and  entertaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam It's incredible how much money this man earns despite knowing nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Happy birthday Michelle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady Ever heard of broken Matt Hardy? If so he would say the Liberal.ie has been DELETED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady You is funnie today Andy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I think this is being overblown, great headline all the same. https://t.co/76y5PBg5L1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonrug Not sure about this one Simon. Amorisino was a medical joker for Munster last year and was pretty poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady Scary how many messages of support they are getting in the comments section in Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's refreshing that the different NFL broadcasters have no problem advertising each other's coverage of different games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some night I will dream of Aaron Rodgers at 10 for Munster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PFF_Sam I don't think that last one was catchable? In any case awful throw from Manning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady @gavreilly THIS IS AWESOME *clap clap clap...clap clap clap* THIS IS AWESOME *clap clap clap...clap clap clap*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf @PFF_Sam After that touchdown, correct decision to not go for two in your  view?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant. #GBNYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvertimeIreland He's good entertainment if you view him strictly as comedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvertimeIreland I particularly enjoy the saltiness from Skip B*****s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers is special. WHAT a play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lambeau Field looks like a stadium and experience worth visiting someday. Brrrrrrrrr....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas This is true. I still think it will be a Patriots vs Cowboys/Packers superbowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Prediction for how many points Patriots will win by next week? Very easy road to SB 51...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 I'll give him a pass given injury. I predict he'll be starting by April.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 I think Saili will end up being the better player by the end of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Cleveland sign Osweiler to a 10 year 250m fully guaranteed contract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 On an unrelated point, I think Saili will be re-signed over Taute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 What would have happened if Sweetnam was fit? We'll never know. Assume Keet starts next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 Being managed would make more sense if he didn't start the training session vs Racing U20s in two weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Earls looked for a lot of work when he came on. I wonder why he didn't start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A win in Glasgow would be huge. The Racing squad was decent on paper but whatever reason they haven't turned up in Europe.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>