<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent whole days looking at the world this way. https://t.co/aymLKMs5jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one more day of this poxy month. And then...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a stiff drink. https://t.co/ERoS5ojuc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HanrattyDave @PaddyMcKenna Ross Robinson's favourite album that year was Lost Souls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyMcKenna @HanrattyDave Next you'll be saying you don't like Doves...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyMcKenna @HanrattyDave They used to do things like this. https://t.co/JHBxHon26H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Film Reviews of DENIAL, HACKSAW RIDGE and TRAINSPOTTING 2 on @RTEArena with myself and the marvellous @sarahgriffalo https://t.co/t4VSpKyeys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Gleesons interviewed, two to go: Author @RoryRua from Saturday's @Independent_ie https://t.co/A1n17i2QyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Film Reviews from yesterday's @Independent_ie of T2 TRAINSPOTTING, HACKSAW RIDGE and CAMERAPERSON https://t.co/1A1MhCMwRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You give good wall, it's true. https://t.co/U6ywV005El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[breathe
https://t.co/xxfPs5fNEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH Auden's powerful Refugee Blues, read out tonight in the Mansion House #HolocaustMemorialDay https://t.co/XfDDJAOqCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best things about tonight's Holocaust Memorial service in the Mansion House was learning about great peo… https://t.co/BffiqhBo0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just home from the Holocaust Memorial Day ceremony in the Mansion House. This solemn event feels more important tha… https://t.co/ol45KtjKPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I review The Fractured Life of Jimmy Dice, the debut of @RonanRyanWriter, in today's @Independent_ie https://t.co/JpnBkjIHHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with @ian_odoherty in today's @Independent_ie - 100million sharks are killed every year. Magnificent animals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallXMurphy @Independent_ie I'll probably do a profile of the family pets eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I interview my 4th Gleeson in today's @Independent_ie. That's all of them, right? https://t.co/7IzjzDrHcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt, from bumbling brilliantly in Krapp's Last Tape to consoling Natalie Portman in Jackie, was a genius and an icon. Very sad news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on @RTEArena after 7 with this week's film reviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHNKNNY Thanks John. Check out Hertzog's Cave of Forgotten Dreams if you get a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHNKNNY title, author?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After careful consideration, the new Jamiroquai choon is the biz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamkeithtobin Not enough acid jazz either...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rebirth of Jamiroquai's cool. Only took 20 years... https://t.co/KXIpkE4WjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@showmemovieblog Thanks for getting in touch. Will DM you today. H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameshendicott ...until a key economic resource in said sovereign country comes under threat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annemccoy One of your five-a-day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VCCDublin @AlisonTodayFM That's more like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IEWatercooler Stop cribbing your content and go in on Ruth Negga being on the cover. You are an Irish publication for Irish readers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please buy this man's darn fine debut novel. Out today. https://t.co/LgnDC2Tsj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Can't do Trump today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Keith Barry to Kevin Barry... https://t.co/msgtt2Ixkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hail to thee, Ruth Negga!! My @Independent_ie interview with the Best Actress Oscar Nominee https://t.co/hA0ZkxCJ86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah bollox. #Oscars2017 #NoSingSt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler Hitler was spying on a political group who he then joined and rose through.. fuck it, I'm not doing Hitler with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler ..this idiot is being equated with a huge fascist empire that made lampshades and soap out of human bodies. Absurd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler It's cowardly to run behind anyone, masked, punch them in the ear, and sprint away. No one accepts this because...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler Yeah what he and his millions of supporters need is a blind-sided box to the face to keep em off the telly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler For a while, yes. The tactic works so well against the Islamists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler And why are we so threatened by a bigot with a platform to air his revolting views? Laugh at him. Disarm him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPaulDuane @eoinbutler So they get a bruised face and go back to their basement? What a great tactic to change his tune...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Darren_Mooney After last year, I'd be utterly amazed if the shortlist was all white actresses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FavillaCoffee @Independent_ie @IndoEnts So cool. Hope she gets a nod tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Why the world is Loving Ruth Negga *fingers crossed for tomorrow* @Independent_ie @IndoEnts https://t.co/hA0ZkxCJ86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altirishmusic @mansunband You never know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altirishmusic The @mansunband convention is on in Liverpool Feb 17. No joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennpops @Deebodee @EmerTheScreamer @ConorWilson Cadbury's Caramel Bunny. There. I said it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I missing something? I loathed this film. I'm a male critic. And I know female ones who loved it. So... https://t.co/S2y223O6f5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's @Independent_ie film reviews of JACKIE (*swoon*) and SPLIT https://t.co/QDsO2JdG8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Split film review in today's @Independent_ie https://t.co/ErIwc3FyKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackie film review (with added paragraph returns) in today's @Independent_ie https://t.co/tLn9z8t8JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruth Negga interview in today's @Independent_ie https://t.co/yGKn7qQd1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And stop calling him a "nazi". Nazis made lampshades and soap out of my father's people. That guy is a fuckwit with a platform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy who blindsided the nazi or what ever he was, punched him in the ear and then sprinted away is a coward. Nothing heroic about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear fellow film hacks: when writing about Denial, please remember it's "historical writer David Irving", not "historian David Irving".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the bright side, @cassmccombs is playing Dublin tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind boggles. https://t.co/z30Z4Dfrqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edelcoffey @louisemcsharry @morganhousel "HEDGE... HEG... YOU-NANNY...." wait, I can get this....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edelcoffey @louisemcsharry @morganhousel I'll find any way to get out of saying 'hegemony' or 'unanimity' aloud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CineramaGav Sympathies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianMLloyd @DonaldClarke63 @lennyabrahamson Didn't but El Club was one of my top 10 last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @lennyabrahamson I thought it was a real cinematic achievement. Soundtrack, cinematography, writing, Portman. All sublime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't seen this STOP WHAT YOU'RE DOING. https://t.co/9SzsOFhFtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingNutGalway Ah cheers, brother. Thanks for saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be away for the Laetitia Sadier gig in @TGSDublin in April so here's my favourite vocal of her entire career. https://t.co/6i1u33m9VL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H_BF This stuff keeps me awake at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H_BF Marshall GPS just out of shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOOK REVIEW: Rockadoon by @RoryRua @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo https://t.co/EJ7aLUOB7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was bound to happen: Flame-throwing mutant guitarist from Mad Max turns down Trump inauguration https://t.co/MkOBma8Zx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I had great moments with England but I learned that success is defined at the e - https://t.co/vHZSNt6w89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline madness round my way tonight but feck it, I'm off to see Jackie a second time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_caulfield Where the Touts have No Shame?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoryRua That review should appear online on the @Independent_ie website in the next day or so. @TheSundayIndo @BooksIndo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo film reviews of LA LA LAND and MANCHESTER BY THE SEA https://t.co/99DCIhTVEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallXMurphy @sweetoblivion26 Never. Read. The Journal. Comments section.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamGeekEire @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo Casey Affleck glumly kicking werewolf butt is most rewarding, alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My review of MANCHESTER BY THE SEA in today's @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo https://t.co/fYApQ57VYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My review of LA LA LAND in today's @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo https://t.co/z1SCA2ra50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of Rockadoon Shore by me in today's @Independent_ie @TheSundayIndo https://t.co/Yeyy20eaIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenJMacdonald For shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenJMacdonald Is Irving described as "historian" or "historical writer"? Please say latter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhappens HB, old bean!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eh, it's effing January and I saw A Monster Calls this week. I'm good, thanks. https://t.co/r925jAhht4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneilllo @irishexaminer Took the words out of my mouth...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and things were never the same again. https://t.co/YbJTit56EW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dobcomedy @WOWPicsOfLife Feckin' arty shots...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jayzus, @josephamadigan has no manners when it comes to debating and letting others speak. Infuriating listening. @PatKennyNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between Jackie and A Monster Calls, I've been spurred on to make a head start on my Best Films of 2017 list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flinched when I saw this on the walk home. #AMonsterCalls https://t.co/bc4kNzisD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me for first 1hr45min of A Monster Calls: "Ah yeah that's fairly sad alright."
For the last 3mins: "Hello, Kleenex? What's you share price?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H_BF Super shot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@H_BF That's the "difficult second album" cover sorted...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hear it for the Doolin Donna herself, @anniedoona]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evadiminutive Drives me mad how acceptable this is. If a man behaved like that about a girl's weight, he'd be Very Very Bad People™.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndoEnts If a sensitive, behind-the-scenes feature documentary comes out of this I'm going to kill someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_odoherty If you're right, and you may be, what a widespread malfunction! Maybe not helped by the death of long-form journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_odoherty For sure but agencies risk leaving themselves exposed now if they don't grill him efficiently. He can just shout them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpswaine The chasm between US and European values was put into sharp focus in that press conference. No trips there for me til he's gone.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>