<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[These ppl make my head hurt. It's one for a new political party. https://t.co/Iz6lFdHsVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Annotated Bibliography:
Go Write yourself!
T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate no because based on your recent tweets you end being awake at 3am defending someone's rights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate would you like some so-called chocolate? Or some so-called wine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diablos20cn or by @BarryDavis_ and We Ain't Petty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems fitting that Nautical Disaster is playing while I'm otw to write the LSAT #IGotThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoser33 right back at ya man! #teammates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btaplatt @MaddieDiMuccio there is a guy who could learn from the idea of STOP THINK SPEAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow it took less than a week to have my new custom @Alomarbaseball bat #RA271 @AlomarSports @Robbiealomar… https://t.co/peTB6E23Ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horsesandbeer @MaddieDiMuccio @OntarioPCParty the pcpo is a HR nightmare!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_Alvarez best of luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoser33 @BlueJays and do you think it would be less of a travisty (🤣 get it) if there a support our troops ribbon on them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoser33 @BlueJays I heard it was on Sundays.... my bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the @BlueJays are going to wear the reds more than twice a year and we are going to buy them, let's… https://t.co/qujzd3hb0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueJays just a thought instead of Sunday, why not wear them on Friday game and add the support our troops ribbon? #OurMoment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate or on earth. However, no jury would convict someone for a throat punch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RejectedCandyHeartSayings https://t.co/SbOFfMfBZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did @realDonaldTrump see his shadow and we yeah 4 more years of hell? #trump #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy heck, we actually agree on something https://t.co/2RPNuX9Shp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Story of my life https://t.co/qM4I39IAlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bri_Appel @ottawa_jen @AnneMTQuach @NDP_HQ already more productive than @KellieLeitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ottawa_jen except in typical #CPC fashion they have to do it with a misguided message]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@happystash just repeat increase security and I'm not a racist 748 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it, wanting immigration reform doesn't instantly make you racist however if your opinion was purely based on fear you're ignorant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExceptionalLiar @MichelleRempel Hey she said 134 that she wasn't a racist so it must be true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bri_Appel the best part was the sigh of relief from @JohnBrassardCPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel right now. https://t.co/GeRKxZGody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't eat Ham either! Should I leave? https://t.co/sYjXlvEkmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both the left and the right need to give their head a shake #canpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Canadian gov't:
Try evidence based decision making! #canpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dedicated mp, but she needs to stop. The message comes across as Elitist and boardline racist 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel 's speech is the a perfect example of #cpc misguided approach. I normally have a great deal of respect for this 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @YahooTV do you have a selective memory. RG said it was a Muslim ban. Blaze media is fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! My @Alomarbaseball custom bat will be here on Friday! What fast turn around! Less than a week! Thnx @Robbiealomar @AlomarSports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren without the Left snowflakes you'd be irrelevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 6wks and 3 service tickets still can't get @canadapostcorp to fix my mailbox lock #communitymailbox #poorservice #nomailservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#food #comfortfood #yummy #foodyyz #yyz #foodie #foodyyz #foodporn #gastroposttoronto… https://t.co/6zWmyMDv7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mustard Pretzel Crusted Rib Roast  #food #comfortfood #yummy #foodyyz #yyz #foodie #foodyyz… https://t.co/YvndsW2w3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuffed Rib Roast!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is the second coming of #hitler #MuslimBanprotest #muslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in the actual fuck is wrong w @realDonaldTrump. https://t.co/x4bR9AbvLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conyakk @lisakinsella @kinsellawarren manufacturers will leave Canada cuz of Trump's changes to NAFTA long before energy costs are a factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you make this world a terrible place https://t.co/4y1c020xaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren you are fooling anyone. There is already one @AnnCoulter, so just settle down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate One would look bad ass in your office! https://t.co/3i0bsvwbUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ordered my custom @Alomarbaseball Bat! Better get yours now!!! https://t.co/9Dke4xoV1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueJays you really need the photo of Kevin M riding shotgun wondering if he forgot anything 🤣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren the USA could not survive without a global partnership. Your ignorance and hypocritical opinions are extremely entertaining!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New phone number DM me for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren so being liberal is a character flaw? https://t.co/2IlLKKp8pF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks like the Secret Service is doing the #mannequinchallenge around the @POTUS limo #Inauguration #InaugurationDay2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First the Leo memes had to stop and now the Joe Biden ones, sad day! Oh and racist bigot is president, also sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyBats19 hits 55 homers this year! You heard it here first! #welcomeback #canadaisyourcorner #BlueJays @bluejays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would have to agree, but if we let the PED players in the HOF then Pete Rose/Shoeless Joe need to be in the HOF https://t.co/AdcBAgk0ST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Single sized epicmealtime style dinner @crackerbarrel baked tortellini #food #comfortfood #yummy… https://t.co/o3cku4XQeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YorkParamedics @normbarrette @DurhamParamedic or let's add another couple of sports to battle. Baseball/Softball perhaps?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate @Wilnerness590 that's should on a sign when you drive into Toronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjohnoliver @NicoleArbour I'm hurt! I was just pointing out you forget to cite your material]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate I must say between what happened with peel Barrie &amp; Toronto police.. a renewed focus on deescalation tactics is in order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add @iamjohnoliver to the list of ppl @NicoleArbour has ripped off! #notfunny #notcomedy https://t.co/5jZEXCt7co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate the liked is for JB signing not you dying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaffordShow fast forward to when I'm in a nursing home. I'll sit there and sing the fresh price theme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellieLeitch @natnewswatch @PArthurHerald Letters don't make the leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate @KellieLeitch definitely a sign of insecurity and makes me question her leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate been there 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP discussion and community engagement is what makes York Region so great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP I agree 100%, but you now have my scientist brain all fired up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP much better conversation than trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP this a great conversation Because some argue dui rates have plateaued, so how to do we measure effectiveness moving forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sums up my feelings. Knowing the hurt is caused my friends that responded! https://t.co/4a1HejB8QC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is excited for @nbcsnl this week! #goldenshowers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP has it been shown to be effective in other jurisdictions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP ok, it would just seem in today's climate where it's difficult enough to my a charge stick for a DUI, why add an extra variable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP don't get me wrong I hate drinking and driving and as a medic I have seen the destruction but I want to see the charges stick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YRP wouldn't that be a Privacy violation? And/or effect the presumption of innocence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawandchocolate for the win 😹😹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls I can wait to hear you explain this one #goldenshowers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanstoneL @CarterandKingTO I used this line once when I took a personal sick day #gottaluvunions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hivebaseball will you ship to Canada?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webgemglovecare this makes me very sad when this is less than a month old. Plus the efforts to get it in Canada 😿😿 https://t.co/MDj61I3yDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren the GOP just ran a presidential candidate that demonizes ppl. Let's not forget about Travis Co. GOP chair either. #getreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump yeah ya did, we aren't that stupid to believe your insults! Just stop!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NashvilleCMT @conniebritton from Ranya to Feye, what a range! Most underrated actress in Hollywood #GoldenGlobes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And  @goldiehawn too https://t.co/sYpryfLNV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all agree @IMKristenBell wins best dressed right?! #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smashlanta burn it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@violadavis is just the best! #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate hearing about this, one wrong move and this would be innocent ppl killed. Go to a track!!!!! https://t.co/IvM7WOWim9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving NAFTA would be horrible! Oshawa &amp; Windsor would turn into a parking lot https://t.co/d1AQVPOwUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody is keeping warm #catstagram #cats_of_instagram #mrpresident https://t.co/yBP92xJrAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren look at the difference in approach @POTUS is inclusive &amp; +ive @realDonaldTrump alienates everyone that isn't a supporter &amp; -ive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theJagmeetSingh @JustinTrudeau are Leaders @KellieLeitch is a xenophobic bigot, pay attention #cpc or Canadians will move past your party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smashlanta nice dinner!! I love that commercial!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatCallaghan I can't imagine how you guys do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatCallaghan in all fairness 2am for you is like 7am for the rest of us ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#chickenkiev #food #comfortfood #yummy #foodyyz #yyz #foodie #foodyyz #foodporn… https://t.co/ULSO6QaHvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#chickenkiev #food #comfortfood #yummy #foodyyz #yyz #foodie #foodyyz #foodporn… https://t.co/Kr08IbaoHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#food #comfortfood #yummy #foodyyz #yyz #foodie #foodyyz #foodporn #gastroposttoronto… https://t.co/qKPHLYUzkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mr. President! #catbirthday #happybirthday #mrpresident #adoptdontshop… https://t.co/NZ4bt1vOVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normbarrette @YorkParamedics ..... Please, Ill never ask for anything again 😆 https://t.co/SAWO0eCJxo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>