<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on Radio New Zealand's The Panel from 3:45pm to 5pm today talking about the big issues of the day - and the Sevens. @radionz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prople pouring into Wellington Stadium have officially taken the crowd status up to "virtually empty". #sevens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzjambo @annikakes @malthouse I'd pay money for Lorne Sausage without the hassle of pretending to like the bread, salad and condiments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzjambo @annikakes @malthouse I think the issue is around calling it a sandwich, and it is more of a too fluffy roll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzjambo @annikakes @malthouse We are talking about the same thing. Small square flat Scottish bread rolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you get an email from an organisation you never subscribed to but are like "well, that is quite interesting." #FWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog: @malthouse Scottish Session - beer, haggis, whisky, tatties, neeps, kilts, rugby and BattleStar Galactica - https://t.co/Bc7U7UA1sC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum @ForkandBrewer @MelissaCole @BeerKel I can confirm wrestling is the sweetest of all arts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pdmjohns  Not doing well am I? Except for this beer, 20 year old whisky, and haggis and black pudding pizza...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Scottish passport has been revoked after I mixed up Burns Day with St Andrews Day - and rightly so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Saint Andrews Day! To celebrate, Scotland lost... at cricket... to the United Atab Emirates... #freedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My AT-ACT has been named - Scruffy - as in Scruffy Nerf Herder and it also fires Nerf Missiles. Thanks for all the… https://t.co/VWjvxZQhpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog: Scottish beer takeover, Lorne sausage, Scottish #Sevens, #deepfriedhaggisonastick, poems, freedom - https://t.co/1vRwOdmhWN @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the Wellington Summer. I shall have to put more sunblock on. Oh wait, I meant raincoat. #wellymania]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum Love the franchise - but this series is a little odd. At least Avon is the star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's Insomnia Morning Theate is Blakes Seven  Series Four. I have mixed feelings about this. #teamavon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On yet another Chris de Burgh music binge. He sure does sing about War and Christianity a lot. #noborderline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fitz_Bunny I liked summer before it was cold....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Wellington - do you understand the concept of summer? Like, even on a theoretical level? Love, Wellingtonians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of Optimism: Guy walking to work in 148km/h winds... with an umbrella. #wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disclaimer - that is not my bottom in the @malthouse photo. #iwish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum The Flying Squad? Guv'nor? Check out how much they drink on duty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am watching Chris de Burgh concerts. I am not ashamed. I'm a fan. May own all his albums... #yesido]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipreeve It does not have to be a name of a Top Ten Beer - go creative!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philipreeve That one I do not get...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COMPETITION NAME - Name my new #StarWars AT-AT action figure (NOT a toy) and I will buy you a beer from my Top Ten… https://t.co/EI02GjFSkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynsims This knowledge warms my tiny dark heart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_ob @malthouse Not the only one do to that, tiger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil's Top Ten Kiwi Beers of 2016: Always fun, sometimes controversial. Who makes the coveted list? https://t.co/BnWXfsXSYr @malthouse #BEER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG. Can Trump become US President without the endorsement of "A-List Celebs"? Turns out the Constitution says "yep".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge Kudos to the @BasinReserve and Wellington Cricket. We won the semi-final - and they served @panheadbrewery and @TuataraBrew - Win/Win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I was away on holiday my printer turned itself back on to announce it was somehow suddenly out of yellow ink. #weird #OfficeSpace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFromHereNZ The Big Apple. Somewhere between Napier and Wellington!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back from a fantastic holiday featuring @tamsynbadland, chicken wings,  @baylandsbrewery, @MboroughBrewery, cheese @WestshoreInn and fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil's Beer of the Week: @MboroughBrewery Foxy Red Dry Hopped Red IPA which is especially good fresh off the tap at the brewery. #nbotw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday I went to a roadside fruit and vegetable stall... and bought a black pudding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessikaJayne Yeah - It was Whitewater - not Watergate. Several decades apart. And my point was #VRWC was a distraction from the issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessikaJayne She made up the #VRMC then to cover her husbands infidelities. We are not that organised. Just ask Vince Foster. #filesgone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessikaJayne Yeah - it was a joke certificate that you could print off the Interwebs. I haz no idea how you guys starting tweeting about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessikaJayne @OurPowderDry Not sure you guys got my picture - I am a right winger in New Zealand and someone gave me the VRWC certificate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog: The @malthouse Year in Review, Trump, West Coast IPAs, beer &amp; music matching, @EpicBeer Son of Thor (Chilli) https://t.co/pnNWI9Ap6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you laugh at something you forgot you wrote: "Next time, we drink to monkeys - because everything is better with monkeys."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRashbrooke Willie Nelson wants his royalties for that #oldjoke (well played)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muppet Alert: saying #LanceArmstrong "still managed to win the Tour de France seven times, and even with drugs that's pretty amazing" #cheat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craft Beer Corner Column in @cuisinemagazine - @LordAlmightyAle Stone Forest Ale with skewered beef hearts - went t… https://t.co/vtDu7sLI95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is my annual work Christmas Party. It is at the @malthouse if anyone wants to join. There will be plenty of room for obvious reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer blog: Christmas rant, @EpicBeer takes over, @Garage_Project #12kegs for Christmas (yay), new menu - https://t.co/aSraMOJb9R @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just chilling with my Imperial crew (and random the Sand Person) at the midnight premiere of #rogueone in Wellingto… https://t.co/K7kKKeaZ2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all the hashtags my phone should know, I thought @epicbeer would be top of the list... Sorry all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just switched from Heineken at a function to @eicbeer Thunder at a pub. Staff probably suspicious of my giant grin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starbeer Doing a title in seventeen syllables can be very diff...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Bottleneck @buzzandhum Agreed. "Wonderful Wheat Beers Wet My Whistle" is the still the worst inflicted on one my articles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum I do not run anywhere. You know that. Turns out the answer was more Confucius (this is a magazine article, not @malthouse blog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starbeer Asian style beers - found a good Confucius quote - and it is politically topical here right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secondzeit I quoted Confucius - hardly ever goes wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward writers moment when you finish (what you think) is a good beer article. But you just cannot think of a suitable title.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Spellchecker - no matter how many times you try to "correct" it, I am never ever submitting a beer article saying "fewer aftertastes".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summertime: An article about summer beers - which are not even a real style anyhow. https://t.co/sBwraVxCtF @DeepCreekBrew @julesvanc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoganBeer That rare moment when I am going to be the least offensive person in the room. Last recorded example - 2003 (by accident).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil's Beer of the Week: @MboroughBrewery Hop Elixir - literally, first beer purchased out of the new Featherston Tavern craft beer fridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Elect Trump selects @WWE Linda McMahon for Cabinet. She may not kick ass but she can kick some grapefruits https://t.co/JPGb7v69Wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf Some of us knew that was coming. She has run for Senate before and is a major donor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Epic beer blog: 13 tap takeover for @EpicBeer 11th birthday, Star Wars and @johnkeypm's favourite beer - https://t.co/G2ZTJzxXIw @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool moment (2010) when every political leader in New Zealand declared their favourite beer to a blog  - https://t.co/DklWxnq9gv @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My battle with (Man of the Match) David Warner makes it into a Canadian beer blog. Because we be awesome, eh.… https://t.co/0XoHb2aBKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@its_not_lupus @HayleyHeartbrk @DearMama_ @abbey_maree @morgy85 Oh what a maneuver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonogaluszka Wow. It's been a while since that (admitted great) column.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasures from the Thorndon Fair. Ducks, sloths, Pukekoes and geekery. https://t.co/s3eLqJzhjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil's Beer of the Week: @MboroughBrewery Black Nectar Stout. Popular vote winner at a high-powered tasting this week #nbotw @BrewersGuildNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost Oh a number of issues today - may need an email address as it is way over 140 characters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34 minutes on hold for @nzpost and then get a voice saying they have technical difficulties and cannot answer the call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently on hold for over 20 minutes to contact @nzpost - at least they are playing a fine selection of Kiwi songs as hold music! #rockon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Nickelback sign explanation for @davidwarner31 - thanks @radionz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithiesGrant I'm sending this to David Warner...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZDistiller You would be surprised at how many people have sent me this piece of genius!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy construction noise at 11pm - outside three apartment buildings - for wastewater work finishing in February. #wcc #dickmove #noteqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a couple of small but noticeable aftershocks to get one to put proper pants and shoes on. The joys of working from home. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer Blog: Rainbow Project collaborative beers between UK and NZ brewers - and boy are they creative!: https://t.co/MgiKTrEbhI @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaynefrances63 @NakulMPande @QldBaggie Never denied it. Said he didn't know what it meant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NakulMPande @jaynefrances63 @QldBaggie I freely admit that sign was the inspiration. Then I found it is also a thing in US sports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent It may have something to with the fact that he did not have real elections, far less term limits. He was a tyrant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fidel Castro - Sic semper evello mortem tyrannis" ("Thus always I bring death to tyrants"). #nolegend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The word hero is bandied atound too often, Spilled Beer Guy at #NZvPAK is my hero. @markmywordsCGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greigmcgill @PirateLifeBeer @mcleodsbrewery @BehemothbeerNZ @malthouse Oi. That has been pointed out to me by my girlfriend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monica_mead You provide a great quote - you make it into the story! #moreofasweetbaconsandwich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcleodsbrewery It is such a good cause I decided to take it to the extreme. Luckily I will be buying one today to save my soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Wellington - today - attend a Japanese festival, drink @PirateLifeBeer at @malthouse, then support @SPCAWgtn at @BlackDogBrewCo #welly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer Blog: Pirates, @PirateLifeBeer tap takeover, @mcleodsbrewery/@BehemothbeerNZ colab, sausage rolls https://t.co/4SQpcPuYww @malthouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's insomnia theater is Starship Troopers. Thankfully, I adore this film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how you do political satire... well played @garwboy https://t.co/IfuhWBSOGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington - Hi-Vis is the New Black. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog: Cider, earthquakes, Ciderhouse, I almost picked President Trump, Canberra beer, footnotes -&gt; https://t.co/ZNmz1P0NuY @malthouse #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rare photo of me doing good - collecting monies for @SPCAWgtn https://t.co/bC6XJwlKdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear earthquake. You knocked my Chuck Norris autobiography off the book shelf and onto the floor. This will not end well for you. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuwZealand Had a lot of fun in that bed with the piggy we stole from the shed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennhendry Three pairs - just to be safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's dress code is "dress like you might have to run out of the building and stay out for a few days" #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah - sleeping is way over-rated. #eqnz #rollinrollinrollin Safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday evening. Hoppy beer, listening to John Denver, and missing my lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collecting for the SPCA outside David Jones this morning (8-10). Give me money! #spca]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>