<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber is back on instagram and my life feels complete again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizBallmaier @samlandreth @EmBallmaier SCREAMING FOR ALL THREE OF YOU!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my brother: " I should really wash my work clothes" 
me: *finds brothers work clothes in my laundry basket*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as a couple walks separate directions in target to begin their shopping, she says, "see you in a few years sweetheart"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grip my coffee tight and talk to it everyday... like it is something that might save me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[another year marking the loss of my best friend. doing life without you is at times so empty, but I smile, proud to hold your memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and when you don't think you can do anymore - try once more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lastkevstanding bahaha! I don't recommend children try it, but I made it work! My shirt is dry! Blessings!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MisstaJay haha! It survived! 45 seconds at a time! Woo!!! I have a shirt again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do you think if i put my shirt in the microwave to dry it will catch fire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you are not chained to the secrets you create. find freedom in that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[get to the gym. realize my pants are on backwards. this. is. my. life. 

coffee delivery, anyone?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brushing your teeth to then quickly drink your coffee.... wouldn't suggest it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying "yes" to Jesus and not to the world is possibly the toughest decision I've had to make. Even still, it is well with my soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta get out of my own head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloDannyOwens SYM = save your money. and that is easy when you're not spending it on gas 😛]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life hack: eat while walking around the appie table. Makes it look like you took less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahaspen_ we all good! made it out strong, haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahaspen_ current status: lying on the gym floor letting my heart calm its beating, lol, whoops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 shots of espresso at 8:30pm was not my best life decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching couples fight at the gym is my Monday morning entertainment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought my first pair of sweat pants yesterday. The word cozy has completely new meaning now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dyer has read,"9 minutes remaining" for the last 20 minutes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmBallmaier i laughed SO HARD when he walked over and gave me the dollar. #dead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time my co-worker makes a sexual joke towards me..he owes me 25 cents. I earned this dollar in less than 5 mi… https://t.co/mWpHZ4AIIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*spends 35 dollars more to get that 7 dollar shipping for free*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmBallmaier guy at the gym with the last name deol..and wearing a sweater to rep it. It only has me thinking about that salad tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the newbies here at the gym thinking, "new year, new me"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandyJoJohnston dang! A note would have been easier than talking! Wish I thought of that sooner!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[current aesthetic: gripping 4 mini ice cream buckets, a bottle of wine, 3 choco bars, and a bag of gold fish. 2017 diet is coming in hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImStephRivera haha, got off the train about an hour ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImStephRivera I'll never know. I couldn't bring myself to do it! I tried to do it- I did try!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmBallmaier LOL. My stop is in 2 minutes. Not enough time! The love story ends here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: he is on my train back to Canada and I am currently hiding the furthest back seat. https://t.co/JqGmyJY6Vm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crashed straight into the cutest guy at the train station and in my flustered state... I looked up at him and said, "thank-you" #dead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy didn't lock the washroom door on the train. Walking in on him was like walking in on 2017, wild]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pizza , blessing us since birth https://t.co/l5e2H1mbfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahaspen_ On my way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing with myself: 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samlandreth @EvanDalen @LizBallmaier @EmBallmaier MY HEART CANT WAIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moms in McDonalds lobby giving dinner threats: "you're not getting any ice cream unless you finish your french fries" 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out here surrounded by Christmas lights and I just see everyone out here holding their spouses and suddenly I feel cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wrapping all those Christmas gifts thinking, "man, these are so good... I wish I was gifting them to myself"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ioegreer @ScottBorrero  S A M E! 😭 this is so good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[feeling rebellious of all sorts. I just walked through IKEA backwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sitting here wishing for chocolate, and honestly, I don't even really like chocolate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[boys. the reason wine was invented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 19 year old sister: "mom, guess what I did today?" 
Mom: "you woke up by yourself today?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmBallmaier bless you! 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how many times is hitting snooze too many times? .... asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my hedgehog, Fred, hasn't been eating the last 4 days. Please pray for Fred. 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davidgr30431023 lol. Was thinking "all alone April", really.😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@couldyouclarify #lifethough This honestly made me laugh so hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 and my future 2017. Because same https://t.co/1TEv6Jo1IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*eats entire family size chip bag to hide evidence that I opened it*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in a state of missing @EmBallmaier https://t.co/HYk4ORfmye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up dead from laughter. RT to save a live @EmBallmaier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you think you know someone, but your whole relationship has been a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*usually leaves 10 minutes before starting work.*  never been late. Today, *leaves 45 minutes before starting work* arrives late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just spent 50 dollars on hedgehog toys. I don't even give myself that much luxury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last night: lost my phone. Went back 2 mcdonalds 20 min later to find it...found it in the trash can inside my folded up to-go back. LOL HOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMPATIENTLY WAITING https://t.co/6pfM4scPtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a huge shoutout to melatonin. Thanks for bringing sleep back to the schedule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I work at a pool and the entire water polo team just dabbed at me on their way out, one by one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I showered today. It is going to be a good day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My room adequately resembles my mind. something similar to what the after math of a nuclear bomb might look like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this whole being patient thing is wearing me thin. I could use a nap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guy at the gym fell asleep on the stretching mats, but honestly, same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goals, really https://t.co/m9rhHL0ojL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Is. Everything. https://t.co/RxmsllxQPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same though 😂 https://t.co/jnOMi55W3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vllmnn I actually sleep when it feels like home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloDannyOwens easier said than done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[current mood: https://t.co/wRLx0p1zE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lastkevstanding haha!!!! ok, fine! I'll be #basic when it isn't popular anymore 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just purchased 200 dollars worth of gym attire. Eats McDonald's for dinner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a "how basic are you" test last night and only scored 20%. And like, honestly, I'm disappointed in myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What better way to live than for others to feel Christ through our own lives, the Glory of God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is so pretty I could drool" ...."I just wish I could drool on command so you could see my emotions right now"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[low key screaming over here because this basic white girl is ready for Christmas! 1 month away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I hope you have a great night with me on your mind." and that is all she wrote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want bad gas station coffee, a tank full of gas, and a heart full of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's raining.... quick! let's all suddenly forget how to drive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the bus driver is swinging his hips and singing his 1968 CD jams. I already love this shuttle ride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a hard time looking people in the eyes. I feel like they are reading my soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it is a shame to see how "social fame" can quickly changes a persons character. It makes me wonder where their heart stood this whole time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a girl my age with a flip phone today and for a minute I wanted to be her. I miss the simplicity of this social world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmBallmaier YEAS YOU ARE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[throw them middle fingers up- it's Friday! https://t.co/1PT7seQWjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last night: met up w/ 2 strangers. got chased by the cops. lost my phone at the "crime scene"... forcing us to return like ninjas. #living]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[random post:the last few days my eyes have been almost completely swollen shut &amp; docs dont know why. It is very painful&amp; prayer would b nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I woke up from a terrible nightmare, so, I am going to close my eyes and someone wake me when there is better news#Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbrookesmith amen! I was getting real bored, lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when the person you were supposed to meet 30 minutes prior says "2 away" and then takes another 20 to arrive.  It's fine...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he said to me... "look at this brick wall... can I be a hipster now?" https://t.co/bJratUQvY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samlandreth it is allowed! Always allowed. bb bois always play. 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samlandreth LOL! This is my life. can't a girl just feel for no given reason?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if rhi rhi and drake can't keep love alive... what even is love? #realtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner conversations: 
Mom: "we just sold a 42" TV why are you looking at 55" TVS?" 
Dad: "because I'm blind and I could see on the 42"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloDannyOwens no, I really don't! But I want to get it!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>