<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Collectorgalaxy @justinseeley looking forward to following the hunt for Boba. Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinseeley really enjoying the latest episode of @Collectorgalaxy Almost walked into traffic listening to the rocket firing boba story!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only good thing about the Pro Bowl is seeing the teams lined up with their team helmets on. Looks kinda cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge @TheMichaelNipp @davedollar @RemodelingClay that might actually have been better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @davedollar @RemodelingClay @jd_burge have any of you fellas seen Exposed with Keanu Reeves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docllv @MileHighReport better yet, I made it to Mile High in 94 for last ever visit of LA Raiders. Disn't go well either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docllv @MileHighReport I've had to watch NYG, Skins, 49ers &amp; Seahawks beatdowns at about 3am. Refused to go to bed until FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docllv @MileHighReport First pass of that game. Deep sideline to Nattiel (I think). Thought we were going to win that one. How wrong ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sydark71 apparently you can play it on Tabletop Simulator via Steam as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sydark71 think he was considering ordering tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sydark71 Exposed with Keanu Reeves. Sounded like a straight up cop's partner is killed thriller. Some weird shit happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me watching a movie right now https://t.co/vG0wV8c24x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp ah, ok. Don't feel so dumb now. Country music doesn't really reach us here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp Red Cup? What's it all mean? What's the play on words here? Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scubedpod very enjoyable. Had to stop at Rebels as I haven't seen it yet. The Jyn/Rogue One chat was great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay haha that's all I'll see now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay would quite like a Lions one too to be honest. Always liked that logo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay I shall seek it out. Hoping this bad boy is my next one https://t.co/tPOtFAsFBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay The U, Stanford (Elway connection) and FSU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay ah, got you. I like that cap. I have a thing for caps. Have about two dozen at home. Only got 3 college caps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay I'd take a stab at 'yes' being the right answer though, given your location.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay I don't really follow baseball, sorry. NFL is my US sport. Watched some hockey when I could see it but not for a while now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay as a kid outwith Star Wars and the other obvious ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay agree on Point Break too. May as well throw Ghostbusters in there as well. Red Dawn and Ice Pirates were two I watched a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay I wonder if it subconsciously steered (pardon the pun) me towards the Broncos a few years later? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay was the original set in Colorado?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay kinda why I avoided it. The characters all looked very "Twilighty" to me so 10 mins was as much as I could take]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay ...tourist eyes seeing tree lined streets with big houses that have screen doors and porches. Prob nothing like Boulder ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay nice. I've seen about ten mins of it and the leafy streets I saw reminded me of Boulder, CO but I suspect part of that is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay oh really? Cool. (Not the movie). Where is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemodelingClay man I love Red Dawn. That's a great movie. "Wolverines!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to go for a walk and listen to @scubedpod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarWarsScots @StarWarsUK I'd go stormtrooper (Snowtrooper if I could pick any). Not ready for the 'enhancements' of the Death trooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDeucecast @shazbazzar ahhh, my bad. Great show. Like the Rogue One discussion a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shazbazzar you were meaning Mt. Tantiss on @TheDeucecast right? It was in the Thrawn trilogy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarWarsScots Coruscant is ok. The Republic capital planet goes to the home system of the sitting Supreme Chancellor so 000 is ok for now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp the footage from the Trump rally made me feel ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp 13th was excellent. Quite scary throughout but really interesting. Birth of a Nation looks utterly horrifying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast this will be my 7th title I've seen in January for the first time. Ticking along nicely so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast plus my wife is out of town for a few days and will want to see Spotlight now I think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast as I'm in Netflix 13th wins. Spotlight is on Amazon. Too lazy to change apps ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Webster_YNWA @JimSpenceSport Worked for them myself, as did my Mum. I held the trolley record for the Victoria St, Perth store ðŸŽ‰ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDeucecast need some help. Should I watch Place Beyond the Pines, Spotlight, 13th or Dawn of the Planet of the Apes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Reinebold it's in the bag, Coach. https://t.co/FhrNFZVHTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. Looks like the Trade Federation droid control ships. https://t.co/4YKzYZ69Q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@no1stuntmaster brilliant isn't it. Been one of my favourite shows of recent years. Felt like it was made just for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Inselaffe76 that's my wer cousin that wrote that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeTarkin @sandcrawlercast do another one! Get Tom Berges on! For Jedha! Another exclamation mark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty cool. https://t.co/kCizUUMyps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarWarsScots Palps could have killed him any time he liked. He needed Anakin to see him losing and 'save' him to aid his turning him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pablohidalgo pop over to Scotland some day ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter did a quick FN-2187 sketch earlier. https://t.co/3TASmJK29T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge I remember a delegation of Cree visiting the Scottish Parliament a few tears ago so definitely a connection there somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge yeah, I think so too. When I read there were Koreans, Chinese etc fighting the Allies on D-Day I couldn't believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge one of my ancestors apparently became a Chief of the Cree tribe (think it was Cree anyway). I'd like to find out more about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge never is when it goes against message though. You never here about the non-whites from WW1/2 really but there were plenty fighting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArkhamAsylumDoc it saddens me every day I hear this talk. Humans should be better than this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArkhamAsylumDoc the thing people who protest about immigrants in the US/UK forget is that almost all of us can be traced back to immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joemcalinden oooh. Is there perhaps gig news afoot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandcrawlercast @DengarDan @CollectorsHutt really looking forward to this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jontlewis 9 white Sy dupes if you want them. Not sure what to request in trade so offer whatever you fancy giving up. Stevemcg in the app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jd_burge @blackvoices I first learned of the true colour of the west in a small museum in Glenwood Springs, CO. In 94. It was fascinating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gbodancer Official twitter quoting me. A game late though. https://t.co/pnVdSXX5DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek nice. I have a maroon jacket like that. Also have a Harrington. Love my Harrington. Desert boots in my wardrobe too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now well into S4 if The Clone Wars. A few filler episodes but in the midst of a decent few eps with Pong Krell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoffeeWthKenobi @Fandango sitting on 6. Hoping I can squeeze one more in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast haha no they still show those on primetime BBC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDeucecast @TheMichaelNipp well Jake the Snake was excellent. Sad news is UK Netflix has no 30 for 30s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDeucecast @TheMichaelNipp I'll check when this is finished. Really hope they are there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp don't believe so. Our Netflix is like the cousin the family would rather forget. Not too bad for TV but pretty bad for films]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast I wish I had a service that showed 30 for 30. Only ever seen the one on The U. It was brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelNipp @TheDeucecast really great so far. Used to be a big wrestling fan back in the 80s. Remember that Steamboat match clearly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choking up here #JaketheSnake Damn you @TheDeucecast !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitchTweets he was immense. That Broncos squad was unbelievable. Elway, Sharpe, Smith, McCaffrey, Romocop, Neal Smith et al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww man Jake the Snake is wearing a Raiders jacket. BAD JAKE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This record could stand for a long time. #TDforNFLHoF https://t.co/KB5rORoMGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Butch 'The Natural' Reed with his natural blonde hair isn't in it though, I may boycott @TheDeucecast  ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Jake the Snake documentary. Another @TheDeucecast tip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyWanKenobi one that I didn't have. Weren't many, but that is one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek maybe at my Mum's somewhere. I was a ten year old Mod ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek you'll have to let me know what songs are standing out for you from what you've heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek used to go to school in the 70a with my fishtail parka with The Jam and The Who painted on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek aww, nice. My favourite band of all-time. The album All Mod Cons is a masterpiece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skageek used to love how the guy in the 'Don't Speak' video had on a Jam t-shirt. Guy had taste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip 1. If New England is playing you support the NFC team. ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/TfD2BPSKM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarWarsScots you got that right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Star Wars Funko Pops? Give @FunkoSWGuide a follow. This man knows his stuff. RTs appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast definitely. Haven't seen the second one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast I have an Odeon card so have been six times! Yeah, Monsters was ace. Remember seeing him on BBC breakfast talking about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast I've pretty much only seen Rogue One since December.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomBrogan @FraserC69 it got so bad in one nightmare my primary school slid back like the pool at Tracey Island and the missiles flew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast he more or less re-used in Rogue One?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast I liked them both, but Godzilla more. Lucy was a better idea than what I saw though. Dis you spot the two shots in Godzilla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TGGamingReviews hell yes ðŸ¤˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomBrogan @FraserC69 please, no Threads mentions. I had nightmares for months after I watched that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireherting @teamcovenant they look very cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomBrogan Coisty! Pity that $#%|!|â‚¬!~ Sandy Clark is there. I do not like that guy. Selling Danny Griffin. What an eejit ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice! Cheers Tom. Genuinely 3 of my favourite Saintees in the one on the left. @JimMorton10 is a legend ðŸ‘ https://t.co/fGelg4AilQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast @SW_Prequels yeah, ok. Or go Celtic (with a k sound) Jedi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewinBelfast @SW_Prequels One begs to differ ðŸ˜‰ https://t.co/fHOGd5sgFk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>