<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndseeykelly ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ aye next time I see u you'll be getting the whole bunch ðŸ‡ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamiebrodie7 @rmurrell91 I'll DM u the now mate #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmurrell91 be a hero if u do mate ðŸ’š ggtth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HFCTransferNews don't think this is true whatsoever but hope so ðŸ™ðŸ»ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmurrell91 u Ken anyone with an ST who's no going? Sorted 3 need a 4th lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheryllfyffe5 David can show him how to ðŸ’©ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ am no risking cleaning that up ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheryllfyffe5 if u get Brodie to pee in the potty on sat James will ðŸ’¯ copy him ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very slow time tbh but it's a start ðŸƒ https://t.co/A6RfbAOocU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LC_Flamingo @JackFyffe1875 should bring alcohol into fitbaw ðŸ˜‚ nae mare boring 0-0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LC_Flamingo @JackFyffe1875 I thought it was a sport... was Taylor no tipped for sports personality a few times?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman @Janjo1874 Dylan mcgeouch going off right before u went 1 up was diff in 1st half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Janjo1874 @iainmccalman I was stunned use were 2-0 up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiegers55 @iainmccalman am a fuck I just hate them slightly less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiegers55 @iainmccalman ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚âœŠðŸ»ðŸ’¦ who is it use are 22 points Be Hyndman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiegers55 @iainmccalman Rangers than hearts? Hibs than hearts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT @iainmccalman this is a good start to my dream day lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman any these cunts on FM ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman our defence is solid and if we have our full team I'm confident.. but again I know zero about ur new players ðŸ˜‚ never signed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1990strang @iainmccalman tickets are gonna be gold dust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman rather than ma 0-3 predictions last week haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman confident than I was when we drew you last year. Derbys a Derby eh anything can Happen I'd take 0-1 right now lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman Not as good to watch but more confident of getting results, also the signing of Humphrey is exactly what we needed. I'm more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman ðŸ˜‚, even if they are decent I reckon these games will come too early for yous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman ðŸ˜‚ still confident mate no seen half ur team before lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't see any of them happening but Hendo and Stokes would make this the best day ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackFyffe1875 @gglfc123 ðŸ˜‚ go hard or go home son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackFyffe1875 @gglfc123 stick it all on score and win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale1690 @JackFyffe1875 seen worse tackles in a warm up for a charity game ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where it takes u bout an hour just to cross the road ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickyWhytock for moments like this ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to this nobody ðŸ˜‚ cathros been editing his stats hahahaha reckon I'd score 8/8 in league 2 https://t.co/PxuSjToPe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheryllfyffe5 it's @Dale1690 we r talking about here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[95%of hearts song book involved 1902... GIRFUY #wee championship side will embarrass u on 12th Feb https://t.co/TwkGWcWSMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themcinallys like kickback there's some retard hibs fans LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themcinallys just for the record roberto Carlos was a left back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themcinallys genuinely never heard of him, hope he plays on 12th lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themcinallys ðŸ˜‚ u comparing a boy who's scored goals for a team that half ma 5s team have played for to ur record scorer ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting my pals, 4 months till he notices ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’šðŸ† https://t.co/iQkJzJhdff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @DeanPearson10 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre I'll never find it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @DeanPearson10 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre I can mind a snap chat of u blasting out SOL ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @DeanPearson10 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre I was sending them to Jamie ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre @DeanPearson10 ðŸ˜‚ aye and me hahaha! Was a wee stare and a smirk beforehand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre @DeanPearson10 1 of the funniest things I've seen, guy singing ur song bouncing beside u ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @Allyb123xx @addymcintyre @DeanPearson10 Steph u coming to the roseburn before the Derby lol?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @Christiep78 @DeanPearson10 @Jaymondo10 @addymcintyre so urs aren't the best lol?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christiep78 @DeanPearson10 @Jaymondo10 @stephwalker141 @addymcintyre was dean who asked me to start singing it ðŸ˜‚ nae reason just coz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christiep78 @DeanPearson10 @Jaymondo10 @stephwalker141 @addymcintyre ðŸ˜‚ positive it was hibs v malmo, walking round to the game am sure it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanPearson10 @stephwalker141 @addymcintyre JAMIE WALKERS....... ðŸ˜‚ she can take the banter tho lol good lass and closet hibby ðŸ˜‰ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanPearson10 @stephwalker141 @addymcintyre best time was before a Derby Steph walked into office and told me to shut up.... 2 secs later..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamiebrodie7 genuinely never knew until the day lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephwalker141 @DeanPearson10 @addymcintyre ðŸ˜‚ just seen that pal! I've never once sang it ðŸ‘€ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚ xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be honest, Bikey chose hearts cause he will get a game there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ct_Tommo7 that's mental lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do away goals count?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davethehibee it's with hills, first winner up like no fussed tbf just be happy if other two win haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Davethehibee fucking annoying ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See if u do a lucky 15 and you've got a non runner what's the script?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshY1875 @CammyHFCLoudon no team talk needed for tincastle... just play this..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamiebrodie7 why would I lie ðŸ˜‚ seriously I'm 29 in April]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamiebrodie7 swear ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamiebrodie7 nah u playing in a team mate? Gives a shout if ur needing a player (genuinely I'm 28 tho ðŸ˜‚)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbiegers55 do u no need to have a bird to have a cheat day ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hertz77 @chriswilson98 most of them after 99?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chri5t1neGauld ðŸ˜‚ Think Paterson sale was funding some of that to ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chri5t1neGauld never says u didn't ðŸ˜‚, I'm saying hearts wouldn't financially survive 3 years in championship lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chri5t1neGauld either way ðŸ–•ðŸ»ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it's "but Hibs have a prem budget in championship" 
Annnd? 
Would hearts be able to do that for 3 year? ðŸ™„ #bigteam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chri5t1neGauld ðŸ˜‚ we either are or we aren't lol? #makeurmindup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chri5t1neGauld ðŸ˜‚ cannot wait for this game.... Bare that in mind "championship team" ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatalieEadie it's gonna be a nightmare ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can hear a faint Bring on the Hibees hahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abiemccracken I know ðŸ˜‚ wonder how many folk have screenshots of ma tweets just incase haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I canny celebrate this! This is the time to play these mugs!! ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeparkx @erinhunter93 @humphrey_17 I meant to write 4 lol ruined itðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeparkx @erinhunter93 even weirder that @humphrey_17 has 3 legs lol no wonder he's so fast ðŸƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWright24 on Derby day it's class in there lol wouldn't walk past it any other day though ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWright24 ken lol but am hoping we've chucked that tag haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanWright24 I'd say it is to mate, all the pressure on us lol... no fussed who wins the night tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswilson98 @Garymckenzie7 @iainmccalman purely cause Raith defence looked no bad 2nd half ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswilson98 @Garymckenzie7 @iainmccalman I'm over the excitement of the draw so keeping how confident I am to myself lol ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswilson98 @Garymckenzie7 @iainmccalman don't think bookies will have us as fav but confident myself ðŸ’šðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weesue13 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I know what it is lol I just don't know why Monday is to be like it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Messi handle it at Gangzhoue on a cold Tuesday night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weesue13 what's that lol?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswilson98 ðŸ˜‚, tbf I can't see it..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriswilson98 ðŸ¤’ 2 day sleep is needed ðŸ˜‚ see u on 11th/12th #possibly haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hmcconville_x although going on Jeremy kyle and then saying this is personal makes sense eh ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hmcconville_x ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ haha I never cause I was on the phone lol raging now haha! Shut yer puss haha the most Scottish saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hmcconville_x shocking eh ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shame... hope you pull through #hope ðŸ™ðŸ» https://t.co/gqw1gwpNiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaeIrvineHollid ðŸ˜‚ Sundays are bad enough without any this 666 caper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackFyffe1875 @Alancooney4 @DeanPearson10 I reckon they would've got sick of me kissing arse if I was there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could easily Sunday sesh like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobianderson08 am in the house n I've just had 4 fags in a row and want to hit the boozer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna have to calm down, the hibs players might freeze when they start singing oh when the hearts, go marching in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fraser1980 @Robbiegers55 it's his suit he wore to the final

And cause their pish Robbie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ call hibs a wee team and say IF we beat Raith in same sentence https://t.co/xcvJlqMMua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmccalman Ken the script mate just waiting for the usual bites ðŸ˜‚ Ive not been so confident in years tho haha like a bairn the now hahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading between the lines.... use r shitting it ðŸ˜‚ and rightly so... surely no again hahahahahahaha IF use beat Raith ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hertz77 Chelsea hull or Raith hibs mate u decide]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>