<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Academic nephrologist here, ditto. https://t.co/6jVi7Y6eAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'punch a Nazi' meme: what are the ethics of punching Nazis? | Tauriq Moosa https://t.co/OgJDuEJwVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey everyone, @AJemaineClement is winning this Twitter thing at the moment. Get on over &amp; have a look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing mental health in the workplace: Advice for employers and employees https://t.co/c5pAmLYhTQ via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[`Feel the pain, feel the joy - &amp; sidestep the little bits of history repeating' https://t.co/5BTrMQtMVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poyanmehr *at the hands of old white men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manwhohasitall Wonderful achievement for a male scientist! https://t.co/xcQ76XVYxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brzoskos Gentamicin for 5 days adjusted by trough levels: 2nd best antibiotic known to man (after benzylpeniciilin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorLudlam welcome back Senator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To underline my commitment to defeating imposter syndrome, just responded to @HelenRazer &amp; @paulkrugman (separately) on Twitter. So brave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman @GreatDismal A narcissistic personality disorder is not technically a mental illness (alas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My best response to this: get over your bourgeois overthinking &amp; imposter syndrome, &amp; get on with making better pub… https://t.co/5m3RL8wEOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As all books are: why should we read your ideas, you imposter?😀 This restrains my own efforts, &amp; spurs me on (so mu… https://t.co/8FQnafNmJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WePublicHealth Access to primary health care (incl  those w/out $$$) is big issue in Oz, but only private insurance rebate discussed in MSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WePublicHealth You are right to raise the importance of health services for those with no money: it's a personal story for many others too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WePublicHealth Isn't your local Aboriginal Medical Service, or Family Planning Centre, free also?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camusfallen @AvrgeJoeCyclist That's "old-school" rehab! Chapeau! Are you planning to stay safe in Wanaka for the next 4 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camusfallen Need recovery suggestions, old man?😀 https://t.co/MnmE1qZBOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinSGaynor And all our children are above average ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoGlassTaste @davidbewart I dunno, I wouldn't piss on him if he was on fire &amp; you paid me ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heldavidson Croc stories require the nuance &amp; subtlety only available from an experienced correspondent 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NephJC Dipping in from wards, sorry for no introduction: Australian nephrologist from Darwin, no COI #nephJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kidsbeansdoc @NephJC @kidney_boy How do we know that those who've experienced dialysis before transplant are more adherent, beyond opinion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatherineLBates Cycling is both a cruel mistress &amp; a team sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclingtips Where was Dan Fitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham @Sarah_Bakewell Enough 'SPLOSIONS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@velocast @CalebEwan @JessiBraverman @CyclingAus @usacycling Out of a Xmas cracker, surely? #dudewithtache #RoadNats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDW_ You mean that all the 2016 #workcake efforts were bought?! I'm now TOTALLY disillusioned with 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@manwhohasitall Best if men tried out on not-for-profit boards first to see if they have what it takes @MeganLawtonLLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bridgeyb Congratulations on your promotion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coopesdetat welcome to our world #nt #darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hswapnil @burnskevd If you're so worried about per. biopsy, consider transjugular biopsy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nephondemand Only biopsy if h'turia or albuminuria. Distrust CrCL: suggest Nuc Med GFR measurement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Monash_SPHPM You have all the other buzz-words, but forgot "agile"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former Oxford English Dictionary editor explains the word 'pom' https://t.co/guHYiGx2bP via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kidney_boy @hswapnil @rheault_m I was wondering, but sometimes we Australians worry that Americans always want to be taken seriously! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kidney_boy @hswapnil @rheault_m How do your patients fund sirolimus for their ADPKD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMattGB @kidney_boy K+7=dialysis, not calcium or Insulin: insulin will just "hide" K intracellularly until dialysis over, then leeches out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Badves Thanks. Must find time for research one of these days ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another win for @anmfbetterhands NT Branch: well done Yvonne &amp; team! https://t.co/IpjBEzHspp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMattGB @kidney_boy Treat ECG, not number! Wait for peaked Ts, if not QRS&gt;120 (coming from NT, with lots of missing dialysis. Hypos maim!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iGas2 @ben_hr @AndyDW_ So, despite seeming hyperbole, AIHW hospitals data analysis shows inequities ARE universal in Australian hospitals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iGas2 @ben_hr @AndyDW_ This systemic lower care &amp; outcomes everywhere has been happening for as long as we've been able to measure it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iGas2 @ben_hr @AndyDW_ By universal, I mean that Indigenous Australians get lower levels of hospital care (&amp; worse outcomes) everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iGas2 @ben_hr @AndyDW_ PM&amp;C reports based on AIHW analyses show universal disparities in care &amp; outcome: Indigenous Australians  miss out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmillerheidke Congrats &amp; thanks for latest album! Almost all my faves - but what about https://t.co/9NICxWUdew ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Duro_Kolar Congratulations! By (imperfect) recollection of Australian data, you now have 98.5% chance of graduation! @PhDForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to say if your child asks 'what's the point of maths?' https://t.co/Eyo6IuJvZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally autographed by good sport @fanniebay! Here's to good government in the NT! #neveragain #ntpol https://t.co/hjD4X5vlwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reallykazcooke Bought a copy for our Ms 8, but my wife won't hand it over to her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callapilla "Poleesh Remover of Na-eel" in our house. #LegoMovie Careful, authorities may read Twitter &amp; bring spectacle to an early end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 A very ugly picture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely requires rural gerrymander? RT: Trump/Brexit success could herald Aust regional, rural revolt https://t.co/L7KMSiuhAn via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDW_ Blessed are the big noses https://t.co/Th58kuxouD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@manwhohasitall is so clever, he just has to be a woman! https://t.co/Rm9jGOABvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ace! Cool! https://t.co/EaDiCdaR1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WDNWPT Dialysis truck helping people in 'kidney disease capital of the world' https://t.co/oyD223tYww via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook could help lower Indigenous smoking rates, @m_hef from @MenziesResearch says https://t.co/fnA28j4qWr via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toates_19 Why isn't fludrocortione any good in CKD (he asks, suspecting answer is aldo agonist effect - but is there evidence of harm)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but have you thought about what you'll do with your hair now? https://t.co/igGkMqFBSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paywalled, unfortunately. https://t.co/3qDSkuRy1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dialysis is a tough gig for a Foreign Minister! https://t.co/7c1CqGePS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hswapnil suggests @ASNKidney will not enforce `no photos' policy at #KidneyWk. What do others think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ASNKidney bans tweets from #KidneyWk: why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendonln Thanks for the clue: obviously Brugada Syndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eleytherius Turgid 2 hour meeting with Police Asst Commissioner about NT Alcohol Mandatory Treatment program data (incl. ED attendance, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chest pain before arrest? https://t.co/GwsehGOMVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @garvey_gail of @MenziesResearch! https://t.co/5TK40loKAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDW_ Thanks! Didn't think the story would travel so far ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDW_ Understandably, I'm no longer Director]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyDW_ As Director, I used to rate my performance daily, but found it too depressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @AndrewLamingMP had paid attention during his time  in the NT, he wouldn't be defending Bill Leak, partic. so crudely @timsenior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camusfallen after meeting RDH DMS today, this is bittersweet: it seems after @Gurrumul thing I am also banned for… https://t.co/WMyeMlWNk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeySlezak Why didn't @NickEvershed wear his `lucky socks'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that include something for @VladoPerkovic to shave with? https://t.co/vT5iZy1uFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, @armagny https://t.co/dMrA3jB8X3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KearsleyJamie Oh *(disappointed it's not inner thigh)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three words: Joint Strike Fighter https://t.co/3zpPEW3fJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What more would he say about today, @camusfallen ? https://t.co/wfmaswIlu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KearsleyJamie Can you give us the wider view for context, or is that not safe for families?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drjustincoleman Of interest? `Eliminating Routine Glucometer Readings in the Office Setting' https://t.co/w20NFzcTdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CKD_RR Research paper is not yet online at Cell Reports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a well-deserved shout-out to @NickEvershed in the discussion. https://t.co/Kal9UAeIgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collaborative approach delivers research with influence - @MenziesResearch https://t.co/SiG5UNl1QD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 Dangerously close to `un-Australian': your tweet is now being examined by the Australian Signals Directorate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KearsleyJamie @daviesbj 'You can't buy happiness, but you can buy a bike, and that's pretty close.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance pays. https://t.co/j7nCHrVFdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something to think about from @NewYorker https://t.co/a6pFYCvAlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@camusfallen My aunt lives on Lough Gill, Co. Sligo, &amp; looks out at the Lake Isle of Inishfree every morning. `tho a Prod, Yeats was alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[`The best lack all conviction, while the worst are full of passionate intensity.' Take heart, rest up &amp; get well,… https://t.co/CWYGaoFlGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fjcaskey @EraEdtaRegistry Didn't the IDEAL study put the timing question to bed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colvinius About  NT dialysis story: I think you've missed point. Need for dialysis is set to increase by up to 70%, not actual services]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The four words that made this doctor the most hated man in a room full of doctors https://t.co/OomQ8lv4lK via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @heldavidson! Apparently it's your fault. https://t.co/0WuYoOhRc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dialysis treatments set to increase in NT by up to 70 per cent https://t.co/7fe998DMP4 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heldavidson The absence of air-conditioning you decided to keep to yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great leap forward for mice fertility https://t.co/SPiGr898ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not necessarily: remember MRC Streptomycin story, where early benefits led to later resistance &amp; failure. Drug shor… https://t.co/XIKq310088]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open access here https://t.co/rKyQkUWtrH https://t.co/TwAmxuQ6pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenDwyer12 @Rglangham Kidney disease is not a priority ... thus can be unfunded &amp; invisible. What is not measured is not seen. #nhmrc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>