<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitTwinPeaks you don't need to tell me twice! It's cued up already. Even though I can actually quote the entire series :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyallbaynz lovely day on the bay ðŸŒž&amp;ðŸŒœ https://t.co/54dXtJgt9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steelbanks they thought people wouldn't watch a show about housework either, but now there's about 20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubNZ did they actually get FORCED to apologise? Are there photos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher also try journey through twin peaks - that was my Saturday night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling @SarahLibrarina @ddale8 I'm suspicious of his ability to tweet succinctly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLibrarina it's getting dangerously close to awaiting celebrity bowel movements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester @WgtnCC so nice! And magical! But it's WellingTON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher @Spotify now there's something we can all agree on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn thanks to your wonderful, kind and enthusiastic driver on newtown park bus to town this morning #378! Made my day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher I'm so sentimental the bass slide doesn't even bother me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher what are you saying? I think you'll find it is a FANTASTIC song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's little as heartwarming as airports at Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieRitchie1 @NewshubNZ "it is what it is" means nothing. Translation: "I don't give a shit."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laneasinlois it's not the most attractive beverage I've ever seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CzechWonderNine @IBCycleWay @WgtnCC @nzpolice ...because people keep arguing about what people should be doing. The layout is flawed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CzechWonderNine @IBCycleWay @WgtnCC @nzpolice i know it's not hard in theory, but it isn't working. Someone is going to die on that road...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlastairGSmith @IBCycleWay @WgtnCC @nzpolice @wordpressdotcom good in theory but IT DOESN'T WORK. See also intersection blockers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CzechWonderNine @IBCycleWay @WgtnCC @nzpolice I don't think that's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBCycleWay @WgtnCC @nzpolice it's a shocking layout not the cars' fault: we HAVE to cross the cycle lane if we want to turn the corner...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__apf__ today LinkedIn told me I might know me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz although I would have expected slightly better acting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz is there any doubt now that the whole "contest" was a total set up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STForeignDesk @STcom it's called the "North Island" and it's a 5.4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDxx @Kiwi_Chatter I don't even think that's true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher thank goodness! It's late and on a day of rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher autocorrect. HOPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher I how's you chose bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haquaman @BR3NDA @jennymeyer43 @wellingtonnews that's what I don't know. And that's why I'm focusing on what I know. Which is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @jennymeyer43 @wellingtonnews also transporting people and delivering food and supplies to those affected by quakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boswellryan was just saying you must be exhausted after your marathon work effort! Well done ðŸ˜Š and well deserved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA Loads of slips on the road in Vogeltown/Mornington area!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boswellryan @justin_lester @1NewsNZ maybe "some of wgtn's CBD" would be more accurate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher no Christmas is complete without it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher a good eclectic including Run DMC and Harry Belafonte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher just spent 2 hours listening to carols and helping 13yo make Xmas decs for her door at boarding school :) feel all xmassy ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways saying "Hence why"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laneasinlois thank you my friend, got it! Rudy says hi back! ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laneasinlois yes please I would!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markcubey I didn't think it was possible, but heroing might be worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsNadine we got an apartment on https://t.co/g0Xr7CDCoK in Austerlitz (sp?) Mins to metro, and overlooks Nat history museum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laneasinlois overarching framework]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennaLynchNZ @NewshubPolitics something Gareth Morgan has consistently done over the years is disturb me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman being interviewed on RNZ this morning said "antidotal evidence". I've been thinking about what that might be all day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrientalBayNZ ðŸ˜” so great while it lasted!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz @georgiastraight I've seen clearer Sasquatch pics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack why has no one noticed you only have THREE fingers????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@instagram I'm in a security code loop of death and I can't get anyone to help me. HELP?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 I agreed re name badge :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Cormack Siem take longer than others! Plus sun helps and we haven't had much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress @rpy so much better in black and white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OffTheTracksNZ @YouTube I thought Lindsay and I were the only people who knew about this song!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OffTheTracksNZ I love your work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I didn't know it was #loudshirtday! I had a meeting at MSD and thought it was their casual Friday fashion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel like a little kid waiting for my #littlegardennz to sprout https://t.co/O1UhucmOWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few days late to #talklikeapirate but he's off now https://t.co/PuuUlQCJ7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG so happy about that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseagodinet l'oreal a million lashes is awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME WTF. Rapist. Convicted rapist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseagodinet see also: Don't tell me what I think is "hilarious!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not news @ONENewsNZ https://t.co/lDoeCmynzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @Orcon also how many times you have used the phrase "it's Chorus' fault"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher @SarahLibrarina @MikeNeill5 I was thinking town if Ok as am meeting a friend later too! And family later again :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLibrarina @MikeNeill5 @stevegallagher Friday? 6ish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling oo oo do another one about vaccinations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz maybe mcVillain with a silent q could be your evil alter ego?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher @MikeNeill5 @SarahLibrarina I am very excited! Not sure of plans yet but likely sat :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher @SarahLibrarina @MikeNeill5 chance of a quiet beer this time next Friday or a coffee Saturday morning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Medalled" is not acceptable as a verb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn when I tweeted you, and at willis street. It never showed but stayed on the electronic sign the whole time. Sign is Pointless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RPT @metlinkwgtn world-class even.  The 11 is 15 mins late and it's freezing out here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as you're happy to factor waiting for a bus that never comes into your commute, @metlinkwgtn's service is A-OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiNZ63 @lyallbaynz me too! It's so disappointing our reputation relies on these lazy people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyallbaynz v disappointed at dog owners not cleaning up their dog poo at the lovely Ataturk. It's a total sh*tfest. https://t.co/TTpjDXUVmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 he's somewhat high maintenance (just fell asleep!) but awesome ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 my dog looks like this every day https://t.co/1HAh6yvbhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ONENewsNZ can't you just call her a "murdered woman"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laneasinlois the bad news is that they are &lt;&lt;all the rage&gt;&gt; here in London. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz I remember having the air con set to 29 degrees! It's a heatwave in London today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz stressful trying to get anything done! You may have assimilated better than me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz I'm good thanks! Realising how much less stressful intl travel is in the UK than Brasil :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening in Brazil today, @mcquillanatorz? Am loving your updates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some horrifying reading about Donald Trump https://t.co/L782TIGMcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roualb https://t.co/7qf0G3XzMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 sorry to hear that! Nothing like ND to cheer you up ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz @jasonleejitsu we saw a guy trimming trees by swinging a chainsaw back and forth on a length of rope. It was also dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz @jasonleejitsu that's how I remember it ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald how much was Trump's outfit worth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher Maybe Springsteen's The River?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher and then: I got caught by my own autocorrect. Life. Shout out to HUHA though. They do great work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher HUHA ha "loose weight" even.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevegallagher I'm with you! Terrible word. Or non-word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNBR surely evidence that crappy customer service and lack of foresight does not a successful company make]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous in your neck of the woods tonight @lyallbaynz https://t.co/kZuYjDlxm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways love the correct use of its]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubEnt @NewshubNZ the sky is actually falling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gasp! These youths and their modern fancies... https://t.co/hBk3I8cSTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm doing a story (for an internal publication) on commuting. Do you have a complicated commute? Would you be ok for an interview?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSReynolds or "you won't believe what happened next"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>