<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronandusty yep - absolute belly laugh. Well done @Ciara_Knight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laugh out Loud - genuinely :-) https://t.co/vbClUJLf7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ancestryhour thanks again for hosting a rapid fire and entertaining hour! #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ancestryhour limited ability to research family line at the moment (work!) but having fun helping others #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtcherleyONS I didn't like to tell my (brunette) mother ;-) #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival Not too far off the mark ;-) #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtcherleyONS ;-) I met an ex of his years ago, apparently he always had a thing for blondes @DSRGenealogist @janenharris @WDYTYA_UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival I used to play piano but would love to be able to sing. Currently, I sound like a crow :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DSRGenealogist Well we used to live with Joanna L &amp; my dad has a soft spot for her still :-) #ancestryhour
@janenharris @WDYTYA_UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival I'm hoping that grouping of first names hold the key, if naming convention still applied then #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival 2nd half of 19th century into early 20th (1911) #ancestryhour Surname is common as muck though so will take some digging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival I'm really hoping that I'll find one was a late blossing singer and there's hope for me yet ;-) #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival I've finally confirmed that at least one is mine (a music teacher) so will now explore link with others #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_percival I've been finding multiple newspaper refs to people with my family names as musicians but no link until now! @ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ancestryhour On a happier note, I've finally found a reference to musical talent :-) #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ancestryhour and it looks like my trip to #wdytya is mostly nobbled by work unless I come over Saturday Redeye &amp; try to cram everything in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starryblackness What a smart woman you are :-) I need to find a spare leaf in your book! #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtcherleyONS sorry to hear that. May he RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ancestryhour apologies for late arrival to #ancestryhour "a woman's work is never done..." :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesskellynt is it being sponsored by the makers of some new and fabulous waterproof mascara?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthebackpage Hi there, are you connected with "The Big Blue Bus"? Just found a receipt when I was with you but labelled for diff company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember those days! @OfficialCamogie #WomenInSport https://t.co/JfIFW3LHaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YvonnecWhelan Thanks Yvonne. I think, the rate I'm going, I'll be sweating it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a cold, my typing is starting to resemble my speech! *by/my *do/no
:-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicrosoftHelps *no (not "do"! I have a cold!) Getting started with Project &gt; Introduction to project management is the location in HELP 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicrosoftHelps Hey MS! Project &gt; Trying to d/l "Project management quick reference guide for Project 2010" but do link :-( 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie I think she'd thoroughly enjoy it :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie you start it, I'll sign it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie him cowering in the corner, blubbering? 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie maybe Enda could bring Dr Eva with him to DT. Imagine her roasting him over his diet ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie one of the reasons I rarely watch TV. Twitter alone these days is enough with every new story from US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neev_ie #MedicationNation didn't watch either, was in bed sleeping. Was the reaction "FRO!"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraVanVleet yeah but Louise M. probably not that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EU_Commission @Tupp_Ed missing sexual orientation and sex... Those are next in his list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle shade delivered by the best @MerriamWebster and @theirishfor #trumpelstiltskin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VonnyR7 I've a school bag somewhere 😉 @7worldscollide @98FM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronandusty I think there's a panorama programme about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7worldscollide haha! I wasn't going there!! @98FM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronandusty I know! I mean people with dementia can be difficult but that's plain heartless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josefoshea it's gotten so bad I'm not even sure if that's photoshopped!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder who this family voted for. 😒 Horrible treatment. https://t.co/NQ75eJzNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading back to school @7worldscollide  https://t.co/iaXtTcbp1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimKilbane One for you Jim, from your Irish counterparts https://t.co/GaSoZVkovR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon it's one of the great things about @LeapCard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieAMcCoy @Claredaisy @DonnaIRL #insomniasucks what was going on last night. 3.30 before I could sleep, alarm at 6 😴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juneshannon #darttales don't worry, they'll take it from you next time you top up 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ that sounds horrible!@RosemaryMacCabe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting the @ACLU - matching donations, @patrickc of @stripe and #Limerick https://t.co/XFgal6tPHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ what on earth happened? I'm seeing various obscure references in my TL to this subject]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiLoingsigh And not taking the medication!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiLoingsigh And all the stuff making "Big" news is burying all the other important news of things he's doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionaDeLondras Hi Fiona, offers of help from @Claredaisy and @JoBW for #TrumpBan https://t.co/CSqodwxYyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cabrinid exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh boy... https://t.co/faV4bYDT3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EastleachGL7 Hello! Thanks for the reply. I didn't make it any further than Gloucester and documents mentioning Eastleach this time. Soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jerrybuttimer like I said, I admire you. But finding a positive in Spicer's Cork connection is scraping the gutter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LornaBogue @unapower Dear @jerrybuttimer I admire you for many things but wise up. Hitler had a connection to the Gresham, still evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pvespertine you've made my day. Saw @billybragg almost 20 years ago at small underground gig in Dublin. Powerful stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pvespertine oh Ellen! I was a fan from the beginning but I think you've surpassed yourself tonight. Even @billybragg !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @pvespertine has just picked music from every country #Trumperica has banned, along with a few others. Nice work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great radio on @pvespertine - opening track "Open your borders"
#Trumperica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CCNewsdesk I don't suppose you have Congregationalist burial records from 19th century? I'm planning a visit for genealogical purposes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @VisitNewOrleans I've long wantd to visit. I planned to come in 3 years. I can't in good conscience visit USA now. Maybe post 2021 :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor @realDonaldTrump is so insecure about the size of his PENIS he gets photos of his hands photoshopped https://t.co/ccbYDdHCkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitty_kelliher Well, not living in London now but born there -)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitty_kelliher That's ok. Same here ;-) Chat includes amateurs like me and professionals #ancestryhour We help each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizlyricfm Currently listening to @MetOpera Barber of Seville. Next stop Robin Williams.Thanks for the inspiration :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitty_kelliher Ah so that's why you were asking. If you're doing family history, join us Tuesdays at 7 on #ancestryhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joancooke5 Absolutely. Brought a bottle to my uncle in England last weekend. I am now "favourite niece"! @Casserly_Rock @TeelingWhiskey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joancooke5 Tour was a once off. We'd get more bang for our buck with a bottle ;-) @Casserly_Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joancooke5 It was lovely. Next time I'll just buy a bottle ;-) @Casserly_Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joancooke5 So I hear Joan. That's such a shame, we had a lovely day. I think I walked the legs off @Casserly_Rock He's on way home now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock hooray!! I was getting worried. You can do anything. Really enjoyed the day. Lovely to meet you. Enjoy those cinnamon buns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitty_kelliher you're welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corkonians, this sounds familiar. Would you Adam and Eve it? https://t.co/pUzPCEVbCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Christmas, just Dublin on a winter evening https://t.co/sLcF1VF4WT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intoxicated by the smell alone @TeelingWhiskey #spiritofdublin https://t.co/warjzKiPx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book display at @HodgesFiggis Dublin ☺ https://t.co/OwEs9vzYNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fiver off your next @HailoIreland with my code TARA2099. 
Confession, if you use it, I'll get a fiver off too 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joancooke5 see you in a bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock I've a table downstairs. Buns have arrived]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock Yep! About 12.30?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock Hah! True enough. My mates may not join us until much later, they're house-hunting (more whiskey for us!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock that sounds like a pleasant way to spend the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock Already! Blimey! You really did go for crack of dawn service. I'm barely awake! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuirkyKakes I really enjoyed it, even more so when I realised that logistically it's easy to get to from home! @onthebackpage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaks in the White House, leaks in a hotel bedroom, verbal diarrhoea: is there a Tena Lady big enough for the Gobshite, Incontinentia Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made it to @onthebackpage Pint of Craft Beer and any pizza just €12 - even without the beer, I'd go back for the pizza! Delicious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fobraonain Sweet Jane... Oh god. I've so many grainy memories of student houses in Ranelagh listening to the original with smoke everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7worldscollide Boudoir pink and Inconic Nude lippie plus a brighter (light) pink lip crayon. Total cost (sheer extravagance!) €5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmcgovern That would be lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmcgovern A mate caught short (of beer) in my house drank it. I replaced it. He ordered a bottle at the bar tonight and re reminisced ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmcgovern You, or more precisely your birthday beer, came up in conversation tonight. At this rate it will be mature for your 50th! :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derekf03 truthfully, I was more struck by the photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tumpelstiltskin's white knuckle ride with Theresa May. It looks like she's leading someone a little infirm https://t.co/SvdWhenSE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock hahahah! you can FRO. Tomorrow I get a lie in! :-P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock not unless I have to be, why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7worldscollide I have to stop on O'Connell St this evening so will pop in then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know things are bad when @nytopinion reminisces about the "halcyon" (my phrase) days of Reagan
https://t.co/VEFZpawpkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7worldscollide if I get near a shop this weekend, I'll pick up some for you @BeautyHourIE @Primark @weddingbeautfas]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>