<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta @MxDEJ @amylmcdonald Goddam nanny state crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta @MxDEJ @amylmcdonald In OZ we now have 'fireworks day' on the queens birthday holiday. Home use of fireworks illegal now...... (1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacebunnyday It strikes me that the EU is pretty much exactly what Hitler wanted, but he is not at the top, Junckers is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget By 'part' do you mean decisive role?

*just aking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maureenkspeller Go not gently.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndutton13 Must be hurting good old Dick's oil &amp; bribe income.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget @okayultra @mjanetmars and yet you are right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget @BBCNews If Marine becomes president what impetus would that give Brexit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget It seems a familiar pattern......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta I understand that the word you're after is 'little' not big!

*Rumour based on hand size]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave Bernie would have beaten him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget Great story that lends itself to a movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget LOL - you sure it's not Napoleon from his other book?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeidiStea @HutchinsonDave LOL - had a Doberman once who could do that with a 5 foot fence, while carrying stuff (a broom) in her mouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPCarney @ColumPaget @dcexaminer A puzzling thing - A US policy I can support 100%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @PFT_Live I know he makes money from promoting it, but most of the games are rubbish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivEchonews I'm sure it must be the weather in January and February......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwardoverend age and treachery beats skill and youth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougieFFC @okayultra I think animal farm speaks much more strongly about the leftist culture I see around me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeElgan LOL - It wasn't as bad as I was expecting......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling @Patriots @spurs @NFL Another 'weenie roast' from the flammenwerfer of NFL writers and debunkers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deb123xxx Buy lipstick and have your lashes done.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreatDismal Our day in the sun, I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deb123xxx LOL - does that fit in with your massive detox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroguyHawaii @MikeElgan Can't here either - they can, however, dismiss you from Government employment with cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoserHoes @2DeploraDogs @MikeElgan @leahmcelrath Hard to stop crime, just stopping most of the killings is hard enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2DeploraDogs @BoserHoes @MikeElgan @leahmcelrath It's sad. Over here we'd lock the place down till we'd disarmed everyone. Sad its illegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattblaze LOL - keep your hands away from the button, Don.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath @MikeElgan Less than a month into 2017 - that place makes more death and carnage than my whole country - national disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scouse_ma Old white women getting horny for adolescents.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travelinglens If there are no gears in the head, is there air instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHSommers I just can't believe they will ever forego the compulsory support aspects....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeElgan Well - we all know that the full Oxford is the definitive English Dictionary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomgauld @HutchinsonDave You could perhaps modernise that by putting the machines in Burkas......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave I heard the oval office is being renovated shortly (thanks Obama) and he has to spend his first year somewhere else,,,,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave God, think of the Novels and PhD treatises that could come out of it.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scouse_ma LOL - I'm just ignoring that crap! Nice brown Toast, nice brown chips - crispy bacon and make a buttie from it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling @MarcSesslerNFL @DanHanzus Didn't see the Oban anywhere......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@europafreunde All US officeholders retain the honorary title!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ticiaverveer @HutchinsonDave Does she still have copyright? What would her royalties be now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commiserations @thomasmoore27  - at least you got the pick right on the pod.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntonyGreenABC You mean back to the shambles of Australian politics......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dameshek LOL - that has a very different meaning in Australia!

@nflukhank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggrosenthal Not a surprise after last week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When will they hire a good Special teams coach?
Shambles     again
@thomasmoore27 @OllieConnolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amused a lot that Adams dropped that - but at least it was after the TD. Go Pack
@thomasmoore27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ree2306 @thomasmoore27 Weakish players poorly coached - the D has very little chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @harrymccracken @TheOnion I don't know about that - even Pravda is more reliable - ha ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 and out to start the second half - I hope that isn't the story of GB in this game.....
@thomasmoore27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dameshek If he does that Atlanta will set the interception record!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So - GB defence is still lost in the fog? and can't catch balls yet?
@thomasmoore27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 He is, at his best, a mediocre DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 He needs to do better with what he has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 Indeed - anothet Dom Capers masterpiece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nflukhank I know - he can resign then GB can hire a decent OC for next year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Ryan doing his best TB12 imitation yet.....
@thomasmoore27 @OllieConnolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Reinebold That is not how Aarod operates.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me @thomasmoore27 , or is that Falconns offence starting to look a bit puffed from running downfield so often?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bed-Time @thomasmoore27 The colander defence GB are rolling out is not looking very good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacebunnyday Is that Triggly Puff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave Ok Aye! but you see, in this case, they will be, after Dawn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonBanks No - he's wrong and you're right because my team will win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling Losing their marbles in Indy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ghostinthehost @HutchinsonDave The world is getting blurry as dawn approaches........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave Is it going to 'Trump' all the previous books in Fractured Europe??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubeempress @edbott LOL - you'd a thunk he'd have the bakery build a wall......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacebunnyday Is it #peacelovingS&amp;M-march?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 #MCFS - and don't be claiming any shortbread, McVitties or other great scottish treats......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q: Do the English make any biscuits with the transcendence of: a freshly open pack of oreos or fresh toll-house cookies #MCFS @thomasmoore27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 LOL - why not just admit that the Americans are the cookie masters and Englishbiscuits are all equally horrible.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon86murphy @thomasmoore27 Is that Jordy Nelson? Bit hard for my old eyes to tell....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeduncan Is #TheEmperorWearsNoClothes another Caligula story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndutton13 Pray for a miracle that allows one of them to replace the AFC team. That way they can both get in......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcSesslerNFL Honestly Marc - certain sulky pod hosts have blocked me so a copy and paste means I can at least see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lottelydia @mikeduncan Nice guys come last - all of history says this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@europafreunde then pushed him to the ground and stomped him into unconsciousness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave Well - so much Democrat and GOP blindness and stupidity in candidate selection was a 'miracle'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget I'm not sure that Truman wasn't stronger evidence - at least Trump has a raw charisma - Truman was just a lucky accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spenno_77 What self-respecting country lets scousers have a meaningful vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget LOL - It being '1930' again is merely evidence of the same old inability to learn from history........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LibertarianBlue Using ethics and journalism in the same sentence is so 20th century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robkroese I'm sure people will miss the government................]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasmoore27 Perhaps they could even arrange a snug little office for him, possibly several feet underground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HutchinsonDave Climbing onto the roof with my dad to watch sputnik2 orbiting over Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget How 'bout goddam 'nazis and commies'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maureenkspeller @KentHighways Bastids - they have to wait till 7am round here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drkiki Fire both of them, properly investigate the fraud claim, then start over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling The A10 of NFL writers devastates another  memetic horde of mythology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget I think it's become the Overton cheese grater - holes and leaks over the whole expanse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget The British have been world leaders in Bullshit since before the Romans landed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggrosenthal Is that called talking up the trade value??

*asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thus began her reign of terror.....
@mikeduncan https://t.co/ZQxicPdkvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget LOL - absolute mastery of multiply ambiguous puncraftsmanship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this needs is a lot more sand and Charlton Heston! https://t.co/ENrsdx3ZQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta @scrivener Should be in the lecture theatres and tutorial rooms in every university.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling @AppleSupport @iBooks Buy a kib-ndle and use that. Hasn't let me down yet - notes etc always available on-line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossTuckerNFL Obviously because winning games is hard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisWesseling Well, at least not till after Tom Savage is injured.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColumPaget You underestimate the power of the dark side - keeping 'them' out of our paradise will always be popular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggrosenthal The boys lousy Q1 was the real 'enormous'!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>