<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of students rushing in this morning, wanting to print. Just remember this valuable piece of advice: https://t.co/jsjqoHtZqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last week, our whiteboard question at #NW was What Country Do You Come From? Come by to answer this weeks - What La… https://t.co/AOVLCdnH5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's today, now! https://t.co/7f9BDuTzN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NW Campus library could get a little noisy while the elevator is closed for servicing for the next two weeks. https://t.co/5nAnUy0rzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop into #NewWest campus library to answer our whiteboard Q this week: What's your favourite movie? Here's what we… https://t.co/rOf2HjRJGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like everything is back in business! Catalogue, Subject Guides, all working again. Woohoo! Thanks for your patience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College website is back (yay!), but Library pages are still down. Looking into it - hopefully will be resolved soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It looks like college websites, including library pages &amp; catalogue, are out of service right now. Please check back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our bookstore voucher winner, @Ash_Felly!! Thanks to everyone for entering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter by Jan 14 for chance to win $100 bookstore voucher. Spread the word to your friends &amp; classmates (maybe they'… https://t.co/R57hVmEeYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renos almost complete on the new IT office at the entrance of the NW library!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick it up here! Golden Globe winner: The People v. O.J. Simpson: American Crime Story https://t.co/15ZfrnuKcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow us, tweet us #douglasismylibrary &amp; you could WIN $100 to spend at the @douglascollege bookstore! https://t.co/SDbdyqCs8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both campus libraries closed tomorrow &amp; Saturday. Intersession hours begin next week - 8:30-4:30. Full hours:… https://t.co/KUdoRJtW6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab something for the snow this weekend https://t.co/XoIRJ9c7bi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both campus libraries will be closing at 5 pm today. See @douglascollege for updates on College hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another beautiful book tree at Coquitlam campus library! https://t.co/E78nMIj3Zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with exams! We're open usual hours https://t.co/sYPeJpyW1x &amp; we have group study rooms https://t.co/pQjXrFZQpo so come on in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book study rooms in advance for your final exams group study sessions (cause they get busy)! https://t.co/pQjXrFZQpo https://t.co/LWXxwpaer9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a break from textbooks?We've got stuff to read just for fun &amp; curiosity, too! https://t.co/n0lwZH2ugL https://t.co/3g9Rtp7NCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a library fine, pay it before the end of day Dec 3 to have it donated to the @dsu18 food bank! https://t.co/hGy2u9X1ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you take steps to make sure the information you see online is true? Learn how to evaluate it. https://t.co/vhm0oaathr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay any library fines between Nov 28-Dec 3 and they will be donated to a good cause: The @dsu18 food bank! https://t.co/hGy2u9X1ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 3D printer is being set up in #NewWest library entrance RIGHT NOW! Come by to see it in action - til 2pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come by the #NewWest library foyer tomorrow, Nov 23, from 12-2 to check out a 3D printer pop-up demo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoid exam-time frustration/panic. Check the exam sched https://t.co/vplC2XcrI9 &amp; book the technology you'll need:… https://t.co/tUOvKfPduR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know much about NAFTA, we can help you with that. https://t.co/iUnnL0lE0g https://t.co/FvCHG9SUta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can borrow a laptop from the library! They're popular, so book 2 days in advance when you know you'll need one:… https://t.co/3C3utTVIN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbowchow Slow reply, sorry! If you are registered for Winter, have no overdue books/fines, &amp; paid all fees, you can borrow over the break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book a study room for your next group project ... or whatever these folks were doing.  https://t.co/WOCX0x4Pcc? https://t.co/X49lzItkTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to learn more about liberalism in the US? https://t.co/tJCSyG4Kg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We haven't forgotten the influence of the First Ladies in our new Political Science books https://t.co/CmV0eihMQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know more about Trump, we've got the newest stuff for you! https://t.co/FhcbUXRlV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got great databases for your next Political Science Research paper.    https://t.co/1V8uU55pkF https://t.co/WWhv3XPzna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the left to the right, we've got great new books about US politics https://t.co/dJVKGPMg3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week (due to obvious events south of the border) we're taking a look at our Political Science resources.… https://t.co/OJOvPSlTe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, remember the fifth of November https://t.co/gJSi5vHwFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OTD Barack Obama became the 1st African-American President  https://t.co/KooudWAKPY https://t.co/m5pnVL9n3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DC Counselling Services are having a career exploration night on Nov. 16.  Check it out! https://t.co/SJ4zV1UZAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emperor Meiji was born on this day https://t.co/xSoVs209mZ https://t.co/2G0eCZXmhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographics of outer space.  Drop what you're doing and get this book now! https://t.co/xIhNaXUEta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup the library has more than just books. https://t.co/gvFrLvyzLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a place to work on your next group assignment?   We've got rooms with shared tvs.  https://t.co/pQjXrGhrNY https://t.co/HsDSe9Btla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting started on your next paper, but feeling a bit stuck.  C'mon down and see us. https://t.co/xiXZPwJmND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey this weekend, we've got you covered https://t.co/9ZuPz5oETs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@douglascollege employees! Celebrate Open Access Week, learn about DOOR, &amp; eat some cake! 1-3 pm, drop in to NW Li… https://t.co/xp1l32ywgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@douglascollege employees! Learn about DOOR from 1-3 pm today at NW Library Classroom. Check DC Connect for info. https://t.co/HWm7cqgXD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get access to over 80 open education resources! Learn how here: https://t.co/H1D4Dg6iur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the GG winners! https://t.co/95EKJt2Bhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Douglas_Library Oops! Too late to delete &amp; edit, but we should acknowledge the typo - not about*, not about not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the first music bootlegging methods - bone music. Huh? Read more: (it's about not skeletons as instruments)… https://t.co/J2g42yNq4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dive into the other side of economics https://t.co/7sBSa4g0v9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Pro Tip: next time you've got a Sport's Science paper, go to one of these journals first.… https://t.co/A0REZeF5Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know there are some ways to celebrate Snoop Dogg's birthday, but we're just gonna say we got some books - becaus… https://t.co/moHyWmLmlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get ready for Halloween  everybody  https://t.co/tjm6TxLSLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, thank you @guygavrielkay .  Although casting back, Summer Tree was '84 and your hand in the Silmarillion was '77. So we're good w iconic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy Gavriel Kay is talking tonight at #VWF16 tonight.  If you haven't read Canada's iconic fantasy author start now… https://t.co/C6joaaOaUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @VanWritersFest is on right now, so check it out and find some new authors and grab some new books there or at @Douglas_Library  #VWF16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1967 Puyi the last emperor of China died https://t.co/VS5rwN4oJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got only the finest databases for Sports Science  https://t.co/l94xoFeJ9d https://t.co/aMWB724qFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're looking at the Sports' Science department this week - partly because we all ate too much turkey last week.… https://t.co/FY9ToMjEEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OTD the Walt Disney Corporation was founded https://t.co/NM8bSOqAaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OTD the Black Panther Party was founded.  https://t.co/NbRhLTVYR4 https://t.co/n30MDjqIia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Canada, and the world's, greatest economists, John Kenneth Galbraith, was born on this day in 1908.… https://t.co/kwIZnGOC8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sing a happy birthday to ee cummings https://t.co/PGLeL76fTb https://t.co/CVI3tz7CT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Dylan has won the Nobel Prize in Literature! We've got a lot on him, including "All the Songs"… https://t.co/bV09YdefnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Youth and Child Care students: we've got all of the journals you need for your next paper. https://t.co/Y4KbTbzFEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admit it: we've all spent days playing Tetris, but now you can learn where it came from:  https://t.co/7pfTzNEln7 https://t.co/P2yiabHZ42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending tonight's "Trumpification" lecture? Prepare - or follow up - with new book 'making of Donald Trump"… https://t.co/eGhJR69zCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to find more books for you Child and Youth Care classes?  Check our collection starting around HQ 767.8 https://t.co/FnOocNPZuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is #AdaLovelaceDay.  Daughter of Lord Byron and the first person to write computer code!… https://t.co/bujjf7mldf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got an essay on Pop Culture?  Well we've got the Academic books to help back you up. #Library'sGotYourBack https://t.co/qj9XOXRWC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be a turkey when doing your next Child &amp; Youth Care project. We've got over a dozen databases to help you!… https://t.co/z9lAJrNtXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving everybody.  See you tomorrow https://t.co/65oduAMend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The library is closed on Sundays, but that doesn't mean a librarian can't help you.  Try AskAway for real-time help. https://t.co/yKX7eq7YqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Department spotlight for the week is Child &amp; Youth Care and the best place to start is always our subject guides. https://t.co/2xYlGCg2Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APA, MLA, &amp; Chicago! Running Head, Footnotes, &amp; Hanging Indents! OH MY  Citations are tricky, but we can help.… https://t.co/YsQcgN3t8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is cold and wet outside today, but the library is warm and dry and folks are here to help you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to read a business journal while on the go?  Try Browzine.  https://t.co/Yzm6jKNvZ2 https://t.co/aUvfYRKFF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling stuck on your assignment?  Come and ask a librarian for help.   https://t.co/yKX7eq7YqY https://t.co/dnhHmF8SeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave your business textbooks at home today?  Come to the library for our Business textbooks on Reserve.  https://t.co/EalrePT1da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't remember where all the databases, journals, and books are for your business class?  Just use this:… https://t.co/ZjwxBiIWJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to see any films at #VIFF ?  We've got lots of great ones for you to check out https://t.co/ccxEFNDaIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea @_Kathy_Gaynor .  Ok who wants to name our stapler???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that when you've got a massive term paper, we've got the big F'n stapler. (Honestly this thing scares us a… https://t.co/W0W2a5APoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try Business Source Complete for articles, country &amp; company reports, SWOT analysis &amp; more! https://t.co/edBmQJjRb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OTD Sputnik, the first satellite, was launched.  https://t.co/gHXTzED6Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week we are taking care business ... or at least all the things you need to ace your business classes.… https://t.co/40vFirRmRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know more about #bannedbookweek , check out this interactive timeline.  https://t.co/JONCPh0oZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes people really get tied up about #bannedbooksweek https://t.co/ztdNiCbHjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Published in '37, challenged in '91, Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck's Of Mice and Men is part of #bannedbooksweek https://t.co/IIRz1uwBjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still one of the most controversial banned books of all time.  #bannedbooksweek https://t.co/tTAJ2io9XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey .@RandomJackJack sadly we don't have direct control over the heat/ac.  :(  But we have books to keep you warm! https://t.co/hssup4bTFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey .@iAaron_Guillen thanks for letting us know.  CEIT has just installed a new pipe for traffic, but they can see if it needs tweekin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomJackJack Yeah, it's chilly! The facilities department is aware of this and is working on it. Hopefully it warms up soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to do your English papers in style ... MLA Style
https://t.co/y4tRhGr8d0 https://t.co/ZcwsmhhaQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Graphic novels get banned during #bannedbookweek https://t.co/3mQHSIUiTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it is curious what people want banned during #bannedbooksweek https://t.co/UcRYOd5uaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got a dozen databases for your next English paper ( https://t.co/aWdZh1C3UK ).  We've even got the Oxford Eng… https://t.co/8WuYWZ4Vfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to read a censored book this week for #bannedbooksweek https://t.co/PT4rXtwGHj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>