<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmwolfinbarger @TheAuthorGuy Better yet, go visit their district office. They are there to serve you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True bipartisanship. @CocaCola and @pepsi working together side by side at @UTAustin. https://t.co/e91jBiGcKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep singing it though. Lord knows we need it. https://t.co/cYm0udXp3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that GPU still available @DotD? If so, when does it expire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given that I love @altonbrown #GoodEats, I shoulda been grinding my own spices all along. Store bought curry's got nothing on your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Go visit our rights @USNatArchives (with support from @archivesfdn). It really is moving; connects to our past… https://t.co/hV4nxyrOKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy anniversary @CriminalShow! My favorite: Deep Dive. And every time I hear #imphoebejudge. #imWITHphoebejudge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunker down and godspeed, y'all. https://t.co/HwbQqnWtRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth. Yum. So glad it was a busy night here. https://t.co/fdUjxjdfqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NumbersMuncher @TheJeffGoldman @redsteeze I'm not sure. Midterms favor GOP. And more D Senators are exposed in 2018.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, outside my office (where I am not)... https://t.co/89qLT1BCu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy Voldemort is a good shorthand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy lest we forget it wasn't the people in DC who elected the impending shenanigans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is DCA-IND on AA for $112 RT non-stop considered a decent short-haul deal? If you actually wanted to go to IND... @TheFlightDeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's @replyall is a story about dangers of the President-elect. It's so well written, they only had to mention his name once 37 min in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buttermilk biscuits using an @altonbrown recipe, served with mushroom gravy. https://t.co/dBJuXFv0zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @mattnathanson, did you know @Phantogram also has a song called Bill Murray? https://t.co/cXPFWX8Fqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Thanks for the responsiveness. I know you're handling a lot of calls now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Thanks for the response. Rebooked flts were cxd too. I'll have to call later for a refund unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has @SouthwestAir cx'd ALL flts to ATL for next 24 hrs while @Delta is still running most? Does one know something other doesnt? #avgeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And by the way, love your products. Hope to visit @TheSill HQ in NYC one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! Can ivy (and most houseplants) grow up through DE / hort sand or does it block new shoots? https://t.co/2JtRp4wCTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will English ivy spread in indoor planter if topped w/gravel? Or other tips please for fungus gnat issues? @BBCGQT @TheSill #houseplants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hughlaurie in @NightManagerAMC is terrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please, @united. Consider applying your rules consistently. Or just leave it when it won't change anything except to foul the #PaxEx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[78 seats open on this @united flight and again gate agent tries to say my bag is oversized. No bigger than anyone elses, 2 flights in a row!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There needs to be a jetlag @Bitmoji.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @DotsLines for keeping me company on yesterday's line and while jetlagged in today's destination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She had the kind of legs that kept her butt from resting on her shoes..." will be one of the greatest/oddest openi… https://t.co/Ckp3xTf9Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This MileagePlus Gold member is beginning the find @united's arbitrary forced gate check policy annoying. Premier Access is anything but.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spaceship Earth. https://t.co/ShuBb3Ar9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watched ENDER'S GAME. Like most books turned movies, its rushed: oversimplified story, character devo. Just showing off Battle Room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “In defense of 2016.” https://t.co/K8rR46UrjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers to @MrJamesMay on an excellent Ford GT40/Ferrari P3 film. That's the quality @thegrandtour has been missing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saying, for a guy who thinks a man eating ice cream likes other men... https://t.co/TjmiD3bTm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many matching waistcoat and blazer sets does @RichardHammond have? Safe to assume they're all bespoke, I imagine. @thegrandtour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a similar issue and the cause was the battery. @WoelAJilliams @internetofshit https://t.co/mTcy9YJoez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who you are is @ActuallyNPH, but what you are is #winning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mays of Thunder" starring @MrJamesMay #GrandTourAFilm https://t.co/6P2Xn8J8Jj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days like these, it's good to be at @TheMoth, a community working to bring people together, even as darker forces t… https://t.co/vY64FRIghM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free to good home: one ticket to @TheMoth StorySlam tonight at @HowardTheatre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I interviewed H.E. Kenichro Sasae of @JapanEmbDC for @CongStudyGroups #InProfile. "Honored" is not enough to describe the experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote a letter. You should too. https://t.co/vJSu43ErXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @KirkMcPike Well, in this round. Nevermind the first two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But seriously, at long last, they are now truly back. https://t.co/VdeCuHSgwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The DB11 has made me change my trousers. https://t.co/VdeCuHSgwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @PoPville, 2016 suggestions for where to get Christmas trees in DC, especially to support a cause?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a Thanksgiving miracle! https://t.co/EFXxoxvZNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StoryDistrict This looks great. I'm not sure if I'm the best fit, but I'd love to get involved somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFlightDeal it's like DC is being punished for politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red, white, and blue. God bless America. @thegrandtour https://t.co/0JUmJM7cNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention @AmazonVideo, ready your servers for the onslaught.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it could be champagne. Too much? @untitledcarshow @thegrandtour @Jalopnik @AmazonVideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's too much to say it's therapeutic, but it feels that way. It feels a bit grand and beautiful. https://t.co/qYpSf0CbLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I first read the concept and saw it's almost 2 hours, I nearly balked. And yet, it totally works. A marathon n… https://t.co/p9qSjbPwdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sehr zu empfehlen. Lattes down, folks, we've got work to do together. It's time for more dialogue and exchange, not… https://t.co/6LAub87JeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It really is from the heart. ❤ Thanks for sharing. #storytelling https://t.co/ShXgeKwdXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This works so so well. https://t.co/7Auv7VbSs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More squirrel news for @TheAuthorGuy. I'm not sure how you can tell if a squirrel is drunk. Acting more or less squ… https://t.co/cQZryXFauF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be honest, he's only talked about maybe 12. And then it's things found on Wikipedia. https://t.co/3gBS0djTTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope @CNN  at least bought their touch screen computer dinner before poking it to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit goes to @Mandolin_Orange. Their one banjo joke of the night, but it tickled me. https://t.co/ijK3MrPo5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Pergamond, how many banjo players it take to screw in lightbulb? (No idea, they all just sit round complain about plugging things in.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just published on @Medium, my latest #InProfile, featuring H.E. Kurt Jaeger of @EmbassyLI. I love his passion for t… https://t.co/u5g5hzqFeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the risk of sounding uninformed, where did your squirrel obsession come from @TheAuthorGuy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many nations hold it on a Sunday and give folks the day off. And none of this Sabbath excuse: Bible says to seek ju… https://t.co/iLQgCZLwl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate Halloween. And worse, the Halloweekend. https://t.co/HnhDRf2ZCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When good things collide. @SongExploder @SaraWatkins @ChiPodFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per @WillieWatsongs last night, a daily dose of banjo is vital health. Starting this morning with some @NoamPikelny to share the love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely evening with @odonovanaoife. Her art makes my soul lighter. And heavier. All at the same time. https://t.co/EOYO1oiDvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy My favorite city and home for two years. Enjoy the museums, but play Kafka for a bit and brood in a cafe with a notebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was also an awesome episode of @songexploder. That erupting guitar line is killer. @mattnathanson @mitskileaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow. https://t.co/VwafObYC0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @laurenspohrer for making @CriminalShow happen. Even when Google could resolve cliffhanger, I'm so grateful to have them tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks, @CriminalShow is as compelling on stage as through your headphones. @PhoebeVJudge is a magnificent storytell… https://t.co/sa9OqbLyNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegrandtour Is there a US link? Not for the contest of course, just the playlist. I've got some travels ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First attempts at #bonsai training begin. Lord give me the patience because ya know I haven't got the wisdom. https://t.co/BVrU0yG89F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good week ahead: @CriminalShow @jamminjava, @Phantogram @930Club, and @odonovanaoife @thebirchmere. #LiveforLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I Replaced The Word ‘Millennials’ With ‘43-Year-Old White Men’ And Now These Headlines Are... @AmandaRosenberg https://t.co/TxrPcqKMX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, more #TravelsWithPlants. #houseplants #willow #aspargusfern https://t.co/MIVQMRvthM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Why is No One Eating the Pumpkin Coffeecake in the Breakroom?” @HilalIsler https://t.co/DS4Nb6LqId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAuthorGuy I get bored quick, but then people watched LOST for 7 years. Plus Jason Bourne is still making films, somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me right now, in fact. https://t.co/thMCxc2H5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcasts, especially @radiotopia, are so meaningful to my ears, heart, and head. If you feel the same way, join me… https://t.co/ZOLytjP5ZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since joining @PDIPOA, I can't stop looking at flags. https://t.co/02qr1oqHf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're beautiful, #DTW. Well done. #PaxEx https://t.co/bD8vPgWg0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protip: Fly early, fly often. https://t.co/lYHNp6x6D0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrellcdow @romanmars You'd think they're was an asphalt shortage in this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyClarkson @StevenVanDyke Agreed though, props to the crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandracooks @Pergamond It being fall now, here's tonight's apple pie. https://t.co/5EC9n9gqkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we all share are stories. https://t.co/qHT24uyiLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @pleasantpops @CompassCoffeeDC and @amsterdamdc within walking distance, my work day will be much better. https://t.co/FH0B6Jf13Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of police activity. https://t.co/1JK5TVK7kM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's @TheMoth Monday. Thank God. See you soon @howardtheatre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #storytelling. Hello from @StoryDistrict. Next Monday @TheMoth. I can't wait. https://t.co/b3mFbXLCug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandracooks @Pergamond ♫"Peaches in the summertime and apples in the fall...♫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandracooks @Pergamond #GBBO lends itself well to marathoning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petersagal I'm also keen on the memorial at the Pentagon. Highly symbolistic, but it really works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pergamond @alexandracooks Yum. Do you watch the Great British Bake Off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CriminalShow "Final Exit" has stayed with me the most. Thanks for the update in today's ep. #criminal50 https://t.co/7sJZcULi1h]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>