<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KhaleesiHood @AndelaAz @champagneandres @heathslawley @HeathHussar @zane it wouldn't be too bad constant reminder of our stress with Louise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndelaAz @champagneandres @KhaleesiHood @heathslawley @HeathHussar @zane yessssss damn it, Zane had to make it such a high number]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndelaAz @champagneandres @KhaleesiHood @heathslawley @HeathHussar @zane lets do this..we have to convert people to the Zane and Heath life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonnash I aspire to be like Sassy the Sasquatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@champagneandres @AndelaAz @KhaleesiHood @heathslawley @HeathHussar @zane OMG HAHAHA ITS TIME GUYS TO BRING OUT EXTRAS!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane LOVE YOU ANYWAYS BOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@todderic_ the 1975's feels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ @tooextraaaa @zane calm down babe Zane probably won't notice this anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tooextraaaa @zane @punkturtle_ WE HAVE A BELIEVER ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeathHussar @zane @punkturtle_ BITCH RETWEET THIS NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heathslawley @HeathHussar @zane I can see a whole bunch of us doing this... honestly ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ @zane omg girl you are confident and crazy HAHAHAHA BABY YOU ARE TOO MUCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ @zane this has to happen cause I know I'll lose and I want Zane to pick my tattoo HAHAHAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane if I lose this bet with my friend...she's going to pick a small tattoo for me and she needs help..if I lose can you help her pick one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayalvarrez guys seriously if it didn't work out with his ex he's allowed to move on, everyone fucking has to so leave him alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmyandrei @carlyincontro @goddess_eriu @zane @TheGabbieShow @todderic_ @ImNotScottySire @HeathHussar dude these are actually amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ @zane @YouTube well come here and get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ @zane @YouTube no I just know I'll be able to eat some food with the other person GAHAHAH oh wait I owe you food too don't I?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane @YouTube well it would be free for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane @YouTube PLEASE ZANE ILL BUY YOU FREE FOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeymanfs the amount of times I've done that and lost one with my best friend... I now owe her free KFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makaylafaithf @TheGabbieShow @todderic_ @zane @HeathHussar @carlyincontro @goddess_eriu @ImNotScottySire same though HAHAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexaiono PLEASE PICK MEEEE I WANNA HEAR SOME PLEASEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyincontro OH MY GOD HAHAHHAHAA i feel like i can relate to this relationship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so my friend wanted to see what jack bass looks like now... "also the stalker of the gabbie show" HAH @TheGabbieShow https://t.co/Z87DYgvYH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@todderic_ FKN true as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeathHussar @YouTube YESSS HEATHHHH OMGG IM SO HAPPYYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS PUT IT ON MERCH OMG ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS BAM straight in the pan... people better have this on shirts for when you guys go on tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeathHussar  IM SO PROUD HEATH â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afterglowfranta @lizakoshy AWW THIS IS SO CUTEEEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is honestly my favourite video on the internet https://t.co/cdmW0fvMM2 @DavidDobrik @lizakoshy  XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyincontro OMG THEY ARE SO CUTEEE I NEED 20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane this is hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGabbieShow put on old socks and run around cleaning the floor with them and edit while you do it? All in one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zane i fucking love this AHAHAHHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidDobrik @YouTube MEEE THIS YEARS GOAL IS TO BE SHOUTED OUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But when you get back to your house and realise that you had something there that could help you open it... that's stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to the neighbours house because you can't open a jar of salsa... now thats desperate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyincontro sees scotty walking around with the wig and makeup on still: "baby you still going at it?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyincontro i feel like this is just a usual conversation though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinaIona true thooooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hijazi_zane AW LOOK AT THE MUFFIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Haunted_colours @HeathHussar or it could just be his drunk nickname for @zane HAHAHAHAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SettleDownNolie @HeathHussar that is honestly the way it will turn out for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexErnst I FUCKING LOVE THIS HHAHAHAHAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImNotScottySire ohmegee i wna be clickbait shoutouty songg pick me 4 gud timez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#teenwolf my heart cannot handle this! too much #foreverstiles #rememberiloveyou #findcanaan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalichica12 WHY ARE MY EYES ALL SWEATY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voiddanvers its raining i promise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MTVteenwolf poor peter.. im pretty sure he would hate fire by now... i dont blame him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EthanDolan @OVERBOARDOLANS PLEASE FOLLOWWW USSSSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MissingYouAnthony https://t.co/Do1wKImzfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexaiono @aussieaiono OMGOD CONGRATS!!!! DO IT FOR THE AUSSIESSSSS!!! ALEX ARE YOU GONNA DO A MEET AND GREET WHEN YOURE DOWN HERE?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loopeleven OOOOH I COULD ALSO BE DJ HANSHIZZLE CAUSE THATS ONE OF MY FRIENDS NICKNAMES FOR ME (given in history class, again.. dont ask) :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loopeleven oooh my dj name would be CloudyPants because "Cloudy" is my nickname from my friends (dont ask) and i never wear 'pants" so yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexaiono smooth, so goddamn smooth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkturtle_ Yes it is ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the one and only!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS damn... for me that would be a nightmare too :( xx love you ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 I HEARD THE NEWS!!! CONGRATS MINA!!! OMFG IM SO HAPPY FOR YOUUUUUUU!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylanclark #AskLittleSea if you were a loony tune based on your personality, which one would you be? xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenstatic IKR YOUR SO COOL!!!!!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenstatic AAHHH yess the freedom of love XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenstatic HAHAHAH HES GONNA BE LIKE THOSE KINGS WITH 500 WIVES XD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenstatic you too Adie future Mrs Irwin!! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teenstatic HEY THERE!!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 @Ashton5SOS ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ THIS KILLED ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 I can tell ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I've been reading the tweets ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 you know I just realised we always talk over public tweet! We could just dm ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 baby you were born that way! I'll give you the applause though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 sorry I've been looking these up all day in class ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 yes!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ also have you ever tried to eat a clock? It's very time consuming ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 hahhaha!! How was your day?!? Did you know I was wondering why a baseball was getting so close to me today.. Then it hit me ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 SORRY FOR BEING SO LATE LOVE!! Damn your a hit with the ladies! I bet your even better with the men ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 I have to admit and I'm straight..she's hot ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 sorry for the late I was teaching my friend some Spanish so he could talk to his teacher ðŸ˜ I taught him something rude ðŸ˜ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 omg so true ðŸ˜‚ and the student becomes the master]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 YAY!!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ now now children stay calm its only me! Today let me teach you about 5sos ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 did you know booby trap backwards is party boob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ your killing me! I also forgot to tell you being friends with me means a shit load of random facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 that one was stupid ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 YES! Cause I'll just come up with as many as you ðŸ˜‚ you know I'll never workout ðŸ’ªðŸ¼ cause it just won't work out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 omfg that was the best one yet ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 aww your briliam ðŸŒ¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 I understand your pain ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 don't worry it happens to me too! ðŸ’˜ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992  I have a feeling your going on a Luke spree?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 OMG ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ SO TRUE!! BTW I SHIP YOU WITH ANY OF THE BOYS THAT DESERVE YOU ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‰ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 ok ok your trying to kill me aren't you!! THAT WAS THE BEST COMPLEMENT EVER THANK YOU ðŸ’•ðŸ’ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 aww you've made me blush â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸ðŸ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5SOSQUEEN1992 WOAH WHAT?! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes 

Thank you for giving me hope that I can become like you and follow my dreams! I love you so much please follow me! â˜ï¸ðŸ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sorryimkathe same with me for Shawn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamftsandy LUCKY HOW DID YOU GET HIM TO??? OMG IM SO HAPPY FOR YOU XX YOU GO GIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shezzajames its says its private ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solodmheIpers CONGRATS ON THE 1.45K DARLING GLAD I COULD MAKE IT HAPPEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyBlackKiss damn this hit me in the feels @Harry_Styles idek?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyBlackKiss he's smirking.. He knows what he does to us! Cheeky little bugger @Harry_Styles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmxhelpx I know the pain of loosing someone you love â¤ï¸ I hope your able to overcome this â¤ï¸ we will support you and give you all our â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradthesimpson @ShawnMendes OMGOD. YES WILL U COME TO AUSTRALIA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>