<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Young Thug supporting Drake for the rest of the European tour... deeeeeecent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't been in college since January 10th and stayed in bed for my first lecture back... picking up where I left off anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music is 100% the best thing in the world I couldn't live without it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steam rooms are incredible I feel like a new person after 30 mins in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To go Alan fitz or not ......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to cleanse myself in westpoints steam room later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmoran88 a work of art davy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Byrne98Emma it may aswell of been slam dunked that's what it looked like, looked like a truck ran over the thingðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had my first cup of tea in 4 days, it's the little things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smashed my screen to pieces heartbroken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carliecorcoran1 clowns is all!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Byrne98Emma please don't say that ðŸ™„ they literally do my head in only because of how I look with them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stand people who put others down for doing something wrong in the gym or for them being out of shape, at least they're doing something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to get these braces off in march feels like there on years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lyncchh cannot wait chief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amsterdam tomorrowwwwwww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronLeonard11 @Craig8Penguins iasc !!! Would you like a soft drink iasc you bloody .... eejit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig8Penguins tin foil hat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joefitz22 @richiecleary01 you'd know that I have my hands on some anyway ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜•ðŸ˜•ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richiecleary01 @joefitz22 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the red hulk himself, id be privileged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falling in love with the gym all over again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs faaaack legend, that's what was wrecking my head having to email cunts and allðŸ˜ lovelyyy think I'll do the same, 7 or 10 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs that's serious, I was looking at places and my head was frying need to have a look on airbnb, long you going for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs accommodation and all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy about everything these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days are dragging out honestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No work in the morning thank fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only thing on my Facebook newsfeed is two people becoming friends it's getting out of hand hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@its_SebyM rather listen to a chainsaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been in bed more or less 19 hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fuliginouswolf keep him outta sight till playoffs and all will be revealed ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daireobaoill1 @ethanownie97 the severe pressure of the study I did definitely didn't help anyway......... ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daireobaoill1 @ethanownie97 grade 1 groin tear and the man flu boys my life's looking grim at the minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daireobaoill1 @ethanownie97 I actually got a little bit freaked at that, started getting sick after he put that in the chat ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlakwhelan a bad bad bad case of it help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming down hard with the flu. Whyyyyyyyyyyyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back out to work now in that weather........ grim as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That wind is blowing the briefs off me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs I'll let you know chiefðŸ‘ we sleep on the beach or something be grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs back from Amsterdam on the 26th so if yous haven't done anything then I'll get back to ye ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidBohs same with me u can only get flights for a week or two weeks I'll only be goin a week,I wont be lookin to book anything till im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caseyronan16 @DavidBohs in the same boat only me and 1 other interested,accom is too expensive and think wer only thinkin of doin the weekðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackrowe_11 only I can't claim if I'm 6 feet under]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlakwhelan I am jay z ...... your tweet is right tho how do people think EDM is just noise when your listening to it ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlakwhelan sorry boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly got folded in half and taken off the map for good by a car on the way home from the gym. First and last time cycling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I listen to music every second that I'm able to, it's the one thing I'll always love in my life don't know how some people don't like music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7Seandoyle no surprise there ... cos your up for a prison sentence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could be a black person it would be ASAP rocky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethanownie97 only thing he's favourite for is not getting picked for the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethanownie97 what's so funny...............that's exactly what's gonna happen ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethanownie97 bollox yeah I'll wait till I collect my all Ireland medal and MOTM award]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think I'd have started studying after failing my exam Friday, think I'm just gonna drop out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's it only 4 my god, so bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a long long long time since I've enjoyed watching United consistently ..... wish I was rashford what a sicko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig8Penguins another pathetic joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conor_Hynes29 in first year next year bro, mad it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brother just got picked up from junior wrightsðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ that's weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First college exam now at 3:30....still haven't done a single bit of study and I was prob in about 5 of the lectures, see u again in summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hands down funniest man out there at the minute @dean_gilroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone come kill me in clonee and put me out of my misery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Broughill97 wasnt able to chief,ill be using tony sutherlands learner car for the test so he needs as much notice as possible to book it in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booked my full license test near the start of November and still haven't even got a date for it yet... what's the story there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother of god Kylie Jenners snapchat............. one of the sole purposes I'm on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working up at Hartstown school tomorrow weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cianmcgarry86 if you find another person give me a text chief I can do it whenever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coachellas lineup is unreal....... some day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone looking to renew their westpoint membership. Need two more â‚¬200 each for the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7Seandoyle ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I can always count on you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corn on the cob + braces = bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely haven't a clue how to study for college exams. Gonna take a beat down on Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig8Penguins Funny you say that.... I've a snap / caption to show you ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The money I spent last night ....... gave the black lad in the toilet 20 euro and all dunno what I do be at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DL_6 hahahhaa yeah just insulted at being asked in the first place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got ID'd in in the Hartstown. Has there ever been a lower point in my life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carliecorcoran1 hey um can I get one order of sweet chilli chicken, chips, cheese and onion hunky dorys and a glass of milk please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously need to get back to the gym it's becoming pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carliecorcoran1 you're a legend honestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carliecorcoran1 this is getting out of hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carliecorcoran1 I don't even like corona anyway.... I was holding it for someone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok we get it your going to the Hartstown today. No need to tweet it 15 times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine looking like Odell beckham jr what a baller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick topping .......................... wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished up work until next year, wages in today, Patrick topping later to get leathered.... life is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in from work. Up again at 7 for work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno life without free internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stand people who complain about their job all the time. Save it will ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you pay 100 for an MK ticket your an absolute skitzo honestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just won the yeezy raffle. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylan_forman98 fact assholes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing annoys me more than people blatantly ignoring your texts when they know it's there. And they don't like it being done to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeezy raffles are ran by frauds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7Seandoyle the breads there boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westpoint renewal is 245..paid 175 for it last year what the fack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Byrne98Emma my god what a joke I knew it'd be bad but that bad??? It was mayhem, I never wanna go out there againðŸ˜•ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As if I didnt hate maynooth enough,seein perverted boggers wearing crosshatch and v necks let out for their 1st time has made me wanna leave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WadeDylan never smile showing teeth ... yet ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pervert harry kearns better be taking off these braces tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WadeDylan when the bloke said that to me I gave it back to him and got 3 cans instead, absolute frauds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My intuition is tellin me there'll be better days]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>