<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The US always did have a tough vetting system for refugees – @sarahglidden explains https://t.co/wPp5E3mgWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longlostleah @SundaymagSST @SundayStarTimes salad spinners have brought me joy too. Middle age has not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aquidity @KMHouseGarden it's a cool place, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ why do I have no service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should welcome more refugees here https://t.co/a7dXUjbLgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She forsook god above to bring us her love #PJHarvey https://t.co/TsrxQeapSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the cusp of something big... #PJHarvey https://t.co/6tcTA5yDK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire you too - I hear good things from the Auckland gig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight in Wellington! https://t.co/BfXp9bxHDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf haha cool! That may be my only work of fiction that's not out of print]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adzebill snap! Only I already ate my focaccia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf I have only read 1 of her novels - should read more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 10 year old bought this under the impression that it was Jabba the Hutt's sailboat https://t.co/8IDpuz0hq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf check me into that place! Anything good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks but I should give you some, since I use 3 every decade!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks ha yes! I bought them from the Persian Network when I was still living in AKL, along with my barberries. Closed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am finally using the dried limes I bought in 2008! They didn't seem to have an expiry date... https://t.co/95B6HwDcVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More on the #WomensMarch in Wellington - how do journalists write so fast? https://t.co/MGJr2gRGXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now at Civic Square #WomensMarch Wellington #WomensMarchOnWashington https://t.co/EdlUKc4sCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarchOnWashington Wellington https://t.co/3Ny0xIVBSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auchmill it was great! And I'm a sucker for the dioramas https://t.co/0Vmvk9rPY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casshw I am putting that into my calendar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casshw we should make a date - when are you free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auchmill I will! Although is this the same exhibition that ran at the Auckland maritime museum?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off on a Petone adventure! First up Settlers museum, next up Indian spice shop! Maybe I'll stop off for some salted licorice too #staycation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portrait of untidiness, or I go about drawing my life without moving from my seat https://t.co/7ibqpF75Ir https://t.co/IZ1skQLfzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso you gotta get a press. Peak fun at my place: squishing the masa balls on taco night @Nicola_Maggie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nicola_Maggie your father-in-law is very clever. Still love my cast iron press Alia lugged from Sunset Park, NYC for me @gtiso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelking70 Nick the manspreadiest of them all...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemWilder offset by excellent lipstick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amylsacks ha! Yes! With a phonograph wound by a monkey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to do with this pile of treasure? Pressed in Wellington! Alas 100% hymns, not jazz or ragtime, classical or sh… https://t.co/ZzhTy8Tyiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hissingswan yes, once in Auckland but it was just her and Mick Harvey – looking forward to the full band experience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hissingswan @FreoArtsCentre @PJHarveyUK report back please! Seeing her next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hissingswan it's really good, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks I &lt;3 screen time. That's when I draw comics &amp; finish off books. Maybe other people's kids are better at self-entertaining?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelking70 my policy is to only ever enter @unitybookswgtn when I have money to burn. No leaving empty handed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelking70 @helen_lehndorf I might try a couple of nights in kaitoke to ease us in... but yeah, the prep makes me anxious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso oh yes. I am pretty crap at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf hmmm maybe... Jonathan is adamantly anti camping though and I don't know anyone with a bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is still my favourite writing advice, from Janet Frame https://t.co/Mpm5HiA1wQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf just a flying visit – 2 days driving, 2 days in AKL (it's when school starts!!) – but hopefully it should be sunny and fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf I do regret not organising a summer holiday this year though... Jonathan has worked through &amp; I have been a total housewife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf I haven't even bothered this year. We are going to Sally's wedding in Auckland and my parents are coming down to babysit O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf holiday! Yay! But yeah, I know that panicky feeling... good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathrynvanBeek thank you! So good to hear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahbellechand thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahbellechand is that yours, Sarah? Looks amazing! Love the above window bookshelves @rachaelking70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to pop into the Mansfield birthplace to pick up a few pages of my manuscript; my son played with the doll's hou… https://t.co/dmK9dGhaZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought this tote from the @aucklandmuseum online shop and they sent it with a beautiful hand-written card!… https://t.co/HBHJNagrHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMakereti yes - and I still haven't managed it today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artandmylife Otto keeps on getting ideas about games he's going to design... I hope he follows through one day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenager – a school holiday comic https://t.co/WnSrOwImgp via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lydiaXchai thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rephraser I was thinking of that novel. We had a bird burial earlier. I neglected to convince her she was a boy missing a vital component]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School holiday update: Violet is catching flies, creating boutique hotels for them, naming them. The low temperatures makes them compliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf @ElizabethKnoxNZ is running a world building course – perhaps a spec fiction/fantasy term?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lydiaXchai lovely to hear! I hope it continues to please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like they did it on purpose https://t.co/eqnojmDGcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are only 200 copies left of @threeword3 and that's it – a moment in time of NZ women's comics – get yours now https://t.co/KpUv9JldbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RKPriestley oh no! Sending speedy recovery wishes @WgtnFree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira @auchmill @TSleigher so good but I think I must've blinked too much because my eldest is almost 14...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me, harvesting dialogue for comics. I was inspired by the BFG. https://t.co/noCy2eQlNw https://t.co/2maZB3ZnWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadameOrrocks although having said that I've barely swum in the Wellington sea since the early 2000s! Such a chicken @giselledraws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadameOrrocks @giselledraws He tino makariri te moana - my kupu o Te ra - the sea is very cold down here in whanganui a tara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllanDrew75 my son named ours steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieFern I thought they might break in the plane ride home.... maybe they're still there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieFern me too. Now regretting not buying all 6 of them at that Nelson op shop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giselledraws what a beak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giselledraws what is a snipe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso I'm drinking one with you https://t.co/0QJR1VSxwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronyaB that is frankly terrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching this Swedish meatball demo is a perfect accompaniment to starting volume 3 of Knausgaard's My Struggle: https://t.co/BMfeFMWxOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craig_Gamble yeah he always was rather vile on TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBroatch thanks - will listen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blame my teen antipathy to pre-20th century lit. In April I am meant to be talking about Austen like some kind of expert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep on forgetting that I have to read all of Austen's books by April cos I somehow got to this point only seeing the TV &amp; film versions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylanhorrocks @PatersonMovie I really want to see this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpeacekeeper aaargh! That sucks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpeacekeeper it's impressively liked and retweeted too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaah, spinifex and cattails – the consolation for another not-quite-summer's day. Could be mistaken for a beige cos… https://t.co/t6rMmtiiK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wfp_MartySmith @KirstMcDougall @Knhannah @ashleigh_young the spice drawer, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hissingswan I just realised I have Everyday Style too - serious life porn. Still contemplating if sewing from it is wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah @ashleigh_young do you tie your read books up in string?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleigh_young @Knhannah btw did you see this? https://t.co/l9nqNmY3wC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah @ashleigh_young aaaargh! That being said, I can never find books when I need them - mine might as well be shelved that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes @lottajansdotter yep and I've got a huuuuge fabric stash to get through]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf ooh what's that? Tell me more (and good luck)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got the new @lottajansdotter Simple Sewing book, giving me NYC &amp; linen jacket yearnings, even tho I know sewing turns me into a demon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CherylBernstein @alexandra_balm @AnthonyByrt must read! I loved 'A Heart So White' – it had (mis)translators and art fraudsters in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahbellechand ooh now I have to see that AND lala land (am hopelessly behind in movies) @lithub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethKnoxNZ @FergusVUP @ashleigh_young @Craig_Gamble if anyone wants Moroccan mint tea, that's my harvest this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FergusVUP @ElizabethKnoxNZ @ashleigh_young @Craig_Gamble I was doing the gardening and the neighbour's beans have invaded my compost!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf @swimmingwbooks my tomatoes are still a miserable 15 cm high - admittedly I didn't plant them until November]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowman_0Linda that's what I should've done! Instead I shall deliver scratchy overtired children back to their parents today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf @rephraser @guardian I know, it looks intense. I still might make it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rephraser @helen_lehndorf how could you, Fraser? Talking of savoury cheesecakes, I almost made this tonight: https://t.co/LZCWU3f9Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seven-year-olds having a sleepover are still not asleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_writehanded_ thank you! I often read your writing and it's really powerful and I probably forget to say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical self-acceptance – my first comic for the year https://t.co/wk3GC1sKUg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>