<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a rooftop carpark. Can anyone explain the point of this crossing? https://t.co/AM5gAmJWEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickiewoodsford what's the one back right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howardparsons74 this is a 'wearable'. Tracks loads of metrics when running, swimming or cycling. Wouldn't be without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garmin inexplicably set to miles not KM. I have just run 17km of the most hateful mental arithmetic ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No idea what this is but it was 75p in the supermarket. https://t.co/jWFTwMRWf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickiewoodsford yep. We're there pretty much every saturday am for a structured session. So the drowny looking bits - technique building!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've managed to catch an earlier train. It is packed, it never ceases to be amaze me the number of people who feel their bag needs a seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going by the price I assume there's one of the new limited edition solid gold jewel encrusted Toblerone in the mini bar fridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Wembley! https://t.co/RyhdZVfRFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in Notting Hill. I've seen Richard Curtis and just paid £3.75 for a sausage roll. Standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez I'm working in one of the better parts of London. It's an actual thing here. Italian stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oxfordgirlie I'm in a hilton. Can you guess what's missing from this picture? https://t.co/heaDFKcgWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No dancing tonight on account of being in Surrey. Mrs B didn't go. No idea what they did but it's 2 weeks to the big band dance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swam in a teeny tiny hotel pool tonight. It had 'a jet' which was supposed to create an endless pool. It didnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle I thinking traffic may have a slightly regulating effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for a take away ordered via nus eat. It's late which is fine. But annoyed I'm having to chase it when they have my phone number etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle I'm not sure what to do about swim time for Brecon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle well done. What time did you put for Cardiff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle I think I'm most excited about the window sticker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Debbos is this your house? https://t.co/fNTxKVOxdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez tiny bit of Karma!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez very happy for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez view from platform 1 this am. https://t.co/K5pk194Di6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds in fairness Ruth I'm like that every morning. It's just usually a lot worse following a big race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just bumped into my sister in the station. Which was nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiniest touch of the post race John Wayne walk with the first few steps of the morning. But it really is all good today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ben_Blackman @UKRunChat I had similar. Local physio told me I could continue running (with some stretching). Money well spent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez I've got tables like that in my front garden!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal conditions were pretty miserable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal 59:32, missed a pb by 7 seconds. My fault should've checked what time I was shooting for. Pleased, all things considered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal how did you get on this morning? (I mean the race rather than the double breakfast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez I am incredibly envious right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez its effing awful in the diff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireinwales @firsthurdle @stokesie84 cold, wet, miserable. Missed a pb by about seven seconds. All things considered loved it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez drizzle? Showers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racing tomorrow. Haribo for breakfast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickiewoodsford have you not been watching the news? Wall building is very much a no-no right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howardparsons74 it's a home made takeaway with all of the elements that make the real thing so tasty removed or replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've just 'enjoyed' a fakeaway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez @Debbos I did an actual swear then. Most of it is taken up with ironing board too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard I'm not sure what would have failed me 1st, mind or body. Very well done. Any news on your op?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard THREE AND A HALF HOURS!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal you've clearly seen mine rider for tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal it was the last one in the shop. I promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've bought a new suitcase. It has 4 wheels. Once upon a time suitcases didn't have any wheels. We managed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't going to run a spring half marathon. Was then offered a free place in the Bath Half. Now I'm running a spring half. #idiot #cantsayno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez @Debbos curiouser and curiouser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez @Debbos but apart from the tiny room, overpriced cuddly toy and shower in the middle of the room, its all good, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should I be watching on netflix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is out. I have the house to myself. Won't see the kids till tonight and Mrs B till tomorrow. I'm extraordinarily bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirManofNote have you got a new instrument or effect or something. It sounds very different? (Not a complaint BTW)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds just stick at it you'll be amazed at the progress you make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds that's completely brilliant Ruth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Text book dicking about with panorama mode this morning. https://t.co/cbtRiYJqVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My marshalling view point. https://t.co/mHwhKy8WtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White rock runners providing all of the volunteers at Barry Island parkrun this #thankyoumarshal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barry Island sunrise from Marco's. https://t.co/AtoK0o6ZAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure what has made me happier, seeing a man mowing the roof of Gloucester Services or being able to tweet about… https://t.co/hHbbPzjqIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle Yes Ma'am! Usual rules apply keep me posted on your travel plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireinwales I also successfully appealed a parking ticket last week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slimmer of the month. I win fridge magnets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KulaBeth ignore me. I read that wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KulaBeth are you going to Finland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez @ kulabeth got me a Portland. It doesn't get more kook than portland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wednesdayweighin 1.5 off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez nope, but theyve gone.right to.the top of my to.do list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign for Lichfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal cake too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal yep. Flat, fast and I suppose because it has a very limited entry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal have you done it before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal I like it. A pure 10k seems to be the rarer distance. Are you ready for Lliswerry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day trip to the Democratic Republic of Birmingham tomorrow. Early alarm to avoid traffic. Couldn't keep my eyes open earlier, now wide awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Dunedal standard distance for our Thursday club run. (Round the bay)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crispypancake49 back in the day I passed my WSET professional certificate in spirits. Who knew it would come in so useful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crispypancake49 from memory it is the blue agave plant. (I used to work in the drinks industry)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilkes66 appeal it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard not sure. I've just downloaded the manual. I bet it's a case of something being slightly out of alignment. Would love to fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard I might have to dig the manual out and troubleshoot it now I know it is possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard I've got one. It only picks up cadence. It's only ever done speed and distance one. Drives me mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PICollard how are you recording/calculating speed and distance on your turbo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm clearly getting old. I've just got in, but before locking up I had make sure the kids were home too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really rather chuffed. https://t.co/G4qW11xZ6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez dig deep. You'll get through it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez quite a big step up from the loo roll holder (and a blind?) if I remember correctly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez what's he broken?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaztri some.agreed lane sharing etiquette would be a good start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaztri a bit extreme, but you do wonder what people are thinking when the pool is busy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a special place in hell reserved for the swimmer who gets into a shared lane of front crawlers and starts swimming breaststroke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wednesdayweighin 3.5 off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez may have mentioned this before, they are affectionately known as toffee-fifi at ours. A mispronunciation by a very young Alice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ballroom news. More tango. We learned 'Back Corté'. A quarter turn in 4 steps starting with a male backward step. Tango continues to rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morleybonez in fairness its not all your hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LyndaDavidson22 they look alright. I've never been a fan of the HEB cake type things. Do they pass the taste test?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of a surprise when my Hilton app invited me to check in for my stay in Surrey tomorrow as I'd meant to book for the 30th. All sorted now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Binge watching "A Series Of Unfortunate Events". It's rather good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds I'm sure you'll improve on that next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds #dfyb I'll hopefully see you down there. If I don't, enjoy it and accept this is how Saturday mornings will now be spent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthLeeds I promise you won't be last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firsthurdle in and working local so if you want picking up from a station just shout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Debbos i don't think I'll be digging the car out in the am. Sadly it's pretty much clear skies.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>