<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[To find out more about what I'm up in the National Assembly &amp; how to contact me, please visit my website https://t.co/5d2ZSoeqeZ @UKIP #UKIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TimetoTalk Day is tomorrow 2 Feb. Remember to take 5 minutes to talk about mental health and change lives… https://t.co/TwivVD6Uig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute lie. Stop trying to make political capital out of the Holocaust. #Disgusting https://t.co/ayBkdufWvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour just lost 3rd ShadowWelshSec in a year. By definition, next one in is a 4th ranker.  #WalesDeservesBetter… https://t.co/qT7zuPwCSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are about to get one elected for Stoke Central. https://t.co/TKX2sRbrfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling with energy bills this January? Find out how @BritishGas can support you. https://t.co/bM9zkiZjA3 https://t.co/gVu65yi6sj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am proposing a Public Sector Pay Reform Bill along with other #UKIP colleagues. The ballot will be drawn at 1.30P… https://t.co/ddRCooYnAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TimetoTalk day is on 2 Feb, remember to take 5 minutes to talk about mental health and change lives @TTCWales https://t.co/HcfWfAaiaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very sad loss for all who knew him - we have been friends for 50 years. https://t.co/t2QyBdpOi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliament must now get on and pass legislation to enact Article 50. Whatever the remoaners think Britain will leave the EU. #UKIP @UKIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to go live on @BBCRadioWales to discuss the Supreme Court Judgement. #UKIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune in to ITV Wales now to see me on @SharpendITV. @UKIP #UKIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's a SURRENDER' – Ukip warns Welsh Brexit demands would keep Britain in the EU https://t.co/VlUdETZLr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next stop - I'll be on @SharpendITV tonight to discuss the events today and those coming up. Tune in to @ITVWales_OnAir at 10.40pm. @UKIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you there. https://t.co/dLzk7ebLYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to go live on @BBCRadioWales. @UKIP #UKIP https://t.co/VlKUE0xfmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being interviewed by @ITVWales on Carwyn Jones's ludicrous Brexit plan now. https://t.co/fvoBVItuuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carwyn admits he wants no immigration controls. The Norwegian model would be a terrible deal for the U.K - Wales voted to take back control!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@fmwales kindly answers my question on immigration however admits he wants the UK to adopt the Norwegian model. Absolutely unacceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived for @AMCarwyn &amp; @LeanneWood's press conference on an alternative Brexit. https://t.co/wyNbQmhu7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News from the National Assembly. #UKIP @UKIP @AssemblyWales  https://t.co/Ceok0e4VQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My closing remarks today in why UKIP members will be voting against the Wales Bill. @UKIP #UKIP #WalesBill https://t.co/xV3RvSJ7w5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be outlining the reasons why @UKIP will be voting against the Wales Bill today in the next few mins at https://t.co/kDilXzMZKH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see @Plaid_Cymru will be voting with @UKIP this afternoon on the Wales Bill. https://t.co/XoXZMb0mrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always enjoy a ding dong! https://t.co/sIv9gHNG0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No it isn't my lucky day - I want you back please at full throttle asap! #VeryQuietRoundHere https://t.co/6vT63H68bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling Powys, calling Powys - who are your NHS #PowysStars - name &amp; praise them! https://t.co/EHcFetmNhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great evening - onwards &amp; upwards! https://t.co/ESRd5XYMP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AM calls for delay on business rates increase https://t.co/VN3pLD72Xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for pointing this out - will have words about this dereliction of duty! https://t.co/E87Rx0zUR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed! Pleased to support this @NickFerrariLBC. Petition: Make it a specific criminal offence to attack any member https://t.co/hG8hJB4qHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did indeed - amazing acoustics. https://t.co/GSDMelYCAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news. #BringItOn https://t.co/VdDZIL0Kla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our shell-shocked Civil Service is simply not up to the job on Brexit  https://t.co/azMXKZjw7O via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaven forbid they should deal with anything serious. https://t.co/Dw9DDABqa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's look forward with optimism to the future. Happy New Year to you all! #UKIP @UKIP https://t.co/jNjcBx4A1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HappyNewYear  Blwyddyn Newydd Dda to everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belated thanks 2 @bethanjenkins 4 her Xmas gift - one 4 each member of #CultureWelshLanguage&amp;CommunicationsCommittee https://t.co/a64NOCDjNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HappyNewYear to everyone.  #UKIP brought you #Brexit &amp; #UKIP will make sure it is delivered. https://t.co/pabggLy93W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many congratulations Pete - richly deserved. https://t.co/UpdpeUpv3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnChambers777 thanks John and a happy New Year to you and yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They need us far more than we need them #BrexitNow https://t.co/gvWFiOKOI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyRajaUK @brit_battleaxe thank you Danny and to you too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinJHC1 @AssemblyWales @UKIP @BBCWalesNews  I guess it was a highlight for me too - a long night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that mean I've got wear it again tomorrow! https://t.co/AwkuTNTl3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting - Thank YOU for organising it.  https://t.co/aJEiG7Nn1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just what is going on in my absence! https://t.co/PiOr1jwN9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cysticfibrosis #yesorkambi https://t.co/YpG4sFwCy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now sitting happily in the thick of it! https://t.co/0otoimmB6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BeenThereDoneThatSeeEarlierTweetPleaseJoinIn https://t.co/V8kGpSKC7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I can wear a daft jumper so can YOU!  Sign up now. #christmasjumperday https://t.co/gM33GWxKkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Gareth! https://t.co/nG6MtwHeiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting and speaking to students from @UniofReading about my work as an Assembly Member today. @AssemblyWales https://t.co/ELrWW9gIt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to welcome you both to the Senedd. https://t.co/Lsd3ndVlmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @paulnuttallukip, Paul Oakden and @prwhittle for coming to see the @UKIP team at @AssemblyWales today. https://t.co/lct9sl7Qau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywales396 if you have not had reply to an email please send again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's he got that I haven't? https://t.co/N1Xyl2fFxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afondarwin if a building was collapsing I presume you wd rather first out than last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU has always contained the seeds of its own destruction and will implode. https://t.co/Xhnv0KC1lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CompleteCarCrash  If @SarahjOlney1 really had 2 go 2 another interview presumably she can tell us what it was?… https://t.co/MyWRAKdLKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tenby school row moves to the Senedd https://t.co/BjOYCfp4jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @UKIPinWales for updates from the UKIP Group in the National Assembly for Wales. #UKIP @UKIP @AssemblyWales… https://t.co/XvfC3EGSiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just doing an interview for @ITVWales before Education Question Time in @SeneddSiambr. @UKIP #UKIP @AssemblyWales https://t.co/ukcPxQWTsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pleasure to meet you &amp; look forward to working with you in future.  https://t.co/sOKWGg20a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted @paulnuttallukip is new Leader. He has the experience, talent &amp; vision to lead #UKIP into electoral success locally &amp; nationally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds join hands around Pembroke's town walls https://t.co/zhek9Al0ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just about to talk to Olly on @BBCRadioWales about Brexit &amp;
UKIP Leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arwynbayley @nomorescamseve1 @NFUtweets @NFUCymru of course you do and, as I said, thank you for being so frank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arwynbayley @NFUtweets @NFUCymru well that is for them to answer not me - thanks for being frank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arwynbayley @NFUtweets REPEAT: I was invited by the NFU so, clearly, they want to hear what I have to say even if you do not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneWood I would be happy to talk to you about the truth rather than gossip.  Your office or mine?  Next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arwynbayley @NFUtweets Because I was invited to do so by the NFU.  I am UKIP spokesman for Agriculture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am here you know. https://t.co/mGnbygqQGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just received this from @wgcs_community. Very poor response. I shall continue to raise this issue in support of… https://t.co/dzG2AnKC5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting @menantiviolence day in the Senedd with @brit_battleaxe. #NotInMyName #whiteribbon https://t.co/cF7AaBTUUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realJoeSimons my pleasure -good luck with your aspirations but, as @brit_battleaxe would say, never let politics take over your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy morning in Pembroke 'Linking Hands around the Walls' with the Mayor, Cllrs &amp; townsfolk.  @pembscastle - birthplace of Henry VII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a chocolate lunch with @wickedly_welsh time for steak'n'ale pie @thenewthreemariners https://t.co/iI57o3lm2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moz_1983 have explained it was a mistake - I do not support them in any way whatsoever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moz_1983 thanks for drawing to my attention - it was a mistake and now swiftly deleted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @BBCRadioWales Carmarthen studio ready for interview about @WelshGovernment &amp; #SupremeCourt #Article50 https://t.co/Ft6X9lZ7J7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No silly jokes please - they are so predictable! https://t.co/OEkSwLdaVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paul2777 @paulnuttallukip hear hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She will! https://t.co/MW2MsChRbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandersn85 - lucky strike at 500th!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know - we will fight it. https://t.co/WQgdTo6bFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last of the pork'n'laverbread sausages sizzling in pan.  Time to go see @Aberdyfibutcher and soon! https://t.co/7TstlwD79h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to attend the launch.  All power to your elbows. https://t.co/fuKojDJz1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is an historic moment for the Church of Wales". AM welcomes female bishop | News | County Echo https://t.co/ZbYIgr8HK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicsavage2000 I know - it must be stopped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicsavage2000 very aware of this - present situation is ludicrous - things must change:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured to lay a wreath at the Wales National War Memorial #WeWillRememberThem https://t.co/HOEI681Jgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dianedarcy12 @NeilUKIP well met in Fleur - looking forward to catching up on the match but great result!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to you all for such fabulous entertainment - enjoyed by all. https://t.co/fj5MQs4QqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She moved eventually - but in her time not ours! https://t.co/AqTSpwsD2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet you both - good luck with the project. https://t.co/V82Wv4nX1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricYesyev @paulnuttallukip which bit of Democracy do you regard as 'implanted' ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnorMouseUK @LordAshcroft thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncmillwood @paulnuttallukip John, it shouldn't  - we all want the same thing so let's unite and go for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TewkesburyUKIP @paulnuttallukip thanks Stuart - Paul will make a great leader - the future beckons.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>