<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When pinoys complain about not winning #MissUniverse..It's a freakin beauty contest for god sakes! A useless one as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realize how much clothes you've got..wooops! Off to the sallies for them! i'm sure someone needs them more than me. #Joysofmoving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're not sure whether you want to get the lead or be a bouncy fairy coz it's fun. Can I do both? #Iolantheauditions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im so ready for this! https://t.co/UpoBuJA62f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got home early from my shift to "rest", yet I'm in bed doing more work... Things need to get done. Can't afford to be sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of being an adult. Got to go to work even though your sick. Sigh. The things we do to pay the bills and fund dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaoELo lol no! I'm pretty happy with my career choice atm haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many bitter people on twitter about #MissUniverse. It's just a bloody show that's very sexist and does not promote equal rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get the big fuss over #MissUniverse. I think it's very sexist as it objectifies women. Overall it doesn't benefit the human race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump Faces Backlash For Insensitive Tweet During Travel Ban Protests! TSK TSK https://t.co/4nmcZLGlS2 via @EliteDaily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please take me to NY! https://t.co/qge6EFm2Xh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've planted 32 trees just by searching the web with Ecosia.The little things count! #green https://t.co/C8vjpivv8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/7VYFNqIQ8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish, please say something about the #MuslimBan situation. NZ should welcome refugees &amp; do something about Trump! #DoubleTheQuota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlizada what's the point of miss universe at all? Pageants are a waste of money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're too sick to practice your songs for an audition :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up people! https://t.co/1C6q0bptgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another dictator! Wtf is happening to the world! Clearly humans haven't learnt from past mistakes! https://t.co/syQHgf5O9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please!!!!! https://t.co/dOQ72wh42i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduation in May then Postgraduate Studies for moi! https://t.co/KDFRB1YzYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 Days left! Would really appreciate some help to fund my summer program. Follow the link below! 
https://t.co/DrP4TI0DQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 more weeks of hell! Note to self, try not to do everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your 300-level music journal turns into a massive rant about NZ identity in order to achieve the word count. Such is uni! 2 more weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Singing School 2017 on https://t.co/7EktCAWxRR https://t.co/DrP4THJ2YN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slab climbing is quite interesting at Tinui #wellingtonrock #nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last audition for the year done. Only have 2 more concerts to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully the weather's good this weekend. #rad #climbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Help me to win what I want! https://t.co/36odurAsfg #wwyw #climbing #iloooveit via @iloveclimbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pighati did nzopera yesterday, and today auditioning for Maria for west side or a solo from Les Miserables for a Choir Concert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Audition of the week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head hurts from all this study! I'm so drained by work and uni.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your argument wins against your Prof. #bestfeelingever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is up with all these bomb threats. Does it mean classes are cancelled?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lab Report introductions are hard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does one strap a wrist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old School 80s and 90s Music is the way to go when studying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're 7 marks off getting a distinction in your singing exam! I hate winter colds and flus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at uni, trying to study like a good student.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twas a perfect day to go rock climbing at Titahi Bay! #climbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got myself hooked on these "keepcups". I spend way too much money on Soy Hot chocolates. #green #keepcups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you live 20-30mins away from the airport! So convenient for early flights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Oh darling, would like some tea?" (British accent) - When you become posh because of high tea. #operagirls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington Singing Comps day 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrinityC_L thank you! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance certificate singing exam with Trinity College London, Done!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing exam in a few hours. Am I ready for this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of those nights when you get 'how to life' advice from movies. #TheDuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end, it isn't about popularity. It's about understanding that no matter what label is thrown your way, only you can define yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of Taupo District Council: Keep the Taupo Rock Wall Open http://t.co/3QvYFiZSlb via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a trip for two worth $4,000 to Cuba, India, Italy, Morocco, Peru or Australia. http://t.co/LX9BuMSgkd #TourRadar #Intrepid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more dairy for me #hayfeverseason #singer'slife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently my french singing is better than german hmm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up really early. 2hrs til roadtrip :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Performance done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I sleep or finish my assignments? Can't do an all nighter... Life as a singer...-sighs-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got prescribed 2 more inhalers. FML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasses need you right now..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face all red thanks to mulled wine! Such a nice midwinter drink &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coz I was spandangled last night. I climbed a pole and danced on it and ended up hurting my right ankle. Still cant walk. #blameitonthebooze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did my first route setting today :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it no more shopping!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everything closed on easter. This is sooooo boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the hairdressers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pighati sounds right I think?? Im still working on my Deustch Grammar lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my loveliest cousin has amnesia. Oh nooooooooooooo :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE  I knoow ae! #iwantobeabillionaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE fair enough! Get one of the canvas classic jeeps &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE I knooow just saw! haha! what is your car atm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get your bestfriend's permission to stalk the girl he likes :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to the Garden Party Guys! They're really good! https://t.co/pzRHOiGHlf  #musicClassmates #mustwatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting bored... tweet me guys! XOXO #ifolllowback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a second hand mac for this stupid yet significant music software for university :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE I knooow! I bet its yuuum! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a walk to maccas.  Frozen fanta just made my night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I cook some food or just die of hunger coz I can't get out of bed :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writer's block :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fluffyjustineee Stressed out sa Uni!! hehe thanks Im loving it right now! and yup I will haha tomorrow maybe sa uni haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to start stretching again :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE What the hell?!! That is huuuuuge! OMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasting my internet.. I've only used a gig this week lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain rain go away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All alone in my flat while eating cake. Yup! This is my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to go home and eat! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglyduckling kind of. I just need to say "balikbayan" and they'll give me a visa for a year haha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faglyduckling Haha! yeah! hopefully I get approved for a travel visa.. since Im still in my Philippine passport :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iheartpotteryow that sounds cool! Cool songs though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iheartpotteryow what is that? Lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iheartpotteryow ooh fun!  I miss dancing :( whats the theme?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iheartpotteryow miss you moooooore! Hows sjym?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tummy's is growling :L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost halfway through 105... Im getting bored :L #2hourlecture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At my german lecture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE Thought it was funny so sent it to everyone hahahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helloNICSSIE haha met these lovely aussies on our way back to the hall from clubbing haha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving out :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 more day before moving in :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My voice is back yay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claireeerivera currently on holiday til 2nd march. Not sure kasi vacation nyu may pasok ako sa university]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>