<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Until next time, warriors...stay strong and connected! #Sistergiant https://t.co/wuTxm36yjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moral arc of the universe is bent by the people! Let's go warriors! We are headed towards the long road of just… https://t.co/KLNkepOObH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership holds the space for the genius of others! Stay connected! There is nothing we cannot do! #Sistergiant https://t.co/iENMxVciAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economic justice is a moral issue. We are revolutionaries as a birth right! Identify with those who made it right!… https://t.co/sdgRjqqWTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest power to provide peace is to reduce the suffering of other human beings. #Sistergiant https://t.co/F17rAk01Yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith = evidence of things hoped 4. It is not blind, it is visionary. God's will has never nt bn done. We will get… https://t.co/Ag4tg78ZjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we need is already placed in our hand. Look at what is already there. Be guided by the spirit...hand in hand… https://t.co/iqbz46iujQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are wide open to the leadings of the spirit! Continue to share the love! #Sistergiant https://t.co/HPQzi4MEXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a team that supports you, there is nothing you can't do. #Sistergiant https://t.co/fbW8C7IGtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you willing to run into crumbling structures and be in communion with people? How will you show up? #Sistergiant https://t.co/1N3ocmrgzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We R the weavers of civic fabric. Direct access, support truth, economic sanction, &amp;culture in artistic abilities.… https://t.co/dWlFN4r0Ad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great leaders makes leaders of others! We are all leaders! #Sistergiant https://t.co/G4MYf5uyr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It only takes 3.5% to make a shift. There are 50-80 million people like us! We are $30 billion in economic power.… https://t.co/ISL0NljI8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You feel worthy when you behave in a worthy way. Don't wait to get ready! We are all children of God and that is al… https://t.co/VcmBHYoQus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spiritual mountaintop is never about me. It is always about we. Run for office! #Sistergiant @CTZNWELL https://t.co/Fr2VSppetN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the marketplace of democracy, we make the change by deciding what we are willing to risk. Become the stakeholder… https://t.co/x1PYYoZeXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citizen Giant - Be a co-creator and co-author. Practice citizenship (solidarity in our togetherness) #Sistergiant https://t.co/ndvTFwihJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has not yet appeared to us who we shall be! Who we are &amp; what we are capable of is not yet known. Where do we go… https://t.co/17CA0lCHJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we do can never be un-coupled from how we do it. Moving towards transformational change &amp; away from transactio… https://t.co/ymPk0M0VX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spirit says, "Do not be concerned with your readiness. Just be consistently aware of mine." #Sistergiant https://t.co/QAbPwZLLqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make yrself available 2 what needs 2 B done next. 5 minutes of meditation is enough to allow the spirit 2 B N charg… https://t.co/kyHlHRlVP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is the dis-ease within the human race - that there is a malignant belief that it is just about me! #Sistergiant https://t.co/w3mmjfDDGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is always the direction in which we will best be used. We are all programmed for the highest manifestations o… https://t.co/iVgkRkxn5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great American Awakening! Final stretch of the summit! #Sistergiant https://t.co/1juYPUVjie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This will be our reply to violence: to make music more intensely, more beautifully, more devotedly than ever befor… https://t.co/SYPJ9GVSCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Depth of sound penetrating the souls of eager Warriors at #Sistergiant symphonic harmony...like the sentient beings… https://t.co/9WZcENciCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must be in divine partnership with the earth. Search 4 air under the other wing when dealing w/the grasping hold of… https://t.co/MZhY4WcAqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biocultural heritage of people and the natural world much be honored! #Sistergiant https://t.co/WPp87mlV33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of each other's energetic countenance. Pray and take a break when needed. Then rejoin the fight!… https://t.co/r5mNUEZhh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick your issue. Learn on the fly. Join a team U can relate 2 &amp; trust. B civicly engaged! Hold elected officials ac… https://t.co/PcH7R7x9S1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to pray FOR the front lines. Now I pray FROM the front lines. Get informed! Be involved! #Sistergiant https://t.co/xKDsAyGf5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An overture from a neighbor is the biggest motivator for political involvement and change! Reach out and Stand up!… https://t.co/tBDJzqiUN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something! Get active and involved! #Sistergiant https://t.co/JUGWyGAfMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connection is the key to reclaiming our future! #Sistergiant https://t.co/T7rUtnzJru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Defeat may serve as well as victory to shake the soul and let the glory out." Edwin Markham
#sistergiant https://t.co/ek2FlWbJED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't combat bigotry with revised version of bigotry! Simply adding other Islamic countries 2 the Muslim ban is not… https://t.co/OCkK6nx28d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the politics of projection that is at play here! Beware and be active! #Sistergiant https://t.co/WoY9h8OeTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authoritarianism uses terrorism as a tool for gaining political clout. RESIST! #Sistergiant https://t.co/tF1yiU5wyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every man of humane convictions must decide on the protest that best suits his convictions, but we must all protes… https://t.co/BTrG0bxcr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanitarian work is the right thing to do and is utilitarian! Here is what you can do. Give to the cause!… https://t.co/TeU6mWYSb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Muslim ban is making America less safe by keeping out those who have already proven they are die hard loyalists… https://t.co/oH48nzFFSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be mindful of the current moral squalor as it creates an inherant danger to national security. #Sistergiant… https://t.co/QE3Bchi8yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every person has a shallow and shadow element. Debate passionately. Win deliberately!  #Sistergiant https://t.co/MhAGgcpAo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat organically! Eat consciously! #Sistergiant https://t.co/qS8dKgW2y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must know where our food comes come. Agriculture has an impact! Get involved. Make a difference! #Sistergiant https://t.co/dksehwfBLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agriculture is a solution to a lot of problems including climate change, environmental degradation, and poverty! St… https://t.co/A10dTkJBM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatness goes beyond standing smart. Greatness is winning! Policy issues matter! #Sistergiant https://t.co/4lx2MIoTGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No factory-farmed meat! It is immoral. #Sistergiant https://t.co/5TjAlkbzYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything we do is interconnected. Keep the moral high ground. #Blacklivesmatter #StandingRock Dems must follow th… https://t.co/uGE9KIarES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must be on fire..warm and welcoming! We must be smart and involved! #Sistergiant https://t.co/vTb8UynJnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats have to clean house right now! #Sistergiant https://t.co/Ye8vqOqrCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must infuse spirituality back into our politics. #Sistergiant https://t.co/kvqgiTGpE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The politics of conviction will eat the lunch of the politics of convenience six ways to Sunday! #Sistergiant https://t.co/v0hE0WtzLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are here as a movement of movements - Democrats and progressives together. #Sistergiant https://t.co/deY3ueeIK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the soul back to the Democratic party! Stand up and be engaged! #Sistergiant https://t.co/FbnMfb0w9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love like there is no tomorrow! Stay connected. Be strong! Be the love! #Sistergiant @FitMuslimah https://t.co/7qsQKo9NRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The presence of the activism is the strategy. Stand strong! Be the love! Be the light! Make a difference!… https://t.co/yeIW801Zv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles arise on conviction. How deeply you believe and are willing to act on it is what matters. Stand on your co… https://t.co/oEUQTwwOZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about the vision of America &amp; then act on it. Give the Dems the cover they need to do the right thing. RESIST… https://t.co/guOj8qiK99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the time for resistence! Be strong!The Supreme Court matters! #Sistergiant https://t.co/25Tm3lyr8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create a situation where the legislature has no choice but to represent the interests of the people! PROTEST!… https://t.co/hfBAKq54k9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If not now, then when? Stand up! RESIST! We need something that is unprecedented in American history! #Sistergiant https://t.co/QYOlWnZflt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is radical! Get money out of politics! Stop gerrymandering! #Sistergiant https://t.co/z0LYb8ns9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The states are laboratories for reform! Automatic voter registration...Go Oregon, WV, &amp; CA! #Sistergiant https://t.co/dMpnLW4lhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Rosa Parks! Be the resistence! Don't stand around waiting to be led. Be the love! Make a difference!… https://t.co/CUhkKmV13b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy works better when more people participate. Voting is not a privilege, it's a right. Voter suppression is… https://t.co/R1MuYhCla2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voter suppression is a national scandal that deserves greater attention! #Sistergiant https://t.co/ve195mNS9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vote is the key to social change! #Sistergiant https://t.co/YTdsyElMDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's rights are universal rights! Men are joining the March! #Sistergiant https://t.co/FLroZRS0xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UnionTemple is now a sanctuary place! Create safe spaces for our brothers and sisters who need it! #Sistergiant https://t.co/3APxqpXu96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smash the patriarchy! Stand in your Truth! Love long and hard! Be the change! Make a difference! #Sistergiant https://t.co/xYO3PRDThm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choice has consequences! Less climate change! More ethics! The struggle is real! #Sistergiant https://t.co/KUkPyhKYOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminists Welcome! #Sistergiant https://t.co/J6UovMFGk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home of the brave! Choose what is right even when it costs! #Sistergiant https://t.co/e1a5VlMLxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whose streets? Our streets! Share the burden of carrying the load for racial justice! #Blacklivesmatter #Sistergiant https://t.co/jjwIzXT4DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action is the antidote for anguish! Be brave! Be bold! Be the love! #Sistergiant #Blacklivesmatter https://t.co/qHK0e0mtOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the streets today! Stay connected forever! This is the age of protest! Be the love! Remain active and engaged!… https://t.co/ZWSqlhfeB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resist! We have birthed a new Era! 5 million strong...standing for intersectionality and what is right! #Sistergiant https://t.co/t6FdyRkuph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were made to be courageous! Stand strong! Conserve mercy and justice then apply them liberally! #Sistergiant https://t.co/lJCioeMtEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are coming out...in support of what is right! Speak up! Be out! Stand in your Truth! #Sistergiant https://t.co/I6MBd6F9S8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give peace a chance! Be active! Be the love! #Sistergiant https://t.co/EK3gkG3C0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are my tribe! #Sistergiant https://t.co/i8s6e9th7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bringing a little pricey of heaven right here on earth! We are all on, interconnected and share the same energy.… https://t.co/wxv8B9NM8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask the question, "God, how will you use me?" Don't mess with our blessing! #Sistergiant https://t.co/KHPvHxsxTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go to https://t.co/GuiDN5FXTR for information on progressive social justice and immigration issues. #Sistergiant St… https://t.co/Z0kM6Bo4wS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focusing on the crimes of the marginalized people in our community creates chaos. Be pro-pluralism! #Sistergiant https://t.co/FR65gtDMqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By suspsending refugee re-settlement program, we turned our back on the world in its hour of greatest need! Demand… https://t.co/SQlNBvL4hZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 years of resistance speaking at #Sistergiant praying with the community for the collective! https://t.co/KOWACT8yrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we Re-establish the relationship to the land, anything is possible. #StandingRock #Sistergiant https://t.co/KVhIQ8RcNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educate yourself about indigenous people. Turn anger into intellectuallism and action! #StandingRock #Sistergiant https://t.co/WwQgLx3Jbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use the power of your citizenship to help protect those who can't speak up for themselves. How will you show up?… https://t.co/4DxL6ZKBpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bump rush congressional offices. Show up and push them to go further. Organize, stand firm and stay steady.… https://t.co/wsfQT4gdOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exposure is everything! Get in relationship with Muslims before they need us. #Sistergiant https://t.co/nPw6pZPjmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace the power of relationships. Relationships are the building block of love and revolution! #Sistergiant https://t.co/ofQP8iJiEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let faith be used as a wedge to divide people or raise hate. Muslims are the canary in the coal mine in this… https://t.co/FoiZbVmXQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panel speaking on ways to engage around human rights issues.  #Sistergiant https://t.co/QJAIi2hePj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rules of our lives are determined by politics. Get involved! #Sistergiant https://t.co/yC4eKmAaY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identify politics is reaching out to the disenfranchised for social justice, not just political benefit alone. E Pl… https://t.co/v79szINKF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find a spiritual grounding to make politics work. Strive for equal opportunity in education and social justice.… https://t.co/k7UWc6XDJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the money - Border patrol and prison industrial complex. Theresa Casper of Ohio -Run for office! Be the chan… https://t.co/Mbk4uyNPna]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>