<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[No he wasn't. https://t.co/91qApVpbwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is shockingly horrible. 
(But why are they throwing 'Eurovision' around?) https://t.co/UNHkAZmJaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theipaper its not it's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesrbuk @mrjamesob "Let's have an HONEST debate on immigration..." https://t.co/yykC76Zxrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good old @coyleneil, the reason I still vote Labour despite the dreadful leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 @YouTube I used this as a headline on a beauty page only this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellothisisivan @braintree_ as a child I loved that wasted, laconic sexiness in Shelley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellothisisivan @braintree_ he was so cute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbingham I may have confused him with Michael Elphick dying. He'd look TERRIBLE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellothisisivan oh, I confused his death with that other bloke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Barron: as if Hywell Bennett had lived until 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's favourite Bay City Roller was Derek. https://t.co/jdZpOothWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyAnMatthews have you seen all her replies? Almost feel sorry for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharz1705 They're brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KitchandBot I wonder if she was prompted?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greendoondoon Probably up to 12 at peak times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greendoondoon BE CAREFUL! She has 66 followers. #powerful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gwladruns @loukoelzer ORANGE of course. He loves orange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 Dave, she's got 66 followers. BE CAREFUL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he's hungry Trump shouts, "I vant a Viscount." https://t.co/jdZpOothWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamarks My week's been shite. Am taking pleasure where I can get it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Citizen_JC I want them to adopt me. Though I'm as old as Brandon and Rochelle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rochelle has no idea who John Torode is. #FurtherBackInTimeForDinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leejonathan Yup. Maxi dresses have much the same effect too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leejonathan Larger women favour this look a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swansonian It is as most of the@ would never watch the news or talk about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one's watching big old fakey copycat 'me too' crap BBC show #Commonsense then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit headline, Grazia. Hot Stamp, We Love You So is better. https://t.co/axrtPGctoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKav20922342 Like a normal person? Don't be silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VerityKalcev Going about it the wrong way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's Just Not That Into You. #Pip #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FabFitzy No, that's a nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FabFitzy @ukschizophrenic Isn't it amazing? I remember I woke up thinking I'd dreamt this pic, but it was REAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ukschizophrenic @FabFitzy She doesn't embarrass easily. https://t.co/VSUi7Rpo25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimbobaroo Sack the designer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAKE NEWS ALERT! https://t.co/k4Y62bkuZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsPottingShed @realDonaldTrump I'm sure he's one for upholding tradition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsPR @BBCOne Got your work experience Tweeting again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsPottingShed @realDonaldTrump Send Princess Michael of Kent to meet him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deadbloke That would be a bit weird if she did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs May pops out for a pint of milk. #protest https://t.co/ieBpibQbBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwensDamien "I've tried every diet going. Nothing works."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is no fun at all. #AppleTreeYard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KavanaghCk @Telegraph PREMIUM? Oh, we have to pay to read that? #Drat https://t.co/Ju3CERtm8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clairywoowoo @RadioWatcher I ADORE Feltz. She always strikes the right note.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clairywoowoo @RadioWatcher It sounded JUST like Down the Line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hockeyfrilla That doesn't help when you're in bed with Mr Burns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, Wendy Deng now has a 21-year-old boyfriend. 
#PoorJerryHall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouAmuseMe @davelee1968 Ha, ha. It's too cold to wear them at the moment though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 @YouAmuseMe Playing with fire, Dave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouAmuseMe @davelee1968 oh, really? She's not blocked me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelMoran @johnrahers MM is somewhat obsessed with bodily functions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luckycow0 @Nigel_Farage @piersmorgan @ITV Better thrown it out the window, just to be sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. Just checked my diary, I appear to be having a shit that night. https://t.co/VpzNb3Xssi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fifisyms @SonnerSounds I believe everyone who has a voice should be standing up to Trump's disgusting behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg Her musical knowledge wasn't so great. Also, stop asking speaking for women! It's just YOUR view/taste!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redskyatnight @melstarsg Snap. I have first hand experience of her too and found her equally annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg Yeah, too in love with herself though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg I seem to be alone on that though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg Both. She is NOT the only working class person in media, nor the 1st woman to write about periods and oh, Common People? Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg I couldn't stand that one! Hated it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melstarsg Nope. But no rap either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profanityswan He used to dance to it with his baby daughter so I forgive him slightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who do we think 'the girl' really fancied? Macca or Jacko? #DesertIslandDiscs #DavidBeckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisamarks He could've gone Spice Girls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Parsons has a pic of himself on his desk with the words "This is the boy who grew up to be the man who sold a… https://t.co/LvCmf45uvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rev tries it on with Mrs Rob. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrDarch Ooh, that'd be awful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gillalexander Yes, we will HAVE to protest if it happens. His smug face on meeting a royal, though... https://t.co/hRpwrpsHn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrDarch My sister is called Sarah Tobin so each time I see your name I read it as her, and then you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Jill storyline continues to be baffling. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we REALLY going to welcome him here now? #MuslimBan #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpHotels Staying at George V in Paris. It's stylish, classy and cool; not gaudy or gold or ugly - you'd hate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I know we've not always seen eye to eye." A line oft-used in soaps but never heard in real life. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those Scots love alcohol eh? #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McBANTER ALERT! #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I still don't understand how you ended up making a baby." #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Boutique" #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profanityswan @SkyNewsBreak TAKE THAT, TRUMP! https://t.co/KAQFooItEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting on expensive perfume doesn't make you look better, anyway. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Common people continue to STILL be hilarious. #thearchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 It was squished at the bottom of page 2. I think they knew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mumbler3 there's not even a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crap cartoon in yesterday's Times. https://t.co/BLOAk41GF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs May says Hitler "did things his way".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidclewis @davelee1968 @RadioTimes And TWO pics of Farage in one image. https://t.co/K0231Aqnhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 @RadioTimes Embarrassing isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What twat wrote this Tweet? https://t.co/4n3miz8pje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flamingnora I had a little bit of  sympathy with this opinion on Inauguration Day. Not after today's events.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flamingnora Yeah, let's give him a chance eh? Fuck off, Tom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody's perfect, eh?" https://t.co/mG8RvZOq50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 We had both. AND sweet cigarettes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 They sold them in corner shops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelee1968 We had plastic ones that were red at the tip. We put in talc to blow out 'smoke' - though no one in my family even smoked. Odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick I'm already exhausted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InspectorMorose Frothy. But salty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinDelamare1 Surely someone asked, "What IS that?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Egregiousness I thought the same this very morning. I am VERY pro-life but not anti-abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjohnhart Both. He's a polymath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimbobaroo Maggie Smith is just gonna be "Downton's Dowager" isn't she? https://t.co/RfUpwKgyzz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>