<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice @brentmusburger tribute from @SteveKornacki just now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Skype questioner skips the preening, goes right to praising the president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec on Betsy DeVos: "I am 100 percent confident she will be the next Secretary of Education."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliemason That's "Commander Eli." Please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe one of these local TV folks on Skype can ask Spicer if they have a back-up nominee for EdSec?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the content of his character... https://t.co/fmbGT0h7Bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$12.8 million in contributions to Trump's campaign ended up going to Trump's businesses. https://t.co/fnBLX1zom6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @mikiebarb on today's The Daily launch. Gorsuch convo w @adamliptak adds value amid daily flood of news. https://t.co/k61523D8JT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's discourse on black history, he is somehow the central character. https://t.co/gDa1zYYB3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, on Chicago violence, Trump threatens to intervene. "If they're not going to solve the problem...we're going… https://t.co/MzShjG1fDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Should we keep quiet as we watch this? Is this why America was created?" https://t.co/tjGLi0Jm5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump marks Black History Month —&gt; https://t.co/eGUE7p8NvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Trump's over-hyped primetime SCOTUS reveal and a presidency focused thus far on making television: https://t.co/5J2X0LTHI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Gorsuch. And now the entrance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's media blacklist returns in a slightly different form —&gt; https://t.co/JQdmejM7l7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koch world frets over authoritarian aspects of new GOP regime, via @rebeccagberg https://t.co/7VNCKooLql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where we're at... https://t.co/A6l0dR4tRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time Trump mistook a MoMA sculpture for a coffee table. Fun @SopanDeb read. https://t.co/zyDxHX4ILJ https://t.co/gQVoPfOeee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["BUT, OBAMA...[fill in the blank]!!" @anniekarni takes note of the Trump WH's favorite deflection strategy. https://t.co/aTcgalXELC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the networks are all gonna just play these staged photo ops w/ people like Rudy praising Trump while he sits and smiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer continues to insist "it's not a ban." Tough to blame media for getting it wrong, when Trump himself refers t… https://t.co/tr26biRZ2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ms. Yates is an Obama Administration appointee who is weak on borders and very weak on illegal immigration." https://t.co/oL8agPWDDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. https://t.co/0h9wr1mmhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Trump has lost Bill O'Reilly. https://t.co/iSQDDTMI1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuval Levin: Trump EO "elevates dubious political symbolism over governing substance and seems likely to undermine… https://t.co/B4Oy24GN6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s just a very indirect and gimmicky way of deregulating." https://t.co/ysqrR0RiPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer: "The American people support what the president is doing."
Reality: Trump's disapproval rating sets record: https://t.co/HdRGW4hY0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer is blaming press for "nit-picking" on Holocaust statement. The RJC is not the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says Axelrod was often in NSC meetings, that Trump is being "transparent...not willy-nilly." https://t.co/4D0CYd13lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...and by and large, he's been praised for it." Um... https://t.co/TqivINw2Cj https://t.co/9C61gI8yU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coach Kerr getting a lot of non-basketball questions of late. https://t.co/J36VZbbYTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["bullied into having their green cards taken away." https://t.co/EvV2sdhDfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't issue a statement like this if you think you're winning the war of public opinion. https://t.co/skBipmjIZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As moving and timely a piece as you're going to find today. https://t.co/7W6m6iqFzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When does a value stop being a "fundamental" one? After you win an election? https://t.co/TDVRTonZLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many Republicans said this then. None are saying it now. https://t.co/hYuzkgHkrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If Reagan’s dominant emotional note was optimism, Trump’s is fear." https://t.co/m9Q2tpBWSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a bet here, validated by his campaign win, that people can't tell the difference between showy gestures and… https://t.co/yxtlJqUZ65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we were supposed to take him literally? https://t.co/R3DKBlDpyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine. https://t.co/Aupn2gKMID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed mensajes: Trump deescalates fued w/ EPN on the phone, keeps talking tough on Twitter. https://t.co/XCdUnciMl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigrants here legally now fear foreign travel, being unable to return. Via @elisefoley https://t.co/4ns8B0cBJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain also urges Trump to "reject...reckless course" of lifting sanctions on Russia. https://t.co/2VR6jLvNJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine. https://t.co/6IIpLxy2j3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some nice feedback on our Trump/Mexico policy coverage in the reader mailbag this morning: https://t.co/3rIja8xqNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orwell wrote, “the very existence of external reality was tacitly denied by their philosophy. The heresy of heresie… https://t.co/8gaGWzbGuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @poniewozik piece is spot-on. Bannon may want the press to "shut up," but Trump sure doesn't. https://t.co/38OQY72PMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Trump, Everything Is a Rating https://t.co/XhNPUwrjU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anything is possible." https://t.co/Vt9A7EnDLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPN didn't really make it sound like this was a mutual decision. https://t.co/Af1vRfDwd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...such a meeting would be fruitless and I want to go a different way."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "The president of Mexico and myself HAVE AGREED TO CANCEL our planned meeting."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says press won't report on March for Life like they did on last week's Women's March. "Nothing fair about the media."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Border Patrol confirms resignation of Chief Mark Morgan: https://t.co/KWR8pMCtFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's the single biggest simultaneous departure of institutional memory that anyone can remember." https://t.co/xVL7dabHMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More: Trump admits he was "surprised" when Mattis told him he doesn't think torture works. https://t.co/wnQKtFfUgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to David Muir on the use of torture: “Do I feel it works? Absolutely, I feel it works.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec references “a lot of people who are dead” who are voter rolls as justification for federal investigation of election fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And yes, one way or another, as the president has said, Mexico will pay for it." https://t.co/K9UR51n5cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump chooses a portrait of Andrew Jackson to hang in the Oval Office, via @maggieNYT. https://t.co/HFnrAkorwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most likely an all of the above situation. https://t.co/EzUgM8ENMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this. https://t.co/RDARqpRIZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/H1mXNCFnNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where we're at. https://t.co/awUS0Md5aM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickRiccardi @JonMurray harder to spot parody these days, tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's a dark time right now."
Information lockdown hits federal agencies." https://t.co/2G1edmMioX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anything's possible."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer (on fraud): "He believes what he believes."
@jeffzeleny: "What does that mean for democracy?"
"It means I've answered your question."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["His reality is impervious to challenge" is the best line of that story. https://t.co/Ya4k7zAzCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked if voter fraud believe an reveals Trump's insecurity, Spicer says, "He is very comfortable with his win."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He did not answer the other part of the question: "What evidence does he have of it?" https://t.co/A4JPz1GcJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has interviewed 3 apparent SCOTUS finalists: Gorsuch, Hardiman &amp; Pryor. Via @elianayjohnson @ShaneGoldmacher https://t.co/e7pZDgftxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. Just revealed timing of SCOTUS pick after his staff was trying to get the pool out of the oval. https://t.co/Sy6wqXRgsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching him explain every EO is reminding me of John Madden's old thing with the telestrator. https://t.co/tOiYDvSQx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philip Roth does not hold back on Donald Trump. Not even a little bit. https://t.co/L7mJLjj2Vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tirades about crowds Saturday. Debunked claims of voter fraud tonight. Every news cycle, a new confirmation of this… https://t.co/ivlBm7qRr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: "Bothered" by being called a liar, Spicer recalibrates his tone, pledges to try to tell the truth. w/ @jdawsey1 https://t.co/NPsAzyaEzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only those tricky TV sets had an off button. https://t.co/x8tNdsAyXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the answers are coming so quickly, it's almost like he's ready for the questions that are coming. https://t.co/i5cWILUcdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer starts with a rim shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A fight over who had more people at the inauguration? That’s just not worth your Saturday night." https://t.co/Vaxic12A6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He's off to the worst start of a presidency in a very long time." https://t.co/6kIFNqPrjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We will prove worthy of this moment in history," says POTUS, two days after the inaugural address that called for such rhetoric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good explainer on the origins of the term "gaslighting" here: https://t.co/omtkob9GNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SykesCharlie: Trump, by lying and disputing obvious facts "is waging war against credibility itself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting he didn't tweet this from @POTUS account... https://t.co/Rc3NlL5ht1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course. https://t.co/FBnvJy1FEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In defining America so narrowly, Trump has awakened another kind of patriotism — dissent. https://t.co/vx2fVWa4Pr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart observations here from one of the best. https://t.co/xLK5hGCM3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just answered a shouted question from @Acosta, for those scoring at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd Size: Small. And other astute @anniekarni takeaways from Trump's sui generis Inauguration Day. https://t.co/OY89MbNjY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Inauguration Day of jarring contrasts, befitting a divided country. https://t.co/vx2fVWa4Pr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aside from the "we" talk at the outset, almost no effort to recalibrate the angry, divisive campaign rhetoric for Inauguration Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaugural speech doesn't just "sound like" his campaign speech. That ending WAS his campaign speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When "soaring rhetoric" is mildly insulting... https://t.co/j72VwCCJNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, guys, there is no pivot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's stark imagery of "American carnage" is remarkable in an inaugural address.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We the citizens of America," Trump begins. Big departure from "I am your voice...I alone can fix it."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>