<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Have Hearts even been mentioned in this prematch coverage?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser read this last night. So funny. The Weasleys are the best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didnae half make hard work of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniBlack21 tell me about it! Hoping for a Rudi og to make up for his volley haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniBlack21 we have to! Trying not to get too excited about the derby just yet haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right let's get Wednesday done first Hearts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is rod stewart steaming?! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was fucking terrible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great weekend in Crieff with the family. Now off to Kirkcaldy ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡»ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser there's one that lives near me too ðŸ˜¬ https://t.co/GwL5Ov54e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Crieff hydro and just saw a St. Bernard. Living out all my dreams today ðŸ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annual Souness family trip to Crieff hydro. Going to try and forget anything else is happening today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a man â¤ https://t.co/yaeuIREgCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie I had no idea what was going on that entire episode #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama videos making me so emotional right now. Crying https://t.co/Z3nXCGpJtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me during that whole episode  #Sherlock https://t.co/GxYtCbQqfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to work tomorrow after nearly three weeks off ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/WsN1imb6Lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bouncing about a hostel in the middle of New Zealand at 3am to this screamer. Thanks for the memories https://t.co/w7ABe5qGtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prattprattpratt went to see Passengers today. Loved it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time #Sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that was terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgie bound to meet the troops ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡»ðŸ»ðŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell 2016 won't quit. RIP #CarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day with all the family today. Ended by watching 'it's a wonderful life' with the old man #merrychristmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning with my godson and wee cousins, afternoon in the pub then panto tonight with family. Merry Christmas Eve! ðŸ»ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndsaye79 @Jonny_Mackenzie was just about to say that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day at work for three weeks ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼ https://t.co/CpM2MgeQqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That second half is up there with the worst Hearts performance I've seen. Get sammon and watt to fuck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally Glasgow bound to meet the troops! Buzzin!!! ðŸðŸ»ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopetofly_x fucking tune!!! And you're going on on your own cause there's nae chance of me going on it haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopetofly_x yes to Dickens, no to starflyer...seats falling off last year, nae chance I'm going near it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopetofly_x this is also my plan for Sunday ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas lunch at work and I'm in the pool in half an hour. Need to go lie down ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two 5 year olds putting the world to right on my bus. Great chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@leslieodomjr Christmas album is just what I needed this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome Ian Cathro! Buzzing! ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡»ðŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crieff breakfast â¤ï¸ðŸ˜ðŸ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking hell!! https://t.co/7eu7HJTR7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearts win, couple pints with mates and cuddles with my niece. Top Saturday all round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Missing!! Why do we have to wait a week to find out what happens?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeyGardiner95 off your fucking head!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them. Great to be back in the wizarding world @jk_rowling #FantasticBeasts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New John Mayer is exactly what I needed this year https://t.co/nyvysEVRNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser #seanbarryfanclub https://t.co/yWVf8gv3Y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ollyofficial sorry but David Attenborough is winning right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited but also dreading this ðŸ˜ https://t.co/tT9EE3uKc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to concentrate on this wee one. Everything else is too much right now https://t.co/G36PDygWjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously America?!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze I want a kardashian style show but with the obamas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna miss these two #ElectionDay https://t.co/omdU56rgjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead huge well done on this weeks episode! Killed it! #thewalkingdead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love David Attenborough so much!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniBlack21 thanks buddy!! I'm in love ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Hearts. Embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now for an hour of not knowing what the fucks going on #TheMissing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHERLOCK!!!! I can't handle all of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM GONNA MISS BAKEOFF SO MUCH!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so stressful! #GBBOFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Jane tops it with a double #gameon #GBBOFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Candice getting a Hollywood handshake ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got up at 2.30am to watch and I'm still like this #TheWalkingDead https://t.co/X6vJbFHu49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkJeffries94 feel free to come to Westfield and buy me and Linz some pints ðŸ»ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is boring! Someone punch someone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First 20 mins of work spent discussing Harry Potter #ideal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyF212 I know!! And the dad with the police women?! What is going on?!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching The Missing. Have no fuckin idea what's going on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectly describing how my week is going https://t.co/tXUwjvL8ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze this sounds like the opposite of a problem to me right now. Send them down my way ðŸ•ðŸ•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to met some of the biggest arseholes that live in the uk #TheApprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one should head out to watch their team and not come home. RIP to the Rangers fan who lost his life today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking hell! Boom #djooooum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a goal!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopetofly_x so good eh!! I'm obsessed with all the kid actors haha I want to adopt dustin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart! https://t.co/UC4nPjoteg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has it been two years since I went to New Zealand and Australia?! Time flies #crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ollyofficial why do I feel like you're lying in your bed hungover tweeting all this ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antoboyle just saw #thecursedchild you were incredible! Whole show blew my mind and your performance was one of the highlights. Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry, Ron and Ginny out for pint together is actually making my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entire potter cast is in the pub I'm in. https://t.co/3qxXwouIuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cursed Child....there are no words! Thank you @jk_rowling for bringing this world into my life. It means more than you'll ever know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on the first half of part one... https://t.co/1P6x9bcA8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopetofly_x stranger things!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally seeing The Cursed Child today!!! ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/uHFnYmr3YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folk sitting in front on the train are eating salad and strawberries while getting smashed #whit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work done. London for the weekend and see The Cursed Child tomorrow âš¡ï¸ðŸ‘“ðŸŽ‰ https://t.co/Ig9vbzy1cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easter road to watch the u18s derby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyF212 @hazel_fraser I watched it not that long ago. Always been one of my faves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyF212 me too! Was getting all emotional ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart #emotions https://t.co/2hYAigJLC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_snooze much better result than when we used to phone them smashed on the way home from away games ðŸ˜‚ #susosusosantana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty muddy done! Now for some prosecco in the sun â˜€ï¸ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser I think Mary poppins is my favourite. So funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents getting a new phone is fun... https://t.co/6hPXNUEZuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 Reasons To Protect David Attenborough At All Costs https://t.co/eoCBEbF7Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgusting amount of Celtic fans in the polwarth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser @ollyofficial amazing eh? Love the wee remix in can't stop the feeling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazel_fraser @ollyofficial @BBCiPlayer it's so good!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also @todrick is giving me life! #ElsieFest]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>