<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[But not before the "reforms" are fixed to give Aboriginal children, low income earners and casual workers better ac… https://t.co/qMcxqjAaU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lanai Scarr: It’s 2017. Why is the cost of childcare still a joke? | DailyTelegraph https://t.co/6rYkXrh753]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childcare rebate: Government accused of 'holding Senate to ransom' to fund bill l. Yep! https://t.co/DaMqQIy7fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh it is. Yes please watch. (*wipes tears) https://t.co/kekn5267bR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those same families would now only receive subsidies for one day a week of childcare. Currently they receive at lea… https://t.co/fsVdwViTQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Turnbull at #npc . "This year" they'll ask the Senate to pass their childcare package. Like they did last year. https://t.co/g3SHBC1rZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hicks_tamika @tsv_bulletin No. just that he wanted to make sure Education spending was spent well by the states.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annabelcrabb Too much tofu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny Or she is in a situation in which she's choosing the hill she wants to die on. Sometimes naming is first sign of control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we really back to "stop the boats"? #npc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny @abcnews Sometimes the woman does not have the power to demand her children have her name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though they will not deliver any more childcare. https://t.co/885VmYVOh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds scary? https://t.co/j4Binkk9oR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it starts with early education. https://t.co/XYIrJluwKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr Turnbull will also signal he intends to seek a new deal with the states to improve the outcomes." NQF at risk? https://t.co/4tJz2365ln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Malcolm Turnbull will press ahead with changes to childcare..."
Press ahead with bad policy stalled for years?  https://t.co/Qgy9kJQVuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateEllisMP @HuffPostAU Seems strange that he thinks it would go through without the bad bits being taken out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter that large providers push childcare package's passage it still cuts children's access to early education esp Aboriginal children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another go  at childcare  reforms as Turnbull's big policy announcement? The reforms promised in 2013?  https://t.co/46UNjUTLbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull to combine bills to try &amp; get childcare package through parliament. Now just one big bad bill.  https://t.co/X4UOC7x5fo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxGrarock Sadly, no. This was a real tweet from the head of education and care in NSW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant! Teenage me so identifies with teenage @vanbadham https://t.co/YpjPEHY2v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateRWashington ABC says fire brigade giving out water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateRWashington Ouch! 5 hours on that road would do me in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateRWashington Why so long?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good. May her baby be delivered healthy and may both be safe and well cared for. 

https://t.co/WpQD3ArFrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh @georgiedent if you work out how to stopping feeling mother guilt can you please let me know? Signed a bad mum.  https://t.co/08TvxNWRFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShoebridgeMLC @kymtje @kelmarx83 @newcastleherald Is now thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NSWEducation bureaucrat deletes tweet equating preschool education with Nutella and retweets sans image.… https://t.co/THwRWTdGon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It will get worse, as power intoxicates Trump and those around him." 
https://t.co/GbN4oJbL9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just one really "bad dude" though. https://t.co/XcUCriCpgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellomista @melissacbrooks Yes. Because it's so... related? #nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is NSW Dept of Ed saying their preschool funding model "Start Strong" as useful to nut free preschools as a jar of… https://t.co/0tsVOkEZVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would NSW Government compare their preschool funding program to Nutella? Because both are insubstantial and not… https://t.co/xz5j8mksuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissacbrooks @smitchellmlc Exec Director of Early Ed just tweeted it. Start Strong name of new (bad) funding model for preschool ed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @mscott how much is Dept paying PR company to promote new preschool education funding in NSW? Is this the best… https://t.co/qlpLWoZHqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @smitchellmlc is this best the Dept's PR company can come up with to publicise the benefits of preschool educat… https://t.co/shGpiUxbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they could afford to! NSW spends less on early education than all other states &amp; territories hence we have… https://t.co/66XmR2k7kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would it really hurt us to be humane to a pregnant woman and an unborn baby?  https://t.co/PqRCaPTBr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want clever Year Ones? Start with addressing early education funding shortfalls! Exactly @sarahinthesen8  https://t.co/h9Og69k3t7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneMGibbs3 @KeikoServices Arghh, Arghh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeikoServices @LeanneMGibbs3 Arrghh! *Sets up reminder to stay away from Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Scomo, it may not be the best time to point out the similarities between your boss and Donald Trump. "They are both businessmen".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeanneMGibbs3 Fiddling while the world burns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So fund early education where literacy and numeracy starts rather than adding another test for children in first cl… https://t.co/VylYGR0PKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private schools supported by public funding. Parent fees "icing on the cake."

https://t.co/A9ePAmuSzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @1RossGittins warning on dangers of privatising assets at expense of community. https://t.co/Z8Es9Hyft3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the countless hours she has spent in the sandpit will be probably just as important to her future as the syllabus" https://t.co/kCsbvlquWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And preschool! Early learning as (if not more) important than school education. https://t.co/1TclcNaSK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennislong1950 People who love others do not use cap lock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like an alien when the people I follow coz of their politics become strangers tweeting about a ball game. #trumpnottennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxGrarock Good on you and welcome! Our hashtag for the sector is #ozearlyed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxGrarock Welcome to the dark side!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to update your bio @smitchellmlc ? Welcome to the world of early education and care. We play nicely on twitter using hashtag #ozearlyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Mitchell new NSW Minister for early education and care. Here is her maiden speech. https://t.co/cvg9EpGY4W #nswearlyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For whom? https://t.co/qi5yW0HqrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matildasurtees If you didn't drink this poisonous stuff you would not have these issues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Birmo a light touch assessment still instills fear into children + parents. Good teachers would already know who is behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More skills checks and now on younger students? https://t.co/57heiRkqoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although school education sector rightly mourns the departure of @PiccoliMp he really did nothing for early education as NSW Ed Minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Childcare is expensive, but not working costs more" says mother of three @georgiedent  https://t.co/DR7BUDXf9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamstaples @JaneCaro @smh A bit hard to understand your main gig - ensuring education of children in public schools without experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissacbrooks @KeikoServices Or for education and care services. But he does seem straighter than many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeikoServices She will go to. No word on her replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissacbrooks @KeikoServices Sad. Qualities we'd like to see in more pollies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissacbrooks @KeikoServices Would love to know what his party and the Tele had against him. Too sane for both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janecar73 Actually Betsy DeVos! But I knew who you meant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Private school educated Rob Stokes to be new NSW Education Minister? 

https://t.co/Y4cZZonxN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is selective school education bad for kids? https://t.co/Swnr81BOl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lengths our cruelty forces people to go to. 

https://t.co/zlA76YZOnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when a country doesn't regulate their childcare well enough. https://t.co/FmOzdrLZBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research proves that even by the age of 6 girls have internalised messages that they are not smart enough. 

https://t.co/oNTfXkWoS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need to test out your April Fools jokes in January. https://t.co/8j5YlThrlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronwynHinz Did you say yes though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we all do. https://t.co/urzOmg6kFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maggiefifty And other shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Domestic violence is a risk factor for other forms of criminal behaviour." Good to see this written @JennaPrice 

 https://t.co/T5ErG2EW0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously? https://t.co/GVhTAp4bvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will @LeslieW_MP be dumped as NSW Minister for Early Education? Given lack of knowledge shown in Estimates hope so. 
https://t.co/tqXS3rOSg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a strange beauty in corporate holdings in the sunset. https://t.co/bbMBk5BFcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Thanks for caring for my children’ Now that's the message childcare educators want to hear! #ozearlyed https://t.co/QQWMljr3de]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving watching a smart woman repeatedly point out dodgy logic to a dodgy politician. https://t.co/1jTxyWy91W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the tears @murpharoo . This is brilliant writing. These are the stories women need to tell. https://t.co/bitgysDLgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It seems that early education now has more in common with being in prison than the carefree days gone by." Really?  https://t.co/Dx3kMofbXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already 3 of us down this year. The war against women continues in 2017. https://t.co/FtUObvv8mG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamMcNicholas @KeikoServices There is! We missed you as well. And see Karl's helpful advice about not doubting your sanity over the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January sloths! Hmmph. The rest of us have been hard at work fixing the world one RT at a time. https://t.co/DVQZegPVff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeikoServices Sorry, already gone! (Well, a lot of it!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the best friends. They helped me demolish this for my birthday despite my massive over catering. #stuffed https://t.co/xw0P8mPf0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" She said one area Mr Baird fell short was investment in early education."  Aboultely @TracyHowe67 !

https://t.co/GPF2SuE4C3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could we start with asking them to be civil in discourse?  

https://t.co/MUKlstmkCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the kids' signs.  https://t.co/9l45sLIwgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing pics of #WomensMarch https://t.co/9VtrJcFf68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we can't believe you are still having to do it either! Or us! #womensmarchsyd https://t.co/1tkXFOiWAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And their service approvals. https://t.co/hhndp4y61n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But we can't forget about the polar bears either. #womensmarchsyd https://t.co/63nINnSqIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. It does, really. Respect for all humans. #womensmarchsyd https://t.co/buSG9eSVBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure is! #womensmarchsyd https://t.co/mTwVI8yijh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#womensmarchsyd https://t.co/oR4Wp9tJIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzamina It is!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>