<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted to vote for Lucas tbh https://t.co/63heFZcr8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS A FUCKING TRAINING SESSION, ALL OUR PLAYERS ARE DEAD AND THIS CUNT STILL CANT STAY ON HIS FUCKING FEET. https://t.co/L1KmhGDJa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope it's career threatening https://t.co/T7d96amvSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presume this is meant to be a literal metaphor https://t.co/MKwH4BfMcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@attwood10 Suggest you stop getting cocky on the internet before I find a lawyer who doesn't just do parking fines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@attwood10 "Oh, I can look like a big man on the internet, aren't I brave" Absolutely pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welbeck v Leicester. I was 5 rows up, 3 seats in and somehow ended up at the front of the upper tier hanging over t… https://t.co/qTXmdurpe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mesut1079 I'd say Saha but think Klose knocks that out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank Lampard was massively overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this would be.....shite https://t.co/NnL1sDDTQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Link me to the exact report that proves this fact immediately https://t.co/P24QDaj240]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably voted Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we sack Shad Forsythe now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arsenal fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver lining. Our midfield injuries means there's no way Chelsea can predict our midfield. Advantage Arsenal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't this blindingly obvious? https://t.co/iD8ruL3V1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan You talking about your kids? Or your views?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banter; Bellerin Mustafi Koscielny Banter; Banter Banter; Banter Özil Alexis; Banter. Reckon that's how we line up Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanWright0 that's putting it lightly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iwobi and Coquelin in CM on Saturday though.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexis might be genuinely retarded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unleash Jon Toral imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely watford will get tired in the second half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if we got any of those PEDS we gave Alexis back in November]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PainInTheArse yeah I think there's little chance of that tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PainInTheArse extra violent foul and I'm ok with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would be the fine if we just played Xhaka anyway on Saturday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower Nah- could walk it easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower He not live in Totteridge anymore then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower The big man must've told him about the delights of that area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else is excited for the Chambo Coquelin centre mid pairing tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington They still get a lot of airtime on some radio stations. Never listen to radio but always seem to hear them. Cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower Which is 100% the only thing stopping me moving there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower In Stanmore? Yeah, nice but fuck Stanmore/Harrow etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harlow_Gooner Three terrible bands. Don't worry, won't let it slip how badly wrong you got this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower As if they'd name something after a black guy in Hertfordshire. Way too out of touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XhxkAttack You are wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower Looking down on everyone else from the top floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PainInTheArse They're well known for being shite shite though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northbanklower Might struggle to do that in a flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking house hunting can fucking the fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richgooner1886 set up new accounts imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most overrated band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@attwood10 Is this the banter account or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball Absolutely not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see Gedion Zelalem channelling his inner Freddy Adu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball You don't half produce some shite nowadays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't believe its 6 years since those slags smashed £35million on Andy Carroll. Still freaks my nut to this day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need 236 and a half spares for Sutton (a) RT ME RT ME NOW RT ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball Sutton got Arsenal away. Three minutes ago. This is as late as all your transfer reports. Fix up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could play Sanogo, and he'd still be shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could genuinely play Ospina in the Sutton game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope we score a billion goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaleyAFC @attwood10 @Mesut1079 Juve couldn't afford him. Not sure Bayern really could. No chance we'd sell in PL. PSG most likely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mesut1079 @DaleyAFC @attwood10 True- but I'm just hoping the fact he's come out twice and said he's happy here swings it our way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaleyAFC @Mesut1079 @attwood10 Reckon Sanchez stays, but on obscene terms. We can't replace him so we'll have to pay what he wants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full of admiration for Corporal Jenks pricing himself out of a move from Arsenal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is nonsense. Imagine Ox and Coquelin v Chelsea on Saturday https://t.co/8uWtGe6Dvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how sky sports will manage to make it look like the Dimitri Payet transfer is the deadline day saga they desperately want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCK OFF https://t.co/XlwsboK2hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball no one cares except for Neil Ashton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can have nice 20" tyres but when google maps decides to fuck you up in the middle of the South Downs in this we… https://t.co/pWGywTu19F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[160 mile round drive tomorrow just to go for dinner. BUZZING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May have to change this opinion https://t.co/jZBjdxHzff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, Ox's two best performances for us came in centre midfield. Granted, not with a child next to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our centre mid is the epitome of banter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball ROY ESSANDOH THIS IS FOR YOU RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bould is putting himself in at centre back https://t.co/SUR3R2rt5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of being barbaric? https://t.co/9PCeQ8iwHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho once said he wanted to break Wengers face and the FA did nothing. There's your consistency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sell him immediately https://t.co/zkpRJtGzKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm also really not up for spending loadsamoney on a bloke who is made out of papier-mâché]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington True. Just a feeling it has a purpose this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reus talk now is surely us playing the game with Sanchez?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arsenal Are we struggling for content today, lads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to respect Trump for sticking with all the stupid shit he says. Definitely thought he'd backtrack on most. Top commitment to his brand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably because you say "da" https://t.co/WhvmKLQvyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arsenal Francis Coquelin is like Owen Wilson because I can't stand either of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking lol https://t.co/ofiFXNrDhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Puel been linked with replacing Arsene yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are becoming more and more tenuous https://t.co/l3smLrHuf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caution_nick @XGames I have no idea who that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames Could be. The air she gets in the pipe is just incredible. Definitely has the ability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PainInTheArse Rugby with protective pads. Therefore, soft rugby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames Yeah, she'll smash it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PainInTheArse Get to fuck you soft rugby loving nonce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames Have to admit Chloe Kim is one of the most insane athletes I've ever seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames I'm all about the snowboards, but increasingly interested in skiing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames Mostly live, but obviously at silly o'clock in the morning for us. You watching for skiing, boarding or snowmobiles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames We do, but it's buried at the end of the sports channels section.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyEdrington @XGames It's a fucking nightmare to watch from the UK. Not even advertised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should all do yourself a favour and watch the @XGames this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonathan Pearces commentary on Cantona kicking a fan at selhurst park on talksport just now was sensational]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mesut1079 @arseblog Maybe Bobby actually knows he's off and doesn't have the heart to break it to us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mesut1079 @arseblog I thought the same. You must tell you're agent what you actually want, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@F365 This Spurs captain was linked with Bayern Munich and Man Utd. You'll never believe what happened next! https://t.co/jEx8nv31nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest surprise about that photo is that 1) Alexis went 2) Alexis went without his dogs 3) he's not sulking on his own in the corner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However it probably makes sense. Timing clearly isn't his strong point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fucking white bitch" seems a strange racist phrase for a white guy to use]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>