<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real Anyway, bored now, bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real Right, anti-fascists are just as bad as Nazis &amp; black lives matter activists are the same as white supremacists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real "We shouldn't silence differing opinions" https://t.co/WwFWDA6dJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real "Surely these Nazi fellows have some ideas worth listening to &amp; we'd be ill advised to treat them harshly"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's neat how the more she lies the more lopsided her face gets. Like half her body's trying to crawl away in shame. https://t.co/Vlk726uq7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or refuse to answer, or clumsily dodge the question, or have ministers provide misleading &amp; foolish answers, as the case may be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that our Prime Ministers have to regularly stand in front of blistering criticism from opposition parties &amp; answer hard questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliamentary democracy is much better than other forms of democracy. https://t.co/XeBPOgCbCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real A hearty rejoinder. I salute your scintillating wit.

Anyway, bugger off &amp; stop making apologies for Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casfucker4real @uwurodi Towards committed, intractable Nazis, I'd agree. Young nitwits just flirting with it can maybe be talked out of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real 

Nazis: "The white race is superior &amp; we are going to slaughter subhumans"

You: "Let's hear them out"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uwurodi @casfucker4real On one side, Nazis. On the other, people smashing Nazis. 

Yes, totally morally equivalent. Good insight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fortyfs It calls a certain day and place to mind, indeed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the fuhrer has good advisors surely they'll help to rein in his worst tendencies" https://t.co/s8b12Ra1iO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nia4_trump @Gavin_McInnes If Soros sponsored this, you'd surely have rock solid proof in hand before making a legally actionable assertion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider Thank you @Nordstrom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle He ain't doing particularly well in Canada at the moment. And it's a golden time for crude bigots in the GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willing to bet Kouvalis will move to the States and set up shop as a GOP strategist or in some other capacity aid the Trump administration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle He'll move to the States and attach himself to Team Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's of urgent importance that we give this unstable vengeful racist with no impulse control more nuclear options" https://t.co/ludDmVN66y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hey_Flike He plans to make an announcement to that effect tomorrow apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @goldsbie for retweeting this and other timeless Kouvalis Winning Wisdom aphorisms this evening. https://t.co/d0XJhl4RUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle ... and then continue working towards full implementation of the most extreme versions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani Depends whose windows you broke and who you punched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani So, y'know, while I acknowledge the brutality of American history that's not going to stop me from castigating modern fascists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani Not nearly enough, but Trump &amp; his fashy acolytes are bent on reversing all progress of the past several decades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani Clearly the US began as a white supremacist project rooted in genocide, yes. It's made a fair amount of progress since then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZaidJilani What's to debate with neo-Nazis? 

"I think non white people aren't really people &amp; genocide is good" 

"Hm, I disagree"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great! 

Still going to do everything I can to help ensure you're a one term mayor though, @JohnTory. https://t.co/X5pAtM5aCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're an unprecedented disaster and disgrace of a President and are going to be impeached within the next 12 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... twitter users who'd happily serve as volunteer anti-Nazi moderators, or c) he really wants the Nazi clicks &amp; active user numbers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does @jack not kick Nazis off twitter because a) he's seeking an algorithmic solution, b) he doesn't understand there are thousands of...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probability of this dweeb getting impeached by February 28 seems fairly high. https://t.co/dbVPTYSAAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. Now resign from politics. Go open a Keg franchise or something similarly innocuous. https://t.co/FrAHU7b9NT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old orange man nearing his own inevitable demise, petrified of everything &amp; everyone after a life spent soaking in hate &amp; rage &amp; fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuinely believes desperate refugees are nascent or imminent terrorist threats. No grasp of history, world events. No grasp of statistics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stark fascinating thing this imbroglio make clear is that Trump is exactly as stupid as he seems. https://t.co/45V0z3j9wq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't think it's..." [house stormed by Nazis]

"... strategically a wise move to..." [dragged away by Nazis]

"... punch Nazis" [killed]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're living in super-fucked times here. 

He said, stating what has been very, very, very obvious for many, many months now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chilling article. Trump through the eyes of a holocaust survivor. https://t.co/4kVjbM9Dx8 https://t.co/eI72ylxLCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surreal emotional timewarp. Stepping back into waking dream memories. Extremely powerful stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and walk around the grounds, and see (in crude paper-model-esque VR form) exactly what I used to see when visiting... lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're both long dead, the house sold years ago. I hadn't seen it in a long time. To be able to stand on the driveway in VR &amp; look at it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spent an hour or so flying around southern California in Google Earth VR. Relaxing.

Also visited my grandparents' house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We need to wait until it's too late" https://t.co/WtSsFJCASt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destinal Cool, whatever then. Let's lie back and let neo-Nazis do whatever they want. What harm could come of it? None that I can see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destinal @method899 You're not really grasping the dynamics of the ascent of neo-Nazism in this era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoDespair @clovis_cormoran @upkody @sesquential @iddqkfa White supremacist hate speech isn't cultural discourse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing all this, we have zero obligation - none - to listen to or tolerate Nazis, or to allow them public platforms to spread their hate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazi ideology isn't mysterious. It's not an unknown quantity. We're not uncertain where it leads. We know its trajectory in precise detail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People, we really need to..." [gets arrested]

"...ensure the Nazis' rights to..." [taken to camp]

"...free speech are respected" [gassed]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwelsh People being targeted by neo-Nazis get to decide whether or not they're going to respect free speech rights of neo-Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBriggs @AlexSteffen Well, obviously, you then write various strongly worded op-eds until your forcible removal to internment camps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerie_modesto @brianmwang @DellaCooper3 "Is this man who demonizes Muslims &amp; bullies everyone he meets a racist bully? No way to know."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has so much of the population come to view the President as deserving of / requiring king-like deference and obedience?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't the US start out as an explicit rejection of kings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alt-right alt-right alt-right"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very rich famous white guy with zero to fear from Trump urges citizens to embrace white nationalist administration. https://t.co/5hU2aIqHc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@opalsoap Good times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's cool &amp; all @jack but GET THE NAZIS OFF TWITTER. https://t.co/xviuNxxynN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Half-Life 2 future is already here, just not evenly distributed. #welcometocity17

https://t.co/4w1K5UqSC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@throwitinmyhat The man exists in a state of permanent rage and frustration. Bodes well for the future of life on Earth, I'm sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle I'm trying to figure out how I can purchase one of those abandoned missile silo dealies. Ride this out way underground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle "They could be the next Boston bomber!"

Dude's exactly the same raging pig-ignorant bigot in private that he is in public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle Yeah, saw that. Because he's furious about existing deal for US to take 1000+ refugees from Australia. Amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshMLabelle The fuuuuuck... ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@throwitinmyhat I read it was the reverse - Trump hung up 25 minutes into what was supposed to be an hour+ call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, what? 

Been largely off twitter today. He threatened to invade Mexico? https://t.co/9knnyC1Qd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mgrcharliecash Fuck off, Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are subhuman scum &amp; I will work to ensure Trump exterminates you"

"I really object to that"

"Why do you hate free speech!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazis sure love free speech and tolerance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@method899 @draiochta14 @absinthol This is not a time for "hey, let's let the Nazis speak". Country's on fire. Don't hurl gas on the flames.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@method899 @draiochta14 @absinthol Trump is running a white nationalist administration &amp; neo-Nazis are on the rise everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrainStemSoup2 You don't fight fucking Nazis with logic. You shut them down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draiochta14 @absinthol Cool, well then let's all sit &amp; listen respectfully to everything Nazis have to say about ethnic purity &amp; genocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draiochta14 @absinthol Shutting down a fucking neo-Nazi isn't "silencing free speech".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UCBerkeley Good. No-platform that Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hm, white nationalist extremists want to exclude white nationalist extremism from counter extremism program... https://t.co/BrR00VEAdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebiThornley I'm happy for you that you're so excited about white supremacist fascists taking over the country. Enjoy being a neo-Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker ... I just pointed out the absurdity of the scenario that Trump's lying about... 

Anyway, whatever, enjoy the fascism. Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker That makes lots of sense. 

Anyway I'm sorry your education system failed you. I hope you get the remedial support you need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker ...votes in Michigan, Pennsylvania, or Wisconsin, where if 100k votes had flipped their way Clinton would've won. 

Sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker ...and New York, the two states where they were already ahead by millions, and they neglected to get anyone to cast illegal..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker Right, so the Democrats conspired to rig the election by getting millions of people to cast fraudulent votes in California...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker There is zero evidence for large scale voter fraud. You're choosing to trust 1 psychopathic liar who falsely claims there is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @ACLU - if you do this, I'm cancelling my monthly donation. Y Combinator = Y Collaborator. https://t.co/KCW7QmawTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPeaceTalker Amongst other luminaries, GOP's own speaker Ryan says there's no evidence at all. https://t.co/0wZfaQ8uPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying around Toronto in VR makes it super clear that we live in a very, very low density city. https://t.co/ASFHQrBM2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not seeing a downside to this. https://t.co/3ib3ckSwt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then took off the headset &amp; checked twitter and oh right, this is where we're at https://t.co/xyfUwOLSbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And every human who's ever lived, lived here, &amp; nowhere else. 

Spent 2 hours flying around the planet. Extraordinary, elevating experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immediate physical non-abstract reminder that oh right, we just have this one planet, and here it is, and we're all alive on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start in space, hovering over the planet. Stars all around. Spin the globe, zoom in anywhere, right down to street level. God-like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a Vive. Hooked it up. Spent the evening playing around in VR. 

Exploring Google Earth in VR is close to a religious experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenMikeLee Good job, fascists! Way to steal that supreme court seat! Tremendous work wrecking democracy! May your Reich endure 1000 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg It's reassuring to see that no matter how many years go by you remain the same old rock bottom stupid despicable creep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, if you're the opposition party, would you opt to *only* criticize a fascist President for things less-fascist GOP members might oppose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why US politics has ratcheted right for decades. Democrats allowing GOP to control all the framing. https://t.co/uXbD0lJfG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not guilty" ain't synonymous with "innocent".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joe_cressy @TorontoStar Thank you!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>