<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong coffee. Dropping the kid(s) at sport. And the dulcet tones of @pineyzb on the wireless. #kiwisaturdays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie me too. Can't go past Garagista. Not sure this 433 will be meaty enough. Arguably like the Nix :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie I will report back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[433. The new @WgtnPhoenixFC beer. I think the name is related to the amount of money I'm likely to spend on it. https://t.co/pkDJeVBsNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win or lose, on the craft brews. #NixLevel https://t.co/DDP0PKil4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 you're so on message it's nauseating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliChahrour94 on a shitty Tuesday night...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton @NZPhotomac @Yakcall not proud of what I did but it had to be done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrontPgFootball dreams are free. Football stadia aren't. Maybe if we had a licence...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robincrimp bet you have some sort of 4k set-up too so you could see every chest hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WELvMVC that must burn Finkler being the time killer against his old team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrontPgFootball but there isn't one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 needs more hash tag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WELvMVC the refereeing in this league is so substandard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @JonoNorman1 one shanked cross does not a summer make!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlsvljvc by game do you mean referee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raena ironically at the north end...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WELvMVC not a bad crowd in. Better than last game. Maybe we should take the coveted Tuesday night slot on the regular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pineyzb Thought the return of the Mac went well; not a terrible headache to have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pineyzb Does Kosta warrant a start against his old club on current form?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 I'm not sure Barba is worth over half a million bucks a year either...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 having seen glimpses of his ability makes the disappointment all the more acute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbgaustralia staggeringly just been dragged after contributing his usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 indeed. Nor are they. Is Roly the biggest disappointment in Phoenix history?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 this has been another tough watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 he's no Appiah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having relocated to the prawn cocktail boxes I can confirm the extra 2000 aren't hiding here. #WELvCCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am perplexed by the fact that anyone rates Rodriguez. What am I missing? #WPXvCCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd roulette. What will they pretend the crowd is today? #WPXvCCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruno_smith22 @YellowFever_NZ @pineyzb @Dale_Warburton The Backbencher of course!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @pineyzb could you not find someone full size? #hobbitdale @Dale_Warburton https://t.co/hwzUSFQ2dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely there is a dog missing from the logo of this Italian wine shop in Petone? #doge @yasdh https://t.co/Rfo1jIcdpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NZFJeopardy. A: @pineyzb's last resort. Q. What is @Dale_Warburton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @Dale_Warburton #NZFJeopardy A: a valuable qualification which helps coaches progress in NZ. Q. What is a British accent (any will do).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Dale_Warburton Also in #NZFJeopardy: A: Essential tool for modern-day football transfers. Q: What is a fax machine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpmaj @NZPhotomac @SimonHampton9 can't have current situation. Would make the world cup into the (laughable) club world cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpmaj @NZPhotomac @SimonHampton9 fair enough. I don't have a problem with it provided they preserve the difficulty of qualification.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpmaj @NZPhotomac @SimonHampton9 Could be right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpmaj @NZPhotomac @SimonHampton9 interesting fact. What's your point though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendangage not sure you've got apples/apples there. First one would have to be 'worse than racially abused' for them to be equiv?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seldom have I agreed so wholeheartedly with the Hampster. https://t.co/XTXIdjn5rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could make life tricky for the ad targeting companies you've never heard of that know all about you: https://t.co/htHIMR5Mdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trustpower I live in Jessie St Petone Daniel. Not to be confused with Jessie St in Te Aro...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@masseyuni's Dr Mike Joy on the Environment Ministry (@mfe_news). A must-read for any Kiwi: https://t.co/THadq9i55I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full credit to @trustpower for sending a nice man down my street to sell fibre that isn't available in my street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds right up @Arowin's alley: https://t.co/xZlnrTtyQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton @Ryans_Rovers @tamcramer  That was a golden shower Dale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheACCnz  Was that just racist from Paul Ford? Is he the peter leitch of Karori?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robgreenwood1 @ALeague you forgot woeful refereeing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonzey0 or time your run poorly and shit yourself... That feeling...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allegedly 5.5k here. Terry Serepisos's accountant doing the gate receipts I think. #WELvADL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eesterbauer today is particularly rubbish though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eesterbauer that is true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eesterbauer but other clubs already in the league cannot... #WELvADL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eesterbauer are you bozza in disguise and do you feel the same way about Newcastle and CCM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metrics. #WELvADL https://t.co/zURzm8cKno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tamcramer @patrick478 I'm a Welnix spy. Of the Mr Bean variety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How good is Ben Sigmund at sideline comments! So relaxed with the players, gets candid answers. Tremendous. #WELvWSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NZPhotomac @AdamRyan hmm the rose tint on those glasses is out of control. But great to snatched a result there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton @The_Nighthawks that step over though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Nighthawks @Dale_Warburton like a hard news themed advent calendar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Nighthawks @Dale_Warburton the internet needs this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@modsta not by a long stretch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 but that is not anywhere near all of Sky's content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 better solution probably regulation of Sky's monopoly position on content, but chances of that ~0%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 Don't think that replacing Sky with FTA is what is proposed?? "Sky may be a pain" is understatement of decade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 history of FTA sport because of law, chicken/egg. You said 'potentially terrible' &amp; I say 'potentially un-terrible'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 but 3. anything that's bad for Sky pleases me. Other consequences secondary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonoNorman1 1. similar law works fine in Aus, but in any case 2. presume $1k/household figure reflects intended support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for haters of Sky TV: https://t.co/2uXAhfbIdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denheath custies are the best thing @modsta ever taught me. Pledge: https://t.co/GuHPDVngJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton Rob Sherman going to put himself in the mix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikz yeah but I'm all about my 10%. Your 70% is nothing to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikz only wealthy people are permitted to be tall, obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikz 10/10 whinge but you can't blame folks for using the recline feature if it's given to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonHampton9 @clevadix ugh don't remind me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfantastic stop it! Jealous. Pick me up for a drive asap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SimonHampton9 some high profile Phoenix coaches were frustrated with Phoenix players too I dare say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie the same players who were frustrated with Ricki's tactics and training sessions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragic state of New Zealand's newspaper of record. https://t.co/hrAf9Enu6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall God help us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rikdog72 I don't follow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rikdog72 plenty of contenders I reckon. Still a plumb job if you're a coach. Mark Rudan? Trani?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewvoerman @WgtnPhoenixFC almost certainly their #1 issue to discuss today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rikdog72 He's the only assistant afaik that has been in charge in an interim capacity twice. Post-Ricki and post-Ernie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Chris Greenacre the most experienced interim head coach in the league?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ernie Merrick's departure has been exactly as his tenure has been: done with class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how Roy Krishna feels today. Ernie finally gave him his chance &amp; his miss has sent Ernie packing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arowin You miss me and you know it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samfromwgtn not only a thriving Kiwi business but also the best place I've ever worked. Full of fine hard working people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton Basically me: https://t.co/ifY3VjrWqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton There should be an enquiry into how Marmite is still a thing. #Vegemite4lyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grim on SH2 this morning. @NZTAWgtn https://t.co/yPmNlcQ7J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year for Christmas I want: to make a start on the way to work if you are not asleep. What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall yeah I realise you were after recommendations. Let me know if you get any. I'm also in the market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall Actually that URL is wrong. Should be .co.nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall Can't vouch for them but seemed nice when I went in to chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall There's a place on corner of Hutt Rd &amp; Udy St. https://t.co/s5hoCpMtZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nerds of Wellington unite! So sad. https://t.co/iqEdPQVOIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Nighthawks @Dale_Warburton so much interest, really the best interest: https://t.co/aQOESzvdlJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>