<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple, true and brilliant. https://t.co/rVY0DQQpEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New craft beer website run by @Pitchfork &amp; funded by...AB In-Bev? World's biggest brewer. Bud etc. Think I'll pass https://t.co/fr1x7zczZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool need a keeper (Exhibit 42) https://t.co/EJ75aHmDuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in other news, why poking out your eyes may make you blind. https://t.co/4WbRreQa6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High of 6 and low of 2 = snow? #AlternativeWeatherFacts https://t.co/voVS6LCFak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know many high school athletes whose career highlight was being featured in a @htsumura story. They beamed for da… https://t.co/LJILU15efr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsumura: My bags are packed, I’m ready to go, I’m standin’ on the other side of the door | The Province https://t.co/RVSxkvnXX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProvinceWeber @jonnymac68 @PaulChapman_ You're in a tough industry. Really hope you land softly on your feet. Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC Sadly this is no time for Canadians to poke fun at American gun laws/ownership/use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC You and 320 million others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC He's just doing that to spite Mexico even more. #PuertoYukon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC Yeah, you guys'll be fine.All ready for the bold new 19th century economy.May need some time adjusting to 19th c mentalities tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC I'm waiting for the EO stating that all chimney sweep positions are to be held by direct Mayflower descendants only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerCTC But he's going to have factory jobs for all of you so no worries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vancity Already been on phone and was told I had to go to a branch for a print out. If you have other sol'n my DM's are open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Vancity I have the "electronic pkg" (online only) but to access records before 2015 I have to go to a branch to get a printout? Cmon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asifintoronto @nytimes I'd be more concerned if you discouraged the sentiment. Already subscribe to @TheAtlantic; considering @guardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recently subscribed to @nytimes. Seems like a good time for ensuring well-funded investigative journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seattlegal20 @acoyne Sold! Vancouver needs more taco trucks (and sunshine)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne Hey WA, when you're ready to leave, we'll take you, Oregon too, as long as you bring this guy to head up #Cascadia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Steely @seattlesoccer @vanufc @SoccerMuck Plowed snow and caught loads of pellets. Pile is mainly ice unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fredcutler @CP_CNC @Russcher @Redarmy16 @WillCromack @gasawers Coaches need to see it as a tool and not a rule to be exploited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjfletch74 I appreciate that they were trying to facilitate games being played but yeah it was a bit odd. Never played on a field like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfslioch It was a concern. It might as well have been a pile of rocks  it was so hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw a SMHer with these today. Ball passed gently to defender 15 yds away. Waits til it stops. Hits long ball like i… https://t.co/Xtj2BwybRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josipovicmladen Totally ogranic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confed Turf in NV today. We played a lot of short corners https://t.co/xhLwGuj1sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomNamako @SoccerCTC This feels like we're in for a very long downward cultural spiral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too funny &gt;&gt; Brede Hangelands hilarious Felix Magath story and more from the recent "Heia fotball" podcast : soccer https://t.co/qxl3BVkcYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DMoney604 Ahh, mix tapes are back.... https://t.co/D9EUydfgbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got the highly sought after follow from @DMoney604. When does your next mixtape drop DMoney? 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitudes towards mental health will only truly get better when conversations extend well beyond an annual effort by a telcom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help: does anybody know when the schedule for the Gold Cup will be set? Can't find mention of it anywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alikira2 @ubcmsoc I think you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alikira2 @ubcmsoc We figured 88 or 89 as Kernsie and Ric are in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful but could use an 2017 update &gt;&gt; Here are the most and least trusted news outlets in America https://t.co/tVd93YBVzE via @bi_politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unionthug There's a point where 'support' turns into self-aggrandizement. This guy is way past that point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeper should've got it 😎  https://t.co/6ukfwpDj5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_lebwhite @CanadaSoccerEN But yeah, only shows video of players coming out from tunnel. Not showing the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_lebwhite @CanadaSoccerEN Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d_lebwhite @CanadaSoccerEN Poked around there. No sign of a link.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanadaSoccerEN Can't find the stream for this anywhere! Link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubcmsoc You'd need two nights just to cover @alikira2 antics alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing a bunch of my @ubcmsoc teammates from up to 30 years ago &amp; hearing the same stories get embellished even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cforcilly It notes which of the fields at Memorial is the turf one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretAgentL @qz Don't worry, the saviour of the middle class will make it up to you in 10% off coupons good at Trump golf courses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On his first day as president, Donald Trump charged 5 million homeowners an extra $500 a year — Quartz https://t.co/lMTEgVpH1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cforcilly @vanufc VPB have updated their fields for the weekend here: https://t.co/KrlYwvFVJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The effort going on behind the scenes at my club, &amp; I'm sure others, to get as many games as possible played this w/end is really impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 Honestly, I try not to debate/engage w/ ppl who don't declare who they are so bye, good luck &amp; enjoy Breitbart, InfoWars etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 Bit of a feeble straw man argument to conflate being concerned with Trump and supporting anarchists smashing things up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 CBC, BBC, NYT and Guardian for me. Time for you to stop being angry at so many and posting anonymously about it on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summarizing the madness &gt;&gt; [Public Record] | Tower of Babble, by Joe Kloc | Harper's Magazine https://t.co/pMxM7Bpylf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were listening to this with no knowledge of the USA you'd think 95% of Americans worked in factories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly he forgot to write an inauguration speech and just grabbed an old campaign speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 We agree on that. It's just more problematic when those running for office do it &amp; base their platform on it &amp; not policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 May want to move to Denmark but we seem to do okay here https://t.co/4BcbdnpYY9. Trump sells fear, not solutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes This is in your sports section? Did the deer have a rifle? No. So it's not a sport is it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobloblaw1717 I take it you're a Trump fan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregorYoung Apparently no time soon: https://t.co/fBaHgo1FN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AmWay billionaire zealously fought for private &amp; charter schools; now running public ed in USA.Where does this end?  https://t.co/7sGABMsLHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save this for when you're feeling very down about our game. Messi &amp; Alves...what a combo they were. https://t.co/hMPM4EedUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinelmes @The_W_Address It looks like something that came out of a gin-soaked NASL Board meeting in 1981.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_W_Address Is it April 1 already?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the creative efforts of some to make their empty YVR house look lived in due to new tax. Smart home apps working overtime #vanre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher Can you imagine if we had a culture like that here? How far ahead we'd be compared to where we're at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher Yes. Even likelihoods depending on the age (one form of context)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher We should be wary of accepting things as 'absolutely' true in the absence of context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea, Tottenham, Liverpool, Man City, Man Utd &amp; Arsenal 'keepers ranked | Football News | Sky Sports https://t.co/JNOLqP7zAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asifintoronto That too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hatrik10 @innovatefc Chasing young players at grassroots levels of soccer is absurd to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hatrik10 @innovatefc We don't do invites. We put our info out and any players from other clubs can sign up but we don't ask them to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hatrik10 @innovatefc We monitor our numbers and add extra sessions as necessary. Unusual as we know from history what to expect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hatrik10 @innovatefc We charge $20. There are costs and it should be user pay rather than subsidized by others at the club not attending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are tickets available on TM for $290 right now. Not cheap but nowhere $1585 &gt;&gt; U2: $175 to $1,585 in 13mins https://t.co/8GxXeN6lkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would be enought to get me to Seattle on April 8 &gt;&gt; Radiohead Concert Setlist; Austin City Limits  https://t.co/1agqGftZ5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrTheBlackHole @colinelmes I'm gonna work on a "He's 38 years old, never scored a goal!" chant to aim at opposition strikers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSSRovers The Hip crept into my soccer life as well this past year. Here's part of a pre-season email I sent to my… https://t.co/Nz1mb4LKeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinmccauley Yeah, change it, coz why would you want to stick with one of the most iconic badges in the game...Smh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markstkhlm @innovatefc @Russcher @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @colinelmes Delayed onset muscle fatigue the morning after = hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markstkhlm @innovatefc @Russcher @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @colinelmes And everybody leaves convinced they were right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Yes. As does encouraging kids to watch games on TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Shooting is the skill i would spend LEAST time on in isolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Yes but I don't spend valuable training time on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes I did but its not a drill that I ever use.Was snapshot for homework]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Yes, start w/ slight/reduced pressure. Build from there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Eg: https://t.co/PeLCGlg40A Would drills ever teach that 1st touch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Still contend 1st touch w/ &amp; w/out pressure = 2 totally diff things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Repetitions maybe don't see issue w/ assessment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes True but I'm not talking absolutes.PL early &gt; ball literacy via SSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes There's so many conditions you can add to SSG's to emphasize tech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Russcher @innovatefc @Steviegrieve @WillCromack @markstkhlm @colinelmes Just don't get why ppl think bias towards SSG precludes tech dev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stirling_j I'm trying to guard against confirmation bias but that was an excellent def'n of the 2 schools of thought &amp; why one needs work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the positive side, at least they both can't lose. https://t.co/IlHW9jmSdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalMohmand1 And former NFL stars.  Antrel Rolle: https://t.co/PzNX7sERvR. Bo Jackson: https://t.co/KGMu8Ln6KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalMohmand1 Agreed. Been saying at some points universities will have a hard time running teams &amp; being credible in face of CTE research]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalMohmand1 @Deadspin A hit like that could have left him in a wheelchair for life is my point. Football has a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalMohmand1 @Deadspin Yes, some cause broken necks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the One... https://t.co/FZb4QrTVCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@putupwithjones Didn't know that. Interesting that Dier also off the grid. Developed at Sporting Lisbon: https://t.co/OXga3be2if]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>