<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Experiential Learning as the theoretical underpinning of Work-Integrated Learning. My weekend reading fun arrived t… https://t.co/sLDxREwJvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had the privilege of hosting Heads of Career Services at our @sheridancollege HMC campus yesterday.  Today I welcome our Heads of Co-op.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that the days are getting longer.  The sun staying out after 5pm makes me happy.  Happy Wednesday everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @the_ssu! I got to try @PlayStation VR! It was too much fun. Thanks for creating a fun and vibrant @sheridancollege campus life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too! https://t.co/j9kM1t1BVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoo-hoo.  Just hit 300 followers.  Thanks for following everyone.  I hope from time to time I share some neat insights with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan - seeing the future back in 1979! https://t.co/rbCVQ8N0Ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the time of the year when I start dreaming of being in a canoe paddling and fishing with hot sunlight on my back.... *sigh*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been watching Federer for years. A true Champ!  /Federer beats Nadal in Australian Open final to win 18th major https://t.co/R7Y1EM0w4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Employers Say Millennials Need These 4 Skills in 2017 via @forbes https://t.co/Y8I2iaVWWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love #dblblue Friday's! @sheridancollege I'm wearing my double blue Sheridan shirt &amp; rockin' these socks today. https://t.co/Dd2qPb1QdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan Peer Mentor – Trafalgar Campus (#Oakville,  Ontario) #job https://t.co/6DQ9o281m5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan Peer Mentor – Davis Campus (#Brampton,  Ontario) #job https://t.co/5QuAXZ4noj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan Peer Mentor – Hazel McCallion Campus (#Mississauga,  Ontario) #job https://t.co/R6yzcfOiDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier Wynne announces new job experience fund during Kitchener visit https://t.co/mawywAQY6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a great conference #cannexus17 ! So many passionate folks about career development. Last keynote is about to start then back to reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a day of learning and sharing with other career development professionals at #cannexus17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it reasonable that I expect to have free WiFi everywhere i go? And if it's slow ... I get annoyed. Am I unreasonable? It's 2107 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wanted to do this! Apparently this is the last week to try it @OntScienceCtr ...don't miss your chance! https://t.co/OZ0JrsusHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chantale and I had a really fun date night at the Ontario Science Centre! @OntScienceCtr https://t.co/wtgymEgxdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My inner gamer is exploding with excitement - why you ask - bc LCS is back!!!  https://t.co/ttirCRO6Rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google stopped asking these 7 job interview questions because they were so tricky https://t.co/fYoO3oYbes via @sai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't lie...I did laugh out loud when I read: #DoesItFart? Scientists compile database of which animals pass gas https://t.co/y4ed3F5D7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan your work - then work your plan.  I always find the planning part so easy, why is the rest so hard? Have a great day everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Deputy Premier @Deb_Matthews for being a part of @sheridancollege #sheridan50 https://t.co/J7O8GzfLkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one and only Hazel McCallion kicking off our @sheridancollege celebration. 50 years!!! #sheridan50 https://t.co/Vrp5uL0XO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students @sheridancollege @SheridanFAST and drones. Lots of training needed to fly these bad boys. #sheridan50 https://t.co/71mLiMh5Oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan @SheridanFAST has wicked cool robots! @sheridancollege https://t.co/mLM2sMZizg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today got started off on the right foot.  A free coffee from @TimHortons never tasted better! Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had my first @UCalgary @UCalgaryEduc Ed. Doc class for this term last night. I start preparing Methodology chapter before candidacy exam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blast from the past ... I don't know why, but I laughed hard when I saw this: https://t.co/chr79eLEDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This.  Safety for yourself - and don't forget it's also about safety to all the other people/drivers around you too! https://t.co/CN6o4zaB8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too cool! https://t.co/QmF6AK9rPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronJMoser no I think someone else narrates his book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, I admit I'll be watching #goldenglobes tonight; however, I will also be doing edits to my disertation proposal paper at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I start listening to Stephen Hawking's A Brief History in Time tomorrow in the car. First time I've hoped for traffic on the way to work...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just learned that @OakvilleLibrary has audio books. I just saved myself a boatload of $$ by using public library! Love it - thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruno and @the_ssu got moves!  @sheridancollege @sheridanbruins #SherOrientation https://t.co/wDmqL4SDQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do bc it's winter orientation @sheridancollege Trafalgar today! Meeting new students &amp; families is a highlight of… https://t.co/bCBJQYYP7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty incredible career.  Congrats @MLauer on your 20 years @TODAYshow.  #ML20 https://t.co/iiq33j3Got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough loss... https://t.co/WEo7N2dWyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol @saviasays ...to be fair, the bread was a bit under cooked.  ;) #peoplecanchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first attempt at baking ... went for something ez like banana bread. It's actually not bad. https://t.co/8mkOwiFi4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to @sheridancollege our new students!! Our @the_ssu is giving away prizes. #sherOrientation https://t.co/yUi5rOoz8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 5 Biggest Questions About the Universe (and How We're Trying To Answer Them) https://t.co/uioLWl4hDr via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when 2020 seemed so far away in the long distant future??? Now as we enter 2017 it seems so close...Happy New Year everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been another amazing term spent with @sheridancollege students.  Reminder: We close today at noon and we'll see you in the New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the holidays, you will. https://t.co/GPrRB7VTof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our @sheridancollege @coopsheridan students constantly amaze us all. https://t.co/0mKaHQwdzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooooo... that looks like a whole heap of fun!!! Enjoy! https://t.co/jxCFiG8d6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @lolopopy ... thought you'd like this.  ;)  Happy holidays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok-so I work w/ the coolest people ever-got this in an email today. If Khan doesn't say Happy Holidays, I don't kno… https://t.co/3CBK756r9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one. The only. @simpsjea. From @coopsheridan. You rock!!! https://t.co/9Nw3snxOV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ugly can a Student Affairs sweater be? ... there are double blue prizes. Lol. https://t.co/iTZPQ8tsvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our @sheridancollege students are absolutely the best. Period. So much talent and passion. @Sheridan_Arts https://t.co/YbjAzpcht5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spirit award winner Fran Burke from our very own @coopsheridan @sheridancollege team!  Well earned!! &amp; 3rd time in… https://t.co/vDZ1h61xj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An @sheridancollege academic term in review by @bezely_maria at our Student Affairs team meeting.  #lovemyjob https://t.co/ZXU79vnoiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colm Wilkinson says: 27 years ago he opened Phantom of the Opera at this theatre. @ColmWilkinsonNY and 17,000 shows later he's here again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 10 min Colm Wilkinson will be singing on this stage. #musicaltheatre Ed Mirvish. Mom and son night tonight. https://t.co/qM2lj7ToYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, so I'm a year behind on this - but it's worth a watch. Obama and 25th ADA https://t.co/8gsVTsW5Z0 #accessibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaf-Blind Harvard Law Grad Slays Every Expectation, But Don’t Call Her An “Inspiration” https://t.co/VH4IXkTVfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experiential learning: “the process whereby knowledge is created through the transformation of experience” (Kolb, 2015).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to do homework on the weekend ... this is how to do it with Christmas music in the background. https://t.co/VfDPHMZ6Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... and yes, "twitter breaks" do serve as a nice intellectual pause from being focused. But party is over now...time to get back to work. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make no claims that writing scholarly papers is "fun", but I can definitely say that proof reading my own work on Sat night is "less fun".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would be a major money maker. Wish someone could figure it out! lol https://t.co/kzL77fpx7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the concept of #uglysweaterday ... I just wish I had one to wear today!!! https://t.co/uc8UBO6HdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats for completing another academic term @sheridancollege students.  Enjoy your well-earned break and we'll see you in the New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to both @sheridancollege &amp; Twitter @DrJanetMorrison!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PS: Look closely to this around 53 second in.  My musical theatre debut! https://t.co/HI2yRkr7rD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Holidays! Sending along some festive cheer, during this magical time of year.@sheridancollege Musical Carol - https://t.co/rbaUmdPjrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['America loved Alan Thicke': Canadian-born actor dead at 69  https://t.co/jDFGXTLuye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful winter wonderland today.  I'm starting to really get into the festive spirit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote car start = worth every penny this morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat quotation from John Dewey's 1938 book Experience and Education.  p3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[only by extracting at each present time the full meaning of ea present experience are we prepared 4 doing the same thing in the future" p2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“We always live at the time we live and not at some other time... p1/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful winter weekend. Listening to Christmas carols, candles lit/fire on, and drafting a lit review on Co-op Education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Google. We’re set to reach 100% renewable energy:  https://t.co/0kpGGFOAN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prepare students 'to fail' so they can learn, report suggests https://t.co/yD8XmygtFH via @timeshighered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 International Student Buyer Behaviour Research https://t.co/fBDOYt0aa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting viewpoint. Seems Twitter worthy lol: Quit Social Media. Your Career May Depend on It. https://t.co/MxfENgEc2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter is coming ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education programs at @Siemens Canada. Working with students and grads. Work-integrated learning. #hiec @HaltonIEC https://t.co/1zeV31L9z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future according to @Siemens.  Great presentation by Dr Murad #hiec @HaltonIEC https://t.co/EfsYVCLKP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mayors singing happy birthday to @HaltonIEC for their 27th year of connecting industry and education. #hiec https://t.co/ZC8xD2yNIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing.  I used to work with Kevin Junor.  Great pick! https://t.co/MQZE0Okllt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check this out @Sheridan_CC &amp; @coopsheridan ... we're doing great work @sheridancollege to help our grads be career… https://t.co/d5zJnwHC9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students @sheridancollege BizTech Today! Don't miss opp 2 meet employers looking 2 hire you! @Sheridan_CC @CPHaesler https://t.co/y7OuLBdSE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil is my classmate for Ed D.: Until tomorrow, the whole world is my home | UToday | University of Calgary https://t.co/oOrtnGfFu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope to order mine this afternoon. Thanks to our brilliant students!!! @sheridancollege @sheridanalumni… https://t.co/uzyMRCbZvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another example of how volunteerism develops employability skills &amp; networks.  #italladdsup @Sheridan_CC… https://t.co/emgKDm2J0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite is Hallelujah (1984) // Five remarkable Leonard Cohen Songs via @globeandmail https://t.co/ahHgwK5n9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google: $5 million in grant funding to Canadian nonprofit organizations using technology to tackle social challenges.https://t.co/2IuzOZmkbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheridan tops the list in annual ranking of research at Canadian colleges https://t.co/pYrD5VknhC via @NewsInOakville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employers and students connecting. This is what it's all about.  Join us @sheridancollege students &amp; thanks to… https://t.co/lmfsU7F7Sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True true and true!  Get involved.... because...  #italladdsup https://t.co/wt4o7pBSuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a student at @UCalgaryEduc ... I had to stop by the University in Lisbon and visit the Faculty of Education!… https://t.co/OkpZaaVNKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got back from an amazing trip to Portugal. Some teaser pictures of a great country to visit. #Travel https://t.co/foUrmcXOLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had such an exciting Community Event w/ Links2Care last night. Volunteers, a panel, cupcakes, and our community par… https://t.co/D4nwV6HBD1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>