<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkeley students destroying their own student union]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkeley has gone from the free speech movement to witch burning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My photo - new little free library at 16th and Q! https://t.co/AvqUTghSMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see his master in Moscow https://t.co/ridIX3beQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump tyranny forced me from the sidelines to streets https://t.co/xKZlW9AEC5 #resist https://t.co/QeLx0Kvuca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resist: A Week of DC Protest https://t.co/xKZlW9j3Kx via @joeflood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the beer/shot thing that so many DC bars are doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't be a MD resident - I don't have car to crash into a house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punkaboo @washingtonpost as a new MD resident you have to drive into someone else's house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put in my "don't fuck with me" face for my first #wmata trip of the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[photos from the Muslim Ban Protest in Washington, DC https://t.co/ffk8wnFfRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not just give the city to @MD_Driver_in_DC??!! https://t.co/SP11WKM7PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumaImtiaz Duke's Counter would be a good choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resist: A Week of Protest in DC https://t.co/xc6fZGVh9d https://t.co/2POIdYLIpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Begin impeachment proceedings https://t.co/c93rbkXvMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnn is a parade of horribles, a panel of the damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what does Putin have on him? https://t.co/SY6gcEru4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yogitastic this is what happens when you don't eat bread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abeaujon let him spin a Constitutional crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yogitastic grounds for divorce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC bobcat: head to the White House! Democracy is in trouble!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at least we're getting some pretty snow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reminder: civil service serves us, not the Dear Leader https://t.co/ea9ntWJGnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer is one angry College Republican]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikkimann17 saw a bobcat in the wild once. muscular little animal. keep the poodle away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[city needs bobcats and hawks to curb the vermin https://t.co/QfZZv4v801]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisbossi that's a banning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisbossi are you on a green card?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dusting of snow at Logan Circle @capitalweather https://t.co/UIK0w6YsWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artologica @gabe_klein @TheAtlantic @EliotACohen wise, optimistic article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters pass the National Gallery of Art #MuslimBan https://t.co/Kz0SHZKOsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some broad is taunting the march from the Newseum residences #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pedestrian heaven, vehicular hell #MuslimBan https://t.co/ylgorDBUYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gridlock around the Verizon Center due to #MuslimBan protest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scene at Trump hotel is tremendous #MuslimBan https://t.co/m16GPWqQSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisbossi protesters should lay siege to Trump hotel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna have to go a different way #bikedc https://t.co/Wei55nrKQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MuslimBan protest in Lafayette Park #dcresists https://t.co/e5YTeOrBXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstration has its own dog park https://t.co/NnT52i0mrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowds assembling at the White House for the protest https://t.co/1IOlt8KaxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of #bikedc en route to the demonstration https://t.co/CI8dQp9p30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fraud finds success in Washington, DC. Check out my funny satire DON’T MESS UP MY BLOCK https://t.co/eZUImPDenx #fiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be our greeting from now on https://t.co/lIuO3yw4tG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans too? https://t.co/eup0XhGHDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punkaboo awesome! I'll follow up via DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives wailed at the power of the elected monarch. Now it's liberals turn. Let's downsize the Presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nobody has any idea what is going on" America, 2017 https://t.co/g2WLbzsvPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpHotels visiting the Old Post Office in DC, before it was taken over by a con artist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We ban Muslims but not the creepy Trivago guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punkaboo and when do I get to take a picture of you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharrowsDC on both sides? our long national nightmare is over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nice article about Charm City https://t.co/wnwFPC7aJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punkaboo well, when you look that good...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Arsenal fans are lively at @luckybardc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Young Pope is some nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten miles on @bikeshare in the cold today and I could literally go to sleep right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is like a consultant who causes chaos to disguise his incompetence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The swamp welcomes Steve Bannon #dcresistance https://t.co/WPhF0jjQw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An evening of bike touring at The Bike Rack https://t.co/DBmroHaPfr #bikedc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: bring me Teresa, she's the Queen, right? No? Then who the hell is in charge of England? https://t.co/LvjnWDHIO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-life die in at the White House https://t.co/xNfrifUqmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday Coffee Club is five! Come get some cake at A Baked Joint #bikedc https://t.co/y2bIYW2Ga7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is the ultimate bad boss, surrounding himself with consultants and lackeys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yogitastic he also knew how to throw a wild party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yogitastic he actually delayed civil war. He was for the union]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharrowsDC go where the wind takes you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommend that petite cyclists quickly put on 50 pounds to stay upright in that wind #bikedc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump merchandise for sale outside the Treasury Building #igdc #trump @ Treasury Building https://t.co/gRjdEotMXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry #bikedc there are awareness cones to alert you to the missing ramp https://t.co/Z1Nuj99hhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Potomac is angry, my friends @capitalweather https://t.co/JO76s3PVPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy headwind on the Capital Crescent Trail #bikedc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgetown students discussing trigger warnings so the millennial stereotype is true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nduley @amyfries @AlexTimesNews "in the heart of Old Town"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Oh my god, the Front Page is so lit, I'm totally going." Georgetown Law student. Fear for this country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the inventor of Immodium should be the next person on the Ben's Chili Bowl mural]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is @RogueNASA going to restart the Shuttle program? Because that would be cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt communicators work for the public, not Trump https://t.co/j1SjNb59MG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal workers' Twitter brushfire burns Trump https://t.co/bHabBzN5Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[best thing about the Greenpeace protest - embarrassing @ClarkBuilds. They're scum for destroying the L St bike lane… https://t.co/4Qh3yex5wW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scenes from the resistance #ResistTrump #greenpeace https://t.co/1pMLPZClRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And watch out for Pat Collins in the bike lane #bikedc https://t.co/qxZOpvBlti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look out around the White House #bikedc One of the ramps is MIA https://t.co/VnvDA2gAYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has not reached NOAA yet https://t.co/rr8TmW6Arp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information wants to be free - why Trump can't muzzle govt communications https://t.co/j1SjNb59MG #socialmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a standoff https://t.co/5c1mAO4xmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samerfarha no way did you retweet something vegetarian. What did you do with Samer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace demonstrators unfurl Resist banner at 15th and L #bikedc https://t.co/fmzHGGLghb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharrowsDC is that at 15th and L?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Women's March - more people than I've ever seen in DC https://t.co/tiVBKFBxrl #womensmarch https://t.co/5EXiCc5Emw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L is blocked off at 16th too #bikedc https://t.co/spMESSZDAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads up #bikedc - 15th and L https://t.co/6YYNNvC1ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all entering the Badlands now https://t.co/COjKIqVaO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's March: A Day of Hope https://t.co/tiVBKFBxrl #womensmarch https://t.co/yewjBe8P2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kebursaw they should turn off the wifi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laptop campers occupying every seat at Compass. Should just drink coffee at home - at least I can sit there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration Day: American carnage on the streets of DC https://t.co/NfIfh4eRgT #protest https://t.co/jvigmylvge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration Dispatch: Day of Fear https://t.co/ATt4AueNvN via @joeflood https://t.co/X8AH3lrnLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer is a sarcastic, bitter, thin-skinned liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Sean Spicer press conference https://t.co/ypU0f2GJGf #WhiteHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Sphincter, indeed]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>