<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Rena Kidd is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/3NlKoHR7EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALL WALLS MUST FALL is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/inOIcGhgRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[June Bailey is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/AvfZ5KV4eL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jong Bohr is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/ljmwk0rntE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Log Books Unlimited is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/I6qlcndYmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karen is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/v6diBcxTk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juliette Witt is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/qqaUa4mq57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flor de Sal Resto is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/alIvB38nJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shawn Vanderhoven is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/yAkZ1g0oII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathrine Schwabauer is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/BFyXMviKrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SJF MaterialHandling is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/0gHe3PI0sA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser Goes Political With Pro-Immigration Super Bowl Ad https://t.co/jHM4w8OdjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know your stuff - to be the #leader of leaders. #in #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melvin Kishaba is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/ZwE5lzzek0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it today to change the world tomorrow. Be the #leader others want to be lead by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonha Richman is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Ar43dgYRaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Super Bowel weekend! I'm not into the sport, but enjoy the fun if you are. #in #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rowena Sharp is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/sX1KFfzmhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17554185 is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/2YTT0yw9QI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evon Cockrell is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/mvvuCXHvIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Michels is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/LjXVoHyhRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norman Pennimpede is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/VqJkK5Yyh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fidel Grau is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/leSh7XjCRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know Donald Trump is in for a rough ride when judges rule against his executive orders. #in #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Canada -- Hudson's Bay is considering buying out American department store Macy's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ArtCase Restorations is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/icbBPSnnJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrutinize everyone's shoes. The more attention to detail someone takes in the little things - the better they are in #business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never leave money on the table.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House Of Darrion is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/TdlbSOPNkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APH Law PLLC is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/yC09qJ69Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saqib Napster is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/9jYZCWHH5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vince Green is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/wsV1WLe76O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat's CEO once pitched the app with this fratty email — now it's worth $25 billion #in  https://t.co/QJdLdIc50k https://t.co/2RnCxtaiuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MateMedia is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Igo5RrPer5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic Tooltips is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/7kgny37zNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ene Daniel -official is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/aru7iSwphC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Mohamed is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/BKNTUn9DTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathryne Stear is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/9tvLhp2bs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NorthPage is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/K7pUqMGB1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea Posthumus is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/kcZYE7xhvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathryne Stear is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/9tvLhoKA3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noel Cheatem is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/VcR2Ius4mX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Krista Tangerman is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/jMQLxRsoyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea Posthumus is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/kcZYE7OSTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noel Cheatem is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/VcR2Iuatvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[john reilly is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/K3F2embPXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Crespo is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/i36aY4dJL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Wieand is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Rw2uR1A9yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBiz NYC is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/AsEykKmn50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joan Carbonell is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/1NAeGASuXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saasabi is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/sLabIbTjMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle McGlade is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Xv0e1TRLDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan Sinar, PhD is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/z7i3cAUUsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who fail to plan, plan to fail. #leadership #business #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arlen Mcclymonds is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/EvmWlodylv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligent Office is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/ZRyh0riaM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to start your own #business? Go for it! Success doesn't happen in a cubicle making someone else's dreams come true. #in #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's up with those big white splotches around Donald Trump's eyes? Spooky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok - who trusts a rat - I mean a groundhog? #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicholas A. Fields is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Qa5dlzl5WX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan Holding is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Pqj44Ssl6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best #business #leaders are like groundhogs - up early to tackle the day. #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mini Smalz is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/CuCdhll5UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Mockup is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/mCjzKs0p7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azumo is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/8gKZWKtQxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #startup invented a new category of #search software so good Google uses it

 https://t.co/DG3lwciSE4 https://t.co/FnQHAwjfHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blanca Moore is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Yfr3NOjuwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Eschbach is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/1DvLVZXmNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BEST #business #leaders share their good and bad stories - even with the #competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evon Cockrell is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/mvvuCXHvIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexandria Salinas is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/CsTgDiRcH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DailyGreets is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/ebmxR7w1qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be all that you can be? TALK to people. NO. Really. TALK. Don't text - talk. Real #leaders take the time to communicate in person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Todd Sivers is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/uBrehQQJdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IN #business you have to know when to hold them and when to walk away to be a great #leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CassidySchuler is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/8mSGY2qhEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Dance is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/SP3Jac4pNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ricky Forbes is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/xfGKqU8C0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerri Mundhenk is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/ICv4II6VVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for our Prime Minister for correcting FOX News. Great #leaders know the importance of getting their facts right. #tum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praveen verma is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/JGMo5B0QOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocky Younker is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/dOjp1GEyqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does #February and being a great #business #leader have in common?
....
#Time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHSR is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/gJFBrgC94F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @TimHortons is running their annual #RollUpTheRim contest - wonder how many fights will break out again over used coffee cups?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be a great #business #leader - then take great action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexandria Salinas is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/CsTgDiRcH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shawana Stabs is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/1Lkfpuysa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rueben Norlander is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/RQGggGK3sj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Custom Tee Shirts is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/Cp0xsioS1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanelle Romanski is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/wsbOAojDlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blair Newstead is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/VNlPSH0oZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZenSocialKarma is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/WNOdFHBaGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Engineering is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/9l0rsxhfbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's this? @IFTTT is removing some triggers for #twitter? As we move towards automation, IFTTT is removing key functions I use grrr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Kosti is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/mEO1vjfc1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cammipham Hi - thanks for the follow CamMi. We met a few years back didn't we? How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mariela Otake is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/QJskZCS7fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Max DesignX is now following me on Twitter! Thx! Pls follow them back: https://t.co/zEiKMGz47B]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>