<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a theme emerging in my timeline: https://t.co/D1H614CstK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Number10gov no we're not. You have no mandate to leave the Single Market. You and Cameron will be remembered as th… https://t.co/MFiJp4BB7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Which is more than can be said for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladytubedriver Hopefully in the toilets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCAmos @UnlikelyWorlds Looks like the kind of place that's going to end up being nuked from orbit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Brexit plan." You keep saying those words. I do not think it means what you think it means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidDavisMP Why do you think you have a mandate to leave the Single Market when Leave specifically said otherwise in their campaign?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltCaStateParks Seeing the picture before reading the tweet, I was expecting a medical explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0000e @annaturley That seems to be exactly how I see it. I think you have the wrong end of the stick. I was referring to Herr Farage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wesstreeting I don't agree with how you voted, but I understand why you did. Keep hammering on about no mandate to leave the single market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annaturley I think an enemy of democracy is someone who gets elected and then refuses to do the job they were elected to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjohnharrison 
Upton Snodsbury, Tibberton &amp; Crowle 
Wyre Piddle, North Piddle 
Piddle-in-the-hole

My family lived in 3 of these villages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7im @WilliamGibson She could test this by tweeting "I would have nominated him" to every nomination Trump makes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Navarr I agree, but you can just search twitter and find her in 2 seconds. Hope she didn't burn a hole in her boat...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torykene @Channel4News Only racists like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ded6ajd I can see that, while convoluted, it does simplify the operations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PATSTONE55 I'm afraid that would put them at a disadvantage. To be fair, my 8yr old is excellent at maths &amp; reading, so methods are working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PATSTONE55 @MichaelRosenYes I can see years of education frustration ahead of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ded6ajd @MichaelRosenYes showing my age here (must admit the way my sons are taught maths baffles me), but what is non-trad long division]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelRosenYes He can read "chair" &amp; "fair", but is it fair for him (age 6) to know that "tair" is alien, and not the spelling of "tear"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelRosenYes I am fuming that my son is having to learn "alien" words. Do they teach meaningless equations in maths now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to the bit where you put your hat on. https://t.co/SwawbmJNRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jhawxrok you think he has just banned refugees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LTEJakee @mikd33 @realDonaldTrump It's not a ban of refugees, maybe if you could read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillageHats Just received refund for my return, sent 2nd class on Saturday. Your customer service and hats are 2nd to none!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesWallis You could be working on a sequel to a game, like... The Extraordinary Election of Baron Munchausen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed How to Write Adventure Modules That Don't Suck on @Kickstarter https://t.co/WHqrbSH0sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ittyblox Thought this might interest you: https://t.co/gHCK3R8kC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshbythesea  reminds me of the traditional folk song: https://t.co/AdtMsYpzm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So #Trainspotting2 is brilliant. At least equal to TS1. Cast, script, direction all spot on. Couldn't have hoped for more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep seeing the word "optics" used. I don't think it means what it used to mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jwomack the goal should be to drive him sane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RellaC I know the ingredients are secret, but I always assumed Coke had some "ginger extract flavor" in it anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a lovely golf course you have there. It would be a shame if something happened to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHSMillion Take home pay has been going down for most NHS employees for the last 9 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHSMillion Last year - 1% pay rise, but 1% rise in NI contributions
Previous year, 1% pay rise but 2% rise in pension contributions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is planning to meet British PM Teresa Green this morning, followed by a phone conference with I P Freely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Pictures of Uley's gorilla John Daniel published https://t.co/MkYIdD1se2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bridge I've seen them in our neighbour's trees before, but this is the first time I have seen them land in our tree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First parakeets in our garden!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headfirstonly @bridge @bittersweetdb Windows key + space did it. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyalMailStamps @DavidBowieReal Can we replace the Queen's head on stamps with David Bowie's head? We could have a referendum for it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wgb Can anyone remember why we started doing it? Also, why some of us appear when you search WGB on twitter but it… https://t.co/lNFuvRk7nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer Like not take away their health insurance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people angry that we have taken back control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@El_Buzz_O Which politicians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP Seems like a lot of people don't understand the way British democracy works, even though they voted to "take back control"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bittersweetdb I checked language settings in Windows 10 but it was all correct. I don't know what hotkeys the little buggers pressed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgregor_ewan Can we crowdfund a sequel to Shallow Grave? @piersmorgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goyacobol Wow, same crowd from different angle. Still tiny, tiny crowd, directly proportionate to your manhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More specifically, the kids have manged to swap the " and @ keys and I would like to swap them back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know how to swap my laptop keyboard settings back from US to UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jupitusphillip @BristolHipp @ChittyMusical Do you get to keep the costume?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists have proved that the size of the crowd at inauguration is directly proportionate to the size of the President's hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenTomCotton oh the irony!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 31 million people saw the tiny crowd and know you lied about it snowflake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orionbooks Please stop supporting hate. I would never buy the @DailyMailUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VonWareWolfe724 @smenor @upulie @PaulBayliss9 @nofearcrf450 Looks like there's only 2 snowflakes here. You &amp; @piersmorgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenGoldsmith I wouldn't eat that, it looks like it has been tampered with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AManCalledUncle It is another Goldfinger building. I wonder if he got paid twice for the design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage @PhilBryantMS @LordAshcroft Did you fall for the "It's fancy dress" gag again? Props for the Bernard Matthews costume though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smileyjim68 @benfenton @Psythor I was thinking he looked like a Norfolk farmer on market day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herring1967 My 8 yr old is studying the Roman gods. I think Mars is in ascendance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just hoping that the inaugural address doesn't end with "Cry 'havok!' and let slip the dogs of war!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AManCalledUncle When I see that building I wonder if it's a copycat or another Goldfinger. Your question finally prompted me to google it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarwickADavis You're going up in the world. My son just saw trailer for Who Do You Think You Are and thinks you're @DavidWalliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hivemeitner Admittedly I now live deep in the suburbs, but if you look across Woodfor, most of the houses are hidden by trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyalMailStamps Those hipsters and their skateboards are a menace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaterstonesTCR are your cocktails conducive to working in a hospital environment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaterstonesTCR What time do you open? I'll be passing at about 7:15am #messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sbisson In other news "Sales of Tricolore soar in Channel Islands"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neillcameron Don't listen to him, the real @mrphoenix was replaced years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fduncan @remotevoices I was thinking more of Dr Jones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnaggs The Count of Del Monte Cristo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@remotevoices brains are chilled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnlikelyWorlds Sharpe's Gold (@BernardCornwell), and The Peregrine (J. A. Baker).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herring1967 Did you show him the play what you wrote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Splitcoil First thing I thought when I saw it was it looked like a toilet in a Mediterranean beach bar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetalMushin @KevBaile @AvenidaDe1aPaz @nicktjacob It's called morals, maybe you should get some?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rezaaslan but apparently she supports free speech and the 1st amendment, accept when she doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tordotcom Classic! I wish my mum hadn't thrown out mine while I was at uni.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins You're going to need a lot more vaseline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed Stay safe! Try to avoid the missiles and the bikers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Number10gov Why are you acting against our nations interests? You have no mandate to leave the single market. https://t.co/n3FYYKrknX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville These figures don't include all the outsourced, low paid jobs that are staffed by immigrants - porters, cleaners, drivers etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yip25 @Tim_Lill @Multilanguman @JamesMelville Is this some kind of joke?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sbisson Theresa May is screaming "I love the smell of Brexit in the morning" while Ride of the Valkyries plays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Number10gov You have no mandate to leave the single market. The Leave campaign explicitly stated that this was not… https://t.co/OWCgsQKGxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladytubedriver Well, someone has to plan the route :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchTrout @Herring1967 @PrivateEyeNews It's obviously a metaphor for Brexit, or an allegory for Trump, or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herring1967 It's amazing that someone who identifies with a muppet should be a muppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gromit01 I was listening to Blue Monday when this scrolled up, so I amused myself by rewinding and watching the mascots dance along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bengoldacre It's that day again! https://t.co/O7JUz2wqS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewroUgh This says they close it at low tide: https://t.co/V3OFkuPWPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hivemeitner This says it just pools up behind the barrier: https://t.co/V3OFkuPWPK that a lot of water pooling up at 65.8 m³/s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Thames barrier is up, what happens to the water that is flowing downstream?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stroppycow I am in the market for a shed this year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManMadeMoon are those Moon patches available to buy anywhere?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakebackpack @ArchiePGH Looks like one of those spam ads from the comments section:
"I earn 20% less than boomers working from home..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I scored 7 out of 7 on the BBC 7 days 7 questions Quiz https://t.co/ZPAYaPMppu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>