<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpawnofJustice @GraceGrann @StephenGethins like the White Paper they keep flashing about...funny he was called on currency today mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpawnofJustice @GraceGrann @StephenGethins worrying, isn't it? Roundly rejected by EU leaders and yet they are ignoring it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazelcowan it seems @StephenGethins entire speech was made to prove SNP don't research and have to lie. Poor excuses for MP's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBlackfordSNPMP and where did he has specifically he won't?
Scotland voted as part of UK. Lying doesn't help your cause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAFCsource fair enough. Everton out of it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALS_Fanzine insurance? (Wishful thinking...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAFCsource Not even in a swap? If we keep him he has to improve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpawnofJustice @2351onthelist @StephenGethins second rate is being kind. They've been lied to by their party and haven't figured it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£800k for the White Paper to be waved around by SNP MP's.
Great price, shame none of it was true or factual. YES thought little of Scots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpawnofJustice @2351onthelist @StephenGethins watched his whole speech. He was disgraceful, rude and lied throughout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAFCsource what are your thoughts about Kone? Will we sell him? Everton out of running? Chance of a swap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish White Paper was based on lies. You think so little of people of Scotland @StephenGethins that you still parrot them. Frauds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you point to majority polls showing Scotland doesn't want Trident @StephenGethins? No? Because you're lying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inequality and poverty is up in Scotland @StephenGethins while down in UK. @theSNP are failing Scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @StephenGethins aware that Scot Govt plans for EU have been widely rebuked as lies and ignored by EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus, @StephenGethins is a gigantic liar.
@ScotTories got more votes than previous years. Vote % isn't the same as "worst result". Liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood most were held and let go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood but they weren't. That wasn't in the policy. It was being aggressively enforced which wasn't how it was to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 😂 for using facts and showing you time and time again.Aww poppet,unionists saved Scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood because it needed clarified. From beginning they shouldn't have been included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood they can't remove green cards without due process and a valid reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 😂 I've continually used data SNP and Scot Govt produced that you've called lies. Reality is Unionist territory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood were but shouldn't have been]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 then why do HMRC state trays what they owe? Oh right, because you're wrong, again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 I do. That's how I see them as shams. Get a clue, get some facts and wake the fuck up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 published by the team who check these things? FFS...they even apologised for it! You're deluded and ignorant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 the lack of self awareness is hilarious. Unionists use the facts. You've shown throughout you don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood @Independent it wasn't a reversal though. They over played the order. Kerry stated they wouldn't be stopped early on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 You said wealthy, not corporations. They pay the tax they owe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 they aren't opposition. Opposition uses facts. SNP haven't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 😂 you tweet that and say it isn't a cult. Of the 14 MP's to be checked for expenses most are SNP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 3rd- under Conservative's only the richest have not seen a growth in income]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 
1st- everyone should pay taxes
2nd- richest already pay vast majority of taxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 ignorant of facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 yes, it doesn't. They can't speak against party and not 1 is city council quality. SNP put forward puppets who are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood Kerry directly said those with green cards will have entry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron24wood those with valid Green cards etc are being vetted. None deported. Likely to able to enter as normal when checked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st @SkyNewsTonight ignores Obama enacted same ban for twice as long on Iraqis and now go on about Fake News which is Sky's trademark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @SkyNews
You ran Trump Ban story for 20 mins and quoted Obama's statement. Nowhere in it did you mention Obama banning Iraqis for 6months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R0BTT1 @CraigHol1968 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 evidence shows Scotland would be worse off currently Independent so to remain in UK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 😂 God you're gullible. Poverty and inequality have fallen
https://t.co/9ZwZOnjJcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 perhaps actually read the Smith Commission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 stats that Scot Govt produced? How terrible...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 Actually I say it as MP'S have group think and SNP voters tend to ignore facts and lie often. See our convos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 I'm the 1 of us able to appraise data and use data used by SNP/SG. You're a deluded cultist. Shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALS_Fanzine love it to happen, but won't...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I don't agree with Trump's ban where was the outrage when Obama did the same thing in 2011? The 7 countries are from Act Obama signed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrwiteTreacle change phase 2 to McCarthy and Jagielka and I can get on board with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoRalston @TomiLahren it doesn't have anything to do with holocaust though. That's just shit stirring. Honestly due to snowflake theory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 then again, sheep don't question the cult...if you did you'd be angry at how easily they duped you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 I've been told nothing, I do my research based on evidence. Sad that you've been so wholly lied to and buy it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 it, also, wasn't research. It was opinion polling which wasn't weighted. Do learn about evidence and appraising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 with every tweet you prove you are incompetent. They said polls will show it. This is wha… https://t.co/lm4otxUc94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 I've used Scottish Government data mostly. Try read it. Even SNP torpedoed the case for Indy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 sent graphs, links and figures. Perhaps you should learn how backing evidence works...cognitive dissonance is sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 5 or 6 get out on TV all the time? Because majority are incompetent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 put back in their box weekly. Lies get torn down and SNP shown as frauds. If they're any good why does the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 Oh put down the Kool aid. They're council level at best and completely our their depth. They're a cult and get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 there is no disrespect to Scotland. I've watched. You want to claim it while ignoring facts, you are biased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 😂 sent you the facts on it and you'd rather belive Farage. Are you really this gullible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 the gullible voted for Indy, SNP and champion economic suicide as you have.Have a sticker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 for example, people think poverty has grown but ONS show it has fallen. Facts beat polls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 also, and it's scary I have to mention this, polls don't show something is delivered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 #facepalm how have polls worked out with Trump and Brexit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffers6550 @Maureen56596209 @ROSAZAMBONINI @snp they've kind of failed across the board...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoRalston @TomiLahren the term snowflake originated from that. Alt-Right use it for same reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahB4LiviMP 😂
You could have chosen something that was accurate. Yes White Paper lied to Scotland. Oil, set up costs, EU, economy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoRalston @TomiLahren it's absolutely not the reason why. It's due to them being told they're unique like a snowflake. Also, soft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 and yet it's been delivered. Shame none of you understand the basics of the policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 yet another lie. What didn't they show up to? You know details of vote are given in advance. Debate is extra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 try reading it.
All delivered. Now stop lying 
https://t.co/LkCH2ZD1c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 you keep saying liar yet have nothing to back your point. Meanwhile, I have backed mine. Wake up sheep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 Actually it's all delivered. Do try read it. A twat would be you who would rather be lied to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 LOL they aren't.  Lowest reply rates to constituents. They ask questions which are poor quality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 haven't had to lie. Because I'm not a sheep and do research of actual sources you are left behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 So UK deficit is falling and our grows and that's WM's fault...are you economically illiterate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 I'm clued up. Perhaps you should research or not lie. Try either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cashley_ade @ScotlandTonight that's weird, Scottish Government website calls you a liar. How very odd... https://t.co/ZAiM95KGoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougChapmanSNP actually to win you'd be best not trying to lie to scotlamd like YES did last time. You lost on facts and being caught lying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 I read a lot of the commission which states we have more and detail it. Try it. Wakey wakey zombie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 politics and geography aren't the same? I'll add it to researching, economics and basic maths]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 we sent 56 shit 1s who like yellow and lie to people but they're there...do you need a lesson on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @thebestbond @Alasdair91 Oh you're a moron. No such thing as London Rule as it's a UK parliament. We have people there. I know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 do you tire of being wrong? You are a lot...UK Govt also filling in for our increasing deficit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 what a moron not checking Scottish Govt budget...it's up in real terms a… https://t.co/5Yq3EExRkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 Vow, Vow, Vow...Smith was comprehensive and delivered it. Stop lying to soothe yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 3. SNP refused to take some of the powers on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 sigh...all vow delivered.
1  wasn't official but still delivered
2. Part of Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebestbond @CraigHol1968 @Alasdair91 it's because he talks utter shite and lies. Hilariously badly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 You must mean "uses facts I don't like". Sadly facts don't back indy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graham020 @HankGoneMad might be. Don't know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 LOL look up official figures. £1.6trn last announced. Quoting Farage...hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 I'll take my apology now for your ignorance. Also for being insulting when you're wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 it takes a complete fool  (you) not to have these basic numbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 was £1.6 Trn...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 oh God you're quoting Farage...
£960bn inherited as of April 2010.
Last official debt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 Fully delivered in Smith Commission. Oh dear...you really are slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 we are Unionists as we do research.  You're Nats as you haven't/can't.Happy being lied to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 LOL I've quoted and used SCOTTISH GOVERNMENT produced data.Tory SNP talking Scotland down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigHol1968 @R0BTT1 @AngusMacNeilSNP @Alasdair91 You are totally brainwashed and really don't get basics. Try not be so duped in future]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>