<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can promote body beautiful or you can fight against it. But to do both suggests that you need to work on your m… https://t.co/0nMwjkl6FN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notboysean @rudemrlang oh god - dreadful. Is he worse than Matthew Todd? I'd find that hard to believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notboysean @rudemrlang dare I ask which publication it is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonder how many people will stop me today &amp; ask who should be the new Doctor? I love that we live in a world where people care!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniversalEvent I do agree re positive male role model but I think female WILL happen. If not this time, then soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniversalEvent why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mooneye63 that may be your opinion but isn't it a bit rude to leave her copied in when you say that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for a female Doctor. They didn't get one in the White House, so let's put one in the Blue House! #DoctorWho https://t.co/800OA66duq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who I'd love to see play The Doctor @katherine_kelly - I'm not sure if her role in @bbcclass makes that more or less likely...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smurphy71 oh absolutely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Brexit ref took place we saw the US as our trading partner. Now that relationship is in question, Article 50 must not be invoked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhoSFX it was very, very hot on that evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhoSFX I don't think he's being critical of you. Rather he (she?) is saying that you're not like the majority of Twitter right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riverisland @reeceking_ "Tuesdays" doesn't have an apostrophe in it, whatever colour we wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heathlenie well, surely it's not surprising that a TV presenter with no political experience isn't up to the job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Roofyj well I am now that you're here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is what four weeks of not drinking and eating healthy has done for me. https://t.co/9yaiSSE9fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Roofyj you're back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rudemrlang yes, but with that face it was more appealing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking of starting a march to persuade Theresa May to grow out that dreadful pageboy haircut she's adopted. W… https://t.co/uBAHXTrhgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happened to Johnny Carter's hair on EastEnders? It has less shape and definition than his character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keetch1701 @blucanary my favourite bits of RTD's writing are his focus on Rose, Martha and particularly Donna and Wilf. But each to his own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronKMcEwan and tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keetch1701 @blucanary that's an opinion but it certainly isn't mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudryT that's reassuring to an extent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat on the train to London eating an omelette I made last night. Its smell is getting me dirty looks. Eggsellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryWales @Trump_Regrets I was going to follow that but I think it'll actually annoy me more than anything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up in the middle of the night and saw this on my phone. United States you have elected a dangerous despot for… https://t.co/unZKh3ny1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbos really? Good. Not that it counts for much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blucanary I just emailed him and got the most lovely response. He is such a great guy. Will miss him loads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alastair_JB wise words. Everyone says it, but few live by it. It's not always easy when the minutiae of life gets in the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wondering how Trump supporters are taking his first few days in office. Obviously the crazies &amp; racists love it but what about the rest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been listening to @depechemode Violater this morning for first time in years. Sounds so fresh. Partly due to its mix of guitar &amp; synth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdiscopop @DirtyPopCardiff people's personal preferences aside, it's seen its audiences massively increase around the world, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GavinWorby he's said that Xmas is his last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi on News at 10!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mooneye63 why do you assume it's anything to do with the schedule? Actors tend to do 3 or 4 series before moving on to other work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Easter sees the start of Peter Capaldi's last full series in Doctor Who. So sad, but we've still got almost a year of his amazing Doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mooneye63 I'd love him to stay longer too. A shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreativeCatFX people who don't like it probably have no souls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BriggsNicholas @ChristelDee we have spare hair! https://t.co/K4JKP32nHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreativeCatFX it's amazing. I'm really shocked that some people just don't get it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's sent me something for approval and it's green. I absolutely HATE the colour green. https://t.co/Qie4dIx5AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the "mentioned in parliament within 12 months" ethos of online petitions is pointless, I have to admit this one has grabbed attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given what I said about online petitions, in this instance I'm pleased to have been proved wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bjc4691 and your point? Am I not allowed to have or express an opinion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthemEditor (and I mean that most respectfully - your magazine is an excellent read).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthemEditor hooray for your forthcoming Madonna special. But please have it fact checked. Your ABBA edition only got A-, for its errors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nyssa1968 @FrankhamAllen @joelidster actually, I'll agree with you on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@04nbod I was being facetious. I thought that was clear but clearly not. Or not clear to you. Anyway, I'm too old to be conscripted!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex I am encouraging people to take effective action. You know this but are being deliberately polemic. Swearing is trolling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@04nbod I don't get your point. I'm not against people taking action. My point is that online petitions are wasted effort, do something else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex then write a letter. Donate to an organisation that opposes. Anything but sign a useless petition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex and I don't know who you are. We've never met. So, yes, I am entitled to be offended that you are trolling me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex I want people to do want they can. I'm advising that a certain act is not as effective as another. So do something that works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 mine will probably have a typo, but it's the thought that cunts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelidster @FrankhamAllen than that, we are raising a generation of people who think you can solve the worlds problems from a keyboard 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelidster @FrankhamAllen look, sign the petitions if you want. I've given it a lot of thought and consider them a placebo. But more 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 don't you think standing outside Buckingham Palace with placards is a better idea, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex I'm sorry, but is there any need for you to speak to me in that way? You're free to argue but drop the bad language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelidster @FrankhamAllen it'll get tabled for a mention by a junior minister within 12 months - wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 in this ever-growing world of keyboard warriors, people need to direct their fear and anger more effectively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelidster @FrankhamAllen Trump reacted to last weekend's march. It will have bothered him. And it made people feel united.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runawaygirlx it's not far away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankhamAllen I was being facetious. The point is signing a petition is the laziest effort. Get out and march.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pystrier so what? Last weekend's march was more effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NebogipfelWho it's a waste of time. It will have more effect to do well organised protests like the women's march.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runawaygirlx it's a placebo. You have a voice, you have legs. Use them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorVortex oh really? I didn't realise that https://t.co/0ErDmYdqlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 It's a placebo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to this tomorrow. https://t.co/zc42QlK2rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did an online petition win WW2? No. Did an online petition get women the vote? No. So it's not going to get rid of Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_lissack oh really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yawn, another online petition. What's wrong with people? THEY HAVE NO EFFECT. Join a march or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a plus, I really liked the Izzy Bizu song whereas I've been a bit "meh" about her in the past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have always loved Ewan but didn't think he came across well on @TheGNShow - especially that first class air travel story that went nowhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His &amp; Hers quiffs and specs - lovely to see @ChristelDee today https://t.co/Yc7PH2wsmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A freak timestorm in the rift brought @captainchristel to Cardiff so we had a quick adventure @… https://t.co/8KCktXoeq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least our Eurovision song sounds credible, @luciejones1 can really sing and it's not embarrassing. Production needs a kick of paint, tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nerdygoldy yes. Have you heard any? He was great in them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevBobMIB yes - it say his name over the final frame "introducing John Hurt as The Doctor", doesn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevBobMIB I'm referring to his appearance - albeit brief - at the end of Name of the Doctor. McGann only in one episode plus web only Ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember us all at Buckingham Palace in Nov 2013 &amp; John Hurt asking Moffat if he was OK to say he was an official Doctor - hell yes, John!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevBobMIB I've not added up the minutes. Possibly. But he did appear in two episodes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I appreciate that, in the grand scheme of things, it's the least of our worries, but WTF has Theresa May done to her hair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt was an incredibly nice man &amp; a wonderful actor. He always seemed in awe that he managed to be The Doctor &amp; we were lucky. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fraxis well then they had the Vamps to redress the balance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pleased that Lucie is being put forward for us #EurovisionYouDecide https://t.co/aCdy5qjsxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blucanary plus she was on SJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blucanary it was quite audible on TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stick a 909 under this song and it would fly #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of that audience booing Lucy should be ashamed of themselves #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank Christ it's Lucy going forward. She's the only one that can sing live and that sang has substance and conviction #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the way Swedes pronounce "you" as "Jew" ❤️❤️❤️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mel: "Fuck it. Shall we just get Sophie Ellis-Bextor to do it instead?" #eurovisionyoudecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Love Peace Peace is the best moment in Eurovision history aside from Waterloo #eurovisionyoudecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you asked everyone in that audience if they wanted @SophieEB to represent us instead of that lot it would be a 100% "yes" vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless you, Mel. No one under the age of 30 has ever heard of talc #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the Vamps really can't sing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love The Common Linnets. Both so beautiful #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>