<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont think @EndaKennyTD would ever pass an oppertunity to kiss ass. https://t.co/bmnMlvMFN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlizzardCSEU_EN Quick Q, the sets from The Lost Army quest, do you unlock all of them (cloth/leather/mail/plate) when you complete it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same deal on planes, or anything with a pressure differential. Force is exerted by the pressurized gas, not the low pressure area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Todays pedantic science trivia: If you open your door in space, youre not sucked out, you're pushed by the pressure of the gas inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Hurt, one of my favorite actors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Risedeer Guys like that dont surround themselves with people that call them on their shit. Groups of circlejerking shitbags.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So thats how planes have fresh air without needing tanks of air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL Airplanes take air from their engines and use it to ventilate the cabin and vent the rest. So its not a tube of other peoples farts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celestalon Balance them within ~10% of each other, so top players switch but the players who actually like the spec dont feel pressure to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely you hurt yourself long before you get to this point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lad has huge biceps but his curls are jerky swingy messes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people with terrible form get so buff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whats that old saying? Its way easier to win people over by blowing up trains than it is by making them run on time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Congress are going to spend 4 years tearing down everything Obama built. No solutions, no answers, just a wave of hatred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_Lonely_G0D Wait is it out in english? Ive been waiting for it for months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No smoking in the Skull Cave"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaberiusLoL or...oooor, bar of soap in a sock. I think that might leave a more lasting impression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tbh I wouldnt give a shit except that Im sick, hes shouting at the wall that separate our rooms and he woke me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont tell them to kill themselves what the fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except hes toxic to his own fucking teammates, who are on skype with him. Like these are your friends, why do they play with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to my brother play league makes me want to out my fist through the wall. Think of the worst toxic player you know, thats him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soundtracks give me weird mental associations. Like how I associate Chuck Berry with time travel and the Ink Spots with nuclear apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget how awesome Jason Momoa is in the justice league trailer. Then I remember and it is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a special rage reserved for family misquoting the simpsons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Ive hit the point at which episodes of the outer limits get really shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#forgeworld do their christmas jigsaw, first comment someone ruins it with pictures from open day. This is why we cant have nice things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WargamerDonal roll for each model seperately, if you get a repeat attack with the same model the damage roll is also duplicated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Risedeer @AzannaBanana I travelled 3 hours from galway to lock myself away from humans in my room with my dog. Tis the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT. Im watching episodes of the Outer Limits and the twist at the end of that episode. Holy fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Write Sins Not Rhyming Schemes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These "has anyone seen" memes are officially worse than the "tag a mate that would smash that" memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maiohnee It scales with versatility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@serial_thriller Yeh, should be the councils responsibility to deal with these issues. Their fault businesses have to take extreme measures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@serial_thriller People are always looking for reasons to demonise businesses for trying to protect their staff and customers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a guy pretend to wash his hands in the bathroom. So many questions. All of them why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out wheatstone bridges are EVERYWHERE in medical devices, which is crazy because they were mentioned once in electricity andneveragain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like World War Z. Kind of okay stand alone movies,completely unrelated to the source, and only cashing in on the name and dissapointing fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get the feeling the Escape from New York remake is another one of those movies that only shares the title witth the original work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss a lot of mathhammer, you dont see it these days. Same with theorycraft on WoW forums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That being said, outside of people moaning about powergaming, theres a ton of decent discussion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[90% of questions asked in warhammer groups are basically answered by syaing "Read the book". The other 10% are people asking for netlists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gym is so hard in this cold. Takes so long to warm up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlizzardCSEU_EN Just got Unleashed Monstrosities, but can't use the reward skin, is this a bug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towelthetank @Alexensual Who cares what some twat says? Just ignore him, its not like he matters with his 7k followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaylandGames If I were to order the prospero box right now, how soon could it be shipped? Heard about diff between "available" and in stock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a dude wearing a plastic bag on his face for people to listen to what we've been saying for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charge maybe? Bash? Thats about it. Actually those are the only way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually cant think of a way to proc it in any meaningful way until the hotfix is in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my first #legion legendary. Sephuz's fucking Secret. The actual worst legendary in the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got MVP in my first #HotS game. Not bad. Anub'arak is a beast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElementGames_ Any update on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the plus side with the pound and now the dollar becoming just glorified toiletpaper, Ordering online is going to be a lot of fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually cant believe this. Even the stock market is collapsing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what misinformation and false accusations can do to a candidate. Nobody cares that Clinton was innocent. #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im half angry and half lost the will to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey we have a highly qualified woman running against a racist, sexist, lying tangerine. And its a really close race. What the actual fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god that guy falling on the #NBC stream. I practically fell out of my chair laughing. #Elections2016 #ElectionDay #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people that say Hillary Clinton is a bad candidate don't know what theyre talking about. 67% approval rate as sec of state. Thats huge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May have had a slight purge of facebook friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElementGames_ Hey guys, can you give me a quote on how much it would it cost to ship the prospero box to Galway, Ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was wondering why I never drew Nzoth in my nzoth deck. Turns out I should try putting him inthe deck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I brought a ton of 40k back to dublin and now I really want to play #ageofsigmar. Jesus I need to make up my mind better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarcraftDevs THIS. IS. AWESOME. Please make this a glyph. Also a little buggy interaction with claws of ursoc. https://t.co/BR0BSkQz3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarcraftDevs Ever considered reducing the cooldown of bloodboil to work as a filler like blessed hammer? Might help with dk dead spots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need an alt to play but I actually can't decide which tank I want. I cba finishing levelling my warrior because their AM is so booooring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read a post from a guy who bought a metal detector to look for lost gold jewelry. I want to say something but I know I shouldnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AoE slash, powerful single target attack, charge. Even RotS makes you get bigger and angrier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly Renek would play basically the same way as a Guardian Druid plays right now, even the skills are similar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly all I really want is a League MMO. Some of the 'class designs' are so cool, like Renekton and nautilus as tanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Risedeer Men on the internet are actually the fucking worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_XOXO Remember youve probably lost more than you think, muscle is denser, heavier. I put on 20kg when i started working out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dat feel when Mendeley suggests a paper to you that has your name on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lecturer keeps saying concentration gradient when it should be pressure gradient and i think its giving me a twitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IrishRail Any chance you can actually get some security on these trains? 6pm Ceannt to Dublin was a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarcraftDevs How come emmisary chest rewards don't scale? I still get 810 items, thought theyd scale like WQ rewards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_XOXO I actually like the other two, the first one is just so good it needs to be considered seperately. The others are just scifi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_XOXO Take a break after the first Matrix before you watch the other two. Also watch pandorum and six string samurai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How to brute force your way to big muscles and permanent muscle damage" starring That Muscular Guy in the Gym With Poor Form]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kids who live next door are running around in full holloween costumes. Children are fucking weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AzannaBanana "Wipe out christianity" jesus theyve gotten more tabloid since  i was a kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually cant believe one of the modules on my masters degree just spent 20mins explaining what a mole is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WormInANet thanks brah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WormInANet Do you remember the thing you taught me to remember the stages of mitosis in the institute? I need it because reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You need to attend 70% of your lectures or you will be unable to take the exam" Dear NUIG, please dont treat me like a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I respect the pointof a strike but this 'holding students to ransom' crap has to stop. Gl getting accomidation and now gl getting to college]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you can afford taxis because of course you cant youre students.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit buzz for 4th years, thats two weeks you cant get in to work on your final year project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im glad Im finished college because Id be so freaked at those strike days. Thered be literally no way to get to dcu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After like 2 months of grinding I finally get the last #Legion heirloom trinket the day before the expansion hits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also THIS GUY. I found a The Warriors referance. https://t.co/J125TMCYty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well at least Doomsday accurately represented Glasgow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celestalon Alternately make AS reduce cd, it flashes on procs but I still have to resist the urge to press it over judgement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celestalon Idea for protpal: Crusader's judgement talent also causes GC procs to reduce SotR cooldown. 1button charge gen doesnt feel great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tv show idea: The Truman Show except with Donald Trump as president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dw about people who talk behind your back, theyre behind you for a reason" Yeh the reason is you're facing a different direction you dope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't know what X is?" Thats not a question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landlords are scumbags, get back in contact with one guy and tells me the rent is gone up. €50 extra per month per person. Go fuck yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THERES A DOG ON MY TRAIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate how shitty landlord treat student, because they know they can replace you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres a murloc in the #warcraft movie!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>