<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA['ittle bus https://t.co/WANaZY33iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit by tiny paper bit. https://t.co/6KeFMVNnDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The joys of working from home, part 42: not having to be out in horizontal rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPER card HOT game SUPER by HOT @dungeoneering SUPER designer HOT @gamesbymanuel  SUPER 
https://t.co/PxKoSFSj6i HOT !!! SUPER...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This papercraft typewriter has a 1-star rating because people thought it was a real typewriter o_0
 https://t.co/rOEanHVVZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done with #GGJ17. Only slightly exhausted after keeping to sane hours.
We made a thing...… https://t.co/umqHb1swEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First few hours of #GGJ2017 done. An idea fleshed out by team Gambrinous. Building to begin in earnest tomorrow morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was thinking earlier it'd be funny if Meitu ended up being some facial recognition data mining thing. 
Reality is probably worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see my pixel^H^H^H^H^Hhouse from here! https://t.co/doykqmjFqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall even ignoring the fact I think HQ wasn't run :P. Political Operative is probably a better card for it, particularly for that deck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall forgot paid abilities costing clicks have to be treated as click actions, so definite window between install and use to pop JH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall btw I got that unregistered s&amp;w call so completely, terribly wrong. I feel unbearably ashamed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall ahhh, the GLORIOUS Breaking Astro Food Exchange!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenuinePanic is it the geek Rapture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to work after a month off. Now to remember how to do the 1s and 0s...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a fuzzy heron, holding a fuzzy MASSIVE RAT! https://t.co/ccnz5YFEbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Google, very much so. https://t.co/maz4TLOfP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my copy of the Offworld Collection. Read a piece on Netrunner and look who showed up @AlphaChar https://t.co/1dQdDJsZ1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By sounds of it, the kids nextdoor got a karaoke machine o_o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intrigued by this. Assuming a cheap maintaining strength breaker is a must have to make it work. https://t.co/Go8KKm8Muf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was about to go to sleep, but then became engrossed by a one and a half hour long video about making a sword. https://t.co/bxFIe7Zz6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall @AlphaChar @HynesSight_2020 1GAM is Tues 3rd, but sure can make it a Netrunner evening too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall @AlphaChar @HynesSight_2020 I... I don't understand. You can travel WITHOUT bringing decks with you?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Pewter_Games on releasing The Little Acre today on PS4, XBox and Steam. With score from @dungeoneering music man @SteveGregan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently time off means hibernating and reading til all hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking time off work until the new year.
Commence doing nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aidowall Hermetically sealed bubble. It's the only way to be sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of course I've left my filament out in the open, absorbing all the moisture. So I guess it'll blow up or something. Pretty sure that's right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sooo... 3d printing. How does that work again? It's been a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such grand plans to get things done today. 
Such plans...

Did nothing.
-_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't I have just stayed in bed where it's nice and warm and have just thought about writing code? 
Is the keyboard bit really needed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix is a terrible drug. I may have just binged all 7 seasons of Gilmore Girls in a very short period of time.
I need help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay, that one envelope from Revenue that I'll gladly open. The one with a load of money in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess if you are going to sit down on a chair, it helps to verify that the chair actually exists.

...ouch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhh! A narrative legacy-like expansion for Netrunner!
https://t.co/Or7hF00a54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a bit of debugging help https://t.co/A8U0uMDFug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAllThing don't forget the mac!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn it anxiety, you're making too many decisions lately. Stop it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished re-watching Freaks and Geeks, again, and now I'm sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaugustine thanks! @TheAllThing is very happy with the feedback on the design. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneHenriksen @dungeoneering It's up there now https://t.co/OMXoFZVxt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ice Cream Headaches, the new expansion for Guild of @dungeoneering, is now available on Steam!… https://t.co/urVFSj6uJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brain has decided to go on strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for a Headache, of the Ice Cream variety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need the extra time to pack the salt in. https://t.co/bAG4g8ac7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yay, a cold. Perfect accompaniment to dem deadline jitters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNoirin I think it may have actually throttled me down to 10% over the course of watching it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy is a terrible, terrible... terrible awful movie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is just full of "I'm an idiot" moments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlphaChar I'll just leave this here... https://t.co/CitBrUj2Om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To GDC or not to GDC?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalobrienz indeed. but still slightly demoralising seeing torrent links posted minutes after pushing an update]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always cool to see people on twitter saying they want to play your gam... oh, they just posted an image of themselves torrenting it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spent far too long wondering why a window wasn't showing up on screen.

My second screen was still off. -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep in the guts of my battle code. This is an ever so slightly convoluted place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tabletop version of Guild just wouldn't be the same without all those lovely tweens... unless...… https://t.co/xatqGVRUHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay candidates, buy my vote! https://t.co/FveoXfeRqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gamesbymanuel the struggle is real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arduous days work today... we're playing board games all day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ApplicationVerificationFailed
ApplicationVerificationFailed
ApplicationVerificationFailed
ApplicationVerificationFailed
ApplicationVerificat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jen_Carey_ but when was the last time you make a clay tin whistle?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jen_Carey_ You should be ashamed of yourself Jen, you've descended to a new low!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit o deforming, a bit o panning. https://t.co/mDQehGicgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@df3n5 I don't think I know what it is either! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All fixed now. Correctly updating the single mesh. https://t.co/U7UMqaGULY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refactored to a single deforming mesh, rather than individual cubes. A few issues to work out... https://t.co/aLka5J7mTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erbridge my Sunny deck might actually be viable if it was being bankrolled by a rich Sponsor Corp! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erbridge janky as fuck, but still want to try it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reading rules on The Big Sell-Out, team based Netrunner variant. I want to play this! 
https://t.co/7vklTKf7b1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent weekend writing C#? Guess I'll spend monday morning trying to remember AS3 syntax!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@df3n5 only the best for such luxury!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There might be a future in this board game thing after all. https://t.co/mOBjnvPSvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The things you fund clearing out rubbish from the attic. https://t.co/ITnx3AdDG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jen_Carey_ can't say 'Thank you' to drivers as you get off Luas, so they're clearly The Others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a look at Duelyst.... because peer pressure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gambrinous @Lpollet specifically
/data/user/0/air.com.gambrinous.guildofdungeoneering/com.gambrinous.guildofdungeoneering/Local Store]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gambrinous @Lpollet so it typically requires root as it's in /data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticky cards are sticky #sweatrunner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chocolate for breakfast may not have been a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papierzeit yeah it's unfortunately an issue of RAM usage atm. Similar on other 1GB devices. I'm continuing to try and get it running better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papierzeit meaning it was likely a memory issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papierzeit it no longer crashes after disabling it? Based on info on the options there it would seem to be an older device?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrating PCs is such a paaaaiiiin! Particularly when there's no room for the old drive in new case. https://t.co/h6KvgEDTHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@braincutlery @Dungeoneering If you complete a Jungle quest/rematch, collecting the Pirate Map from the first hand, it'll unlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PCBushi @dungeoneering If you complete a Jungle rematch, collecting the Pirate Map from the first hand, it'll unlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idlebirch there's an assumed understanding of concepts not fully explained.. a.k.a. it was written by engineers! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I read of this documentation the less I think I understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonTerp Unity. just a bunch of deformed cubes atm. will eventually make it a single mesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prospecting with your head https://t.co/bgTdeK2XAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 3rd dimension is a troublesome beast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[vertex debugging... because I just HAD to go and reinvent the wheel! https://t.co/yaRd6PQGNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a few months, so time to play the "how do I do the most basic of shit in Unity" game again. https://t.co/pkqeXxTYQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed Stage of Development: Indie City Edition on @Kickstarter https://t.co/86kFDbRV8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed Iliad: Heroes of Troy, A clever card game for 2-4 players! on @Kickstarter https://t.co/uoiXNsIT6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a few days off and do absolutely feck all. Pretty sure that's how it's supposed to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've made a terrible, terrible Anarch deck that is going to utterly fail at least 95% of the the time. But, oh, that 5% will be glorious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gambrinous Is the baby tweeting already?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batteries draining.
Send power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New occupation: Vortex Cube farmer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneaky dreams, changing the meaning of alarms.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>