<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Northern Irish woman was reported to police by GP over abortion pills https://t.co/5zwpOMjJYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EleanorHooker_ @jackiepoetry @RuthMcKee @lisaunderneath @MadeleineDL @maddsnacks Thanks Eleanor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RositaBoland I got your gorgeous present this morning, it's amazing, I love it! I thought it was a bar of chocolate at first. Such a heart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This picture is so stark and so grim, living in tents, taken by @FrankieGaffney on his travels. #homelessness… https://t.co/XTH0ClD5Xk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RositaBoland I'm onto the mail! The phone is nearly always under a pillow somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Goslin Stores, a hardware shop in Cabra, D7. Very canny and totally hilarious! #DonaldTrump #TRUMPWALL https://t.co/7G2BpUnM4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @DanniLmc really looking forward to seeing you and hearing your fantabulous #wisewords @stingingfly workshop this Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an amazing rendition of 'The Sound of Silence', when music sends shivers to marrowbone. Gorgeous by @Disturbed: https://t.co/pnZKI2wB0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinDoyleIT @IRLPatricia It just reads like a really silly mast-head because of the stupid word 'Bejaysus', very Northern Irish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IRLPatricia @MartinDoyleIT I think the Martin Lynch mast-head is even funnier. #bejaysus Parochial reporting right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryodonnell03 @BBCTheArchers I'm afraid it's @henrymcdonald who is the diehard Archers fan...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone out there is writing a Catcher in the Rye, aren't they? Catcher in the Tangerine or some small change to the title and *bang* we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War of words as library books contracts go outside Ireland @stingingfly @irishwritersctr @wordsireland https://t.co/n9LapWBNSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wallets by @colinbarrett82 https://t.co/VEdtCqZKA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved #agirlwalkshomealoneatnight too, extraordinary film,an all-time fave. Swedish original of 'Let The Right On… https://t.co/VD9q12LTkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doreen2cv Couldn't agree more re: New @NewIslandBooks and congrats too on your own book success, keep hearing about it at every turn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emmaleene1 @Independent_ie Thanks! How goes it with the new baba?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another mention in Indo today too: https://t.co/5PWlJOzalT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcmonaglewriter Thanks Alan. Looking forward to your gorgeous novel in March. More mentions in Indo today too: https://t.co/5PWlJOzalT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to look out for in 2017 from independent publishers - ROOM LITTLE DARKER is the title of my collection! https://t.co/CIxAseSDlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@griffski We sucked on these segments down laneways and smoked in on top of them using cans of Lilt to rinse it all down. Oh the nostalgia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@griffski I can feel the clog of that chocolate behind my two front teeth, the *lie* that is the velvet, then you bite into a mucky barnyard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinedelw I'll reply to your email tomorrow Mrs! Too much to tell you so I put it off. You'll enjoy my bullet points. Trust me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submissions open for sixteen magazine now! The theme is black. See https://t.co/U9NQdo7tIA  for submission details. #writing #writingsubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo @KtyB Look what I found! You &amp; Mosina in @CobblestoneDub and me and Mosina. Oh but for the passing of time...the… https://t.co/JNvl3YT7jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Joyce book's centenary marked with map project by @henrymcdonald https://t.co/C4SLcnsUFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philip_malley Happy Christmas to you too Philip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has nuclear war already happened and I slept it out? Or is this what they eat in those places that voted for Trump?… https://t.co/gqyHSqsgo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still miss Frankie Lane's gigs @CobblestoneDub with @KtyB [aka The Wet Witch!] Here's Oh Holy Night on Pedal Steel! https://t.co/yA4dVowMTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from a pagan place by Kevin Barry https://t.co/VxA4rouRui via @IrishTimesBooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorra love Jim Sheridan unashamedly demanding change to help homeless, very emotional/honest/simple. https://t.co/TXW4NvX4bF via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The life expectancy for a homeless woman in Ireland is 38, roughly the same age as during the famine period of 1847.
https://t.co/QfLMV1chcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarionDowling Mazzy Star: Fade Into You. My abiding memory of our flat on White Hart Lane. That and tuna &amp; pasta bake. Plus a ton of hash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarionDowling What tune do you remember most from Tottenham campus when we woz topless? Aside from 4nonblondes etc. https://t.co/31yRi0OyU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be chairing a publishing panel @HotelDoolin (2017) writers weekend with Anna Kelly @IvanMulcahy… https://t.co/hqsufmmfW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sing The City by The King Mob [aka @kmobsters + @kparkspoet], poetry &amp; music, great stuff. #bigfan https://t.co/ewgb4MOAiN via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinihaneDonal: you need to accept the fact RIGHT NOW that you'll still be in the bar at 4am sucking on rashers with red eyes the next day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doolin Writers Weekend is 5 yrs old! Looking forward to sheep hills, filthy fudge, fresh air, craft beer, laughing… https://t.co/cLO5Xyow8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting TED talk with @FrankieGaffney about the 'apologetic apostrophe' in modern phonetic fiction + more. https://t.co/gJTVdyUxc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Age of Bowie: How David Bowie Made a World of Difference by Paul Morley – review https://t.co/12KwTUPrw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadgleeson on burning her leg on a super ser while dancing to Ska and other memories of Top of the Pops: https://t.co/SpsiDMthMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange thing to do, count cranes. What is it supposed to signify? Maybe derelict buildings in the city would give… https://t.co/8yYHpmDBnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet this makes the prison service feel all hipster and trendy. https://t.co/5Ql9jauLUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way @somulligan! https://t.co/NkhB1TKEHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beingvarious reads her story from #TheGlassShore @thepooluk: a Belfast student who buys abortion pills online https://t.co/pcVdGnJK9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OranRyan @IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly Aww you too bud. LOVED your crazyass tale and so good to see you thriving again. Take it handy. J x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nessao Lovely to see [and hear] you last night Nessa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this story by @OranRyan Joe the Aquanaut &amp; the Aftermath Blue: complex &amp; clever, funny &amp; weird F&amp;F issue @stingingfly @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly @OranRyan You are guilty too. You really are. Many witnesses here. The wine is bleedin' delicious though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Story of Joe: an every day psychotic drug-addicted astronaut who dreams of the world's end. Poem by @OranRyan @stingingfly @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone was popping wine corks in an unorthodox manner #loudly here @stingingfly Fear &amp; Fantasy launch… https://t.co/tb7ZYJZrqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nessao up next @stingingfly Fear &amp; Fantasy launch: Roger Casement, sexuality, fear in such an indefinably rich way @IrishWritersCtr #poetry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stingingfly @VinoBono It's really good wine too, deep berryish and delicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jroisinodonnell @IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly Yeah, wolves do that. I've met a few meself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anne Griffin: The Boy Who Left; a tender &amp; erotic story according to #miagallagher Launch of F&amp;F issue here @IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning reading of Real Boys by Clara Kumagai (great hair too, it's OK to say that?). Evan Costigan up now @stingingfly @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly I *loved* your story @jroisinodonnell, very primal/weird. It's rare I feel jealous of someone's writing #rocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never been to a launch before where even the vino labels matched the journal cover @IrishWritersCtr @stingingfly… https://t.co/nNHy4kkTvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full house @IrishWritersCtr for @stingingfly F&amp;F issue, the spare deckchairs had to come out. Before I was a donkey… https://t.co/4BnUIuYedV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here @IrishWritersCtr for @stingingfly Fear &amp; Fantasy issue: Mia Gallagher in a gorgeous vampire coat, red wine, some fine words on the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkish feasts at Ozy's https://t.co/wH5Twv2u3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish abortion ban case taken to UN Human Rights Committee https://t.co/rJLG1dFcAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Bush: ‘I was beginning to think I’d never play again’ https://t.co/3SU7a9Agie via @IrishTimesCultr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw sweet. This one's for The Boss: https://t.co/IVR7mZuPAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No one outside Ireland could believe (or does when I mention it) what things are like for female writers here.” https://t.co/6MmnZwpFcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last show for the 1916 Eastrogen Rising takes place 3rd December in Annesley House, North Strand, tickets at door!… https://t.co/CIBWvrRuD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Score! I mooch into the @IrishWritersCtr do to a bit of work and catch a slab of birthday cake as it's Bernie's [th… https://t.co/qP2y294Bxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven Irish writers on longlist for world’s richest literary prize https://t.co/NKzEvW63UW via @IrishTimesBooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screenplays are so technical you shouldn't try to 'work out' the story in a script, do it in prose first. #mindshift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should not be writing for yourself, you're writing for an audience, put them first. Write stories that matter, not just 4 entertainment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone makes you an offer which is more than what you imagined, count to 5 and say 'I really was hoping for more than that!' #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Floor figure is 20K, ceiling is around three times that, though writers guilds think it should be 2% flat even if film goes on to make 2m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being prepared to say 'no' is a very powerful position as a negotiator, if a producer cannot give you a figure, don't take them seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your script is optioned don't get bogged down in the minutiae, if it doesn't succeed, you get rights back. #mindshift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We teach the wrong people wrong things in the wrong ways, don't bother with Uni courses, get job in the industry. #julienfriedman #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People with creative dominant right brains cannot pull apart structure well, left brains can. You need both to be a scriptwriter. #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phenylethylamine (PEA) is released in the body when you watch a good film, same as during sex. #strangeinfo #mindshift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four quadrons: young/old/male/female - your script has to appeal to all four, this is what you have to 'prove' to investors. #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a much more competitive industry than say, writing novels. Costs a lot more. Why do more men succeed in this genre? #mindshift #agent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read two scripts a week and at least 100 in total before you ever try to be a scriptwriter @IrishWritersCtr #julienfriedman #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screenplays are a very specific way of writing, far too much emphasis on formatting and less on how to tell a good story. #julienfriendman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens if the publisher retains film rights to your fictional work? Julien Friedman suggests writers try to keep those rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not enough women are applying for grants and loans to write feature films [in UK] therefore even fewer are making progress. #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London-based agent Julian Friedmann next up here @IrishWritersCtr #mindshift (He's Joe O'Connor's agent). Talking novels to screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never be put off approaching people/family/source material even if you don't have dosh, people appreciate their story being told #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juanita Wilson, author of Winter's Bone giving a fascinating talk here @IrishWritersCtr #mindshift on adapting a story for screen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action is really important, but emotional truth is what you buy into when it comes to adapting story for screen #mindshift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel strongly about the story 'events' will help you work through it, but the emotional logic is just as important #mindshift #screen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within material you'll find structures/sequences that fall naturally into order, opposite to how it's taught. #mindshift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difficult part is getting from that awful first unwieldy document (180 page) to whittle down to screenplay with good pacing. #Mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never fully describe while writing for screen like you can with fiction. Plot is very important, enough action to pull you through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certain things lend themselves to screen better than others, adaptations in segments of 30mins/60/30. Points of change, moments of shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's about funding and hidden biases, how things are judged &amp; what stories are deemed important and marketable. #MindShift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battling unconscious bias (Dr. Susan Liddy) Patronised, overly anaysed, a sense of dismissiveness of women's stories. #MindShift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 13% women of Irish or Irish-based writers attached to 'produced live action' indigenous feature films between 1993-2003. #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Susan Liddy up next here at #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender has always been an issue for me, how I programme @IrishWritersCtr says @bielva, there is a serious need for set policies. #mindshift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every woman who wants to write (film/tv) should be able to write what they want to write but what makes it 'commercially viable'? #MindShift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...considered important. It's about ten times 'harder' for women and the stats confirm this. #MindShift @IrishWritersCtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marian Quinn started off in acting, got frustrated, started to write, made a short film (32A). A film about 4 X 13 yr old girls wasn't...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>