<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pres.Trump's Executive Order on the Muslim Ban might have been that one 'step too far'. #MuslimBan https://t.co/ByUWGmPlsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS position and standing was in decline, these exec orders will revive its broader appeal and facilitate recruitm… https://t.co/Vg1O4VF4U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @SharonBell_NZ @pmbillenglish It will definitely increase anti US sentiment and increase the risk of 'G on B' attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @SharonBell_NZ @pmbillenglish Sooner than we think, especially when China is thrown into the equation .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharonBell_NZ @pmbillenglish This is where NZ has to walk a fine line of upholding ethical concerns whilst mtg alliance obligations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no honour in this!! https://t.co/MgvmFWguws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aganakteo @zealandia @AnnaPowles  and I spent the whole day walking the trails. Loved it. The takahe was my favourite bird though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategika Group Associate Dr Tess Newton Cain speaks on growing  Chinese engagement in the Pacific. 
https://t.co/39OaYWmRak via @abcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @AnnaPowles appointed 2017 New Zealand Centre Fellow at Peking University, Beijing, focusing on Pacific geopolitics &amp; China]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timor Leste  dumps spying case against Australia for 'good faith' oil, gas boundary talks https://t.co/4l7qaIq2l0 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremy_maxie @AnnaPowles great to have someone with your experience as part of the Strategika group Asia Pacific team. WDW!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to announce the launch of Strategika Group Asia Pacific.Thanks to everyone involved! Twitter page to follow! https://t.co/yQ8IEML9MG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia-Pacific Parliamentary Forum opens in Fiji co-chaired by Fiji and Indonesia. https://t.co/lyEQqVlYO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muzzling the 4th estate is a threat to freedom of speech "Trump Admin May Evict the Press from White House" https://t.co/VXuvO8biZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AWHape I know nothing!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took this photo a few months ago but it seems very apt now. 
"Inauguration day merchandise!!! 
Two for the price… https://t.co/sTDt4ADfEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprises here either. What message does this send to America's traditional allies? https://t.co/TN02ZbJfLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This should come as no surprise as #Taiwan  is a "core interest" to #China. @AnnaPowles #TRUMP https://t.co/zitSClO38d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia's attempts at buying support from the Pacific region seem to have limited to no impact on Melanesia's sta… https://t.co/9JA5dJanFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#China calls for a new model of IR and asserts its stance and military presence in the #AsiaPacific. @AnnaPowles  https://t.co/hAThCpTETq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @asianewzealand delegation meeting with Ambassador Cristiano da Costa, at the Timorese Embassy, Wellington. https://t.co/Day5R9BOlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrated war reporter Clare Hollingworth dies aged 105. 
One of the true journalistic icons of our century. 

https://t.co/T5t0ynF40R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Timor might reciprocate by dropping its the case in the ICJ against Australia for spying on its council of ministe… https://t.co/eR93oF3Fou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Widodo and the head of the military Gen. Gatot vie for power in Indonesia. The rise of Gatot could be des… https://t.co/VWhONLKtAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China’s aircraft carrier ‘will push range far into Pacific’ | South China Morning Post https://t.co/hqOQSkpwIi via @SCMP_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fort Lauderdale airport shooting leaves multiple people dead https://t.co/2aP1caPA1l via @cbsnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump 's transition team issued a recall to politically appointed Ambassadors to return to the US by inauguration

 https://t.co/kG43Pgtl2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia  offers to help Philippines to combat terrorism as its warship visits the island archipelago :https://t.co/WRjlrsdGWh via @ABSCBNNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaPowles @nzherald I was once told that I was a mochacino and should not be too close to a white family as they were pure milk.  It hurt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia suspends military cooperation. Kopassus offended by training material criticising the invasion of Timor. https://t.co/WaB3pNMIW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 first terrorist attack! 
'At least 35 killed and  40 wounded ' in shooting at Istanbul' s #Reinanightclub  https://t.co/gpJWok4IMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reported 35 dead and several wounded in an attack on the #Reinanightclub  in Istambul, Turkey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarimAICHE and a very happy new year to you and your family my friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Bans Its Ivory Trade, Moving Against Elephant Poaching https://t.co/Ju4ZWkpgW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Isreal continues to lash out at Sec Council countries for passing resolution. US explains the reasoning behind t… https://t.co/YqjFcVqU1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama moves to split cyberwarfare command from the NSA https://t.co/iZIcRcMjNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MhdKatoub @ajamazing thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Australian police moved on Christmas terror suspects in Melbourne. https://t.co/LDhFpSqJ6v via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MhdKatoub @ajamazing Care to elaborate? Staff involved in what capacity exactly? Where? How many?  Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SolomonIslands  Permanent Secretary of Police, Edmond Sikua has been arrested &amp; charged with corruption.
https://t.co/FUfYhz6vN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaPowles If the beginning of anti corruption arrests, it will show effectiveness of RAMSI's rebuilding of RSIPF &amp; its depoliticisation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kailekke If the beginning of anti corruption arrests, it will show effectiveness of RAMSI's rebuilding of RSIPF &amp; its depoliticisation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SolomonIslands  Permanent Secretary of Police, Natl Security &amp; Corr. Services ,  Edmond Sikua has been arrested &amp;… https://t.co/GpwDjZq7Ah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the presence of several of the diplomatic core one would expect Turkish police to assign a security detail. 
Q… https://t.co/DlZRzlIrfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #assassination  of the Russian Ambassador, will have serious ramifications on the Turkey-Russia relationship. R… https://t.co/huAphZfvm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TimorLeste   election dates have been announced: Presidential on 20th March 2017, Parliamentary on July 8th, 2017.
#timor @AnnaPowles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People’s Liberation Army Navy Training Ship the Zhenghe arrives in Fiji (via @fijivillage) https://t.co/4xFJBZjfsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaADQJB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7.8 quake hits the Solomon Islands. South Pacific on tsunami alert @CNNI https://t.co/QMm5p0HM8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A surge in tribal fighting in PNG's Hela province, raises questions over police conduct &amp; control @AnnaPowles  https://t.co/sZSMt8UYX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaADQJB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaPowles speaking on the Pacific in the 'Hotspots'  panel this afternoon at the Global Future Conference . Very… https://t.co/nHUrNbVcuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China becomes Fiji's biggest source of foreign investment. 
Chinese are nearly half of Fiji's investors @AnnaPowles  https://t.co/cvhPI2BLky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaPowles will be speaking on the Pacific in the 'Hotspots'  panel this afternoon at 3 pm at the Global Future Co… https://t.co/fTI7shmSOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Situation tense in PNG's Hela after convoy attack and allegation of police reprisal. https://t.co/GAQMR1szXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 70 percent of women sexualy or physically abused in Tonga: Survey https://t.co/Ci9DUWI8pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PNG police accused of vicious reprisal on village after ambush on MP's convoy @AnnaPowles  https://t.co/lRf0fxz1jy
 https://t.co/lRf0fxz1jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Samoa police academy delayed in order to select more students. https://t.co/s9wjDpA1aO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CleoPaskal @batchelorshow @GordonGChang @thedailybeast Happy to share sources so we can get a clearer picture of whats going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CleoPaskal @batchelorshow @GordonGChang @thedailybeast Look forward to meeting you tomorrow at the conference. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CleoPaskal @batchelorshow @GordonGChang @thedailybeast Happy to share sources so we can get a clearer picture of whats going on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@batchelorshow @GordonGChang @thedailybeast @CleoPaskal Good to have  issue highlighted but deeper,  accurate analysis needed. Cheers mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An internship programme has been launched in New Zealand to get more Pasifika people working in the public sector. 
 https://t.co/84H3MWb35q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The list of inaccuracies in this story is so long,  I don't know where to start. https://t.co/8dqvADIjSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@batchelorshow @GordonGChang @thedailybeast @CleoPaskal  The list of inaccuracies in this story is so long,  I don't know where to start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaADQJB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Momentous occasion! Int'l Naval Task Group leaving Wellington after assisting quake hit Kaikoura. Ships from Aus,NZ… https://t.co/2JxWmP492Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Participating in the Pacific Parliamentary Forum being held in New Zealand Parliament as Guest speaker on security… https://t.co/6thIQ8lLKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Participating in the Pacific Parliamentary Forum being held in New Zealand Parliament as Guest speaker on security… https://t.co/OWANGTLRMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/kfbaAE8kZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musical chairs being played in the Samoan police force as acting police commissioner is suspended.
https://t.co/op87kyBvXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Navy and NZ Navy in joint rescue operations post Kaikoura earthquake.
@AnnaPowles  @CDF_NZ https://t.co/21A6Yv7huR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MahirZeynalov 
Teaching young Turks the ability to question and challenge the government line is now a crime.
One more nail in the coffin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now for some good news!
Stranded quake cows rescued | NZNews | Newshub https://t.co/0FRT8epj0I]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>