<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This! https://t.co/2VBLipN0Tj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_maleficentt @thehill Ugh, really? I'm so disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alex_simmo He is improving things - I don’t have to like him though. I'll always support the players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel so bad for #BurkinaFaso. They didn't deserve to go out #AFCON2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cosy friendship that Theresa May is trying to build with Donald Trump will be her downfall. It smacks of desperation #StateVisit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila Good for Obama, he shouldn't stay silent. Nobody should]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goals goals goals! This is what I've been waiting to see from us. #MUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice one Smalling!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh! I'm gutted for Nadal #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It amuses me that the commentators can't hide their love for Federer #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karenknowsbest It's so compelling! Nadal is never down and out though so I'm hoping......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Nadal really going to lose this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening Come on Nadal!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes to this! https://t.co/Szm2CUOuh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only positive thing to come out of all of this is that people are waking up. It'll be a tough battle, but he wo… https://t.co/SMohXgz3tr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about Theresa May? The woman has no backbone. https://t.co/PKZ6BL3hsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer has always been the media darling, but I've always prefered Nadal. I hape he finds his A game againn #FedererNadal #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans have found thei voices! Donald Trump, you're in for a bumpy ride #TrumpProtest #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wossy's Arts Show on #BBCRadio2 is just the tonic I need, with all the madness that's going on in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found out that Liverpool were knocked out of the #FACup. Thank you for making my day #WolvesFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who heard Theresa May's speech on the steps of Downing Street when she became leader, remember this - Actions speak louder than words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ed_Miliband We've missed you Ed. We need a rational voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is one sick man. All those who said "wait and see", have you seen enough? #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to see Marion Bartoli looking well again #EurosportTennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karenknowsbest She is, she's been brilliant this year but Serena will always be in her way. I love how gracious she is. I love both of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that fact that these guys are doing so well. These are the true greats! #AusOpen https://t.co/UU92sx8VNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow I'll be rooting for Rafa Nadal. Bring it on! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a champion Serena Williams is 23 Grand Slam titles. Absolutely brilliant!! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karenknowsbest I wanted it too and I'll think there will be even more for her. I wonder if Venus will have another chance though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I love Serena and I'm happy for her, I really feel for Venus and hope she has another chance. #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no, John Hurt has gone! He was such a wonderful actor - good in everything he was in. #RipJohnHurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These commentators still doubt the competitiveness of Serena &amp; Venus against each other. Do they want blood? #AusOpen #EurosportTENNIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus and Serena making history #BlackGirlMagic #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you! https://t.co/t86KRum4BQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see #T2Trainspotting. Also, It's good to see Izzy Bizu and her crew on #GrahamNorton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotMyPrimeMinister chose Laura Kuenssberg because she works for @BBCNews and immediately regretted it. 😂 #TrumpMay https://t.co/8iei4RZTW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first (and probaly only) time I'll ever be proud of Laura Kuenssberg. Great question! #TrumpMay https://t.co/pp04S5b5CP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila @TheView Wow, what you said made me feel queesy. We all know what Trump is. #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCLondonNews, your attempts to normalise Donald Trump by interviewing one off his (few) black supporters won't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each day I go off Sadiq Khan more and more. London is already one of the most expensive cities in the world, a #TouristTax would be stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is not normal times" Finally someone is saying it. Donald Trump is dangerous. If we support him, it makes us… https://t.co/6vtojwqU81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurasenior24 @maisie_nannie @OtiMabuse @dannymaconline They're amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm remembering why I stopped watching #bbcqt #SwitchesOffTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diane Abbott puts up with so much abuse from everyone. It seems that if people bully her it's okay. It's sickening #BBCQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May is a sycophant #NotMyPrimeMinister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Candice is pregnant #chewinggum2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stop crying rewatching Venus Williams celebrating. She's amazing! #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So wait, @SkyUK is going to get rid of @EurosportUKTV and @DiscoveryUK, but I'll have to pay the same amount? I don't think so @SkyHelpTeam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BlackGirlMagic Need I say more? #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!!!! A Williams will win the #AustralianOpen. They are tremendous! https://t.co/waDyfJU2um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised this is the same woman who made Boris Johnson Foreign Secretary. She's no better #TheresaMay https://t.co/VCwPs13ARa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good, and so he should #TRUMPWALL #DonaldTrump https://t.co/rVhDAX6vwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an easy win fo Serena Williams! That's how champs do it #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackscht @Channel4News Some, not all and that's my point. Many white women voted for Trump, but most black women didn't. Reflect that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some are but if you watch @Channel4News you'd think they all were or that a majority were. It's an attempt to norma… https://t.co/rjRasJKDvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see you @Channel4News. Stop going for ratings and show #DonaldTrump supporters for who they are. Most of them aren't black. 😡 #C4News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It irks me that @Channe4News insist on interviewing black supporters of #DonaldTrump, when only a minority of them voted for him #C4News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The writers and producers of #HolbyCity can teach other shows about diversity and representation. They do it so well. @BBCHolbyCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This! #Article50 https://t.co/Nv2gJuyrar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about Ewan McGregor's tweet was the fact that he didn't know Piers Morgan was one of the hosts of #GMB. I bet that hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what he said because I've blocked him. #T2trainspotting will be a massive hit anyway - I can't wait to… https://t.co/T47RWpjR2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Venus Williams is through to the semis and she looks super fit. I'm so happy for her 😊#AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#proudtobeawoman https://t.co/kCtN16FZEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching the news and It feels like an alternate universe - #TheresaMay,  #BorisJohnson, #DonaldTrump. God help us all @Channel4News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is this awful Dance Dance Dance programme on ITV? I seriously don't get it. Time for a DVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I put myself through that? If only I'd known 😒#AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, so there are ten minutes to go and Murray is down two sets to one. I'm guessing he lost 😒  #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will hate this. I'm surprised he wasn't on the toilet at 3am tweeting about it as usual https://t.co/VpLUez5nCv #snl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching the highlights of Andy Murray's match. What happened to his first serve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry Andy, I really need to go to bed #GoodLuck #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Now I can go to bed. Well done @venuswilliams #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should be in bed, but I really want  Venus Willliams to win this. #AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connie is horrible! #Casualty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I don't like Trump, you can't vote for someone simply because she's female. I'd never have voted for Mag… https://t.co/VvaJXOLDTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, I loved that song by Ed Sheeran #GrahamNorton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm enjoying Matthew Mcconaughey on #GrahamNorton. One of my favourite actors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My twitter feed is hilarious tonight #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've done everything I can to avoid it, but I could do with a laugh! https://t.co/1caCxMJKWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in total awe of the fearlessness of Michaela Coel. I'm still recovering 😂 #ChewingGum2 @E4Tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a strike #Senegal #AFCON2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is going on with the television news media at the moment? They're really pushing the anti immigration rhetoric. #BBCNews #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Assange said he'd hand himself in if Obama granted clemcy to Chelsea Manning. Does anyone really think that'll happen?...Me either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Theresa May drone on about a "deal for Britain" is incredibly irritating. What a mess #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Clemency The final acts of an outgoing President. Barack Obama knows how to outtrump #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama did the right thing #ChelseaManning https://t.co/T8hZextV0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter will eventually destroy him #Trump https://t.co/6gKtXG5YqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I look like that at 58, I'll be more than happy! https://t.co/eZ4txdt9aC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satirists are going to have a field day for the next four years. Trump and his cronies aren't the most articulate. https://t.co/trxSTg4SRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Putin has his foot on Trump's neck" ~ Paul Auster #C4News @Channel4News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's interesting listening to Paul Auster talking about #DonaldTrump and freedom of expression #C4News @Channel4News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans need to stop clutching. Who cares if #MLK's niece voted for Trump? It doesn't change who he is or what he stands for. #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when this man made President Obama show his birth certificate? Not to mention wanting to ban muslims and k… https://t.co/LRiAHBEQ5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this | Viola Davis and Tom Hanks discussing their craft. https://t.co/iaebnwwF3U  #ActorsOnActors https://t.co/iaebnwwF3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool fans jumping in my mentions make me laugh!! 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm, I knew nothing about the Casey Affleck allegations 😒https://t.co/wyPGzxqwLQ utm_medium=sharefromsite&amp;utm_source=The_Root_twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, we really should have beaten Liverpool #MOTD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was my favourite question of the night. I feel privileged to have been there. @BFI #FencesMovie #ViolaDavis https://t.co/IjNLLK08Xs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sums up my feelings #MUFC https://t.co/eTh50ZL2rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on my way home after watching #FencesMovie followed by a Q&amp;A with Viola Davis. She is truly is magnificent! #BFISouthbank @BFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really looking forward to @violadavis movie and live Q&amp;A at the BFI Southbank today. Sickness won't keep me away #FencesMovie]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>