<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Survived day one alright, but that could be because the house is full of visitors till after the weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So today I start a period of being a stay at home dad - I'll try and make updates to document my journey into madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like the #trump administration should come with a disclaimer  "The views expressed here do not reflect the views of normal Americans"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLamentB I'm undecided if it's better or worse that those shirts don't have 'Pearl Jam' on them anywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLamentB Shit! I was wearing mine yesterday while painting a wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifth_Opinion Mike Mills is a damn hero you fool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PearlJam @MikeMcCreadyPJ Looks to me like someone needs to head to NZ a little more often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skitchP @chris_mecca @markieburnhope I have no idea what's going on right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meant to be in middle of a #WeatherBomb - strange l can't tell much difference between this and weather we've been having all summer so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all this talk about #ChelseaManning can we please not forget to acknowledge that today is #BettyWhiteBDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewarehouse Your staff in Tauranga might need training on putting disks in cases. Home from holiday to find I bought 2 empty blu-ray cases]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBHiFiNZ how do I go about finding out if an @onkyo reciever I bought from you is covered by the company's Customer Care Program?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalpenn Batman Returns is a great Christmas movie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty excited to see @wolfmother will be supporting @gunsnroses for their New Zealand shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bierman_rob Aren't you a little short to be a Stormtrooper?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it turns out that I'm the parent of that 1 year old kid who beats up the other kids at church. I'm now 'that guy']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifth_Opinion I was expecting Adam Sandler, Tommy Cruiser, and  Philip Seymour Hoffman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how my daughter will now bring the cat an offering of a toy, and when the cat doesn't accept the toy my daughter whacks her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellPirkle @YoSounie @chuckpalahniuk Not sure I really care who that is either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eqnz You're 'wife' alert seems to not be working. She let me sleep through last nights jolt, I heard it was a good one too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreamBabySafety Thanks for giving me the means to cage up my little one. Now she has her own area of destruction https://t.co/JTxwnJ23YQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Tamaki could learn a thing or two from The Rock church - this is how you address the recent earthquakes which… https://t.co/EcfQuqHnGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone bought my daughter a pop-up picture book for her birthday and she's absolutely loosing her mind over it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rescued a bird that flew into one of our windows from our cat and dog. Took a while, but the bird has flown off now
Feeling pretty good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the Seventh Circuit just denied Brendan Dassey's release pending appeal outcome. Will they never let this kid get to #WrestleMania?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david75donovan Bet they were playing Scotland the Brave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david75donovan I thought it was wildly known that 'a galaxy far far away' was in fact The Highlands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Brian Tamaki is getting himself in the news again by being the most unchristian of Christian leaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yesterday houses were wrecked due to the shaking, today can't see neighbours place due to mist. Is there about to be a big rebuild reveal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh how I had missed you aftershocks #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @MightyApe for super quick delivery once again and great service!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EataylorTweets She's way past hinting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess this is pretty much like fighters touching gloves before a match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each morning my dog and cat have a ritual of touching noses before going off and being mortal enemies for the rest of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halloween-that one time of year where kids go and ask neighbours they've never talked to for stuff before ignoring them for rest of the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the past week whenever I get home from work my 11 month old gets all excited,holds her arms up to me and yells 'Dadda!' - melts my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NightTerrorsApp Will this be getting a full IOS release before there's anything for android?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife was talking with me the other day about how men are losing their identity - I know she was secretly telling me to start a fight club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreamBabySafety Your team has gone well above and beyond for me. 
Honestly the best customer service I have ever received.
Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catswithbats Although not something I'd personally wear - I'm thinking there's something I'm missing. What's wrong with it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreamBabySafety Done! Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreamBabySafety Loving how your MAYFAIR CONVERTA 3-IN-1 PLAY-PEN GATE says that extensions are available on the box, but no one stocks them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many people turn up to the emergency room cause their toddler has taken them out. Thinking it's only time before that's me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I know how god felt when he put Adam and Eve in the garden of Eden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give my daughter free reign of the lounge - except one area. That's the only place she now wants to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish my wife an I had that relationship where 'Dibs not!' still meant something and that I didn't have to fix everything around the house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random gym question/observation:
Does a bicep curl count if you don't look lovingly at your bicep whilst doing it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NightTerrorsApp Android release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I felt a disturbance in the Force, as if millions of ppl suddenly hopped on Gareth Edwards' nuts, and were gushing like children. 
#RogueOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successfully managed to pull apart and fix my sons' x-box after my 10 month old got her hands on it. I'm gonna take that as a win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter was given free reign of the living room last night while dinner was being prepared. Anyone know how to fix an x-box and stereo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I emailed back reiterating that I didn't want the money and tried to engage him in a conversation about greed. He stopped Emailing me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Emailed beck Mr Johnson Abu - telling him I had no need for his $6 million. He replied asking for my bank account details immediately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the time I was all 'Whoa - who is it???' But now I've realised I don't really care who's on Lucille's receiving end
#TheWalkingDead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLamentB Stay safe buddy! Hope this doesn't end up being as bad as is currently forecast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLamentB Are you getting out of town bud, or are you going to ride it out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifth_Opinion Did you see that there's a remake coming out next year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds You have very long fingers sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wife: Can you read our daughter a book
Me: You want a balloon?  We all float down here
Wife: What are you reading her?
Me: Some clown story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternclarke I love how the first comment on that picture is the obligatory 'return to argentina please']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateDiaz209 are you worried that some of the shine will be taken off your rematch when @Ealvarezfight finishes @TheNotoriousMMA  at #UFC205]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having watched @TaikaWaititi shut down @StephenPitalo complaining about the dumbest of issues was a beautiful thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shihad_Band what are the odds of you guys doing a Welly show outside of Homegrown next year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaikaWaititi Finally got my hands on a copy of Hunt for the Wilderpeople - what an amazing film with so many great moments!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Link on article I'm reading '29 movie mistakes we'll never forgive', has a picture of Forrest Gump. But I'll forgive that simpleton anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out Rock, Paper, scissors isn't an appropriate way of making business decisions in our office...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomsdayDevice You misspelt Dave Matthews Band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My girl can now stand in her cot and reach the baby monitor - putting her to bed is like watching a cute version of The Blair Witch Project]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifth_Opinion Mel is a god amongst men!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm convinced my 10 month old daughter's dialect is way more advanced then my own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night my daughter screamed at me. I screamed back and she gave me one of those 'I thought you were supposed to be the adult here' looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NightTerrorsApp How long before we can get our grubby hands on an android version?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomsdayDevice Take that back! Mel knows what's up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this day just got a whole lot better. Mr Johnson Abu from the Bank Of Africa wants to split $6 million with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgesStPierre watched through a couple of times, but can't figure out why ur character has broken arm at the end of #KickboxerVengeance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BearGrylls what a great read to be given on Father's Day https://t.co/aMDyadbmT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got woken at 4:37am with a bit of a shake - way too early to get up and try and catch a wave, so just went back to sleep. #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryansawrie @MLamentB For the people on the floor - that set up would be great if you don't want to actually see the performer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesky_iscrape ....CD Included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dog seems to have my wife convinced that we have a ghost in the house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JOEbodeCLARK Can't wait to get my greasy little hands on a copy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomsdayDevice @PearlJam fans are the worst!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like that I now have to scroll down through a list of years to find my birth year when doing online questionnaires]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My weekend stint acting as a debt collector/enforcer was a bust as I came away empty handed.Maybe it's time to rethink my tactics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catswithbats Why would you be giving away this masterpiece?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great fight - respect to both fighters for putting it all on the line. Not sure I agree with the final scorecard however #UFC202]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McJustTweeted What is Crystal Pepsi? Is it like Meth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomsdayDevice I'm pretty excited about this. Been way too long since we've had new stuff from these guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyBuysNZ Cheers for the Rebate Planer - gave it a hoon the other day - great piece of machinery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catswithbats I saw one event just before while at the gym - NZ lost in a big way... and I stopped paying attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 months old. About 50. https://t.co/vdMXLk1Xk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriscornell Thanks, but I think I'll pass - that was awful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris_mecca I think that may still be some time away given the look she gives me when she's feeding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is an appropriate age to give an infant the 'There's a lot of starving children in Africa who would love this food' talk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sprayed dog repellent over tubing that our dog keeps chewing away at. Went outside a few minutes later to find her licking the repellent off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonleejitsu Bro glad to hear that your safe. Disappointing that you had to leave Rio. This whole thing has been 1 giant shit-storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theme of Barack Obama's speech will be - 'Yeah, I know she's not ideal, but she's still better than the alternative!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JOEbodeCLARK Took me a while to see any people in that photo - I thought you were trying to make some 'sad reflection on life' post]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaS_JBnz @JBHiFiNZ This has now all been sorted and the order dispatched. Thanks for your help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonleejitsu Might be time to move back to NZ bro. Kkia kaha - hope this all gets sorted soon]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>