<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You get the best compliments when you have pink hair. "Your hair reminds me of candy floss and it makes me SO happy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @adamshand But don't let it get frosted coz frost will kill 'em.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA @adamshand says Late April / May is traditional time, but otherwise it's just a 'the more you leave it in the bigger it gets'-ish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin when? if it's afternoon i might be able to make it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend yep. the only thing he's going to give a crap about is his back pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if my KiwiSaver account invests in any Trump companies / companies which sell Trump products.  I'll write some letters and ask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is something my work has been doing - it's wonderful!  Go check it out, and also please like the FB page… https://t.co/ukzrlbbRl9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA hmm, @adamshand might know how to tell when kūmara are ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I thought circles were a pain in the butt... #dragons #art #inking #foreverinking https://t.co/VZXjInmXSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshForde @newzedland @Dovil so e.g. an Iranian/NZ person might be going to Iran via the US and show an Iranian passport normally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshForde @newzedland @Dovil yes, but if they found out, they'd still ban you. I usually travel on the passport of the country I'm going to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newzedland @Dovil i think that's at least part of why it's causing so much carnage. no one is quite sure what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil yep. an NZ/Iranian person, for example, would totally be included in the ban, as far as I can tell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_aldous by which I mean, Yay WorkerBe Oasis!  They're cool! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_aldous WorkerBe also own KaiCycle who organise urban composting - they give you a bucket for your kitchen &amp; come &amp; collect it weekly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 2017 will be the next week of my work day https://t.co/vPygYIMDkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've just invented the 5 point search for booze at a party - position (where) glass colour level (how full) &amp; Lipstick (is there any)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronyaB @WgtnCC wow, really?? Was it cancelled by wind or was it just ... petit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyherself errr... the house I'm at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thehoiseim at for NYE sounds like it has a horse in the roof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beechworks speaking as a youngest child, yes absolutely ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike ..  tell me that's not JJ Murphy's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike maybe he's finally read his security briefings. ;)

although tbh this whole US v Russia thing in general is weird ing me out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike I'm so confused. I thought Trumpy liked Putin? Why is he now accusing him of plotting to siege Alaska?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ sometimes unfriending happens by mistake on FB - worth asking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohyoufox Goldings has some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I just made a jolly reasonable attempt at slicing my finger off with a bread knife.  Foiled by my fingernail.  Ow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzyNZ Tagline by @phil_cook :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... strangled by her own bra. https://t.co/AOvlwFjKT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronsingline you clearly know different dudes than I do ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn or just a short time thang... but yeah. BUT PRETTY! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyherself the beard might be one step too far but the hair is genuinely great :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why aren't dudes in Wellington doing this ??? So pretty. https://t.co/bS9DI7vVpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Know any 16-17yo girls? If this had been around when I was that age I would have been ALL OVER this.  https://t.co/JWicWCF77D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ not that I ever heard of but I'm confident the universe will reincarnate them as a goldfish one day :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is SO not what I meant to say. https://t.co/BgCZCyyKLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ I know right?? I was so unhappy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ when I was a teenager friends had a party with goldfish cocktails, with little live goldfish in them :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper sometimes you &amp; your friends would wonder something, like "what year did..." or "who was that actor" &amp; you'd NEVER FIND OUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower does ASOS hate pregnant ladies? that's kinda the only explanation here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seawall but so many delicious stouts!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks sound asleep but every time I stop patting him he paws my arm until I start again. https://t.co/d6y3tP70iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahMcMullanNZ no despair needed, he's alive and well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seatounsteve uh-oh... whatever it was I'm sure it'll all work out ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Wham! and dressing up the dog. What all good Boxing Days are made of. https://t.co/L0dYV6PagL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm worried she's just dangling there on the roof waiting for me to turn off the light again.  Spiders, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog dream-yips woke me, so I turned on the light to calm him down. Big spindly spider ~ an inch from my pillow booting it back up her line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinkelly I'm pretty pleased with how it came out!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An hour walk mostly uphill and he still wants more. Frikken collies, man, like little energiser bunnies. Indefatiga… https://t.co/vfcPiCKQr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flights sorted for GABS Melbourne next year. Now I just have to get tickets :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy cow, I'm exhausted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clint Eastwood. Riding a skateboard. In Italy. In the 60s. https://t.co/ehH9t0sio9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well. A long entertaining evening having met a friend for dinner who was already VERY drunk. But bedtime now. Thank goodness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower and then proceeded to try to kiss me about three minutes later!! I was like "WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower "i don't understand, why are they awful and all bed hopping and what what what" and he was like "OMG I KNKOW THIS IS CRAZY"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower it was genuinely awful. i was talking to one of the ppl i thought of as a good friend saying "why are all these people mental"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower heck no, nor an assistant, luckily! :)  i was a manager of a back office team (no one else from my team was 'allowed' to come)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower i remember crying in the bathroom because i suddenly realised i genuinely hated most of my workmates. i quit not long after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower i went to a "managers away weekend" where half the partners proceeded to sleep with each others' assistants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who can't sleep....... Again. 😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh thank goodness I figured out how to turn off the news feed on my phones swipe left screen. #nomorebadnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ also opinions about whisky are many and varied, so YMMV :) taste em! Try em!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ (ice makes it cold -&gt; surpresses flavour mostly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ the AA (Abba-lure A-boon-a) is smoky and rich, the B (Buh-na-halve-en) is sweet, sherried etc. drink straight or w/ water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ nope, sorry :( I recommend finding a good pub and asking for an Abelour A'bunadh &amp; a Bunnahabhain 12yo. Opposite ends of scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ are you in Wellington? regional wines &amp; spirits do great tastings on a regular basis!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilikeprettycode @ohyoufox Hmmm. Gerty Henry = Gerty Harry = Dirty Harry = mystery solved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronsingline that's a risk i'm just going to have to take. maybe. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, don't get me wrong, I'm happy for him. But how the f*** is this even *lifestyle* news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG BREAKING NEWS - someone lost a moderate amount of weight through diet and exercise. https://t.co/f3oZe2wndl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronyaB now I might have to get kiwi dip on the way home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohyoufox mums are weird, always calling kids by names they don't have. Mine called me AmyJane for no apparent reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debating a Social Media free 2017.  Unless there's another big earthquake and then f*** it I'm all over Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohyoufox welllll, that seems like a sound judgement call on your dads part.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum did @satanCat just claim your beer tulip as his own?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ughhhh, can we just go back to having a Leader with Opinions please? This "I don't know, maybe, i forget, you can't… https://t.co/0UMr0NHJiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fernetdan oh yeah I didn't think about bad santas from that side. I wonder if @nzsecretsanta can tell you if your giftee was Bad Santa'd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz @nzsecretsanta well? WELL??? What is it what is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yessss, my #nzsecretsanta loved her present :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamshand my goodness no, my secret Santa would die of anticipation!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicegalletly lol!! It was bought from the Women's bookshop in Akl so I figured not you ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yay! This is awesome, I've been meaning to pick it up for a while!! Thanks #nzsecretsanta !! :) https://t.co/9m1eK7x5c6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS HERE ITS HERE ITS HERE #nzsecretsanta https://t.co/9JOuWPyCKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlemidge83 @lexhagvfx no it's not papa having probs it's his choir members, so needs to be a multi-person-problem-solver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THINGS ARE GREAT WHY DO YOU ASK https://t.co/nDhMyoixcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High winds and changeable weather? Woohoo, Spring Two is here! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilikeprettycode thamk god for new puzzle!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend My laptop has just started doing that - doing a full backup now coz it is about 7 years old. o.O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeautifulHaze I'm sure @whaeapower would know some very deserving ppl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuchullain i've had pushbullet suggested and that looks like it might be an option.... just pushes files to their phone ... we'll see!!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinkelly yeah, they seem to be having a hard time following links in emails? but yeah.... it sounds sensible ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuchullain they, um, they seem to having trouble following links from emails? somehow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Speedymctavish perfect, will have a prowl and see if it'll work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend oh :(  well, you'll get a happy surprise at the end of Monday I guess??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have any good recommendations for good file-pushing/autosynching apps for iOs/Android phones that might make this dead easy? /EOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android/iOs phones. He's tried emailing attachments and using dropbox email links, both proving to be a challenge for some members. /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad helps run a choir with quite a few technically-not-so-savvy members. He's trying to share score/mp3 files with them to their /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend same here.... my giftee is out and about today and my #nzsecretsanta is delivering to work. 😩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman dude, don't wish that on us!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum my secret santa hasn't gotten their present yet either.  and mine didn't come to work today!  sad santa day! monday will be A++]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>