<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilgherrian it's an Outrage Blitzkrieg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! Yeah! Dude looks like a Cheeto!  https://t.co/JzXZTQMLQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit a dash cam has let me relive my greatest drive thru orders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump humans have been executed in the Middle East. Humans. Why does it matter which imaginary friend in the sky they have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@troyhunt yep, I know the feeling. And I've got white privilege, so it must be terribly anxious time for others so directly impacted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_boycs @HowellONeill exhibit A. Monsters. https://t.co/OwuFuL57eX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably on roller-blades. https://t.co/91fvQ0i3lU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's you stuffed @MrWyattR https://t.co/BrYtgnAJDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This still might be a better approach, getting all the carnage at once rather than the 1,000 cuts / hour currently. https://t.co/EwVFcFgoFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBirmingham can't be long before they start sending dissidents to build the wall though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alasdairtb never knew you were part Minion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you raise kids in a world where the bullies and arseholes win?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardTuffin no, only if he dual citizen with one of the banned countries. E.g. Aussie + Iran. Pretty sure Murdoc… https://t.co/TVVtmNTshH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one-way trip to Mars is looking more attractive each day. Are applications still open?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only they'd stuck with 2 and 4  instead of putting them in power. https://t.co/s8waiyMZou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wil_Anderson #WilcomeToTheJungle
We've got drugs and games
You can have anything you want
If you've already found fame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump not a single 9/11 hijacker was from the countries you're blocking. Disgraceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Photo" https://t.co/cpMwhOfWBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 what about this alternative? https://t.co/FDc1wnQGpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 well there's my Friday night excitement sorted :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 yep, for the sake of all of us there must be some special security on those accounts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wanted to know what happens in the IT industry? We made a behind-the-scenes video for you 

https://t.co/Iu3gVbvODN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 what about tweeting as POTUS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 I haz monthly Azure credits, have done DIY in the past, but not expecting it to be brilliant. Also limits to 1 POP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler mine are electronic, don't think I've saved them from any recent employers. I'd be screwed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csirac2 is there a single one worth using? Just tell me that one :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anyone left who HASN'T punched Richard Spencer in the face?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMFG Hilarious. So glad to have a higher speed alternative where I live (the nation's capital).  https://t.co/jnkzBP1iY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigWtweets holy shit he has a fragile ego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantdm my son was sooo thrilled to meet you in Sydney, thanks for coming to Australia! Much appreciated  https://t.co/9oN1dUtALU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, forget #AustraliaDay  vs #InvasionDay. Coles are selling #ANZAC biscuits FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being a failed One Nation candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can narrow it down to the smaller handset models for a start. #tinyhands  https://t.co/2IZrOxj5ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some bring sexy back, others bring torture back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyBarnes congratulations on your OAM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reynoldsgareth @JustTires2 @pepboysauto and you got to see Three Doors Down, live!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Special Projects for Sophie.  https://t.co/OzqxRvHr4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @elonmusk is fallible after all (or has really shithouse Twitter account security).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't get an invite to the Australian of the Year awards again. Obviously missed out. Again. 
Alternative Australian of the Year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Punch A Racist Day tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis is he still trying to crack the firebombing case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gees, if only Trump and his team went to these lengths to correct mistakes and misinformation. https://t.co/BDgxHME8Hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveanthony followed by calls to nuke them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beat that for a Map Of Australia Schnitzel! 
#schnitzel #australia #jesustoast https://t.co/K1NAUPqXGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on an alternative diet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deanrobertson sad to hear, thoughts with you and the team. Media leeches can shove off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son scored this from the #MicrosoftSYD store today, mad fun! @ Microsoft Store Flagship https://t.co/JrlReGrWHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if Melania Trump was the Manchurian Candidate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our 1st show at the Sydney Opera House and it's to see @dantdm @dantdmlive https://t.co/pRbdaosCQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantdmlive lounge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantdm We're coming to see you Dan, blue hair and all! @dantdmlive https://t.co/07oMF6g8Iz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought this yacht looked familiar. Version 1! 

#australia #yacht #sydney #harbour #australiaii https://t.co/YHwb20qMI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The water was cold! Period. #tinyhands #SpicerFacts https://t.co/RD9B8vdlpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bane copied Trump. Period. #SpicerFacts https://t.co/zL7sMSwtpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is like, a smart person. Period. #SpicerFacts https://t.co/Preq23Xa10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Amazon Fire phone went incredibly well. Period. https://t.co/tE3I2wvwbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storing the year as 2 digits is a brilliant idea. Period. https://t.co/92qWPPbZPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metadata will only be given to a short list of law enforcement agencies. Period. https://t.co/qVVURtmdrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coalition will roll out the NBN cheaper and faster with a superior solution. Period. https://t.co/HFacJuaYU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[640K of RAM is enough for anybody. Period. https://t.co/yqoyNVXG5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the mic is bigger than your tiny fist. https://t.co/O51MQBeGBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardTuffin I think it's soon to be a daily occurrence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a boat! #manlyferry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardTuffin @realDonaldTrump yeah everyone was focused on the Bane lift, but this was way worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March on ladies. May your pussies remain ungrabbed. #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sad part is it was entirely predictable. Such a brittle, fragile toddler. https://t.co/oaLKJAfKn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punch all the Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AusRob you merely adopted the dark, I was born in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too big to fail  https://t.co/bsCVj8Aue1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrtonymartin faking climate change data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigWtweets it's the series finale!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenatorMRoberts you lingered last in line for brains, then tripped over 77 votes to become a Senator. First class dickhead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Into the fucking sun with you. I've had diarrhoea with more integrity than you.  https://t.co/EP9RocW0JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you weren't aware of penguins. https://t.co/n4ugYCE7ix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pumped to be seeing @nonstoptom tonight at the Uni Pub. Going to be awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyvaneyk gotta get my outrage from somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nutella Cronut in the shape of a triangle. Abomination. Sweet, delicious abomination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drink Brawndo. It's got electrolytes.  https://t.co/SPTyUnVZt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe people on Twitter have strong opinions on stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this time of the year - great to rest and recuperate after a hectic war on Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news, it's only 42 hours of travel from Sydney to Reykjavik if you want to catch the live @thedollop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegemite to be Australian-owned again, thanks @realDonaldTrump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AusRob he's got a sore back from backflipping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveanthony was great to see "More Oats Please" get a mention in this article. Great horse, great slogan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyAbbottMHR @BeatCancerTour you claiming travel expenses while on this also?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just look at the mental strain he's under just while posing with a blank writing pad. https://t.co/orzyaTzqCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts so it wasn't an invitation, but you begging for tickets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if the leverage the Russians have over Trump is just the Apprentice tapes Mark Burnett refused to release.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*googling* cooling for over-ear headphones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went outside for a walk. At what temp do your eyeballs boil? Because that's it currently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EventsACT and don't forget the sweet, sweet carb loading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost like she recieved a phishing email and worked it out. https://t.co/O7jkmgboHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't the public just turn up? Why do you need tickets? I have some magic beans you may be interested in. https://t.co/qQM2a1o7fc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis but wouldn't this be a problem now? What's stopping me asking a Christian baker to make me a big gay cake now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Razor wires and snipers for every backyard pool. Only* solution.  https://t.co/jR9bsvXZOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royal Commission into why Smart TVs are such an abomination. Now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteeleSaunders @9NewsAUS I've tried that line, they won't let you back in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EventsACT I'm training for the Canberra Comedy Festival, does that count?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duplicating the entire road system and dedicating one to Camry drivers would totally be worth it for the rest of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis we should definitely limit progress + cont. to discriminate against a large section of the community because cake bakers. FFS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>