<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters understandably begin to think, "they're all the same, let's try something different," and we end up with Brexit, Trump, fascism...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Kinnock may well feel sympathy for an unemployed constituent whose benefits have been sanctioned but has no idea how it feels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[begin to see the world from the same perspective as billionaires. A professional political class, often hereditary, grows up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Murdoch explained why for the long term good of the media we need to take this approach. Gradual seduction, centre left politicians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There doesn't have to be overt corruption, £1m to sign this contract, they start to see the world from the same perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Blairs and Clintons left office they slipped into the lifestyles of the super-rich: private planes to private island holidays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stricken by Alzheimer's Wilson had to be taken to House of Lords, unable to understand because his only income was expenses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harold Wilson used to holiday in Scilly Isles., left office with about £1,000 savings in Post Office account, needed Lords expenses to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest change in UK politics in my lifetime is takeover by big money. PM for much of my childhood was Harold Wilson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives and Republicans do anything their financial backers want. The alternatives, Blair &amp; Clinton don't do anything they object to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with 'democracy' US/UK style https://t.co/NudTpSTped Corporations and the super-rich have bought both sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alt-right (as it's politically correct to call Nazis nowadays) are very keen on freedom of speech. Until they get the power to censor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reference, but if a word is being used in a specialised, rather than a general sense it's way too early. any opinions on it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the much-praised Essex Serpent this week. Very enjoyable, good sense of period but... Did anyone else spot a whopping anachronism?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[which also affects mental capacity, some form of dementia, on the other hand, a real worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a plethora of the world's most expert psychiatrists attested Trump does not have NPD.. PD just a label.. Progressive physical condition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of Borderline Personality Disorder and I'd have felt much happier with her running a country (BPD and all) than the Trump I see even if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to establish Trump has Narcissistic Personality Disorder (say) what would that mean? The late, great Jenny Diski had a  serious diagnosis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been thinking about a discussion @jonronson began last night about Trump, Goldwater Rule, remote diagnosis. Were it possible or ethical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreary, dreary days. Momentum has descended into interminable procedural wrangling, has it? Never saw that coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["... based around the following points. ONE, a 35 hour working week with no loss of pay." Buzz! Militant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not a true leftie until you can spot the flavour of Trot *before* they finish their trademark cliche. "A clear socialist programme"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[from @DAaronovitch (or similar) on how failure to spot the differences between the CPGB &amp; CPGB (M-L) exposes me as a bourgeois dilettante.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riffing on the conversational tics of far left grouplets has given me an alarming flashback to my student days. Now expecting a lecture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as for the dazzling wit of the CPGB (Marxist-Leninist) well, you'll just have to attend a local Momentum meeting for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So unlike the IMG: every one a mixture of Oscar Wilde and Stephen Fry: epigrams aplenty, cliches zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can have a more thoughtful, witty individual, in depth conversation with a Jehovah's Witness than an SWPer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from moral qualms SWP front events should be avoided because they contain SWP members: dreary,dogma-spouting automatons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That one's clearly satire. Too articulate, complete sentences, not enough ME! ME! ME! AND MY RATINGS! https://t.co/jcbaIOs3tH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have David Icke and Alex Jones proved the Bowling Green Massacre was a 'false flag' attack yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roshbeth I think if his best friend asked he'd dish out the polonium personally, frankly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will they take responsibility for the inevitable Bhopals and Thalidomides? Will they bollocks. "Fake News!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when Trump's corrupt, incompetent and sometimes insane appointees achieve the aim of an effectively government-free  Ayn Rand nirvana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite obvious humanitarian concerns intellectually curious to see how true believing free market fundamentalists will react...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And forty years on you end up with Milo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who I blame? Malcolm McLaren. He made swastikas 'thrillingly subversive' instead of evil https://t.co/eHHz7jtuzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last tweet was not encouraging drug use. Listen to the experts "run from the beast" https://t.co/eMXpEJwjBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think nowadays if I ingested Keith Richard-esque quantities of Class As before every news bulletin they might reach 'pretty bad'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the others consist mainly of praying https://t.co/xsZmyrswdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just knew whose side he'd pick between the little guy and Wall St, didn't you? https://t.co/FEtDBPDrH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Will this win the approval of the Daily Mail' far more important to T. May than 'is this action sensible?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never understood how May acquired a reputation for competence despite things like staggeringly inept Psychoactive S… https://t.co/094hqHT3Dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No physicist I and Prof Brian Cox is a very clever guy, but I may have spotted an error in his work https://t.co/8TprirXRM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At one time I was never happy unless I had a fag in my mouth #AmericanVsBritish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden Rule: if you want to understand something FOLLOW THE MONEY. So follow @Khanoisseur to make sense of US politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But you can, apparently, go to Eton, live in a fucking stately home and claim to be anti-elitist if your name's Ree… https://t.co/67VpRegTHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zeno001 ARE YOU SHOUTING BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL DEAF IN THE HOUSE OF LORDS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... will lead to the best of all possible worlds are among the furthest detached from reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re last RT. Even in a world here some believe in chemtrails &amp; radionics the Panglosses who believe "the magic of the market" (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymeath 1 thing I really like about @jk_rowling She used welfare state safety net when she needed it and now pays her taxes in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had I died of pneumonia a few years ago no-one would have said I lost. Why is cancer different?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the effort John Diamond &amp; Jenny Diski put into opposing the automatic use of martial metaphors for cancer but still automatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MusicofBrassica @jonronson And yesterday I was called a conspiracy theorist for being interested in Russian money to Trump links.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonronson Even the really crazy stuff? Chemtrails, Pizzagate etc.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not in thrall to corporate lobbyists, promoting UBI? Too much to ask? Disgusted by housing policy of many London Labour councils.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want a Labour party committed to fighting inequality, defending NHS, rebuilding social housing, opposing racism...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I initially backed Corbyn because I wanted principle over spin. Milne can't spin &amp; Brexit shows Corbyn lacks principles too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstained 2nd time because I was furious with PLP for  putting internal Labour issues 1st when UK was in crisis, PM had resigned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good piece on how Corbyn has alienated all but his most devoted supporters over Brexit. I voted for him, despi… https://t.co/NKac993AFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second, much superior, bus is fairly whizzing along. Not, sadly, to my preferred destination, but we can't have everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bus driver evidently shared my frustration at the rate of progress. I am now on another bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bus is moving considerably less rapidly than I - no Mo Farah - could walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite not being @Gary_Bainbridge I am on a bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vile as most of what Trump says and does is, Russian money looks to me like the smoking Kalashnikov to investigate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Tillerson appointed Secretary of State 4 Transparency regulations on oil &amp; gas co.s lifted 5. Sanctions on RSB (KGB) lifted. No, baffled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to join dots. 1. Streele dossier says Trump promised 19% of  Rosneft if sanctions lifted. 2. 19.5% of Rosneft sold to 'mystery buyer']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As visitor unsure whether to protest bigotry or praise inclusiveness https://t.co/mAZbebc8Te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though, admittedly,, there are one or two slight risks (Hepatitis, addiction, fatal OD) associated with heroin so maybe no drugs at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[measure to reduce mental harm. Always take cocaine in conjunction with heroin. Taking both together reduces the mental damage of coke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you absolutely must take cocaine and would prefer not to turn into a gibbering, paranoid wreck there is a key, somewhat counter-intuitive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not endorse the use of recreational drugs but if someone insists on taking them I can offer one harm reduction tip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can see, regrettably, how the state of the world might make someone think that hard drugs might ease the distress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 60s song suddenly seems topical again https://t.co/bcVI0STrPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama Question baffling me recently - are there no Republicans who value patriotism, the constitution above holding office?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until recently being insufficiently hostile to Russia was akin to admitting a sexual interest in sheep as a vote winner in US politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a child of the 60s I can believe the USA would elect a racist president, but I'd never have thought one beholden to Russia could win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjukes Agreed but *sometimes* there are worthwhile facts bullied into supporting her specious conclusions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjukes Some sound research, which she sometimes does, but stretched to some tenuous conclusions IMO. Tone over-excitable, tad paranoid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterjukes Speaking of blogs which leap to conclusions what did you make of Louise Mensch's recent epic interpretation of spying, Peter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously the world is scary enough without scary cigarettes too. I can truthfully say no recreational fags tonight, https://t.co/UaFYyJvfPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should any cynic doubt that last Tweet I refer you to Messrs Thunders, Perrett (and the late Mike Kellie) https://t.co/0EtOYusBwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, this has been a remarkably healthy, well-behaved, abstemious Saturday night.😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've always regarded Alvie Singer from Annie Hall as my ideal in laid-back confidence now worrying my petite paws have been sniggered at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a (I'm not ashamed to say) dainty-digited man I am astonished no-one had told me that I should worry about this until now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infamousTrans You seem very down today. As someone who has made suicide attempts all I can say is "try to get though it: it passes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lest anyone think I'm encouraging youngsters to take drugs i'm totally with Peter Perrett  on that https://t.co/Nd5Yxr99LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New medication too, so inevitably https://t.co/w2ntOtsHVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed that Williams &amp; Watson so much i'll have another one https://t.co/PRuW3dSEeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A musical response to my new double-headed medical status https://t.co/v9rL1qdg7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could convince today's Panglosses that the magic of the market does not lead to the best of all possible worlds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind you the new one is BPD, so I suspect what he really means is "it's borderline whether you have a personality at all."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have definitely 'grown as a person' today. New psychiatrist tells me I've got ANOTHER personality disorder to keep my usual one company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is a bit of a Cnut, isn't he? And not just anagrammatically. "I can stop climate change by banning talk of it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Economic damage i.e. almost all of US tech industry is built on developing new uses for discoveries made by defence R&amp;D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Suppressing climate change research will mean more harm from it, delay or prevent mitigation action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 Direct harm to citizens' health - making EPA into Encouraging Pollution Agency, having anti-vax crank run  enquiry into vaccination etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-science bigotry of Trump administration stands to harm US on 3 levels..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As someone said t'other day - Trump will make Harper's war on science seem trivial https://t.co/EEXlE3lXF6 https://t.co/S2UrQeUdkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So  Burnley's response to am act of gratuitous violence is the introduce Joey Barton. Should calm things down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My main hope is that Trump's tiny fingers will not be able to reach the button.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>