<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[just finished oral history interviews with organisers of Wellington Women's March for @WMWArchivesProj #activistarchivists 4eva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anybody out there have pro-tools files in their digital archives? https://t.co/SvlUWGnyY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great Californian historian and librarian. Former California Librarian Kevin Starr dead at 76  
https://t.co/vsYFLgbfmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great of California history and libraries https://t.co/16Y2KqqHYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[book I co-edited, includes transcription of diary Berkman kept while writing Prison Memoirs, held @IISG_Amsterdam,… https://t.co/KcJIDhM2o7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[half off and free shipping on Shelia Rowbotham's new book until Jan 1 https://t.co/3HwJnQnpLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flexlibris yes please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ethic digital collecting and access https://t.co/fHVFIbExTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jenny Bunn's talk on 'real thing' of born-digital has so many good questions to think about.  #interparestrust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in Wellington, hope to see you there! https://t.co/7Y54tqoNlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmichalski boo! I am freaking out quietly over here in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjbtw what @bitarchivist suggests is what we usually do logging change w/provenance notes but if dependencies between files gets messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes I feel like you could distill my job to basically this all day everyday https://t.co/R9JO3nYPrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjbtw the hidden patio space outside the Moffit was also great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommended reading https://t.co/n9Vw3a826D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea yes, wouldn't recommend as solution for dig archive, but just as one of many places to have backup. Def wouldn't trust long term!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design thinking for libraries  https://t.co/HCX55Iy0i4 #spreadthenet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research bazaar 2017 in Wellington https://t.co/nw0VYOIIsp #spreadthenet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonarchivist @andrewjbtw @SMDorpinghaus @destreservation yes something it would be really good to do #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMDorpinghaus @destreservation there must be some but should it be available automatically or note that available in finding aid #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destreservation @CLIRDLF yes! Plus it's complicated so many different types of bd records and researchers not one size fits all #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destreservation @CLIRDLF but that doesn't really tell us how successfully we are meeting user needs... #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destreservation @CLIRDLF we think we will soon be able to report on every time an item is requested from dig pres system #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLIRDLF still working out how well or not we are doing at meeting users needs #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We try to make available either in reading room or online, item linked through online catalog… https://t.co/4lHzugHnQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLIRDLF archivist in NZ working with born digital collections #bdaccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really curious about this from archivist perspective. What do researchers want most? #bdaccess https://t.co/s13AXkQula]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ and AUS friends, want to talk about born digital access? tomorrow @ 2PM NZ time. #bdaccess https://t.co/cX2aY3icGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BergisJules hard for "professional archivists" to understand that radical/community archivies might not want/trust traditional spaces?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knfrances yes it is! It even allows us to use EAD and EAC @hokiarchgirl @kiwiandkumara are it's queens and know far more than me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knfrances @shirapeltzman @NLNZ just tick box for only born digital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knfrances @shirapeltzman @NLNZ you can also search specifically for bd across collections with our new system https://t.co/eGQ1Qg70Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjbtw @eiratansey @jmddrake @edsu @anarchivist esp if it's something like "new folder" however we describe empty folders during A&amp;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjbtw @eiratansey @jmddrake @edsu @anarchivist our current practice is to document dir paths durring appraial/accession but not retain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_jolley @markival start thinking of topics for discussion now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_jolley @markival ok, I'm convinved, I'll try to promote a AN/AUS chat a bit more before the day, if you both promise to participate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markival well I was planning to just lurk but suppose we could have a NZ/AU contingent, I do have thoughts on topic @emma_jolley r u keen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that's 7AM and 2 PM Oct 28 for anyone in New Zealand interested in participating https://t.co/1aabTmec5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wish I could magically be in NY for this https://t.co/sjTHwpD9Xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MTGHawkesBay Thanks for having me, it was lots of fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[want to come work at the National Library New Zealand? https://t.co/JSutXc0RS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diplomaticaerin @eiratansey @KDRoe122 potential to allow multiple world views and access into records]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diplomaticaerin @eiratansey @KDRoe122 we've been discussing in NZ Hurley's parallel provenance for desc both gov and indigenous world views]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Jolly shares some very good advice! https://t.co/fya3lkliAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maori archives, iwi, and researchers panel #aranz40 https://t.co/OC60MoH6qJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing example of Maori indigenous archives  https://t.co/M4eeA86IVQ #aranz40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertramlyons @andrewjbtw @shirapeltzman filenames are one of the things @NDHA_NZ and I tried to work through here https://t.co/OVW5lYUhRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fogonwater that was awesome, but I think I might have felt some of that poor kid's mortification, mom shut up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[come, it'll be great https://t.co/ERDZ90AK9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSleigher That whole issue huh? The Zadie Smith short story was pretty great too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beet_keeper I've always been partial to an agony of archivists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costadaniel scary times, they seem to be coming out of the woodwork, https://t.co/tnoG1nw5p5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costadaniel did you see one of the antifa organisers is a middle school teacher in Berkeley and is now getting threats sent to the school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are we insisting users ask permission to publish and why are we 
charging fees for publishing and commercial use https://t.co/fxKQTQLk83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stop trying to control copyright of things you actually don't own copyright to https://t.co/4aP5lSpe1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diplomaticaerin Awesome, I envy you as I stare out the window at a wall of rain. Congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very pleased to have helped in a small way to make this collection accessible. Congratulations @MTGHawkesBay!  https://t.co/YxyOzll5JV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carlota Bustelo describing two ways of thinking about managing gov digital archives #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/SwfAoruE99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amywatling I think they do sometimes. The bottom workflow they do the conversion to pdf/a but still keep the original. But only sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korean file format preservation #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/yZlqt7cpbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. All South Korean gov agencies adopt same edrms, connected online and facilitate transfer to nat archives #ISOTC46NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 200 gov agencies involved and over 2 million records in South Korea's first nat archives born digital transfer https://t.co/NS1NXJ4Cay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recoding keeping and archives rethought as social construct in China #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/1dWNu2iULA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges of digital record keeping in China. Familiar #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/BM86st07Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you wondered @ARANZ_Wgtn #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/Zph762kvj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operating principles of new standard part 2, #ISOTC46NZ https://t.co/7tSH4ZRJrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operating principles of new standard #ISOTC46NZ 1 of 2 https://t.co/VLFGm8yB7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International record and info management in Wellington, first up @CassPF #iso15489 https://t.co/OEaxNnHuxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edrabinski I think so, but @rachelcanttweet is my cousin so I'm a little biased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edrabinski on food stamps during the new deal, https://t.co/rX4WPkK1xM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verslibre  those are very nice glasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TopLeftBrick @edsu I totally use this tool and it is insane, but also amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgschultz hah, we had the same conversation over here, but it was stay up till 10pm. I'm hoping it'll be recorded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genevieve_hk you might be interested in our iPRES paper, it details some of our filename issues and solutions https://t.co/rZeYy8KHBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[character encoding and file names, oh my!
 https://t.co/J9mGiqy1e3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikejonesmelb I thought the exact same thing, hard to survive in London on that salary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexArchivists Did you see he had a private archivist? I want that job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you go to a talk on improving diversity and the audience is 98% female.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlascarides i am so pleasantly surprised at just how good this nomination seems!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennymundy  we were just calling ourselves electronic brain archivists but surgeon sounds even better, would new job title come with raise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["electronic brain" is a synonym for digital. Thank you https://t.co/lKIGhYeHLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to try out this new tool https://t.co/d4nlzQU1YQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a good way to start the day in anger, see how much less you get paid for being a woman! $14,000 for librarians in NZ https://t.co/fR5967vayA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjmeyers @rowmyboat even though it's not processed yet... is there a way to get a copy of the wollstonecraft lecture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjmeyers @rowmyboat what archive does the Mary Wollstonecraft lecture come from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know a report that starts with an Inspector Morse reference will be good. Personal Digital Archiving, https://t.co/orq8HMk6Ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criticalsenses @andreakbyrne sounds good to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criticalsenses @andreakbyrne Funnily enough we're working on something right now. But also maybe a Skype meeting in new year? Been awhile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eiratansey A case study based on the assumption that retaining those is important but not easy https://t.co/AG6eT0scWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anrchivist did you ever see the map of Emma Goldman's lectures Barry did, would be fun to overlay the two, https://t.co/mQ99y9dFun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please come, it'll be great! https://t.co/0NDVC0fA7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BertrandCaron @NDHA_NZ  glad to hear it! And it was good to meet you last week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of #ipres2015 was meeting, talking, and sharing with so many great people.  https://t.co/UtbpSZayGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good conversations in today's workshop, https://t.co/PZmuyLjBJT
 #oss4pres #ipres2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euanc that's the long term goal but we need to keep ingesting until all the systems catch up. Not just Rosetta, but droid, jhove, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euanc yeah. That is pretty harsh. I think it works ok for our institutional context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like poetry, politics, or music? If you're in Wellington you should come to this tomorrow night, https://t.co/szUVU8Bd1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjbtw Yep, that's what we capture, filename, file path, all the dates, and checksums.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to add value. You tell em @agh212 #aranz2015 http://t.co/VD74yZdnt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anne Gilliland and Verne Harris: two of the best conference keynotes I've experienced. Inspired.  #aranz2015]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>