<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump gets wrong about the US-Mexico relationship https://t.co/oo4SOXUiB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These priorities rarely get much attention, since they are bureaucratic. But they are a huge deal. More here: https://t.co/OmHr3yvoFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a big break from Trump's previous commitment to only target undocumented immigrants who are dangerous or threaten the public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It also includes hundreds of thousands of people who have received a final removal order but haven't left the country. Many are families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That includes undocumented immigrants convicted of any crime or having simply been charged -- not convicted -- of a crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's order yesterday makes many, many more people considered priorities, putting them in the crosshairs for deportation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the priorities were revised in 2014, nearly 90% of undocumented immigrants were no longer considered priorities for deportation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These priorities tell who immigration officials should target—and who they should leave alone. They were first created under Obama in 2010.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most important parts Trump's EO on immigration has gotten little attention: new enforcement priorities https://t.co/OmHr3yvoFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's order directs DHS secretary to create a list, updated weekly, of crimes committed by undocumented immigrant… https://t.co/PEFWD7ODS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GAO put out a restricted report today. Look what it's titled -- would be very interesting to read it. https://t.co/jyIVkx6eqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has far less on the mandatory spending cuts, mostly a paragraph here or there on reforming Medicare and Social Security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Heritage budget has a very detailed rundown for the discretionary spending cuts. A page on each program with justification for cuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm comparing to more recent CBO numbers, so these will be off from what Heritage says in the report. But they give you a sense of the cuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By my calcs, Heritage cuts about
- $600 billion from Social Security
- $3.2 trillion from Medicare
- $2.5 trillion from rest of mandatory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the numbers on discretionary: https://t.co/wKIWvItQ8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A note about the Heritage budget that Trump is reportedly working off: Only bout $2.5 trillion come from discretionary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Chetty et al study out today is fascinating. Strongly advise reading through the slides: https://t.co/uTihleFvc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS is more involved with executing policy than setting it, experts told me. You can read that piece here: https://t.co/spR64b5tLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS doesn't have quite the purview of DOJ. But Kelly will have a major role over immigration and refugee programs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Sessions was nominated, I explained seven big areas where he could change DOJ policy. Worth revisiting today: https://t.co/fpFG4iurRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attorney general has huge sway on everything from immigration to drug policy to surveillance to police misconduct. It's extremely vast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the confirmation hearings of Jeff Sessions, at DOJ, and John Kelly, at DHS, begin today, it's worth considering the powers of those depts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One other number: By my calculation, more than half a million people have been out of work 100+ weeks. That's a big number!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's been lots of improvement of course but these are three interesting trends to keep an eye on https://t.co/xZGOp6B7Fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is includes:
1. Full employment is close
2. Black unemployment nears historic lows
3. Long-term unemployment remains elevated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three trends buried in the December jobs report https://t.co/xZGOp6B7Fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Donald Trump really use the contracting process as a weapon? Yep, he basically can. My piece: https://t.co/A1I8YJRRUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @CateMartel's newsletter today on Trump tweeting that addressing his business ties isn't complex https://t.co/myTmLZnV07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Perry would not actually be the first Energy Secretary who previously supported abolishing the department https://t.co/oac7MPQY9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Rick Perry qualified to be energy secretary? https://t.co/oac7MPQY9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hidden powers Andy Puzder would hold at the Department of Labor https://t.co/Cvj8HaySRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What John Kelly could really do at DHS https://t.co/spR64b5tLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Reid predicts end of the filibuster, worth reading his former aide @jamespmanley and @BrianHDarling on keeping it https://t.co/OE3xwF0fkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: That time Obama negotiated his own Carrier-style deal https://t.co/EDjjxw0mq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyways, lots more good details in the piece. Give it a read: https://t.co/EDjjxw0mq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Trump though, interfering with business decisions appears to be a major component of his policy. And that's a major, major change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The refinery the Obama WH helped saved in 2012 is really the exception to the administration's broader economic philosophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's certainly happy to promote those deals and capture the political benefits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's political and economic strategy is very different. He's happy to single out specific companies and negotiate agreements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't think the politics would work out very well and worried about the precedent of interfering with a company's business decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It saved 850 jobs and prevented gas prices from spiking—in a battleground state in an election year. But the White House never promoted it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have an interesting story up this evening on Obama's successful efforts in 2012 to save a PA refinery https://t.co/EDjjxw0mq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Steve Mnuchin could do at Treasury: This just went up: https://t.co/8N5ucNGpzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can Tom Price do at HHS without the help of Congress? A lot. I break it down: https://t.co/nincZ4Aco5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @brettnorman has an interesting piece on a more holistic approach to health care https://t.co/UyN8DEU78Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It includes a deep dive from @DanaGoldstein on the demographics in America in 2050 https://t.co/1vxYvCWt0o https://t.co/EnILdIoEPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a break from Trump, we have a new series looking at the future of American health, called Agenda 2020 up today https://t.co/Arx5J5VOEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 big areas where Tom Price can change policy at HHS https://t.co/nincZ4Aco5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my favorite story of the day https://t.co/PK7PsA5JxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: My look at the challenges ahead for Paul Ryan has tries to reform entitlement programs and the tax code https://t.co/J3ymc5jaTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the hard work of governing, and Ryan has yet to show how he will manage it. More here: https://t.co/J3ymc5jaTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan has worked hard to get the GOP to support his ideas. But to do so, he made contradictory policy proposals. Now he must reconcile them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a piece out today on the challenges ahead for Paul Ryan as he pursues entitlement and tax reform https://t.co/J3ymc5jaTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Myron Ebell, a climate skeptic who is running Trump's EPA transition team https://t.co/lXcMSECc8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about Myron Ebell, who is heading Trump's EPA transition team and has spent his career attacking Republicans https://t.co/lXcMSEkBgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump may not get his Mexico-financed wall but he has a lot of power to transform immigration policy https://t.co/BOoLDCADuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump will have a lot of power to unilaterally transform the immigration system. Here's what he could do: https://t.co/BOoLDCADuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence against occupational licensing laws. https://t.co/KxA2vwUPSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's wrong, of course. But there's a kernel of truth in his comments: the Fed isn't independent. It was created by Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about Trump's claims that Yellen is rigging the election for Hillary https://t.co/gZxp9EFKc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having said that, Bowles makes some fair points in his email to Podesta. Worth a quick read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real thing Bowles misses is Krugman and others don't believe we need a deficit reduction plan right now, no matter what's in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Podesta emails, Erskine Bowles defends the Bowles-Simpson plan from @paulkrugman and others in the Obama WH https://t.co/bs4tGjVYFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is quite interesting from @JWMason1 https://t.co/CWlr38j48C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[w/ @kenvogel: Podesta signed a $7,000/month contract with a top donor https://t.co/Mi5afsA8eQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the first time I can remember seeing a correction on one of Krugman's blogs https://t.co/uL8lU2jcM1 https://t.co/m1MWq1hdCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardRubinDC Yeah, I just skimmed through the paper and looked at the graphs. So they might say more in the text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardRubinDC Interesting hypothesis, that makes a lot of sense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, the rise in average income for c-corps right before the Great Recession is startling: https://t.co/K1DERvBTRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an even clearer picture showing the rise in pass-throughs: https://t.co/OkQ9AA4Cyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business income in the US taxed far more on the individual tax side than corporate side. Huge shift since 1980:… https://t.co/SUGYiYojdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a terrific piece, @matthewstoller https://t.co/64Hobdnxly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BTW here's the link to the explainer: https://t.co/goSZk7KAUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mediators in Florida!
Pscyhologists in NJ!

My favorite is "possible limits on use with locksmith" in NC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the occupations that are exempted from non-competes on a state-by-state basis https://t.co/OTCDRi7wEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexParkerDC Cali, North Dakota and Oklahoma. Odd group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH has an interesting short explainer going through state-by-state laws on non competes. Guess which three states ban non-competes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Econ_Marshall @btschiller Yeah study cited in the piece and I mention at the end there can be other concerns with vertical mergers too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As antitrust becomes a bigger issue, it's worth remembering that horizontal mergers appear to hurt consumers more than vertical ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are other reasons to be skeptical of the AT&amp;T-Time Warner deal, of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But that's only true for horizontal mergers. For vertical ones, like AT&amp;T-Time Warner deal, it found modest efficiency gains w/ no markups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new NBER paper has strong evidence that mergers do not increase efficiency but do raise prices https://t.co/lZlD7HTd2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This headline: "Ernst and Young struggle to account for Trump"
https://t.co/czd2MYGKiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The assertion that Trump’s supporters are all racists has, I think, become partially self-fulfilling." https://t.co/Bp9uTWbqLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you, like me, can't keep up w/ the Trump news these days, I highly advise signing up for @CateMartel's newsletter https://t.co/j6XK7rqHDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In light of the WH's conference on innovation yesterday, I wrote about the decline in business dynamism in the US https://t.co/p5FWX0QTAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Donald Trump's confused portrait of black America https://t.co/crow4Lg6Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The black child poverty rate remains high but is declining. My analysis: https://t.co/crow4Lg6Qn https://t.co/cUhDtXWNQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I go through all of this in the piece, so give it a read: https://t.co/crow4Lg6Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? Largely because the strong economy gave workers leverage to demand higher wages. This is hugely important. Trump misses it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But he also ignores real improvements post-recession and, more importantly, overlooks that the late '90s saw a large drop in black poverty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump paints an extraordinarily negative picture of black America. And black poverty rates remain far higher than those of white Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both of those claims are false. I went into the CPS microdata to debunk them: https://t.co/vD1yibGZUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Trump said that 45% of African-Americans in cities live in poverty.

On Monday, he said that 45% of black youths live in poverty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece: Donald Trump's confused portrait of black America https://t.co/crow4Lg6Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- Clinton's tax plan raises taxes on everybody
- Trade deficit is $800 billion.

Check our full fact-check: https://t.co/aqJanv1zFe 

2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's false comments on economy/taxes:

- Lowest growth since 1929
- Economy not growing at all 
- Taxes almost highest in the world

1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since nothing much is happening in this debate, I fact-checked Trump's statement on the 2015 trade deficit https://t.co/8GLCpMPA8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number of long-term unemployed slips back below 2 million but there hasn't been much movement on that in recent months either.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>