<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacktclose A unicameral parliament and multi-party politics/MMP probably also helps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nleemariu your own grandmother!? 😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanmearns it legally can be up to nearly the end of Nov, a lot of our elections have been in Nov... (the dates I wanted were already gone)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @pmbillenglish, I have Nov 4th on an Election Date sweepstake so could you please...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh boy https://t.co/beto9OGlSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyTravers haha very true -except for all the government spending and state control of the economy that he believes in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New twitter bio https://t.co/ar7Z34jZyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your email signature is seven lines PLUS a "disclaimer" statement, you are definitely including unnecessary information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mz_knewton how do you tell if someone who serves you is a "migrant"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mz_knewton we don't take 100k unskilled migrants. Also employment is rising so we actually do need most of the people who are coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are taps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never comprehend people who lug ungainly four litre water containers around the gym.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This literally says people working in petrol stations and supermarkets have different faces. About as racist as you… https://t.co/cVAPXxxinV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddAtticus Trumpism thrives on being condemned, by the media, the "political class" etc. It probably extends to the rest of the world too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToddAtticus for sure but I just don't think it makes a difference to get hung up on who has condemned what. In fact it might make it worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should do what we can, but be realistic. We need our relationship with America in good shape in four years when they get a new President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it doesn't help to direct impotent rage at President Trump, by simply "condemning" him and his actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it would be nice to hear him say that it is not in line with New Zealand values to discriminate against groups of refugees and migrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be nice to hear from the PM about what his government will do when there is a global refugee crisis but other countries say "no".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimRose69872629 @LewisHoldenNZ @damienmgrant I don't feel deprived. Think it's funny she used my photo and claimed to be doing a "clearout"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmgrant oh absolutely I'm not bothered just think it is hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gave away my shitty old bed frame for free on Vic Deals. Lady picked it up today and she's already selling on anoth… https://t.co/aABRuvfBxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dunne has been in politics for like 200 years, and his mission right now? Shifting the school holidays by a month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview with Dame Patsy Reddy. I'm such a fan. https://t.co/aQQvxKwGTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr clearly not. Just as we can't set $50/hr and eradicate deprivation overnight. Think we agree there's a balance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I read that Womens Marches are "protests against democracy" one more time I will scream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr but few businesses are the size of RB. Also strong case that RB would reduce hours/staffing under high min wage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr but I think this will be the point where we reach a more fundamental disagreement 😬😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr yes I agree. But the parents of the other 60% may be trapped out of work if the minimum wage is set *too* high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @Tim_McCready similar feelings from over here. And politics is better when not treated as a blood sport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr everyone would. But the way the church arrives at the LW rate presumes 1.5 full time incomes raising 2 kids etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr in some ways the living wage argument supports exemptions for youth bc the calculation presumes you have kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr I agree we should have higher wages but the LW math depends on assumptions that aren't true of most people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr yes they are time-limited and only for 16/17 year olds - and fixed at 80% of the minimum wage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr well it's different and it's not how I'd want it here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr correction: 2/3 the adult wage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @ughwhtevr yep and the wage for 18 y/o is only ~2/3 what it is here. Very different in lots of ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ughwhtevr their main minimum wage is high but there are a lot of lower rates for younger people and apprentices etc. Also higher income tax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gareth Morgan: "My Party will campaign for the party vote" https://t.co/6DVxx4N7wG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I said Gareth Morgan didn't know the first thing about politics. Seems he has actually picked up the litera… https://t.co/lIdAZDB5uj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Tom Daley's leaked snapchats another part of his social media strategy to sell cookbooks and workout plans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think food/recipe video Facebook pages just exist to boost the sales of coconut oil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming no I mean... you can bring KFC on planes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming what on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is it going to be politically possible? I suggest without ACT it won't be, with ACT it'll be necessary." https://t.co/L6cRPSUPOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @damienmgrant yes but we could switch provincial holidays out for a nationwide alternative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmgrant @_hehir_ and the era of provincial government in NZ didn't give us a hell of a lot to commemorate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmgrant @_hehir_ FWIW I'm not against public holidays I just think  in a country of 4.5mil having sub-national ones is daft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really don't like provincial anniversary holidays. So, to celebrate Wellington Province Anniversary I'm going to… https://t.co/2zGReQFKXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Obama took the Churchill bust out of the Oval Office because it's kind of ugly https://t.co/BTZIAPPavE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @pmbillenglish and National on 46% in @roymorganonline. Confirms summer conversations: NZ wants the govt's direction full steam ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt probably his name or a simple "my husband" would be fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikutoooria omg that is criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter what comes, you will be inspired by the character and compassion of the people you now lead." https://t.co/FJJKXnnVBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop @rorymccourt anyway I'm not denying values are important, just think it's classic kiwi myopia to continue to obsess over the tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nleemariu also cheesy pet names used in public are the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming also probably bad strategy, as I'm sure most people who read political blogs are already quite aware of how to have their say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone I'm Facebook friends with exclusively refers to their husband as "the lovely man" (never his name), in posts.

I'd file for divorce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl definitely an important event in our history, but it just fucking doesn't matter what any given individual thought of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day, years in the future, there will be no politicians left born before 1981 - only then, this torture will fin… https://t.co/75vS7IRSy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikutoooria overheard whilst changing. I'm so upset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent human beings don't hoick phlegm in gym showers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Labour is committed to keeping kiwis safe at work" 

(Except the ones we want to send on the Pike River Reentry mission)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely terrible weather bomb. Very low-energy. Sad! https://t.co/f73WCWLumY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArchieBuissink I think the short answer is "there isn't one"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean the main legal barrier is the health and safety law protecting workers from doing unsafe work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The former secretary of the EPMU will introduce a bill to remove "all legal barriers" to reentry of the Pike River Mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_victoriajayne_ reaction polls have gone TOO FAR, but that was my favourite pupper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't read past the first paragraph of this column because the author referred to her child as "Miss 7" https://t.co/J1ZMbjgh6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my proposal to deal with the Wellington rental housing shortage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you write "Courtney Place" or "Lampton Key" you would be sent back to wherever you came from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be like a citizenship test before you move to Wellington. You just would have to correctly spell a few well-known street names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we're not a perfect country by any stretch, but people in NZ have access to welfare, health, education. That's pretty rare in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree that inequality (especially caused by the cost of housing) is a problem. But it's not caused by Graeme Hart. https://t.co/w2felnNvRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone confirm whether @winstonpeters is going too? https://t.co/icDqLjiBR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure what part of the article led the social media editor to write that caption... https://t.co/Cu983AFjpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I burnt my hand whilst cooking the other day and now I'm finding it hard to rebuild a trusting relationship with my frying pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very odd remarks from the Mayor of Tauranga, on the highly auspicious occasion of usurping Dunedin as 5th biggest c… https://t.co/4WQTjIVkBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they could be in the next software update that would be grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello, @apple? I really like the red wine emoji, but I also need white wine and rosé ones please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember The Sims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henderception @JosephPagani @BJDugdale the ballot incentivises this: opposition stunt bills that will never pass; and govt ballot stuffing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the category of "things that are quite annoying but actually not annoying enough that you'd want politicians to… https://t.co/uKR2ZqRy7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nutella "might cause cancer". It contains something that "has been linked to" something that "has been linked to" possible cancer. 

Pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is cute 💙🇳🇿🇬🇧 https://t.co/ounPLrWsNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows Whoever is running their ads at the moment must not know that you can target by language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusDCook Not having any of those days for a little while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news. @deniselee_nz will be an excellent National MP. https://t.co/PINvlCRDLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dairymanNZ I am Lil Christmas Cake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative headline: "NZ Aid supports programme to feed starving Rwandan and Ethiopian children" https://t.co/mkU8U6reGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$8.99 a kilo for breasts and boneless thighs this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly false. Everyone knows there's no such thing as a "secret vegan" https://t.co/d2BQmoHqHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, but also... "just" 22km away from Wellington CBD. "Just". 

https://t.co/HzGuMQPMKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the most important day of the festive season: the first payday after Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Waitangi Day vs Anzac Day thing bothers me immensely. They are fundamentally different and we don't "celebrate" NZ on Anzac Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffMillerNZ He was in the United States after all - just using the local dialect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do people normally not fill their cars with gas when on holiday? https://t.co/yjmNM9IEmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see why the PM should be at Waitangi with no right to speak. Having a relationship and dialogue means both listening and being heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people who work on news shows deserve their holidays too but can't we do better than "Dickinson's Real Deal"?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>