<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@quixem I like the kid, but he's about a year away from being an NBA rotation player. And guacamole is awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quixem Holy Guacamole, I can't believe you said that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quixem why is there no downvote button on Twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio vs. Oklahoma City, Final Score: Spurs find themselves late, beat Thunder 108-94 https://t.co/Pnr40XkeqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of the same people saying it's unpatriotic to speak out against the president spent the last 8 years questioning Obama's birth cert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieDiCaro Popovich isn't great at X&amp;Os, he's great at managing, motivating and developing people and organization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_JMoriarty Probably a customer, actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the entire speech. #StrangerThings https://t.co/8LnKOstVkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful speech.  Kind of what I needed to hear tonight. https://t.co/GKnOIbuSaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kawhi Leonard surpasses Tim Duncan’s double figure scoring mark https://t.co/lKWMd5twzu https://t.co/bLiLHGiUib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calebjsaenz I've been writing for a Spurs blog for a couple of years but under no illusion that it's leading to anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spurnandez210 I have a software deployment tonight so I'll be late checking in myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final Score, San Antonio at Brooklyn: Spurs don’t need Parker, Leonard to rout the Nets 112-86 https://t.co/gaF0SUPm8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FillWerrell @Azhog1977 The first set of pictures is taken from the Washington Monument and the other one from the other end of the mall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gasol will opt in for the 2017-2018 season with the Spurs https://t.co/4C1Weba2z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio at Phoenix, Final Score: Suns use fourth quarter surge to outrun the Spurs 108-105 https://t.co/q8YyB2BkVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p2cat I was going with 'Memphis, home of Elvis and the Ancient Greeks', but that works too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio vs. Milwaukee, Final Score: Spurs lose a close one to the Bucks https://t.co/nENNtle9vu https://t.co/sCGDxM6vVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb @SBNation He trips more than Timothy Leary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really have to pay attention before I plop my butt into a chair around here. The cat may have got there first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorGischler Jensen Interceptor is pretty much a British muscle car: https://t.co/CfzFaUbaFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorGischler Or maybe a Jensen Healey instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorGischler The American classic would be a Chevy Camaro, probably the SS variant. If you want something more exotic, Sunbeam Tiger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jollyrogerwilco Can't believe Pau didn't get free throws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_feist Those aren't peanuts, they're free nuts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigSagerJr @Chefdre1107 @THESagerbomb After all, she is the Sagermeister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain on the H-Van. https://t.co/kMH8R80fNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad Sanchez is the third stringer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought a copy of scrivener for the new year. It looks overengineered for the task, but it was hard to pass up at only $29.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the protocol for a New Years Eve countdown when there's a leap second? Do you count 1 twice, or just start a second later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs recover from another slow start, defeat the Trail Blazers 110-94 https://t.co/xjBWqz96qB https://t.co/xrIUKpC7zL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonathon Simmons didn't quite get the alley oop pass, but he had some fun trying. https://t.co/kRLuvsYJDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nkjemisin 2016 has a lot of us feeling battered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei 2016...will the tragedies never end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Don't forget the stupid leap second added to 2026 at the end. 3-2-1-1 ☄️☄️☄️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshEberley @OPUS_Mag Somebody found David Byrne's suit from the 80s!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_orsborn He played pretty well in the couple of games he started, but Murray's development makes him expendable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei I don't think your followers are a representative sample, but it's a fun question anyway. Repeal the 22nd amendment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago @ San Antonio, Final Score: Spurs run the Bulls out of the Alamo City https://t.co/5B2nEs6LPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timc_la Relative to how horrible he looked against the Mavs, yes.  In absolute terms, he showed promise but still needs improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lethargic Spurs get outworked by Clippers bench players https://t.co/8iex14IhXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb @TPM I thought people from Stanford were supposed to be smart. Yeah, obviously the liquor's fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb Take care of yourself #SagerStrongForever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio vs New Orleans, Final Score: Spurs take care of Pelicans for Timmy 113-100 https://t.co/C5jBfaDSRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyBsports That's what DVRs are for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting of Timmy is actually pretty good once I realized he's doing it upside down. https://t.co/7ucRbug5Cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ricktelander @CoachHorowitz13 The bravest man in sports. So sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poundingtherock Sorry about the typo. It's fixed now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb But I still voted no in the poll. The Bucks will probably do OK, but not up to their talent, which is stellar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb He's a tough competitor, and a decent motivator. He might do alright if he has good assistants and GM and lets them do details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@igorvolsky @FoxNewsSunday Landslide? Barely squeaking by in a handful of swing states while losing the popular vote by significant margin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only person who can see Westbrook's toe across the line when he's shooting free throws?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Somewhat reminiscent of Steichen's portrait of J.P. Morgan:
https://t.co/bh6YOoPT59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffGSpursZone Not entirely wrong but his play wasn't any better. I'd pick Manu over him even when playing badly bcuz of leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffGSpursZone Not mad at Jax, completely understand his point of view, but Pop made the right call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thing I learned today: Larry Bird is one day older than I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bowen_Arrow23 Thanks, man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neontaster @Azhog1977 having people's votes count the same is 'disproportionate?' Odd definition. Wyoming votes count 3x more than NY votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffGSpursZone Giannis is a question to which the Spur have no answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cajunfj40 @doctorow Probably right. I thought there were steering arms on rear axle but makes more sense with a swivel on front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorow Direct drive and rear wheel steering? Amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in Austin, you're welcome to drop by for my birthday party December 10: https://t.co/GIgwO3M1oP https://t.co/GIgwO3M1oP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was raised by a single mom who had health issues and paid my own way thru college washing dishes and building a tokamak.  #LiberalElite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p2cat I saw her once opening for some incongruous act, maybe Devo. It was unexpected and awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs overcome slow start and finish strong, edge the Wizards 107-105. https://t.co/SoOJtlB0Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody mentioned that @KyleAnderson5 might be in Pop's doghouse, so I had to drag out this tweet from last year. https://t.co/BzOSdYg0dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs sleepwalk to ugly loss against Magic https://t.co/ncYnwXfItT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DontSayItEddie It's been randomly logging me out all week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DontSayItEddie Yeah, definitely broken. Don't know how to fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DontSayItEddie I'd love to help, but I'm not on the technical end of the site.  I'll register the problem with SBNation tech support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quixem @spurs @NBA I just have this cereal box. https://t.co/p7NQYfXfdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to go for a drive. https://t.co/V2UmtspRpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs overpower Wizards with balanced effort, superior bench https://t.co/rVGTi87IuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffDongson @THESagerbomb Not true, he was on the SA Spurs roster in 2013 that went to the finals. Hardly played, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spurnandez210 Goodbye Charlie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBarrington2 I can draw a better brick: https://t.co/co6wqTHWss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse A real journalist would have checked out the ad and figured out it was a hoax in about 5 minutes, but you didn't bother to check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pau Gasol leads Spurs to a win, but a late run by the Kings becomes a teachable moment https://t.co/b1wutnHTAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From my first quarter notes from the Spurs/Kings game. https://t.co/6vTbWq9Teb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do I look like I'm employed to do? https://t.co/pkujjxvvWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Antonio at Houston, Final Score: Spurs get revenge on Rockets, 106-100 https://t.co/sgOwtVnpvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs comeback falls short as Rockets win 101-99 https://t.co/aYFapFsJOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current mood:  https://t.co/q0FgSD61kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald would be more except for the circuit breakers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bballbreakdown I took 2 years of it in college.  It was a long time ago, but going to refresh it before January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to polish up on my Russian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Butterfly on van. https://t.co/RZ0Xtt5yre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Plus having one polling place per county is clearly meant to suppress urban voting, since urban counties have more pop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald HTML, I mean. Text mail could be a few hundred bytes.  Modern mail takes up a few KB even to say "hi".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Technically possible but unlikely in the current era of HYML mail with attachments and no reply trimming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BernardKerik What a dope! They used software to eliminate duplicates and manually reviewed the small number that were not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta @Fahrenthold I hear Comey's Emily Littella impression is comedy gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta @Fahrenthold So, the first letter was completely pointless, except for the political impact of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffGSpursZone @Machen55 Can't disagree with that. They;re close, and you can make a strong case for either one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #NationalCatDay over yet? https://t.co/nDCSLhmlB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heat gave the Spurs all they could handle, but Kawhi Leonard wouldn't let them lose https://t.co/4jC8evPikm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabihalameddine @tbogg Reminds me of a Diane Arbus photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poundingtherock Tweet something good and I'll put it in the recap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chicazul It's not for opening the cover?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chicazul And the one that says 'Touch Tuning' adjusts the resistance, obviously.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>