<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[.@metlinkwgtn Great to feel looked after instead of like a pain in the arse! #safetyfirst 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@metlinkwgtn Thanks to 712 bus driver on Moxham Av bout 8.20am who waited for this slow cyclist to get to a safe place til passing. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happened to be reading about #GoByBikeDay when this swag from @aotearoabike showed up, cheers! Feeling like a champ. https://t.co/t7uzvpN41o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see the Speaker of the House heading into the Briscoes sale you gotta wonder if we're paying the poor guys enough #waitangiday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is with ACT's School of Practical Politics? It sounds like Hogwarts. I'm expecting candidates to be teens in witch hats. #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost Think you guys might have staffing issues. Came at 11.50 to queues out door, back at 1.30, bigger queues. https://t.co/2K2Nnx39Eq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling like war reporter wearing TV flak jacket to avoid getting killed... Would prefer cycle lanes over vest. https://t.co/99ODSvvjiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickmorgan, best soundbite yet! "It's not really a story about cycling. It's just a story about someone being a dick, really.'']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @patrickmorgan for sprucing up my ride with a bit of political participation #lovecycling. https://t.co/ZePb2I6uCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leebeenz despite abandoning us you will still be peer reviewing my comms plan, so you just wait and see, there was coffee-fuelled progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've had so much coffee you think you might be writing gibberish but it feels awesome so you keep going. https://t.co/0zaB9uHMrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandal_life Something I did before baby, about every 3 months in a fit of self loathing to no effect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandal_life Always thought Rudimental's Not Giving In would be quite motivational. It's basically a running playlist, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandal_life Fuck you I won't do whachu tell me, haha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandal_life Excellent. The Sam and Dave a very nice touch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jandal_life I can't believe Push It is not on the list yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn No.2 to Miramar, yesterday about 4.30 at Courtenay Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctrly Definitely a few  grumpy drivers, which is why I notice the lovely ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn ...your driver waits patiently, quips he'll add it to the bill, makes sure everyone is seated comfortably. Nice one. (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn A man on crutches, a blind woman with dog, and a mum with pram all pile onto a packed rush hour bus in Wgtn and... (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how honest this health star rating is. Wonder if they get half a point for putting it on the packet? #worthit https://t.co/fqmalsWEIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC Thanks for the new pedestrian crossing on Kilbirnie Cres, it's perfect - any chance of dropping speed limit to 30 too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised I have been listening to Wu Tang for the last 20m #whencouplesshareiPods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The excitement when you remember you have uneaten snacks, and the disappointment when you realise it's a chia bar. What was I thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuff my kid just threw in her bath while I wasn't looking: a full toilet roll, a clean nappy, a bucket and a gumboot #toddlerlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a marae to do govt's work #newzealandvalues: https://t.co/gVu68KW4he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leebeenz Yes, I think I was too quick to blame my kid, sounds like I'm not the only one who now has Candy Crush!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klimtypefoundry @arebee Change is always bad, that's a fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment of dread when you realise yr kid's key mashing has resulted in Windows10 being installed on your laptop. https://t.co/FGLlSa2446]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes Me too! It took my 8 months to realise my genderless backpack was actually the best nappy bag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My secret shame at my @SustainTrust desk... https://t.co/sQHcrzWrnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is why you should apply for jobs @SustainTrust... https://t.co/ZYmw2TJfGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come work with meeeeee! Go on.  https://t.co/CJQfFC0nki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirstenmairinz Yes, our Mum's already here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anika_Moa You've no idea how relieved I am to hear Songs for Bubbas 2 is on the way. If I have to sing Tahi Rua Toru once more, Wha...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell It must be hard without answers, tho no motive would really make it any less senseless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read @TaliaShadwell, bloody awful for the Stevens family. https://t.co/o0HYcR8nlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have only just realised that all these bath salts stories were not actually about bath salts. I'm getting old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story perfectly illustrates why we need to double the funding as well as #doublethequota #refugeeswelcome https://t.co/bO6nzAs4e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes the barista told me it was coz they make coffee to taste good in their disposable cups. Pfft. #coffeesnobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes That is not a cup I am keeping, despite its eco-goodness! I am on a journey, and have not come that far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stink, my KeepCup just got rejected at Fuel!? Boo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the bus driver notices you waving goodbye to your kid and gives a lil honk for extra thrill :) @metlinkwgtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @patrickmorgan on The Panel right now, music can be transcendent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just made my debut on @SustainTrust's Home Tips series... talking about poo. https://t.co/TP8banmhes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes It goes both fast and slow, don't it? Hope you're surviving it ok most days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMakes You had a baby! Congrats! If it makes you feel better my bub bit several of my rellies on first meeting 'em ystrdy.Then grinned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone not yet convinced there is 'real' poverty in NZ should listen to @InsightRNZ right now, heartbreaking stuff on the way families live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just used @dompost packaging to wrap freezer portions for my kid, thanks for the inspiration @CalebCarnie https://t.co/I6LyClUw0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a 'dry' topic, I know (pun intended) - but very important we get this right! https://t.co/FJAJNyIAX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, Bowie, so sad! What a man. https://t.co/Bm7K9FtR16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beaut photos by Rob Kitchin in today's @DomPost, best vox pop I've seen in ages. https://t.co/b8tRR0sYSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreerBerry Woah, well done Greer and team! Hope the first few days are peaceful. Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radionz Digging your music selection today, thanks for not playing Xmas carols!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overhead in Wellington: "What's wrong with jandals at work? These are dress-up jandals." #summerfeet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world has gone fucking mad, these look like the most awkward utensils ever invented. https://t.co/Xtn4wBS6ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we stay here we will surely die." Heartbreaking iv on @NzMorningReport with Syrian doctor. He sounded so weary. https://t.co/E1xD0ZTZkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voted for this beauty in @Forest_and_Bird's Bird of the Year, you should too. https://t.co/lDsOu2DKQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ What, you're not working on your yummy mummy beach bod yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't read the news all day, just caught up - the world is an awful place but no-one cares because rugby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beggar to other beggar on Bay Rd: "You got a $1.50 I can borrow?" #kilbirnietweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone listen to my talented friend @klimtypefoundry talk type on @radionz! He might finally explain what's so wrong with Comic Sans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trustpower Our internet has been dropping in and out all wknd, we're in Wgtn - help! Don't make me go outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinclairrobe Expect a flurry of tweets once every three months. Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michelle_duff I'm getting more and more irritated by the phrase 'took to social media to express their dismay/frustration/shock/horror'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dealing with crazy baby hour by taking her pants off and letting her watch The Block. #parentinghacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta Aw, poor kid. I reckon he's a clever dad for tricking so masterfully though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta Heh, that's awesome, I'm using that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revelling in my kid's ignorance of technology. I can put on @Anika_Moa and mumble along and she think it's me with the beautiful voice. Hah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of sicko neighbour has a wind chime in windy WELLINGTON?! #whywellingtonwhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relieved to see I am not the only one wearing my slippers at the fish n chip store. #SaturdayNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When coffee at Junglerama - in the school holidays - is your best offer for the day. #mumlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well put @keith_ng, you can't expect a grown-up debate without good data to start with: http://t.co/DajqMHEVN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherKMcC I know nothing about Pittsburgh - keep posting your stories and I will learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherKMcC Aw, thanks! Yeah, bit of a shock (planned, but life-changing), but slowly getting the hang of it. Helps that she's adorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherKMcC I don't know how we got ourselves into such a pickle. Are you based in Pennsylvania now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir Believe me, I'll be composing ranty comments for Stuff in no time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherKMcC $50k for a house, bargain!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir Yeah, I know you're right - four months out of the newsroom and I'm already one of the jerks saying 'is this news?!'. Soz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir I'm easily irritated by these stories, to me it's a no-brainer and shouldn't be news. But I know others might not see it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir I'm sure they know that adults are doing it for fun so why not talk realities instead of letting internet misinform them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir Why not? If kids know it's meant to feel good they're more likely to say no when it's uncomfortable or non-consensual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zippers, eh? What a hassle. (#firstdayoutofmaternityjeans)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear websites aimed at mums but that don't work proper on phones - get yr shit together, I am marooned on the couch shopping with thumbs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've made a successful transition to parenthood when you get your baby's poo on your top and you don't even bother to change it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyjackman Thanks mate, hope the new job is going well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyjackman Heya, do you know if there's a Givealittle for the Palani family? http://t.co/y9eqfLjAIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir Better be a page two lead Moir! I will very soon be flaky Mum friend, so it'll all work out. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look up, look up from your phones! Nice comic from @XTOTL: http://t.co/46rGr50PZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Jackson's farts ruled out as source of mystery explosion in Eastern Suburbs: http://t.co/gmrVxYnOVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez Only if it put them in a higher tax bracket though right? How many people would that apply to vs who never apply for refunds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez Fair call - it probably works for some and not for others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez As it would most likely hit people on lower incomes forced to work 2 jobs to keep up I'd still prefer to see it scrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez I see. Seems to rely on ppl have a good understanding of a fairly complex system and doing the paperwork though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez Does the refund happen automatically or do you have to apply for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez So you only end up paying more if the second job nudges you into a higher tax bracket?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon they should just scrap secondary tax altogether - seems a mean-spirited policy with little justification. http://t.co/3CjjbRsDO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like NZME. didn't think through the full stop at the end of their logo, it always looks like a mistake... http://t.co/Jw2hYXffzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JOY. TO. MY. HEART. Dancing Dad: http://t.co/SthrF3QSs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely entranced by this David Bowie through the year GIF: http://t.co/U1QwBmJgUx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>