<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastingCouch Just listening to the pod mate, it'll happen. 6 points over the next two games will have us looking pretty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwibardy @KloppGoff As long as that APA stays the same then sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote of the POD, @bglendenning " Oh I'm a slut" #FootballWeekly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10/10 from @beINSPORTS_NZ  here! Surely @beINmena can't be happy with this... I know we're small but do they really… https://t.co/iMvyccJOD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 omg, what really gripes me here is that they are getting paid to deliver such customer service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That lovely fob off with the hand. Always sends the right signal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pineyzb Liverpool to sign him up :)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we should sign @officialcwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Will Suarez break Liverpool hearts again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - I think that's the most inspired commentary about Sturridge that I've heard recently (re being loved). Totally agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening in from NZ @talkSPORTLive. Come on Reds, we've had our rest, time to wake up :) #YNWA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Salvatori_ @beINSPORTS_NZ Can't even get their false advertising correct....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Salvatori_ @beINSPORTS_NZ That doesn't fill me with much hope ;) Plus if I'm a Liverpool fan, looks I'm out of lu… https://t.co/USj9AJBtx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump, since you're signing Exec orders. How about 1 to sort out @beINSPORTS_NZ in NZ? #notthecraziestthingyouvedone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just making sure I'm not missing something.. If I sign up to @beINSPORTS_NZ, will I have access to every game live?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall @beINSPORTS_NZ  @SKYNZ true, i've never seen this. I'm just amazing that the @premierleague can allow this. #theworldwelivein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beINSPORTS_NZ @_Salvatori_ @SKYNZ Translation - you lied and know you really couldn't care less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KloppGoff is on @radiosportnz !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whyWellington? Because I like rain and wind stupid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrostieDaSnoman @patrick478 Thought it was a bit rich of him tbh. The kids looked like they were having heaps of fun though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 @FrostieDaSnoman zone, the language wasn't that bad and he seemed to think it would be completely PG. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 He told off the guy for saying Shit/Fuck a couple of times and everyone around him thought, why is he in the middle of the 2/2+1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I really close to this guy I think... He was sitting at the back. There was a loud guy who's language was mildly bad... 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Strange Games and Things always a good idea to get through the work day. Any other suggestions? @djspinna #DJspinna #upbeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac  Where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRyan Cheers! Hopefully go one better this time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect preparation for social football teams. Click on the link for registration information. #Wellington… https://t.co/5f4SyyndNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unions are hamstrung by their historical values. Can't be turning people down who want to get involved because they are too 'salesmen' like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't blame Chris Wood for going to China if an offer comes up. That's some serious money that would set him up for life...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 @NZ_Football @iluvnix17 @HawkesBayUnited @TeamWelly what happened ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the new garage project beer ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First @WgtnPhoenixFC game of the season for me this weekend. Looking forward to 3 points!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nelfoos5 @LucasLeiva87 @talkSPORTLive ohhh so saving this for the end of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tackle comes in from @LucasLeiva87 " , @talkSPORTLive. Is their anything this fine chap can't do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mentioned this yesterday and couldn't be happier for this chap :D Well done @LucasLeiva87 ! https://t.co/uzOUT2Lwhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastingCouch @LFC_Australia Sounds good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastingCouch Listen to @talkSPORTLive, always decent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tuned in from work in NZ. Looking forward to a good call @talkSPORTLive. You've set yourself high standards this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastingCouch @LFC_Australia Would be keen for sometime in Feb if you've got space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see @LucasLeiva87 still in a red shirt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great show this, keep it up guys! https://t.co/GBx7mjy39K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we all appreciate for a second that 3 more points on Saturday could see us top 4? Well done @WgtnPhoenixFC https://t.co/UipX2kjm0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 @KloppGoff @Tegal1234 Munchen is lovely this time of year ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie @Dale_Warburton Ah in isolation yes. But you forget, all of the other confeds are gaining spots in this process too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajman74 I think I heard Mou yell " Put it in the fricken mixer lads! "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajman74 Sorry.... we're not that direct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajman74 hence the :P maybe against top four club, still funny. Some nice direct play you guys had, right out of the Barons playbook :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManUtd eking out a 1-1 win against top four club  :P?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rajman74 Man Utd eking out a 1-1 win against title favourites  :P?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac turn off then :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodcastingCouch @jamesdrodriguez You heard him James, on ya come then son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhhhhh, short term loan @jamesdrodriguez to @LFC till the end of the season. Wouldn't that be lovely...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZ_Dave @patrick478 I think a shake up in the confederations could be on the cards. Some tweaks here and there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZ_Dave @patrick478 Just imagine.... Mexico having to play in New Cal... can you imagine...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kick around at 12pm, Boyd Wilson for anyone that is keen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall and the training grounds..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall When do we find out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chopahnz Looking forward to a cracking year in 2017 :) I'll be in touch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chopahnz Yeah I did, was great to be back for a bit. Went there a 2 days later, nice to see people staying away from that part of the pitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chopahnz yep, choice of platform also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 Ah just read the news. Strange thing to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarnestoMerrick @kyle_barnes15 have managed to steady the ship. Safe choice by Welnix but very wise. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarnestoMerrick @kyle_barnes15 Also countless examples where it's been a total flop. End of the day it's a gamble. The new coaches 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EarnestoMerrick First board to implement the co-coach model ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGourdie Seen UTD do it and he's like, "why don't i give that a go.."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely said @DevlinLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac Was Ben Sigmund the Nix's version of the Jamie Carragher?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys have the best Twitter account https://t.co/S35VM4NBOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall @Cussen91 No ..... it is brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DanielSturridge proving his worth right there! @talkSPORTLive #EVELIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return of the @DanielSturridge is on? @talkSPORTLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - "I'd want to beat him to death with my own shoe" 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnfieldIndex Listening on @talkSPORTLive, sounds fairly even so far no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - you'd have to say that Everton will undoubtedly pay if they can't make this pressure count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Everton well on top?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - no! The sound is brilliant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Already just by the pace of the call this game sounds like it's another level compared to last week. Fast start. #EVELIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know if it's where the mic is, but this crowd sounds ridiculous on @talkSPORTLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Let's go Reds! Looking forward to a quality call from you lads! Crowd sounds immense #EVELIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I was just gonna ask what your initial reaction was but there it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow... that's a family friendly end to Phoenix City...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcolemanmp Can think of worse jobs :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Yeah @LucasLeiva87 !  Time to shine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol - @talkSPORTLive doing a great job but I'll translate what he just said about that recent sub - "All @Boro fans should be saying FFS!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive Ok, we all good now :) I think...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me @talkSPORTLive, please don't say game over at 2-0 #midliv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just come back to it. @talkSPORTLive how's Mignolet doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive - Lovely sound coming through from the Away fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTLive, Fair call - keep up the good work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was about the weak bench :) @talkSPORTLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on @SMignolet ! #midliv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit unfair @talkSPORTLive , @LucasLeiva87 is class! #midliv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen in from NZ to #midliv on @talkSPORTLive. Expect nothing but the best from you guys, don't disappoint! Come on ya Reds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Aubameyang7 is only 11th, who the hell are the other 10 ?????? :O??????? https://t.co/DVmvQKNS29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 You guys are so stink to him ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm calling it now. The Nix are back. Don't care that it was the Mariners. That was awesome. #WELvCCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyle_barnes15 Possible last season too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved @WgtnPhoenixFC ! Great counter attack with @RoyKrishna21 to continue his goalrush!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This game just got fast..... real fast #WELvCCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andersonn92 Agreed, Footballs a fickle game sometimes. It can be the strangest things that can turn a season around.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>