<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls damn you are one ignorant excuse for a human being!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orwell’s lessons for the era of Trump: Rae | Toronto Star https://t.co/KBcbEdZxD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rover, wanderer
Nomad, vagabond
Call me what you will

But I'll take my time anywhere
Free to speak my mind... https://t.co/jOhqt1SwQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metallica - Wherever I May Roam https://t.co/3ejt806uxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Four Horseman of the Apocalypse https://t.co/qKVIoZ75Hh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megadeth Symphony of Destruction https://t.co/KLIacLlPcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I Play with Madness lyrics https://t.co/Mn2sBPGBKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iron Maiden - 2 Minutes To Midnight Lyrics (HD) https://t.co/lx0zi0OMvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this calls for a song......thanks Donald ya fuckin lunatic. https://t.co/Kq9TfNl9zU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Day - American Idiot lyrics [1080p] - YouTube https://t.co/N4n5ECjbrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dedicated to the 45th President.....here's hoping it won't last.. https://t.co/K5LrKujmGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Replacements - Left Of The Dial (with lyrics) https://t.co/a9ISCYQpR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hüsker Dü - 59 Times the Pain https://t.co/h7yiZihZW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Husker Du - Love Is All Around https://t.co/jbTwVcy9R1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power which has always started the greatest religious and political avalanches in history rolling has from... https://t.co/wewzMYKKHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[simpler times........sing it! https://t.co/y2lnSd1qqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshower - Chris Cornell - Euphoria Morning (1999) https://t.co/Ab0NGKzc8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets talk about Mental Health everyday, not just today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face—for ever.
George Orwell, 1984]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triumph the Insult Dog, killing it at the Inauguration... https://t.co/TkKij3Nt6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that... https://t.co/Q9vRlbmTXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarpdogBrown congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear John Mellencamp's Sobering Political Ballad 'Easy Target' https://t.co/czR0xT6NtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidGogoBlues Congratulations David,well deserved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Rodeo - Dark Angel (with Sarah McLachlan) https://t.co/NhlyIhsKyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[perfection,  lyrics &amp; music Steve Earle https://t.co/N2u5jjxVy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great vid &amp; powerful new song. https://t.co/OPUXsU3hIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case anyone was wondering why Hundreds of Thousands of Women were marching on the weekend, there are several... https://t.co/Bqi03fZAag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls don't let the door hit you in the ass on the way out.....#liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LavigneTavern Looks like you on the right with ton Bouche ouvrez...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lana_Macondo you have a sharp wit, don't stop!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsherman2407 just up here in Canada keeping everyone on their toes..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls looking rough there girl, all the lies getting to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They all hate you Donald, and the world knows your narcissism cannot stand the fact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They did vote, if you recall there were roughly 3million against you, better get Goebbels on the tv again...#nazis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Really?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverSun Blatherings of a fool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lana_Macondo @ezlusztig If he had a soul to begin with, after all he accepted the job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @seanspicer Hey Sean pull your head out of your ass, oh and Fox News it's too late for you folks....it's permanent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EPICGOPFAIL Damn that was funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNL's "Shirtless Putin" Just Hilariously Mocked Trump's Pathetic Inauguration Crowds https://t.co/sEGEFx2dkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We out last night to Conway, Washington had some good food, conversation and caught two bands over the course of... https://t.co/hETGfqoLdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this! https://t.co/EAgvBbihoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took a few months in the late 60's &amp; early 70's for people to come together against the Vietnam War &amp; to... https://t.co/9P0e9dovNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“As I went walking I saw a sign there
And on the sign it said "No Trespassing."
But on the other side it didn't... https://t.co/kwg2s1spMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petunia &amp; the Vipers https://t.co/qUxRSU080M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and People do have the Power, the Suffragette movement, Vietnam protests, Civil rights, equal rights for all. https://t.co/pixGaWvREa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always have faith, the strength of people in numbers will always win out over hatred &amp; ignorance. See you later... https://t.co/CytlPPuKi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[here she is folks........good luck America you are going to need it. https://t.co/JKQQK7Vvah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss Nixon. Compared to these Nazis we have in the White House now, Richard Nixon was a flaming liberal.
Hunter S. Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In these days of difficulty, we Americans everywhere must and shall choose the path of social justice…, the path... https://t.co/egcKuJGVlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd new song from Ryan Adams https://t.co/uXmbLM7ORM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Adams - To Be Without You (Audio) https://t.co/uFflyEMevr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lyrically brilliant.................The professor Neil Peart. https://t.co/gpLzqbNHtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox is live streaming Washington inauguration ceremonies, Lee Greenwood is singing, a sea of white faces, Trump... https://t.co/03jD4Ne9uy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my all time favorite Yes tune, complex lyrics, harmonics, structure......15:37 of perfection.....Steve Howe,... https://t.co/9NcBTyfypf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Howe, Acoustic Guitar https://t.co/NWWybtqbqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Howe... Lead Guitar https://t.co/zmNuKdUVHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect.” 
 Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four years ago today I left New Brunswick at 3am on a solo drive across Canada &amp; the U.S....a 5870km journey thru... https://t.co/mG0QWT6w6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss Cathy https://t.co/m4uM2JEpqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tone........................Sept 2017 Las Vegas play it loud! https://t.co/4yrvhDgeWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancross Rightly so, yesterday's news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these... https://t.co/Ij43BKdov9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just a shout out to anyone interested in an amazing 4 days of music in Las Vegas, this will be my 4th year in a... https://t.co/AnVb5LBqG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[caught Anders in New Hampshire in 2012 in the White Mountains, looking forward to seeing him again in Las Vegas... https://t.co/ZDdA7iuczz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the incomparable Mavis Staples, this Sept Las Vegas Big Blues Bender Sept 7 - 10, 2017 https://t.co/E92UBDSzka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Resist much, obey little.” 
 Walt Whitman,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @NBCNews You are bat shit crazy, just sayin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So here's my playlist for those informative teen years... the idea is to list 10 records that shaped/defined the... https://t.co/objj00s6uP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[little more of Doyle. https://t.co/x326RTPHbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[been waiting about a decade to get a chance to see this guy, one of the albums of the year......Las Vegas Sept @... https://t.co/GAEAJtmxj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN As compared to yourself who seems to be in a total meltdown everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig This will go on, but only for so long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zhu_amy3 @realDonaldTrump You are both delusional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A plan to restore Grizzlies to the Cascades Mountains of Washington https://t.co/057FPHAAoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As usual there is a great woman behind every idiot".
John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday morning, Nov 24, 2002, Wilson Rd. Oshawa,On. you had tea, I had a coffee at a Tim Horton's of all things,... https://t.co/5j4e2YdqWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta watching from Canada, stay the course sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[masterpiece.......Adrian Belew lead guitar.....Bowie, coke addiction in full flight, the thin white duke persona. https://t.co/QceyIlZDvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bowie with Tin Machine.......play it loud! https://t.co/KvqMGwyCxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be my love, we will be gods on nite flights
With only one promise, only one way to fall... https://t.co/RsX9JtXeh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig He lost it long ago, unhinged he is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyMcNulty Ok that was funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nov 24,2002, I first met Cathy Stokes, at a Tim Horton's, romance is not lost on me. We had a tea &amp; coffee and a... https://t.co/4YscPKfzwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone does not think that Russia &amp; in particular Putin is not trying to establish a new world order with... https://t.co/lJip58Tfvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And one more for the man who would be king... https://t.co/AkFtD6AOCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dedicated to Donald Trump. https://t.co/LT8AhbfxSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @realDonaldTrump Oh I think he has much bigger problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think your egg is just about cooked Donnie...impeachment to follow, terrific....terrific!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine Coast https://t.co/bKn2sj0omd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bowie in One of his many incarnations. https://t.co/GuiCUTdaxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my faves https://t.co/ksfdxit8a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please consider supporting Vic &amp; Debbie in the memory of their son Mitchell. https://t.co/p7cn4xZGig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Led Zeppelin-Since I've Been Loving You w/ lyrics https://t.co/J31RGgM20D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Page Lead Guitar, Happy Birthday.....play it loud! https://t.co/c9B7sJzjux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday James Patrick Page https://t.co/m1x2w2PY4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a little shout out to a new band for me, playing the Big Blues Bender in Las Vegas Sept 7-10 2017. 

Guy Fortier https://t.co/49KZnCt4Op]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EinarsonLynn talked to elder Einarson this morning, might take a trip he tells me....wait for it....Thunder Bay..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EinarsonLynn Saw this, going to pass, U2 3x already. Should be good though!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>