<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my car detailed and protected. Really recommend Chris from Finer Details and CQFinest coating. Awesome job, pics to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Bell’s Palsy contagious? just asking for a friend. https://t.co/X63aJnKO7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you “tell ‘im he’s dreaming’”? $62k is outrageous. https://t.co/AwW7HC3T3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Guptill should answer ‘only you know how awesome I am’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs Martin Guptill currently interviewing Martin Guptill “i’m on the sideline with Martin Guptill - are you awesome (girly giggle)?”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Nadal had Federer’s talent, he would be 50 majors+; if Federer had Nadal’s mental strength, he would be unbeaten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jptocker FYI Gazely’s have a 08 Nissan GTR for sale, $62k. Only 2,500 donuts on the clock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer has won over $100m in prize money in his career. Nadal has a smoking hot girlfriend (+$80m).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal, I think, will pound Raonic into oblivion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit tougher for Rog in the second set, but takes it out 7-5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed missing a few now, must have dinner reservations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was my last tweet sexist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The four babes of NZ sport. Sophie looking for a +? https://t.co/swHjBjLSn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed hammered Zverev 6-1, 19 minutes. Amazing performance in the first set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jptocker who’s he calling? Better not be Lisa Carrington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger is going to hammer this bloke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsonga is 6′ of unbelievable talent and 2″ of mental floppiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsonga is one of those guys that can do anything, just not twice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am using Skype for Business on iPad w/AirPods. Work perfectly for business calls whilst watching tennis …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tsonga won no events last year, and $2.25m. Wawrinka won US Open and three others and over $6m. I played no matches and won $0.00 exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two good tennis matches tonight: Tsonga/Wawrinka and Federer/Some Guy. #aussieopen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JamesBlunt doesn’t tweet much, but he is a social media genius nonetheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I like rat. But the tail - not so much” https://t.co/ThC3KdXzaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I went forAtlanta over Green Bay in today’s playoff. They 10-0 after Q1. Kiss of death?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seppi breaks to 6-5, Stan breaks back to 6-6. Tie-breaker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bugger, now he’s doing the 3-ball bullshit. Just did 5 balls. Stan! #wawrinka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another thing I like about Stan #wawrinka , he gets two balls and serves; none of this 3 or 4 ball bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On at the same time as the world’s 2nd-best backhand #wawrinka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wild New Zealand is awesome TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent 2 hours washing and drying my car, and now it’s raining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeff_neave not to be sneezed at. I missed my bursary physics paper by 4 hours, or maybe 24 hours. Destined for management?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeff_neave thanks Jeff. Certainly wasn’t any coaching from me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to mention pigeons blocking the roads … https://t.co/wWzP4f8vI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why the US under Trump is f****d  https://t.co/jw81lCnSGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That doesn’t sound like healthy eating. https://t.co/ppA6OC5f3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voodoo Lounging - YouTube - I want one! https://t.co/gCzTZekleh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter, Grace, achieved NCEA Level 2 endorsed with Excellence. Chip off the old block? #motherssidehasthebrains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this bloke playing Andy Murray wins a set, he will not make it to through 4 sets. He will die. #aussieopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New favourite working position … MacBook Pro on lap in TV room, watching cricket and calc’ing profit margin. Touch bar invaluable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good win to NZ #blackcaps. Great sportsmanship by Bangladeshi team. Great century Kane Williamson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I can go through gas at 5 mpg! #notreallygettingone https://t.co/mn6GvWeoEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Ford GT instrument cluster in action, still wondering about the white.  https://t.co/RWtvaB3nPC via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foam cannon filter is closed, is a bitch to get at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s 8:50 am, just spent 90 mins cleaning the *inside* of my car #roadtrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Athleticism … https://t.co/1AdS5tpqIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sophie Pascoe, Sarah Walker, or Lisa Carrington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not on fire, wot you talking about? https://t.co/IU9dZ3Oo4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#jacksock is a good player, but also a wanker #asbtennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t trust blokeswith beards and no moustaches #jacksock #asbtennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordered my iPhone 8 https://t.co/mdJUNlhhay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful power hitting from Corey Anderson, 94 runs off 41 balls #blackcaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got bad news for you relative to Holden’s. https://t.co/ek7qcv5xAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure White is the best colour though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ordered a new car, it's a Ford https://t.co/NqP2zrGLCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/4 of an apple slice, Fairlie Bakehouse. https://t.co/wG2OZVQ6Av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venison &amp; Cranberry pie. Fairlie Bakehouse. https://t.co/4AvZvIBt7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[… but on the bright side, Merry Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, the #NYJETS still no good, down 41-3 to New England…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In RAINY Blenheim, sunniest place in NZ, on the way to Murchison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzewok @jptocker @roddrury then I won’t hear the satisfying ‘whack’ of those 230m drives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those Chinese are jolly cunning. https://t.co/ojg9v8LYIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jptocker @roddrury mine don’t fall out. They are pretty good, a genuine innovation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jptocker they are super easy to set up, and sound great. Don’t fall out; but I would say … two weeks for the first one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little box in a big box. https://t.co/wiPHsN6m7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I though MIA would find it a bit chilly at #NYJETS , but they are HOT. Giving NY a walloping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefansw 13-inch MacBook Pro - Space Grey https://t.co/Wvtub3l0U6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefansw which one what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NYJETS at home to MIA at 2:30. Currently, they are ‘removing the snow’. MIA must be looking forward to the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if he played for #NYJETS  would be very frustrated https://t.co/zEHDgtGEjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much is £214,950 in NZD?#AstonMartinDB11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had my worst round of golf / important business meeting ever yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ordered the airbuds. $269.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzewok J, where you tomorrow? Do you fancy lunch on RR, 12:30 or 1:00? Apparently I need to ask you about P2P, but that’s just an excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the Chief Technology Evangelist for Salesforce count to 7? I bet he’s terrific at conferencing though. https://t.co/yQNSiC9dvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdered a baby bird this morning, and stole the nest. 1 feather left. https://t.co/zjZiixoDwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacBook Pro shipped, due Friday. I’ll be in Auckland on Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NYJETS win 23-17. I’m certain it was my threats to swap allegiances that motivated them .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NYJETS down 3-17 to 49′ers at halftime. #NYJvsSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #NYJETS are at SAN Franscisco #NYJvsSF. They really really need a win. If the 49′ers win i’m switching back to them instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacBook Pro - preparing for shipment! Will I get it this week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do we think - can @joeboxerparker get the job done? I think so, but I’m on tenterhooks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you just feel like fish and chips. That’s today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Local Rule Eliminates Penalty for a Player Who Accidentally Causes a Ball to Move on the Putting Green https://t.co/oroVoulbeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jptocker mate is a 13? No touch bar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacBook Pro 13 very light also. Mine arrives 21st December.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went into JBHiFi this morning to look at the MacBook Pro 13. It is so small, I reckon smaller than the iPad Pro and Keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ernie Els Demonstrates the Art to a Great Swing - YouTube https://t.co/wTCBqWnDYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reckon Eliza McCartney could twist @jptocker like a pretzel. And I reckon he’d love it. https://t.co/TTYY93Teo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are testing my patience. Watched the game wearing my ‘49ers hat. https://t.co/2Nr0DkeI9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nyjets down 14-0 end of the first q.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nyjets vs Colts. About time for a win, but not a good start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired to post some toes on Twitter. https://t.co/CmUCr7m9Cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m putting @nzewok forward for #Phoenix coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired to post my cat's nose on Twitter. https://t.co/6MO1JUHl8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First of a series? Husband, mother, next door neighbour, postman… https://t.co/44GO22z8Ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trent Boult consistently takes awesome catches #blackcaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner at Whitebait. First time for me, had to eat a bit early as was busy. Impressed, would recommend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jptocker might have to switch back to thr ‘49ers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell #NYJETS lost another one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauden so fast, he scored AND converted a try before France got back to their end!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>