<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#CureRTD #RareDiseaseDay2017 Riboflavin Transport Disorder formerly known as Brown Vialetto Van Laere Syndrome. Sen… https://t.co/maoLWFPvto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZcivildefence Just saw your #DropCoverHold ad on TV. It needs captioning for Deaf &amp; Hard of Hearing. @able_NZ can help. Thx. #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously twitter what's the deal with diesel prices in NZ. 102.99 in Levin. 133 in Wellington !?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emtvnews @TheStoryNZ Love to see the live show with captions every day too so we can watch every night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emtvnews @TheStoryNZ Gr8 story. Love Coed &amp; 1 of our fav terps too! Any chance of captioning on the video? Thanks https://t.co/3APuKyysy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo look at this news, more content with captioning / subtitles available in New Zealand with Amazon Prime, laun… https://t.co/qpiJTFmV2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ um what's the latest? Thanks https://t.co/rp0Ldwt94n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp Hi, does Amazon Prime, launched in NZ today, have closed captioning? If so count us in! Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ what's the story with NZ5082 to Hamilton please? Thanks https://t.co/uqBNMYFu6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClearSigns4U only Netflix has captioning in NZ. No captions for Tvnz on demand either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breakfaston1 change your "LIVE AUCKLAND" on screen now, you are in Akaroa!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuffBusiness will these be accessible with captioning on @NZStuff ? #FingersCrossed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzonscreen awesome - thanks is that a new feature? (I will spread the word!). What % of your content has captioning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzonscreen Hi, can you give me an update on when your great content will have captioning pls? Great for Deaf, HoH, ESL, Mobile Devices. Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSeeHear love this! Audio, #BSL and Captioning / Subtitles, awesome. Happy Holidays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome news @AirNZFairy - if you export the captions file from YouTube you can upload them to Facebook too. Thanks… https://t.co/P651DlTAav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see this @WgtnCC #WellyXmas supporting Wellington Children's Hospital too. #Hospi will be happy https://t.co/Ve338v2wZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ thanks much appreciated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @jmodoh @SKYNZ why can't the live captions from @EricssonTVMedia in Aus be made available to Sky Ch 85 in NZ? #SameContent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome news #captions work with Netflix download service, just in time for #schoolholidays #roadtrips. Thx… https://t.co/3WPdcInx2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNationTV3 loved the show this year, thx. Be gr8 to have live captions so our family can watch on Saturday not Sunday. #NewYearResolution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Netflixhelps Hi, with your new download service will you have access to the closed captions too? Thanks #LoveNetFlix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ Bro is glistening = your browser is closed with autocaps. Pls add good ones. Thanks… https://t.co/pWLlKqQ2pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ Hi team, Msg from Miss 10. Any chance of closed captions for this please, thanks (tweeting from CHC enrou… https://t.co/LFcPm1kqA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ @StopPressNZ looks interesting. Will your video have closed captioning? #gamechanger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deaf_Aotearoa @NZ_ODI @nickywagner link please. Thanks so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@attitude_tv gutted,  loved them last year but following on twitter now. Thanks so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@attitude_tv Hi, are you live streaming #AttitudeAwardsNZ with captions tonight? Any chance of a link? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to Sean, steward on @FlyAirNZ for welcoming Miss 10 in #NZSL enroute to Christchurch NZ5339… https://t.co/ACrCgzAudF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Message from Miss10. Thx for the captions for #NZLvFRA @able_NZ @theNatFdnDeaf @NZonAir #family viewing #AccessAllAreas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top job to pilots on NZ459 from @FlyAirNZ landing to applause in Wellington. #homesweethome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightboxNZ thx for reply but same answer for 2 years and quite a few upgrades. #amazonprime is coming #Netflix has them #CaptionitNZ #Deaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LightboxNZ  heh when you do your upgrade 24 Nov any chance you're adding captioning for deaf? Thanks #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonVideo Hi, keen to know if all your content has captioning for deaf? #captionfans #nz #BringItOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss10 "Mum where are the captions @Breakfaston1 today? I liked them last week". #CaptionitNZ #DeafKids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday avo. Checking @NZGetThru home supplies &amp; @radionz channel tuned to our wind up radio - Frequencies here: https://t.co/ghnb6qltue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNationTV3 big difference between discussion and commitment. #geonet and NZers deserve much better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So little video has captioning for deaf and hard of hearing in NZ - on TV, social media &amp; news online. #Whatdidtheysaymum? #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kaikouracheese we'll put in an advance order now for next year. Love your cheese, #kiakaha… https://t.co/dJfobzyLeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ yup, on the NZ Parliament app (complete with captions) or freeview channel 31.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCDEM you rock! Thank you (no pun intended)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandCDEM Hi, any chance you could fix the auto captions on this vid https://t.co/OmFIISZA5n to make good ones? Thx #DeafKidsInThisHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Responding to the monster" and yes we do need a 24/7 monitoring centre. https://t.co/E0Dnl4Xz2j A great read from @geonet's Director #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZcivildefence Hi, thanks so much for taking the time to get back to me, know you are busy. Keep up the great work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZcivildefence Is this the link for people https://t.co/0rrCZDcyDH Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @1NewsNZ will you be having #NZSL interpreters on any bulletins soon for #EQNZ? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TVNZ TV1 is broadcasting now with live captions thanks to @able_NZ #EQNZ @CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0% of NZ public broadcasters provide 'subtitles' / captions online. @wendyyouens (In fact 0% of private broadcasters too!). #languagesmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss 10. Mum, when will morning TV have captions #ImSickOfIt? Me. #WishIKnew. #TiredofWaiting #equalaccess #Deaf #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZGetThru please add a good caption track for this not the auto ones. Thanks #CaptionitNZ #DeafAware]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KNVRAJU Do you have a link to a research paper / case study.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightboxNZ when will you have caption tools? Your parent @SparkNZ are about 'life, potential, energy &amp; creativity' for 'all NZers' #deaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Er thanks but @LightboxNZ @SparkNZ you SHOULD be captioning already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic. @LightboxNZ advert with captions in @SparkNZ shop. The good: the ad has captions. The Bad: Lightbox doesn't… https://t.co/0ph7WN89QN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@edchatNZ Any chance of a shout out for this school holiday programme in Wellington? https://t.co/EaSiVCYoKF Thanks so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools out! Have fun at Wellington Association for Deaf Children Holiday Programme https://t.co/EaSiVCYoKF #Deaf #HardofHearing #Whanau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can find Wellington Association for Deaf Children here on Facebook too: https://t.co/3LwOyPf1HC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School holiday fun. Wellington Association for Deaf Children Holiday Program, Age 5-13 #NZSL https://t.co/sJu8hj5dSQ https://t.co/PTAgIjUd8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 in 6 New Zealanders watch TV with captions https://t.co/biG2CzXVTY #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss10 wants to follow #Paralympics on TV. Great its on FTA TV, but sad only 1 hour highlight show has captions #deaf #ROLLING #SportsFan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezbear curbs!! @LloydBurr is there a version of this vid with c.captions? (Miss10, deaf, wheelchair user would love to see it) @mojomathers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV needs captioning too - TV, web, app, phone. #accessibility #inclusion #Families https://t.co/7Rt5VpFRLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss10 'when will I have captions on the Rugby? It's not fair, they have them in Aus'
Me 'Sorry, I don't know' 
#inclusion #deaf #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captions on Parliament TV show NZ broadcasters how to do it. Available TV, online &amp; VirtualHouse App. #digital #a11y https://t.co/ChVflorpi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3playmedia @CaptionitNZ 1:6 use captioning in New Zealand https://t.co/lklpAiVRge See page 26 https://t.co/FYE25ffkkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCNews24 Hi, do you have a version of this with captioning? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@accessinclusion super thanks. Hopefully some of these captions will appear on NZ TV as part of passthrough captions :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoadingDocs Hi, will they all have closed captions? Thanks so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@accessinclusion Awesome news. Can't get the press release link working, can you please forward. Thanks. Totally agree #captionsmatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ @skysportnz Hi, pls tell me what code (SN) is on this guide. (M) (W) (F) (NZL) Ok but struggling with SN https://t.co/Ck8BpPy6Cc? thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rikkipoynter thanks for sharing my "I cried today", I appreciate it. Handswave. https://t.co/nL60b3Y5QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I cried today". Some thoughts from me. https://t.co/nL60b3Y5QL #family #inclusion #Deaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fbaccess Hi, QQ, can FB Live &amp; Continuous Live Video support captioning (for Deaf / HOH)? Any info I can read? Thanks so much #a11y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpinoffTV @duncangreive Great its going to prime TV but sucks that my kids can't watch it together now - no captions for deaf on demand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will be able to watch the Olympics with my family and my school friends" like "every hearing person" Miss 10. https://t.co/sPZNwy1qgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJCairney @ChrisKeall @DylanReeve No issue with it going to ondemand but my kids cant watch it without captioning &amp; TVNZ OD has none! so..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vebbed and drive a big red car?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkypeBusiness where can I get some more info about this? Is it same language closed captioning too? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're just temporarily 'abled'. Design for the future you! https://t.co/vkJF3eUaor #Design #UX #a11y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald Pls change the FB topics assigned to this post. They are inappropriate. Thank you. https://t.co/eEiDm47bp4 https://t.co/e24UuOoJii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraging broadcasters to caption is not working. 2 new TV channels. no captions. https://t.co/XKPPtFWwBE (no captions on demand either)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaikaWaititi @wilderpeople Family cant wait to see this with captioning on NZ DVD release, love to see it at the movies! Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building an inclusive New Zealand requires ALL of us to play our part. Some thoughts from me https://t.co/DwGikwXgLl #DeafKids #a11y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riboflavin Transport Deficiency First International Conference. #RareDisease @TeamBVVL #BVVL https://t.co/2t5dlTyIoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCaptStudio Can you point me to a link about the govt funding available. Thanks? PS I know your tweet is old :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss 10 "Mum thats a lot of cupcakes we need to sell to pay for the captions" 
Me "Yes" $200K required! https://t.co/UmLOoNfp6H #CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grrr. This week alone, 3 TV services have promoted their 'service' to me. We won't/can't sign up until there is captioning. #a11y Win:Win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand new channel BRAVO replacing FOUR has 0% captioning. Must be captioned by law in US. https://t.co/AIHp7BneDJ https://t.co/4tDm40B42M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall Great. Shame it can't magic up closed captions for the deaf at the same time. #Netflix overload here (it has captions!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbilityTV Thanks for the information, appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BravoNewZealand Happy to learn that you're looking at it, sad it ain't there at launch. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BravoNewZealand Thanks. Any with captioning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BravoNewZealand Is your TV listing for the week anywhere? Freeview guide online doesn't appear to have it. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbilityTV much appreciated. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcdm4oc @Madman Yup, been there. #Waiting #fingerscrossed for #captions #wilderpeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcdm4oc @orchtweets Lucky you. I spotted a showing in NY advertising captions see https://t.co/WzH4Q2ib7G no captions in NZ #wilderpeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mum, WHEN are they going to put captions on TV in the morning? I've had enough" #DeafKids #accessibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mojomathers @messagesentnz No nothing here yet. @NZParliament? @CaptionitNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZParliament Should we be able to see them now? Haven't popped up and our TV set to captions always on. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mojomathers same here. School closed today (conferences) so we are all watching! #Destiny]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>