<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fun_Beard have you called your senators? or are you just sitting back and doing nothing? because spoiler alert: she might not get confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam @UC_Indivisible @IndivisibleCin @indivisiblecbus @IndivisibleOhio Hey @MklaEames call him if you are free!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiatolentino @samfbiddle what did this say???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awesome! I've been trying to find a website like this for the past week!!! https://t.co/vWVa3dvfC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[please be the pee pee https://t.co/gdeqy8YZtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gayrightswatch glad to see that you've awoken :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The account @gayrightswatch just came out of a two year hibernation :-/ https://t.co/FMP4zS0BTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usuallydecent that would be so awesome! i'm applying to jobs right now actually haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater I should probably quit my job. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@betsy_rioter @j_lowd could you link me to the Lyft statement please? And yes it's awful that the Uber CEO has ties to Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newyorkist also I just want to say that I fucking hate Trump and want to do whatever I can to resist. But this Uber thing confuses me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newyorkist "talk to Trump" as in "convince Trump to cancel the EO"? Wouldn't that be a good thing? Shouldn't we encourage his questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newyorkist I see. That's fucked up that he's a Trump supporter. But I thought I read that the CEO was specifically against this EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newyorkist @scottbix but isn't there an argument to be made that they should provide transportation to help the protesters? Honest question]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater Also full disclosure: I work for Uber and think that they're a sketchy company. But specifically on this issue I'm just confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure I understand the #DeleteUber movement. Did Lyft boycott JFK like how the cab drivers did? If not shouldn't we also #DeleteLyft?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_lowd @scottbix did lyft boycott JFK as well as the taxi cab drivers? If not aren't they as evil as uber?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j_lowd @scottbix what I meant to ask is why boycott JFK Airport when all the protestors may need access to taxis to get to and from protest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottbix i'm really confused. why are the taxi's boycotting JFK when the ban has nothing to do with them? it's all about Trump's EO right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes but it's only for people being detained, right? doesn't actually negate the whole EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg i think this article is misleading bc it only applies to people currently detained at airpots. doesn't halt whole order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope @alfranken runs for president in 2020 and beats @realDonaldTrump.  Being beat by a former @nbcsnl cast member would be perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleTeam is there a website out there that has prewritten emails and dialogues on a variety of topics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most uplifting concert I've ever been to. Great way to end such a horrible week! Also I almost died in a mosh pit.… https://t.co/eSRDXfMxGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST TOUCHED FRANK TURNER'S SWEATY BODY. K I CAN FUCKING DIE NOW https://t.co/o30gTxmUr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is horrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint I want to participate in #resisttrumptuesday, do you have any good templates I can send to my reps regarding the EPA freeze today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csydelko new subscriber here, ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schneider4IL10 Hi Congressman Schneider! May I ask why you're going to attend the inauguration? Will you be attending the @womensmarch too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Is it only Representatives so far? How long do you think before we get a senator refusing to go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FronteraWine We really love your wine.  Do you have tasters we want to taste more!!! https://t.co/jqlutYRAmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump actually, you're the one that's bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg he'd also have to allow for immigrants to become president since he was born in germany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg what's worse than this? it sounds pretty bad already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I listened to Trump's press conference on Wednesday and now this article is scaring the shit outta me https://t.co/NPgF2sMdLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so bizarre I don't even know what to make of it https://t.co/GkmQt3ew6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamchrisscott @FBI who was raker!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamchrisscott what's your address?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a simulation I'm not even kidding this is what I believe now https://t.co/sXkdoDgCHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never understand why Colorado is incapable of plowing the highways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fart Jon Hendren Would Have Won The Election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13,773 minutes of French studied in 2016! That's about 230 hours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 sucks already :-( https://t.co/boL2BXdZSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater And my other resolution is to take care of my body by lowering my cholesterol, losing weight and feeling great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My New Years Resolution is to study French every week in 2017 for at least two hours, plus another language (swahili? russian? not sure yet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater I am really proud of myself. This was a huge success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahdaniel ive yet to see anyone do that but if i did I'd block them from my feed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This scares the shit out of me. https://t.co/p7VW6xnQsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg i value everything you made this year. even the bad tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fart the celebs are at it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahdaniel @tamardrop name her tamar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahdaniel are you gonna do this every time you see a cute dog that needs to be adopted and then end up having dozens of dogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corybe so sad that @breaking is shutting down! are there even any good alternative breaking news apps out there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently he died. This year is a nightmare. https://t.co/rBOJB8B2rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How am I going to survive 2017 without @BreakingNews there to alert me about all the inevitable calamities? Really sad to see the app go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craiggles Adam and I saw the raccoon walking up to the house and the other day I heard something scurrying around in the attic or roof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we might have a raccoon living in our attic but I'm afraid to tell my roommates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csydelko i like how you drop $400 on @tacobell like it's nothing but then wait till ur phone is in smithereens before getting a new one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csydelko She retweets photos of naked people and also I think she's a Trump supporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csydelko @elijahdaniel no, pink with a blond streak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrganicValley We love chugging your Egg Nog as part of our December Daily Food Challenge. Thank you for doing what you do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@V8 Okay didn't try that smoothie recipe but but we mixed it with a coconut flavored @enjoyLaCroix and an @emergenc packet. Delicious!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@V8 we work at @Uber where they stock the kitchen full of v8 everyday. we want to find more ways to get creative with it, any ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@V8 original! my coworker and i did it as a fun food challenge. what a delight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just chugged a @V8 at work, what a great way to start off the morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As it turns out, Pickle Soda is very good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater @tamardrop - https://t.co/GNGAU2I3Wk: i would like to stay in bed all day, @deansdip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit???! https://t.co/Pvr3jkW1oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Um. Except it's actually Thanksgiving?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovHowardDean Not saying you're wrong but if he made it up why does Ford appear to be confirming it? https://t.co/l7vNTTclcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SortaBad I'm confused, if this is fake why doesn't Bill Ford come out and say so? Why doesn't he deny that the phone call happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessesingal I'm confused, if this is fake why doesn't Bill Ford come out and say so? Why doesn't he deny that the phone call happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did my earbuds make it through the wash and dryer and still work totally fine?? Thanks @skullcandy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg @realDonaldTrump HOW ARE YOU DOING THIS??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten Romney would be acceptable as sec of state but I thought he passionately hated Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariavt you did this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this has to be intentional!!! https://t.co/DycWWCUfRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draining the swamp am I right??? https://t.co/rDmfvPDPJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump *speeches, Mr President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_harlock piss me off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg I'm really sorry that you have to put up with this shit every single day. Please keep doing what you're doing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how post-election I assumed I'd have to find a new, non-political hobby. As it turns out, all I think about is politics now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usuallydecent oh nevermind i thought you meant you were bleeding out of your ear like a brain hemorrhage lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddow Either Jon Stewart or Michael Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is so important. https://t.co/HbovfCy3tV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jakewater And is this what it was like to be a Republican for the past eight years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm furious all the time now. Is this what I'm going to be like for the next four years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatanaOfLogic @tomcoates @NickBolton13 Do you openly admit to being transphobic? Or do you have some BS reason why that label is unfair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten they didn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten i want to barf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having anxiety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elijahdaniel sometimes i wake up at night in a hot flash from having a stress dream where i'm writing an angry FB rant about trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothypmurphy she's gonna be a strong advocate for limiting free speech rights of reporters as first lady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@n8ruessupdates thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@n8ruessupdates i don't really use itunes, know of anywhere else i can hear it for free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismessina i just realized i'm the 9999th person to make this joke. sorry for wasting your time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismessina I don't think something like this would really catch on. Sorry :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackantonoff Definitely. Last night I woke up in a hot flash because I was having a dream I was writing an angry fb rant about Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Uber driver is taking us through a McDonald's drive-through at 2:30am I this real life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@n8ruessupdates hey, any idea if there's any truth to the rumors circulating around in this thread? https://t.co/meOWar3SiC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>