<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In politics shared hatreds are almost always the basis of friendships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas improve. The meaning of words participates in the improvement.
Plagiarism is necessary. Progress implies it. I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diligence is the mother of good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No man but a blockhead ever wrote, except for money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe that fits one person pinches another; there is no recipe for living that suits all cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spectacle is the moment when the commodity has attained the
total occupation of social life. Not only is the rel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is generally the best vindication against slander.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paley's argument is made with passionate sincerity and is informed by the best biological scholarship of his day, bu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If stupidity got us into this mess, then why can't it get us out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time of production, commodity-time, is an infinite accumulation
of equivalent intervals. It is the abstraction o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is so fatal to religion as indifference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is what you are in the dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me what you eat, and I will tell you what you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philosophy:  A route of many roads leading from nowhere to nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never continue in a job you don't enjoy. If you're happy in what you're doing, you'll like yourself, you'll have inn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Middle Ages, this incomplete mythical world whose perfection lay
outside it, is the moment when cyclical time, w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Health Day is an opportunity to highlight the problem, but above all, to stimulate action. It is an occasion t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sloth steels from the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the history is a divine work of fiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is a genius at least once a year; a real genius has his original ideas closer together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can turn painful situations around through laughter. If you can find humor in anything, even poverty, you can su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life simply is. It follows its course. Give yourself to the moment. Let life reveal itself
to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to learn than to be rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man is a damn fool for at least five minutes every day; wisdom consists in not exceeding the limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anger is never without an argument, but seldom with a good one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All changes, even the most longed for, have their melancholy; for what we leave
behind us is a part of ourselves; we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Between two groups of people who want to make inconsistent kinds of worlds, I see no remedy but force.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing more tragic than to find an individual bogged down in the length of life, devoid of breadth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People wish to learn to swim and at the same time to keep one foot on the ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age is an issue of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning carries within itself certain dangers because out of necessity one has to learn from one's enemies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every improvement in communication makes the bore more terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation, the most advanced sector of modern industry as well as
the model which perfectly sums up its practice, d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaos in the midst of chaos isn't funny, but chaos in the midst of order is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let every man remind their descendants that they also are soldiers who must not desert the ranks of their ancestors,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An atheist is as religious as a theist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge comes, but wisdom lingers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man lives and acts, not only according to his own ideas, but also according to the ideas of others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas improve. The meaning of words participates in the improvement.
Plagiarism is necessary. Progress implies it. I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The totalitarian-ideological class in power is the power of a
topsy-turvy world: the stranger it is, the more it cla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England…the greatest and the most glorious and beautiful land on Earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key is in not spending time, but in investing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this world there is always danger for those who are afraid of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream is a wish your heart makes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An oppressive government is more to be feared than a tiger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to humor is surprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed you need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human spirit is stronger than anything that can happen to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charity should be abolished; and be replaced by justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember my time in Cambridge, England…That serene, heavenly river;
those grand, gorgeous fields and trees; thos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man, Sir, should keep his friendship in constant repair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thinking has been done in solitude. The worst has been done in turmoil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It requires wisdom to understand wisdom: the music is nothing if the audience is deaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you look for truth, you may find comfort in the end; if you look for comfort you will not get either comfort or t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept the challenges so that you can feel the exhilaration of victory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Here Now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although it is not true that all conservatives are stupid people, it is true that most stupid people are conservativ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egalitarians create the most dangerous inequality of all -- inequality of power. Allowing politicians to determine w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['My country, right or wrong' is a thing no patriot would ever think of saying except in a desperate case. It is like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who excel in virtue have the best right of all to rebel, but then they are of all men the least inclined to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is in their 'good' characters that novelists make, unawares, the most shocking self-revelations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your house doesn't look like a house and looks like a tree that has been blown down, it is time you tried to fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We hate some persons because we do not know them; and we will not know them because we hate them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not change direction, you may end up where you are heading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the principle of commodity fetishism, the domination of
society by &amp;#8220;intangible as well as tangible thi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The victory of the autonomous economy must at the same time be its
defeat. The forces which it has unleashed elimina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never too late to change the programming imprinted in childhood, carried in our
genes or derived from previous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I object to violence because when it appears to do good, the good is only temporary; the evil it does is permanent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you know and how do you know it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consciousness is either inexplicable illusion, or else revelation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is a comedian playing to an audience too afraid to laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If hard work were such a wonderful thing, surely the rich would have kept it all to themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the future everyone will be world-famous for 15 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you cannot get rid of the family skeleton. You may as well make it dance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The artist is nothing without the gift, but the gift is nothing without work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have friends in overalls whose friendship I would not swap for the favor of the kings of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you desire to drain to the dregs the fullest cup of scorn and hatred that a fellow human being can pour out for y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is unwise to be too sure of one's own wisdom. It is healthy to be reminded that the strongest might weaken and th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is good health and a bad memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can those who scorn God revere men?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If one is only to talk from first-hand experience, conversation would be a very poor business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sociology which thinks that an industrial rationality
functioning separately can be isolated from the whole of s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A well-spent day brings happy sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I contend that we are both atheists. I just believe in one fewer god than you do. When you understand why you dismis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man would like to be God, if it were possible; some few find it difficult to admit the impossibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None are so fond of secrets as those who do not mean to keep them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is not that we have too many fools, it's that the lightning isn't distributed right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than kisses, letters mingle souls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadership is the art of getting someone else to do something you want done because he wants to do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America...just a nation of two hundred million used car salesmen with all the money we need to buy guns and no qualm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything in the world can be justified by history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within the specialized thought of the spectacular system, a new
division of tasks takes place to the extent that the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War is a game that is played with a smile. If you can't smile, grin. If you can't grin, keep out of the way 'til you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor to keep alive in your breast that little spark of celestial fire called conscience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A word is dead when it is said, some say. I say it just begins to live that day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survival is for the human animal; fear the motivation. For the spiritual being survival
is irrelevant. Curiosity, co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing money gives you is the freedom of not worrying about money.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>