<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese military says war with US 'becoming practical reality' https://t.co/aiTDHbClnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony inside who? ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene but if you come, build your own house, otherwise you'll probably be homeless or share a room with 5 people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike can #pence be replaced by #edspikepotus ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike happy Friday Ed! Don't take to many executive orders this weekend #Edpostus 45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony Teresa! Get out of this body!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene omg that deserves a mmmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyWooUK you can't do that! @xnthony is already running for it !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jusraff or planes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exciting ! Do they deliver @xnthony too? https://t.co/Q9UmBkhn3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike almost a werepig !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platinumjones who still cares about Enda meeting the devil?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike Yes you can little tree! And you'll see America great again ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony so true!i was there and can testify ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamCiaraKing ðŸ˜±really!?? What about @HateChrisGreene ?!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 or maybe president trump already took all the gold from Fort Knox for his new bathroom...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene @nosmag @CaitlinNicAoidh @CillianMOffcial @BlathnaidRua @ediennico we already new you were ! ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 because colourblind cannot see the golden... Nah just kidding, I strictly have no clue ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danjlevy unfortunately it that soon for @NetflixUK ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 @NetflixUK @HouseofCards best news ever Craig!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony I heard Kate bush applied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 yeah! All filmed with an iPhone 7 plus! ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle you say that, but secretly you're in #Davos with the most filthiest rich people of the planet ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony I only know one of them! But THE ONE â˜ï¸ ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland, a country of coughing people....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calumxjames sorry, I already do ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 that could be an amazing new video game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony did you ask him for the latest news? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene this is your job as an entertainer and public figure ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony and he hasn't seen your liver! (Yet)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle it's for a very good reason, they un freeze the tarmac with their alcoholic breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony and I can cook them too ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony please note that it isn't German, it's from Alsace, the Germans stole us the recipe when they annexed us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the amazing @dylanobrien obviously!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMFG! Teen wolf is back on @NetflixUK ! ðŸ˜  ðŸº #tylerposey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony so gorgeous! This should be your new profile picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 on WhatsApp i.e.. for your text and iMessage it makes no changes,the recipient will just receive them with your temp numb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony #Xnthony and Xnthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 you can, just set your temporary number as primary meanwhile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony or boyfriend material research?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony Donald does, not the duck, the other one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 and Ireland obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike he's probably Irish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 it's not following crowd it's just good sense, I used to work for them, and still purchase apple products]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We want @JonnyWooUK back in Dublin !can @PantiBliss do something for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle omg! You read actual book? ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony you would be the beauty and I would be the beast ! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike happy new year and happy Friday Ed! ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony be careful about herpesvirus ! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle I thought you were losing your voice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony crispy on an apple pie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! Balloons ! Always have to wait 1 year for that https://t.co/3k3d4SN0y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony I'll buy you a new one gorgeous ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony she's playing so well and has a blond wig ðŸ˜‰ðŸŒˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg ðŸ˜² ! Prairie in the OA is so @xnthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 happy new year to you too, and to your family and bf!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish a happy new year to all of you !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platinumjones this one was not bad https://t.co/8aH1t67paE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike phonetically it sounded funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony and when you're a pop star â­ï¸ like you, it's even harder. I admire your will and strength ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 anyway, it was good to speak to someone in German ! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 but at least, you speak German fluently ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony oh no! Carrie fisher and Debbie Reynolds were playing in it???! ðŸ¤§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering when #xnthopanto is coming in DVD @xnthony ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony is Harrison Ford your dad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony because I read all your tweets ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing in the street with my headphones on just like @xnthony , but in French â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 merry Christmas to you ! ðŸŽ„ðŸŽðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiyadhK Your family always does strictly whatever you demand, wasn't probably too hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony this jumper is only fab when you are in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony love is in the air ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jusraff as you're northern Irish, I wouldn't care about it so much ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jusraff Irish revenue agency ? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@platinumjones omg! I just noticed I didn't follow you ! Repaired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiyadhK oh no! Too busy now! Can I watch it tomorrow boss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewDaddario what you didn't know is that they made the tiles ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene mmmmmmmh ! ðŸ˜‰sorry, was too busy before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateMariaGlobal it's only weird, no matter of the gender ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle that's probably a sign that you need to get focused on yourself ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony OMG what should your wife say ðŸ˜±ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xnthony so impatient to get home again ? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDeclic trop tard ! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike you'll always be welcome! And we will always love you ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guskenworthy @YouTube love your vlog, and you're the only one who doesn't like your voice you awful fagot cunt! ðŸ˜â¤ï¸ï¸ðŸ’‹â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike btw, we all hope to have you soon in our green island!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike I was only kidding Ed ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene owww baby face is back! But not nude ...ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddiespike yeah, better work a bit, I wonder how you find time to post so much ! ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 maybe have another nap meanwhile ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdtownley29 what about going to bed? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericnolanlab @labour congratulations! Hard work always pays back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PantiBliss we will miss Carlos a lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@followrivers21 do t be so sure of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@followrivers21 when are you going to write your first novel? ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS mr president, could you run for French presidency please? France would need you so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@followrivers21 we clearly don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMJTDoyle hope to see ya all at pantibar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryShumJr @ShadowhuntersTV can't wait for the new season!!! Hurry upðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xnthony - Numbers They would have won Eurovision! @xnthony @ThePennySlots  https://t.co/9IJvAaHlQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If that's a cottage pie, I'm queen of England https://t.co/2But2o3Bqh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>