<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Need pants? Fast forward pants are in store and online. 
Find them here &gt;&gt; https://t.co/hDGSVoT3me https://t.co/ViuMLcJ7XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting and thoughtful comment about beauty..... https://t.co/wzH40YFAQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Topiary really is quite fabulous....we don't see much of it here though. https://t.co/E2970SfuA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The king of style, David Bowie, shows us how it's done....... https://t.co/8uUt0ihExK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retro inspired cushions are here. Get one or a pair Xx https://t.co/zkASXEknCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bits and bobs that need to go. Come and rummage through our clearance bins of fabric scraps and bags, $2-$15... https://t.co/vo3QjVSHa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's off to Bali?  Always good to know who to see, where to go......have fun! https://t.co/XfxxswPRAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this pic of our gorgeous fit model Naomi. Take a peak at whats new in &gt;&gt; https://t.co/jtIrwaB5bZ https://t.co/RFzMM9kdwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is talented crack up.  Do you think he's ironic? https://t.co/tCILl3OTet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We wish you all a happy New Year and hope you have enjoyed time with family and friends.

Lets start the New Year... https://t.co/3o6mqoIyJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Holidays from all of us here at RM. Stay safe on the roads and we will see you in the New Year Xxx.

Our... https://t.co/HMh8cVFtrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Margaret up to cut.....nothing left to chance here!  All weighted down :) https://t.co/D8Bwn1XG7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wee poppet drew these lovely looks for me.  Designer one day? https://t.co/DLynbNGqZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the Greatest Hits twins.....at our store Xmas party, Friday night. https://t.co/2KpBb9vdKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget we are open late with our VIP event it tonight 5-7pm. come and say hello! 
Happy Christmas Xxx.... https://t.co/56E5BcOC4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget we are open late tonight 5-7pm for a VIP event. Come along and receive 20% off all full price RM... https://t.co/4F0P24SaMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you coming? 

Robyn Mathieson VIP evening, Friday, 14th december 5pm-7pm. Come enjoy fashion, light... https://t.co/x6w5MHMVu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many different fabrics out there! https://t.co/7DCDwjRBIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little off topic maybe but I just love this, particularly Dagmar's outfit.  And didn't Wayne, the Kiwi do well,... https://t.co/B0dineMfx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need some Summer dress inspiration? Find them here &gt; https://t.co/jtIrwaB5bZ https://t.co/MpQf7C8BsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got Imogen, Lili and Natasha from Hataitai School helping out today :) https://t.co/pvmrO9zXFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINDER'S KEEPER'S pre-loved fashion sale.  In support of the Lyall Bay Surf Club we are offering a rack of new... https://t.co/Q25NWBrl5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Arrivals | Summer tops and dresses in store and online.
https://t.co/pkVox6x0dG https://t.co/QqPmSlskBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head on over to the Pop Up Design Shop (8 Willis St). Everything is made in NZ and we are excited to have a rack... https://t.co/7Hye3nIBm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find some balance | The silk balance top will be your favorite top this summer! 
https://t.co/uXRkwrJc8K https://t.co/jHaA6YDDxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All those beautiful wall papers.....poisonous! https://t.co/vJLtrUVJot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['This is mutton shaming, ladies, and it has to stop.'

Nice wee article about what you could wear..... https://t.co/fmQmwVh49e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, it's another of those nasty little insights into the world of fast fashion for your perusal.  Concisely put... https://t.co/yI8LR1kJS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a magical child &lt;3 https://t.co/HGNV2h0N06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are closed on Labour Day, Monday 24th of October.
You can still shop with us on line &gt;&gt;... https://t.co/7PDGfJNZNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coltrane Dress, $195 has arrived in store and online. 
https://t.co/410fhBXdQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a wrap! New season wrap dresses are in &gt;&gt;
https://t.co/hzAE7lT6bL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter clear out. Up to 50% off selected garments &gt;&gt;
https://t.co/esManeQXgV https://t.co/4GBEYaz8qa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely gorgeous prints ! https://t.co/KrpR2kM4QQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So enchanting! https://t.co/g1UPiZMEzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These bright lace dresses are in store an online now. 
https://t.co/hNZ4qXezII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerberas at the Airbnb......#love#flowers#spring.    https://t.co/26dMZfgVzK https://t.co/GvoGkY0Ru2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New favourites are here &gt;&gt; https://t.co/pkVox6x0dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still feeling the chill? 
These woolly migrant jumpers will keep you toasty!... https://t.co/0TQ03FTWde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh, sad but true. https://t.co/LMPWH31Pb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find your wild side. Tropical dress in Zebra print is here and ready to brighten up your day!... https://t.co/8hzqCDyQaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last ones + samples, $150 and under. In store for one week only!
*Prices as marked. Select garments only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art + Chemistry https://t.co/tQIrsyhH6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basics have been restocked in store and online. Find them 
here&gt;&gt;... https://t.co/dZaI0mmXGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating and beautiful but so labour intensive....... https://t.co/R2PnxqKSxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dune dress is in. Wear it your way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How jeans are made ;) https://t.co/znSlfRimR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boyfriend denim? Vintage denim is now in store. Perfect for the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The colour factory :) https://t.co/RhwWVPHM6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['no wonder New Zealand continues to foster generation after generation of artistic talent' https://t.co/3PD0hhc81I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it toast or....? https://t.co/Aj2sT96RW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did my fashion civic duty on the weekend.....I went into David Jones.  I had a good walk round while narrowly... https://t.co/bMnhKKoPnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These crowns are so glam! https://t.co/hfFqBKf68I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These people really know how to celebrate the beauty in all things. https://t.co/1O3mWgCQmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New styles have been added to our sale. 
Check them out &gt;&gt;... https://t.co/78Q3g51tKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just love this full restored mid century home in Michigan, time to relocate ? https://t.co/wLDsu6UhOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey Pokey Tops are in store now! 

https://t.co/FSrxU3NahZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a lovely idea! https://t.co/4BiwbiHunS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physics + Ballet enjoy! https://t.co/AIEIfwbic3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix &amp; match new RM favourites with hand picked retro pieces.

New goodies are in &gt;&gt; https://t.co/pkVox6x0dG https://t.co/VC2h1NY52m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Layer up and keep warm. Winter coats are waiting!... https://t.co/HR8y93JtkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['wastefulness and disregard for oneself and the planet is at the core of the fashion catastrophe'.......think... https://t.co/Yiq3Mxsst1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've reconfigured our display cubes into the window......we think they're looking great! https://t.co/OjaRrkGdWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So lux to walk on ..... New addition to our changing room, courtesy of Ruahine Hides https://t.co/PHisJtsTSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some absolutely stunning images of our fragile earth. https://t.co/lfP6oDditH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabric made from pineapples. https://t.co/RZJRcjaIZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the Hokey Pokey with new prints in store now.... https://t.co/ONs1W1LTiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa looking hot in our Blanket Coat, Forest. https://t.co/5ew8wKKsKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget.... 

Come and see us in store or call 04 387 2290. https://t.co/ciXqW3J8Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FABRIC SALE 
We are clearing out some old fabrics. Bargain prices $5-$15per metre! 

Come and check them out in... https://t.co/hPRpJr7E2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voyager pants are in! Your new go to for work. https://t.co/ABgWLXjxfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving no .19 ;). Seriously though most of these are knitted!  Fancy that! https://t.co/ymlUxsErzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so happy my step daughter has moved home I could cry.  Inspiration, support, motivation.....we are complete, love xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything priced under 
$31 at full retail is killing the makers..... https://t.co/idwD2IikQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you say colour?  Did you say print?
Aren't these images a glorious riot!  I feel
inspired to wear peggy... https://t.co/4zDgP46sbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Cookies &amp; Cream dresses are in store and online now!

https://t.co/pkVox6x0dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great tips for keeping your favourite woollies in good condition https://t.co/sATDNskohR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out and check in at Robyn's fabulous Airbnb apartment in Moxham Ave, Hataitai.   She's had some fun... https://t.co/TacL8zvnyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous winter looks in store, open Tuesday 9:30 till 5. Pop in and say hello! https://t.co/ef2RnTnEta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warm up with our Winter sale. 
25%-75% off selected styles in store and on line now.... https://t.co/YHYMmz9W4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New to pre order....The Maven dress available in two great prints. If you like her let us know X.... https://t.co/BY7nwf9DfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a visual feast! https://t.co/lKiCM34mi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBridgetlala me too, instead I've moved into the airbnb for the night to study :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just landed | Take a look at what's new in Xx.

https://t.co/hzAE7maH3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely not? https://t.co/Cd7KdaEloh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New in | The stargazer dress $220. A super cute shaped knee length dress with tuck front detail and 3/4 sleeve.... https://t.co/DVHekvO5J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good thought provoking article by The Coastal Creative.   There are many people coming into our store who... https://t.co/CLvkmqZMlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobSuisted @threadnz no thats a given!  They sound ....14?  Actually my 14 year old would not stoop so low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threadnz something a little more petite would suit better :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threadnz @RobSuisted eeewh yucky!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WardrobeFlair or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some new goodies are in. Keep an eye out for the Migrant jumper available in store now and online next week... https://t.co/XyTJ41Xnjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capri's and the 100% Merino Migrant jumper have just landed. Find them here &gt;&gt;... https://t.co/gns5lHhZVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accessorise you! New gems in store ready to complete your outfit #sunglasses #robynmathieson #necklace #GingerJar https://t.co/D00r5QTtbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These reports are always a bit of an eye opener....

I can assure you that I know where our clothes are made and... https://t.co/hal8f4xKaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANZAC weekend hours:

Sat: 10am-4pm
Sun: Closed
Mon: 1pm-5pm

OR shop with us on line any time ;)
&gt;&gt;https://t.co/pkVox6x0dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ethereal and gorgeous. https://t.co/BJNdnLY23l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autumn layers to help ease your way into cooler weather. 

https://t.co/hzAE7maH3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Jar jewellery is here. 
One of a kind hand made pieces that will add a bit of sparkle to your day Xx.... https://t.co/HLiOPjGg6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woolly goodness , loving those winter layers!
#wool#winter#robynmahieson https://t.co/XrTGBFnfOn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>