<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines: Stop plans to bring back executions https://t.co/yOVy8bGxpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Franco could be deported because Sweden says he couldn’t "prove" he's gay. Here's how you can help:  https://t.co/EEZvp3F0l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I broke bread with Malcolm Turnbull. Now he's breaking my heart | Yassmin Abdel-Magied https://t.co/zEcjwTrm19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: The Transcript Of Donald Trump and Malcolm Turnbull’s Phone Call - https://t.co/UfvX3Bxlsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bizarre Far-Right Billionaire Behind Bannon and Trump's Presidency https://t.co/d4xoNRRFMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful with that. Take the orange coolaid first - hand it to the groups/ ..... etc https://t.co/CrmeNRMyfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @PaulBongiorno @TheNewDailyAu So .... ???  Oh, right - NOW WHAT. Huh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetUp @MattCNS @BCAcomau  Probably a big man in his gullible /miserable local church  in some sad patch hidden from view of normality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeLoveBernie1 @keidekay  Obviously not. Why ask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The orange fraud "baulks" the deal !!! How many times THIS now - anyone. Just imagine INVESTIGATING THAT. You'd run… https://t.co/G8eFaCZ2Sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note the brevity of the twitter intro. Dammit -  'cos her own name wasn't/ isn't anything to be coy or cagey about.… https://t.co/o3lbG8JTTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking  Umm - formally known or formerly. Right formally OK got it. Phew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn out to be the understatement of the year at least - that will. Bill. https://t.co/tbOW2jkDVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham  Must'nt SAY what OTHER REASONS 'cos might REALLY show us up - GUTLESS SPINELESS  CAN'T THIS CAN"T THAT- I know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham  The New Zealanders have offered to take them - but that might make us look bad by comparison mightn't it - no ?  OTHER REASONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRomeiPHD  Tis the season to be a jolly Robin in a Pear Tree - how very lovely this photo !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidRomeiPHD  I love it, David - what a dear little creature. How very cheering on this day. Warm lunchtime in Sydney Perfect. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @guardian  Some must travel for work and business. ETC.
But at least there would be NO co-operation. EG Trade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinaMac1  ... cleaning, cleaning cleaning - what a concept a real HANDWRINGER HA HA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinaMac1 Never be clean enough if the PM spent the rest of his life plus the lives of how many others  to infinity let alone by hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaMorphis @realDonaldTrump  AH - a mere detail ( SNARLS )  to some !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@capecodgurl @azannaphx @TheLadyArcher77 @Rob_Coh  oh just " boys will be boys "  -  NOW Justice .... WHAT ??????  A pity indeed folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimmaree_tweet So beholden to any muck he'll STUFF UP THE CAKE MIX - stuff the turkey moron - AND mind the mess, why doncha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbulanceVic @CatherineKingMP  And the caring, quick minded civilians also present at the scene. Good responses all round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bonkerseh  Not a joke, then. I see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMurdochTimes @FryGerard @CNN  Does anyone even KNOW if foxnews or Netan - yahoo ( a derogatory term here) have any idea what  is PEACE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMurdochTimes @FryGerard @CNN  Of course there need be no concerns about piece if there's no such thing as PIECE. Translate at will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT - MORE FOLLY !!! https://t.co/5whGEKPwMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doughravme @keidekay @BuzzFlash Jeez these buggers are HASTY - oops Imeant BASTARDS of course. Forgive our LOCAL humour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@otiose94 @Centrelink @SenatorAbetz @john_inkcinct  Ohh - s' just ALGARYTHMS !!!   Naturally OCCURING,  ( well NOT Algebra anyrate )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this another joke ? https://t.co/WLPApYSK44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz  Not Prime Minister Fumble mercifully, can't have a RUFFLE on the SMOOTH HaHaHa !!! I'll never get over these astonishing JOYS !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @TurnbullMalcolm  Yeah - THERE"S NO WARS TO FLEE FROM OR ANY OTHER EXCUSES - how deluded can one man BE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz  Priceles hilarity. So serious for so many, survivors and families that is a helluva tonne of utter DISRESPECT - wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @TurnbullMalcolm  Accident of FATE. What a mishap. Whopper F****up, but. Dire ironies persist - ing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @TurnbullMalcolm See what haste can do - coupled with INEFFECTIVENESS. Hahahahahah  you mean Would be / Mght become]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @TurnbullMalcolm   " Career diplomats " ( sic) Hockey !!! already - well, that was bloody QUICK I must say - MISPRO ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @TurnbullMalcolm  Anyways I'm cackling with ribald Laughter. What a talent as ao potential instgator of SATIRE. A dream HA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @TurnbullMalcolm  Malcom seems to be trying to soothe us with humour, smooth us with inanities or bore us with  .......  ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renewed violence in east Ukraine https://t.co/OhNBfqwn7w via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People gather to protest against the travel ban imposed by U.S. President Donald... https://t.co/Lu4is5NmZv via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UrbanWronski  Wasn't it souring and sickening - its like seeing a matinee idol playing santa claus having a very embarrassing moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer @adamgartrell Ha !!! That's the only kind of businessmen - how many malevolent narsisists call themselves mere  "businessmen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latikambourke  What. This is no time for shilly shallying my dears. Hw to put it to the fellow. The PM is my MP - there are already ISSUES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donvoegt @Greg_MarineLab @TurnbullMalcolm @POTUS I imagine the stress for those in the detention centres, my skin crawls, my fury mounts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndieWire  I love and respect them both - even before this most humane collaboration. May all go extremely well with this intitiative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karanj @GrogsGamut @latikambourke  Hahahahahahahaha - believe some cast and crew could be tempted - maybe sorta kinda. Nah too trivial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What keeps us going is definitely the laughter / ridicule (of course ) Anyone see the recent " The Last Leg " rathe… https://t.co/Ixm229Mk7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @canberratimes  Unbelievably unstable behavour even for a con man &amp; salesman of crap - talk about not "up to the mark "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latikambourke  In this "climate" politically - man you've got to be joking surely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@latikambourke  Plus Trump is a thououghly unpredicable trantrum throwing liar. Lucky Malcom. Could've been even more awkward. Erghh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian  At last a monster confesses ONE tantrum peccadilo - how oddly peculiar. How quaint ( not a compliment )  HA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarmanK1  So I gathered but I did not know the field, I mean the talent pool - I mean - never mind - shucks suckers. Only thing is laughs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rashidajourno @latikambourke @AAPNewswire  What !!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starfirst @LeChatNoire4  This is all too thick and fast for me - I need a gentle peaceful productively creative existence especially lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starfirst @LeChatNoire4  And you Comella lost a shonky 2 horse race somehow. A long painful experience for ALL of us folk globally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @Y7News  The only thing tiresome about retweeting these astounding moments is the attention they get creating "furphys "  Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozpacman @MinhKular @washingtonpost @TurnbullMalcolm  And " this tweet is unavailable"   mysteriously perhaps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_hannam @MinhKular @TurnbullMalcolm @JoshFrydenberg  Enthusiastc cheers all round - HEY !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynlinking @Y7News  Not what I had heard what happened to the rest of the 50 minutes - or is that 15 minutes now. Oh, sloppy speech thingie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh - interesting. Organic wine from ancient stock and so very very desirable I heard yesterday during a delightful… https://t.co/XuLNXdNTV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewhayden @abcnews  He must have been distracted from every day reality forgetting his factual history. " It wasn't ME " he bleats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Roger_Rogering @abcnews  But some are still reproducing I hope. Excusr my terse tone. Today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jim_Pembroke  I cannot stand the modus operandi of this man. Repulsive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReclaimAnglesea You cannot be serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950  This is a teaser right. The same tactics. Why doesn't outline HIS plans to get on with it. What is he NOT telling us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9a1e6c8a99984e2 @DebdebWilder  There just has GOT to be a limit. This moment in our world is lamentable !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz I just want to laugh out loud if the consequences weren't so very serious and what bitter pills we are offered. Nobody swallow that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Negotiator' Trump caves to big pharma https://t.co/bP7TP7QCZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please join me in supporting this campaign: https://t.co/UuEtci5co4 via @communityrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could he do this !!! And why exactly  ??? https://t.co/yQKl3tpAUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damonheraldsun @davrosz @theheraldsun Disgracefully inflamatory front page of gutter press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Scalia 2.0: Trump Nominates Neil Gorsuch For Supreme Court. #Resist #DenySCOTUS https://t.co/MHad8It976]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks https://t.co/6J285di3JE #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hollywood as We Know It Is Already Over https://t.co/OFEIvmiIFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La La Land: a terrible, bland Oscars choice following #OscarsSoWhite https://t.co/mngBmIwALW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four-time Oscar winner Catherine Martin pays tribute to Australian arts education https://t.co/XqaT9QSLQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why this Sydney Festival mattered so deeply https://t.co/xKa3sGBqZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon to media: You'll listen to Sean Spicer and you'll like it https://t.co/A8sC5TU6uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craven, pathetic, inhuman Paul Ryan caves to Trump's immigration chaos as Dems start ripping it https://t.co/BeVNYie66T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this comment and sign the petition. We're not Nazis. Condemn Trump NOW or be forever known as... https://t.co/CBLONHEoj7 via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this comment and sign the petition. This kind of world is not one I want to live in.  With Tr... https://t.co/xJgy5REqFJ via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this comment and sign the petition. I literally can't believe you need to be told to be a lea... https://t.co/D2fo2AZBfp via @ChangeAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snowden @NBCNews How deeply sad this  already has been. Now this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buffaloon @AlterNet The darth vader of the hour - I'm looking up my complete works of Mr Shakespeare of course. Pl… https://t.co/dhHU724TJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohboywhatashot The timing of that questionnaire is helluva cynical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BruceBourgoine @DebdebWilder @mlk_mindful @DailyMirror No more ammo to THat fraud. Mouth off about Kate - WHAT - y… https://t.co/u0gIdWShi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdpearce What a BLAZING farce Hahaha  !!!! ALREADY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro Well worth the read - if anyone has the time anymore - thinking it over - however  ....   !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samdastyari Good man yourself, Samm. I got plenty of time for such a one, even a politician. Good work, lad !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CECHR_UoD @slsandpet @mashable Chorus !!! From here. Also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thinkerdamous @buffaloon Old hat, already !!! Nevertheless .......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsPeach @Earthangel7558 Full text please. First of all. Things being considered. And so forth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @DebdebWilder Gawd - what a BUM !!!!  Bummer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is bad enough all over without this moronic comment fom whom - ach  - who cares who. Foolish yet again !!!  Dis-… https://t.co/itVU3Jox1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 Perhaps the vile conspiritors will have a jolly cup of tea. Or something !!! Where's the hemlock, dear  husband ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet @BuzzFeedNews Arseholes do exist !!! Clearly. Saddening, very.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 Don't worry that's only for a handful who live in Not Utah ? sittin' waitin' to be taken up by the su… https://t.co/TTxjACwLu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet And me with family in the Army Reserves. You'd be stunned to hear which Regiment. I still am. Tho' ough… https://t.co/yIgUclPEcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet Yeah - just FANCY !!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>