<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When Normalcy Is Revolution https://t.co/iZIrPTrp93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Miller and Bush finally get their comeuppance? https://t.co/8fPalYndCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the things going on are so far from decency as we would define it here in America, that we can hardly... https://t.co/TZjknpYmUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could at least one of my Facebook friends please copy and repost (not share)? I'm trying to demonstrate that... https://t.co/2KiprxPGw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SH*T! Democratic Congresswoman Returns From Syria and Exposes Obama's Dirty Secret LIVE On CNN - Political... https://t.co/WmsNQrjmpe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashton Kutcher has saved 6000 victims from sex trafficking, says they all have 1 thing in common https://t.co/jE3JaKCW6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Luther King, Jr. Quotes https://t.co/zPGAuYuVKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s March Featured Speaker Who Kidnapped, Raped And Tortured A Man https://t.co/40h7xq0ITS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim Women's March Organizer Attacks Female Genital Mutilation Survivor Hirsi Ali: I Would Take Her 'Vagina Away' https://t.co/960DwhEWVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A product of her choices, not a victim of her circumstances. https://t.co/gfEmrkZtEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billy Graham's Daughter Gives SCARY WARNING To Women's March Protesters https://t.co/wVq2QdQal9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really important lesson here.  Women who want to be treated with dignity and respect should consider it carefully. https://t.co/6hbw2QhEy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of stuff we on the right have to deal with all the time.  The main stream media is so in the bag... https://t.co/rrkLXwCWw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Margaret Sanger’s Pals Ran a Concentration Camp That Killed Black People | The Stream https://t.co/actyV8IbZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never thought we could become so morally unglued. I'm with this guy. https://t.co/8thqLVrxaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sub-theme of this is whether Blue Team Progressivism is a true religion.  Very insightful. https://t.co/DGfosofF2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leggett vetoes $15 minimum wage in Montgomery County https://t.co/wdhhyom37M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire George Soros has ties to more than 50 ‘partners’ of the Women’s March on Washington https://t.co/ldhosRTw2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to find a stronger word,  but adorable pretty well sums it up. Blew me away! https://t.co/SJs75C3zp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect... If you enlarge areas you can see that the crowd goes all the way back to the Washington Monument and... https://t.co/oaMOhrOpyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March Defends Women’s Right To Choose Conformity With Only One Political Viewpoint | The Babylon Bee https://t.co/Y0ai4OHf5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still full of compelling and urgent questions and observations. Please feel free to refute any part of it -... https://t.co/IbkeMB9rSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of thing is happening more and more! https://t.co/BUF561IZjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Choice" Between Being Pro-Woman and Pro-Life is a False Dichotomy Steeped in Deadly Lies | American Center... https://t.co/6KwChqVG11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who has ever experienced one of Mike Rowe's stories is well entertained, at the very least. But sometimes... https://t.co/3kZfEefaOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You absolutely have to watch this video!  It will show you a side of Iran that's any you probably have ever seen. https://t.co/soO3r1IONa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hypocrisy of some on the left can be breathtaking. They're fine with these designers asserting their right to... https://t.co/ln90cyaSq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want a good description of who God is? https://t.co/K1NIaKwgto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Miller tells it like it is. Wise counsel!j https://t.co/l07p7Va2Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living Christian the best way to live.  Here's the latest example.  A man who's loved and respected by most... https://t.co/6DMFslqBCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bing has kidnapped my Google! Seriously, no matter what I do, I cannot get my Lenovo Windows 10 laptop with... https://t.co/qLhPAmj5vY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a fan of Jesus? https://t.co/0D1CRglPJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Cocker sang this beautiful song that for many was part of the soundtrack of their lives. Not many of them... https://t.co/WUS6mQzOaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please pass this on to anyone who may feel that they've been  born the wrong sex. The cultural cowboys will urge... https://t.co/26oqpEYaWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In private reflection, I had wondered whether we were mourning Carrie Fisher, whom many of us knew only as the... https://t.co/6SJHnKXhhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't have religious freedom, you don't have freedom at all. https://t.co/hHptnOZcdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at what our man Darryl is doing. Beautiful custom made
Furniture! https://t.co/NGAnf0Z9Sr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His life is the single most consequential in all of history, and most people are too busy with other things to... https://t.co/YJGw5x65U3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we believe about God is the most important thing in life.  This is the truth.  Ponder it carefully in your... https://t.co/huXLujcaMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The singer is Mark Lowry who wrote the lyrics to this wonderful song. Read and savor every word here.... https://t.co/74ZiQF1xJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely amazing!  It's like you're in the cockpit of one of the planes and can turn your head and look... https://t.co/CXYmg7N27b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kirsten Powers: Becoming a Christian Ruined My Love of Christmas https://t.co/77hA6YklD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We owe our troops so much more than just a simple thank you. Hard to read this beautiful poem without shedding a... https://t.co/us4sPmCp8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like this will be a great series! https://t.co/3ezGH0lY9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 100% free college that graduates highly sought after skilled men of good character?  Yes it's real, and it was... https://t.co/PqmivfMZNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Aleppo is being destroyed by the silence of the world' https://t.co/Il1fLmeveV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray for Jane. In hospital with abdominal pain and nausea. Scheduled for CT scan to find out what's going on. No... https://t.co/HT747H1H5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some zealots walk into public places and blow them up. Christians do this!  Best rendition of Handel's Messiah ever! https://t.co/68btdXZAFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mathematical probability close to zero? https://t.co/Njq68JKUY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike tells it like it is. Again. As an uneducated blue collar workin' guy he's as articulate as the best writers,... https://t.co/2FNTQqWvBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a heartwarming story!  And what a classy lady" https://t.co/BlGe0Q7J6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maya Angelou: The Decision That Changed My Life: Keeping My Baby https://t.co/Qs6v6PT5HA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monsanto Is Scrambling To Bury This Breaking Story - Don't Let This Go Unshared! https://t.co/6MrfHqRYGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got: Left Brain: 70% Right Brain: 30%. Left Or Right Brain Test https://t.co/7NmE2eYJg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dollywood employee finds burned Bible page after wildfires https://t.co/QQRwWHyOmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The devil hates everyone, especially when they succeed so publicly while doing work in a God-honoring way. We all... https://t.co/Vmj7fSDrLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important point here. There IS a difference between “liberals” and leftists. Liberals are people a lot like me.... https://t.co/O4OYz60lUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/S0kvbZgnWm End Lower Back Pain: Stretch Routine that Ended 17 Years of Lower Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanksgiving 2016 https://t.co/2WWEVHxkYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darwin's theory is falling like a house of cards. The Genesis creation account, however is being strengthened by... https://t.co/5PYVhXkCCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely love this!  Do yourself a favor and bookmark it so you can come back when you have the time and can... https://t.co/zuSY9mp7Bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/9l6uQwvIgM Sugata Mitra: Build a School in the Cloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peer-Reviewed Survey Finds Majority Of Scientists Skeptical Of Global Warming Crisis https://t.co/yX8BtjULBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Hamilton’ Cast Sends Message to Pence https://t.co/nAlTXK3NEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greatest Evangelism Strategy: Get People Reading the Bible (Acts 8:26-40) https://t.co/FpPMqtmUqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Barkley Talks About Donald Trump Becoming President | LIVE 11-10-16 https://t.co/yhTVjHwbyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dealing Gently With One Another https://t.co/0Sa2GTTyi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You absolutely must read this.  Compelling! https://t.co/43o5GtlmXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate Didn’t Elect Donald Trump; People Did https://t.co/N59UgAKCiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise words from Pastor Mark to humble me.  'Cause, y'know, I'm not so humble sometimes. https://t.co/hg2ll6a8M4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Big Lie About Steve Bannon https://t.co/InQOQvfpkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog: Hillary wins the popular vote – not https://t.co/ezaASOW2ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, you can't let your guard down for a nanosecond. The forces that would destroy our great country absolutely... https://t.co/cPUgZUdnVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lee Greenwood’s ‘God Bless The USA’ Just Went A Cappella And It's The BEST THING You’ll Hear all Day https://t.co/0DhfabgFQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Come the Charges of Racism and Sexism https://t.co/JhQYMfPqaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[504 to 23.  That's the breakdown, according to Prager University, of how 18-25 year olds voted in this election.... https://t.co/hyuWePly1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people are upset that Hillary won the popular vote but lost the election.  Right up until he won because... https://t.co/a8jDXW9Jh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Won Because Leftist Political Correctness Inspired a Terrifying Backlash https://t.co/Gl8ZCjPAA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely for real. Try it. You will be eternally grateful you did. https://t.co/3kcu7GXCVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how the heck the elections turned out the way they did?  This analysis seems even more accurate now,... https://t.co/uuNI3xjlyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incisive analysis. https://t.co/ZwZPr5G8kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just this once, the inimitable John Piper may be giving the wrong advice. https://t.co/YnfjBwueRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems a good time to revisit this. Be sure to stay for the part about the shining city on a hill, near the end. https://t.co/9P6cMGOV88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Martin Luther King's Niece Endorses DONALD TRUMP - "I Fully Agree with So Many Things That He's Saying" https://t.co/7knbD5GktU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot summon enough superlatives.  A Christian, a conservative and a Republican - in that order. This is the... https://t.co/qpE4m3DeA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s No Such Thing As A Protest Vote https://t.co/8IqZRVMBdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence that Democrats are impervious to facts and data that don't support their political narratives. https://t.co/oMdC3FoVQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As is true in all of Joel Rosenberg 's writings, this is hard to just skim this. https://t.co/1cO2qFHH56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This decision Mr. Graham has been praying for is yours alone to make.  His message is not about what candidate or... https://t.co/uoQzjOEBzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Just Made an Unexpected Prayer Request... Leaves Media in Shock https://t.co/MPGRJqmRc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Tech, Low Life -- The Amazing Flagellum https://t.co/c1MuWTVBwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Trump Republicans: Spoilers or Saviors? https://t.co/3W3iomGI6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery Woman Huma Abedin: Wronged Wife or Stealth Islamist? | The Stream https://t.co/QZY4aQNsKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely sickening and terrifying. And ALARMING!  Suddenly I don't feel so safe. https://t.co/wKPkkpA7jZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jUjUACrnSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually a bit skeptical. Seriously doubt that I got all 50 right. https://t.co/ztLvXayjMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now for an entertaining little interlude, here's Johnny!

"I hear that train a comin’ 
It’s rollin’ round the... https://t.co/wNvRWSlM6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Grudem has some things to say about how to approach this election. You should listen. https://t.co/UgqZBZhC0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those trapped by poverty see it not just as a lack of money. They see it as:

Poverty is an empty heart
Not... https://t.co/5g4NWhlwzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best campaign commercial I have ever seen!  LOL funny! But effective! https://t.co/n5eBD7cokv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>