<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally and figuratively had no ideas #BowlingGreenStrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite perfect word is "too" perfect because it has that extra additional helpful O. It helps define itself and i always know usage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy as many as it takes to keep them safe from assholes like you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/3. I am greatly disturbed at what is happening to our wonderful neighbour to the south. This #muslimban is wrong,  If not evil in intent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/3 I was willing to take a wait and see approach to the Trump Presidency. Waiting for a balancing of the fervour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/3I believe I am a fair and reasonable informed citizen. One who balances arguments to arrive at a conclusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@althiaraj @InklessPW This is the only time where Bannon's advice holds true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @Lazarus1940 @AlbertaGrl @DougSaunders And if interest rates move up because of Trump loan protests will proliferate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#150GreatCanadianCountry https://t.co/Jtr6phK3qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a Country Song from an underrated Artist. But like Janis said If it sounds Country man that's what it is https://t.co/22h594MMiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are still wearing their ball caps backwards. Or have they started again. Is there a lost decade I'm unaware of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsaur1 @pucktails Why does Mic have a headache? Cuz he just got DROPPED on his head. #MicDrop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundays are made for Caesars #inastein @ Jack Astors - Sherway https://t.co/4jmifhwQIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #bobcole. Haven't always. But I do. And after the Mennonite call  he says" the man from the players bench over there. Is Weber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Happening. Everything is Happening. In the shocking world of Cocaine and Mennonites. #BobCole has made my 2016. Then #HABS SCORE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGarfoose No Never a mistake to lead and mentor others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellie Leitch is going to be very busy screening all those candidates https://t.co/Wjxprx9xHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Zamfir: Master of the Pan Flute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbycosh @RobBreakenridge and they will believe that there is still an A&amp;K Lik a Chik in Cape Breton. And there's still is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$6000.00 reputation. That's quite the reputation https://t.co/VKAQpk1Jt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on Christmas Day He rested. But really, he went and got really drunk. Even Santa can't handle a Cape Breton wind https://t.co/yAA4LmyhJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the random acts of hilarity that @CP24 Headline scroll offers up. But ya gotta be quick. https://t.co/0G3E3KMMjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jack_Astors ONE BIG MEATBALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The team has to make the statement. beware of the statement Price may make if the Caps are allowed to set up shop i… https://t.co/8IgVPb4U4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @towhey @deaninktown And this is how it starts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey @BenSpurr what action, what next Cancel? We wait longer. Financial Penalty? No time gain. BMBRDR doesn't care, can't deliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What. Play by Zaitsev. #Leafs fans who are searching for a defensman You have a serious one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is moving fast for them Picturing Love by July Talk. #JULYTALK  https://t.co/sBgQfbxMqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Kanye and Trump call Legend John Obvious https://t.co/RqKlO8e0HT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Altidore will score the winner because he reminds me of Joe Carter #TFC Head it in Jose You'll never have a better touch in your life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 have a look back at the subtle subtweeting @reporterdonpeat did during the Ford times. The preach approach put Trump in the WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChazEbert @ebertchicago @Suntimes Not Movie related but he did the possibly the first major John Prine review from early Chicago days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaRegber brilliant. That's all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWSTALK1010 okay now. Let's get some perspective. A pedestrian striking simultaneous attack? Enlighten O Headline Writers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's called Doing It Right https://t.co/AtlJr4Q7UW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so often true. It's the desire for a close game. To the Wire https://t.co/3w9jhYRjJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFarber3 #exactafukamundo this is a good game ruined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GreyCup is Shaping Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmMacfarlane @eggb432 @acoyne @AaronWherry @lraitt @StephanieCarvin you're too kind. He didn't. He referred to a list of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the origin of Stockholm Syndrome https://t.co/cHvNRW9AUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jen_keesmaat So that's the origins of Stockholm Syndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching The Last Waltz for not the last time and perfecting my Winter Drink. This winter will… https://t.co/4wfdi1Uyru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PayChen @designtaxi So you have place to put the money you saved from not ever having to buy a wallet again. Or having a social life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well #goshgollygeewillikers at least half of the #sportsnet   #cbc #hockeynight announcing teams have to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is no such thing as #PostTruth There is just lazy thinking. We are more evolved than to succumb to lies as a manner of final debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne @nationalpost    Well just try this.  It may look dark right now but things will break through  https://t.co/QXFNBDoBdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying I Don't Worry About A Thing by Mose Allison ♫ https://t.co/QXFNBDoBdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acoyne @CTVNews In this present Upside Down world of politics this unfortunately is a bad omen. When the balanced few step away. Watch out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the Tenderloin. With grilled French glazed potatos and basil garlic olive marinated… https://t.co/QyKwXJhIPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPER MOON Super Bowl ??? https://t.co/zi65k16BMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the apps for now. Potato Bacon Leek soup and stir fried wontons https://t.co/ZsVX5GBMz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super moon over New England. Soups on Games on https://t.co/SqJzKVsvlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why when smart lady say something smart does funny wolf man interrupt with stupid   #cnnelection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is how it starts! https://t.co/zMTK5U7RWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 quotes one absolute truth today. The situation many Americans find themselves in https://t.co/O7VD0Kjvb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinRatchford there's the brilliant germination of what possibly could be the world greatest Country song here. Let's do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFLLandry I thought the same thing. #CFL needs that home base. Friday Night might be the perfect time and place for a concentrated push]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald still hurts Norm. Thank god its Tuesday and the Blue is good this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarAndWide. Ha. Belt has to match the shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarAndWide FOUND hanging with Chris Christie's deep under the Hudson were the Ny NJ sewers meet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie. Agreed Trump incapable of studious analysis or strategy. Most Media covering is proving themselves inadequate as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint This is as an accurate strategy assessment there is. If they don't get off the " how can I lose to this guy" they will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinRatchford I love you Young Cuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueAnnLevy cmon people so posed. Hopefully it's a little joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell @wendyp4545 always know the answer B4 asking  " see. Just like I said. We caught them rigging the polls and they had to stop "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikebendixen Every Long Weekend. No Rhyme Nor Reason. Other than People like fire works I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieConnolly this is a good game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 @MarkRaymer @JoeyBats19 Good way to ignore the Dog Whistle Mike. I would take him in my line up any day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The band is always great and the setting makes it even better Thelonious Hank at Castros Lounge https://t.co/GZePR3520B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done things never change. Unless one falls into a Domi Filled penalty box  https://t.co/pmAshTcZ8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Salient, they could be better : "do as we say, not as we do” when it comes to issues such as “fighting” climate change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coyleWERDZ @sunlorrie @cathmckenna "and one I must note. Was used by the previous  bloat." They were supposed to be better. Weak statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @globeandmail though pissed at liberals being liberals, I read:found it balanced. Doubt the tweets commenters read at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalter Viktoria Movers. Good efficient Used them many times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy because #lochmess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realFBra @BraddJaffy Politicspeak Translation: So keep those donations coming and get 'em in fast. Deadline approaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWSTALK1010 if it was UBER they'd know exactly when it was coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no idea what's going on in the #Rio2016  #weightlifting by finals but it's fascinating. Go Armenia I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@downsdispatch @NBCNews beat me by 3 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilary not physically fit? She must have bone spurs @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Ariel Rogers and Sandy Chapin have ever met?  I bet they have. Stan and Harry: so much in common]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalter Chauncey would be perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serb Olympic Women's coach Wears it so much better than Trump https://t.co/6y0jcT62bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briannemett yes. I would be. This was mine 2 weeks ago tonight Right In the heart of 'er b'ye https://t.co/ntXgt3p7yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Speech HRC. But why ya'll so surprised by  the concept of balloons? #DemConvention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isolation Beach. So many tiny secret spots in Cape Breton. On the edge of the world @ Louisbourg https://t.co/OpPDTHuqav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary Backyard for a couple of days @ Low Point Lighthouse https://t.co/l4oMVnq4hC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the only person that can walk out of your Ali G interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbycosh @northsidechad explain your basis for that reference Mr. Cash. May take awhile. I have time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie ha!  Pouring through my Barney Miller refs to try to 1 up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCut @acoyne Doubln' Down at the ole casino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie I clicked to see. Then I smirked. Then I loved the reference so I watched. Then I laughed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianabramson I cried because I had no shoes. Then I saw a man with no feet. So I said Buddy you must have an xtra pair of shoes somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Decent Brief. What's lacking ( and is consistently lacking across all media views) is: What would prevent him from winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Here is a great song that expresses your sentiment perfectly Bruised Orange by the great John Prine https://t.co/mVa1tayhEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Wilnerness590  Roof is open. Humidity is on high. Dickey has pitches slopen'  a win is nigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marymoments1 I saw this happen in like real time. Say stuff. Often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacCocktail https://t.co/0L3H2B9zGL  Dirty Harry knew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoCalledSomeone @MacCocktail Chicago Dirty Harrys' kinda town https://t.co/0L3H2B9zGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes things come together in the most perfect way. Mumford Elvis C Bruce Woody Way to B  https://t.co/G590zQYIQC via @youtube]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>