<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting. Also, why doesn't the article mention technique is called Jin Shin Jyutsu self-care? https://t.co/kWR0goFEew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@broadwaybabyto personally, I prefer to meditate alone. I'm just not a group meditator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @broadwaybabyto that there are often multiple factors, and ppl can be a huge one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, clicked more like 5 yrs ago @broadwaybabyto I didn't come to it easily, 1st teacher said 'don't have 2 like it, just have 2 do it']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@broadwaybabyto it's only in the last few years that it has 'clicked ' with me. Used to just do it because I had to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@broadwaybabyto I started as part of my treatment for a major depressive episode (not the last one, the one b4) and I hated it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heh, @broadwaybabyto, I've been meditating for more than 8 yrs, I've just gone public more recently ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poorly. I think my answer to this question is clearly that I do it poorly. https://t.co/roX5ylpSWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice. Why do we hold ourselves to higher standards? https://t.co/nxHJrJ1sJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[particularly struck home for me, bc during these awful times my #selfcare has really slipped. Audre Lorde reminded me of its importance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Caring for myself is not self-indulgence, it is self-preservation, and that is an act of political warfare." Audre Lorde  NB 2 remember now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, I'm gonna start putting quotes I like up on twitter. Just so everyone is forewarned. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But ohhhh sometimes that self-compassion is so hard... https://t.co/kiiHkFUYla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! I have lived for many years by a mantra of sorts "blame is futile" so this really resonates with me https://t.co/JN0IpMsTHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The headline reads "Every year, Canadian police dismiss 1 out of every 5 sexual assault allegations as baseless"… https://t.co/DrQPD3QbCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's all just take a moment and appreciate how wonderful @kady is. Really really wonderful. Also, it means I don't have to watch the debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving kindness #meditation is kind of my go-to these days, and look, science says that's good! https://t.co/MfPMaaPtBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh @gcharlebois, I was so soothed by a giant Paul Simon playlist on Spotify a while ago, I had been away too long (it had some S&amp;G on it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I have let #Mindfulness practise go a bit in the recent horrific events, when I probably need it most. Don't forget #selfcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realization came as I read a tweet where @mindfuleveryday quoted me from a while ago. I guess I shld listen to myself, eh? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realized this morning I am *trying* to not think while #meditating to get back on track &amp; that is probably the opposite of what I need to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am reminded lately that my journey with #meditation not linear. Was doing so well focusing for a while, now I'm #thoughts central]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney yeah, I'm fine. It was yesterday, so I'm still in a reasonable amount of pain, but it's all over now, so uphill from here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@monicarooney I was planning to, but am recovering from minor surgery and don't think I can. My mum and John are taking the boys tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@monicarooney yeah, there isn't a way to download it, and no external page. :( But it starts at the consulate then heads south]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best I can do for a link is https://t.co/cyd8P22wVM"ref"%3A"3"%2C"action_history"%3A"null"%7D&amp;aref=3&amp;ref=bookmarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl in Toronto going to the protest at the US consulate Sat: seems it is now a march - saw map posted on FB event page]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@monicarooney it was just on the event page on FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@monicarooney it's an actual March apparently. I saw the route posted, I was surprised, I thought it was just at the consulate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a moment to read this thread https://t.co/jMqYBzwWZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magicalmudge I feel like I missed the memo that it was mollusk day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayleu Canada also turned away a ship of Jewish refugees during WWII, and ships of mostly Sikh 'British subjects'… https://t.co/REFbTc1b82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a 45 second break to watch art being made https://t.co/NGReQtyrZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, time for me to step away and take some deep breaths. Then write some more letters. Take care of yourselves out there folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snobiwan Yeah, I can usually go 'well, a person with no values could twist it this way...' but I am at a loss here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, what?!? How does that even work? I mean, in that twisted mind, how do they spin that? https://t.co/sGVMevcrSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a scary but vital read. It's not too long, seriously, take a few minutes to check it out. https://t.co/0M3AXeAOVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case anyone wanted more horrible news, that Russian move to decriminalize domestic violence passed by a landslide https://t.co/ughpi5REwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a new statement, but a bloody important one. https://t.co/YEaYWIOXrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is that even a question!?!?!?!?! https://t.co/AqTOqw10u4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To not end a quivering puddle in the corner &amp; unable to contribute to the fight I am limiting my social media exposure #selfcare to #fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oooh, your cat tweets for you too? https://t.co/5r4toCsoTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something I have to remember. #selfcare is important right now. I can't fight if I am a quivering heap in the corner https://t.co/RJBlXtgL9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been such a sad night. Andre was such a great guy. https://t.co/kRuoesuP9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detainees at @flysfo have not had access to lawyers. #LetTheLawyersIn #LetTheFamiliesOut #NoMuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that's weird, I was googling this literally an hour ago https://t.co/1AQfxbo2PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter, I think there is something off with your algorithm when the first tweet you show me in 'in case you missed it' is one of my own...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Megan muttering to herself: *must remember this* *must remember this* *must remember this* https://t.co/NFc4NXmyem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this https://t.co/Jcatwy1o4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say it loud, say it clear, say it over and over again! https://t.co/oU4TXeU8PD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BellLetsTalk has issues, but also may give an opportunity fr ppl w less #privilege to open up if they want to. #endthestigma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I acknowledge my ability to speak openly &amp; frequently abt my multiple #mentalillness issues comes frm my #privilege   2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have conflicted feelings about #BellLetsTalk but ultimately am thankful for the conversations it starts abt #mentalillness  1/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to both of you https://t.co/upmvmlPfWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really lovely way of doing a mini self-compassion #meditation https://t.co/cjr8RCMSTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories of Harris days in Ontario... https://t.co/wNOs6P7Cjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So common to hear 'but others have it worse than me' there will always be those w bigger problems, it never devalue… https://t.co/KLN4sp2SNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a day of intense free floating #anxiety I am very thankful for the #meditation &amp; #mindfulness I practise for my #mentalillness (es)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh, that's an interesting take https://t.co/aQyPM0uKUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some good reminders in here... https://t.co/qIrXuYGh3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear hear! https://t.co/9EdXdhHs5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important reminder https://t.co/KkSjL27QQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems pretty important. Keep plugging away. https://t.co/9IyToCMKYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, seems @TeenVogue is the publication we should all be reading now... https://t.co/Uxi4c3Ma8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fantastically said https://t.co/1IybI3VqCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important words to remember. #wisewords https://t.co/3uDrA7wTlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More good news https://t.co/sRTPe0wrXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My many years long crush on @vincentdonofrio just became far more lustful #hotnesslivesintinyhats https://t.co/Hojyr2GQiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that's good news at least https://t.co/ZL1ANzUlVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to get stuck on the idea that gratitude was for events, or things of the day, this is excellent advice https://t.co/hjk9136EZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such good news! https://t.co/AYEct2Xnep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*hint* *hint* *hint* https://t.co/NPEOSFVr6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said it before, I love the art on these! (And the whole concept) https://t.co/kSm5nni1go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole thread, please read it, it is fantastic https://t.co/VSRHjdqaMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh, nicely said https://t.co/lqCW6sz9FB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Oh, I did the odd thing here or there, mostly just stuck to tending bar like so many actors though. Oh, wait..' https://t.co/Ks65rCvkd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying 2 attract new audiences 2 theatre. MoT has always been about experiential reviews, perhaps accessible to new auds #UrgentExchange 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And wouldn't it be cool if we could hear the opinion of someone who hadn't seen a show since high school as we are   ... 2 #UrgentExchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be clear, a call for experienced writers, who have strong voices, can express their opinions, but don't need The… https://t.co/lwgMHrNgI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To clarify, I have *never* said that my ideal would be a whole publication of ppl who hadn't seen a play since high… https://t.co/DLEZW4jgWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, it's beyond gross https://t.co/uVFMTwChb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Ask the same question, or demand the question be answered before moving on. This is a time to band together https://t.co/AFNUgIh1nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an amazing quote. Immediately brought to mind catholic confessionals and what I imagine is generally just pr… https://t.co/kCXh0Q2woQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They also don't know what Harris did to Ontario in 4 years, (and then he got more) and I'd take Harris over Trump a… https://t.co/5YgENJOR92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe there are people complaining about this. Correction. I *wish* I couldn't believe people are complai… https://t.co/lkVB3lzWj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicarooney Are you home schooling H now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was debating whether or not it was safe to come back... https://t.co/9s1Ktge7Si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is kind of one of the best things ever https://t.co/1EjU0c4CIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree with this. And it applies to all writing, including writing in a #journal https://t.co/HO3j6WzHWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the way these look! https://t.co/NQ4mBE1Bwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even better, write a letter to the Board of Directors. I mean, aren't they the ones who make the hiring decisions for EIC?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure there are others from the board on twitter, but very active kids delayed my search. But the board is listed at https://t.co/fTHqp7emkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ppl wanting resignation of Kay frm @thewalrus, shld be tweeting the board, not the mag. found @burstynh @fgrosso63 &amp; @jodilhbutts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh wow. Have one of these as profile pic on FB bc they showed up in a group I'm on there, I had no idea it had gott… https://t.co/7nnhO8zORB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For all their controversy, such events reflect only a small part of what the group does." OH! THAT'S OKAY THEN! Fo… https://t.co/U1eIt36NrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously! https://t.co/Z51bebflHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, I would even argue about the impact part. You are here just to live your life to the best of your ability. Tha… https://t.co/86Qp55xhm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sounds trite, but it's so important to remember https://t.co/EotAPhJmpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kinda made my morning https://t.co/mNsPLxinfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#confession time, I have never managed to do this... https://t.co/6c9eTorTRi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>