<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, in 1919, the International Labour Organisation was founded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over ninety percent of Pizza Hut franchises were found to be ripping off their workers. #shamepizzahut https://t.co/QCkMTvuy2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They want to measure the negative impact of their cruel cuts to education funding? https://t.co/6AB0YrKodd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hateful, inhuman rhetoric from Trump over Muslim ban reflects hateful anti-refugee lines from Abbott-Turnbull govt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting and shows that, if any doubt, Trump and his team are far from the dummies some on the left paint him as. https://t.co/5NvQ0dYVGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exceptionally interesting summary. "The Knights of Malta-Vatican feud" https://t.co/4GS14Vssoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @netanyahu ... This is your great and wonderful new ally. https://t.co/K47tYtvPEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, that wall entrenches apartheid. https://t.co/5xeik7P5rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheney created this. https://t.co/iVjSTnXn6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under a rock is where @Barnaby_Joyce lives. https://t.co/LpVsSsFwWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replace "same-sex" with "inter-racial". https://t.co/Ciia532y54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull and 60 other Liberal MPs and Senators want to cut penalty rates. That's a wage cut people can't af… https://t.co/YhjfTnJ2o3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a pathetic thing to say from the man &amp; party that destroyed tens of thousands of car industry jobs. https://t.co/B9xh16MYZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autopilotus do you guys have a postcard provider that is Australia-based rather than US?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gr33nrust are you a union member?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no greater defenders and champions of jobs than trade unions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: that last tweet, Brad believes in the constitution and likes computer games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Actually, it's about ethics in political journalism." https://t.co/NkZVI88fkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed Lib Govt obsessed with penalty rates, but lack of work/sales (demand) is main barrier to employment. https://t.co/pWenD9oRsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Lib Govt &amp; big business attack penalty rates, but most small businesses are concerned about lack of demand. https://t.co/T9OxRtvpR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TurnbullMalcolm you'll like this "innovation"... A multinational company advertising how to destroy Australian… https://t.co/JpDznYdltn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does this compare to the crowd at the Trump inauguration? https://t.co/6bnEKnoDvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of snobbery isn't too helpful. 😕 https://t.co/3zsJB3MaFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the battle over inauguration crowd-size heralds an actually very serious issue about journalism. https://t.co/0iRZvqpfUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly symbolic of the focus of this president, and also the struggle for the media to challenge blatant propaganda… https://t.co/wy6QlJxMmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. This is racist. 2. That's Katie Holmes. https://t.co/AMCN6CHz78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being told to go out there and talk about the embarrassingly low turn out, when there's literally everythin… https://t.co/sHXqMJTyve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much winning. Please, too much winning. https://t.co/WPHHEtUJu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid comeback from Chifley. https://t.co/pQ2nEkIHyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wonderful. #WomensMarch 

⚡ The sign game is strong at the Women's March 

https://t.co/0o8lRM7OMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some absolutely wonderful, inspiring photos and videos.

⚡ Thousands gather for Women's March on Washington 

https://t.co/dkX87kYWPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope the Vic Police and Liberal party don't try to use this tragedy for a power grab or political gain...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exceptionally sad. 😢 https://t.co/K57UnV0jUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no. No one tell Trump. He'll flip out. https://t.co/P6flprhDVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#freedom https://t.co/2VMIeivvVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just pathetic now. https://t.co/U4vjYThBom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone knows Trump is obsessed with ratings, but this is just sad. https://t.co/l7tHZrXPOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the CIA is definitely impressed by overblown crowd-size estimates...? https://t.co/MlMb1K6sRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @oz_bandicoot &amp; @mkcully &amp; loads of amazing women at the #WomensMarch #cbr. #weareunion https://t.co/uOjOb3VKmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peaceful transfer of power. https://t.co/plJgttOi2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to president Trump. (ಥ_ʖಥ)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving Dc the way he arrived. https://t.co/t7RyFkbvwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanessaOHanlon @mikelorigan @HMFrost @EmmaLarouche @rosannakingsun hope you'll have a Fb and twitter pages for the new station. 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Federal Liberal govt is using terrible, domestic-violence related murders to hide deplorable announcements. https://t.co/YsZx8lH9ML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More confirmed than your fake report on the CFMEU office raid... https://t.co/xFOkx1WQox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work-life balance, high wages and low unemployment in Canberra. All due to workers in unions. #cbr #canberralife… https://t.co/ayont2gELV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for the human right to strike. This is an absolutely disgusting decision. https://t.co/rjDCYke3kI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should I follow on Instagram?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this real? Seems so mad it feels like a hoax... https://t.co/oNjw57TiAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot odd he felt he needed to put out any statement at all...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Laming asks why education results are declining, neglects to consider appalling betrayal by Libs in cuts to… https://t.co/13RwdtGDOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a seriously immoral and extreme attitude. https://t.co/ApAo7A8A9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news. Carolyn was an important union leader and advocate for higher education. https://t.co/S3FtdRtspL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work used to be done by public servants with no profit motives, until Howard privatised these services. https://t.co/GdB9HDazQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought they went to these events to conduct official govt business and meetings with important people... https://t.co/fRjbeqxcQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because he's about to become the POTUS. Forget the medium, each tweet is effectively a presidential statement. https://t.co/oCSG0dXkG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No doubt there's a lot of Zoolander quips out there right now. https://t.co/iIosAopzFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fake news" used to be called lies or propaganda. https://t.co/ogJ2EOthb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$8000 fine no deterrent for dumping asbestos in open air. Time to strip these rogues of their building license. https://t.co/43FgkpsuQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the wage-premium for union members, and difficulty polling this demographic, these results are unsurprising. https://t.co/Hyf8Sc0ITa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear... https://t.co/76hqnWRUvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkable that the Decision and Hillary campaign were unable to win. Who was doing oppo? https://t.co/ygqpcPY1yL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After three years in govt, Mr Tudge needs a better excuse than blaming Labor. https://t.co/oIt3KcMoK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much dignity for the office of POTUS right now. https://t.co/6QQ93twFiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can this possibly be considered acceptable? https://t.co/QbE72fviOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging by the allowance record, most of the Cabinet have their snouts in the trough too... https://t.co/KrogC17mZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting gender component to the Liberal expenses scandals, don't you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utterly heartless and also incompetent thing to say. https://t.co/yH8JE64OX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt in crisis? https://t.co/drhLinuvSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudge says his goal is to ensure Australians get "no more, no less" welfare they're entitled to. How many people h… https://t.co/6cCLOgMvmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More serious corporate corruption exposed, but Federal Govt spends millions to cracked down on unions... https://t.co/C5EuD8Oa6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More snouts in the trough. https://t.co/Ijc6busTKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds like barbaric blood money,  outlawed centuries ago... https://t.co/3b8kq3BEBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting move. "The ‘Keepin’ It 1600’ Guys Launch Crooked Media to Counter Trump" https://t.co/IcGEfaaqOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exceptionally concerning. 😞 https://t.co/fTL2aPiHjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for these four to be stood aside while their appalling conduct is investigated. https://t.co/WJKnOLV1rz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd take Elizabeth Warren instead tbh. https://t.co/gLgkUrBnm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These grubs don't just have their snouts in the trough, they've got both front trotters in there too. https://t.co/ivAMlg7EhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Age of Entitlement...? https://t.co/b67kISqY1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohanwords that is appalling sexist language. 😡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obtaining financial advantage by deception? #leybuy https://t.co/fMylUmiKyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bronwyn Bishop blaming "socialists" for criticising Sussan Ley, who spent public money to buy a luxury apartment, i… https://t.co/gtc8qAzm37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are on Centrelink and make an improper claim, the Govt refers you to a debt collector. Susan Ley gets to repay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were an everyday employee &amp; stole from your employer through false reimbursement claims, you'd face police. Susan Ley gets to repay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Liberal party pursued Peter Slipper to the bitter end for less, and prevented him from repaying the amount. https://t.co/ZyuyjtaSaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blame @TurnbullMalcolm and @TonyAbbottMHR for sacking Centrelink staff and cutting funding. Shame on them. https://t.co/0ShOzDxVQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real story of what happened when the Swedish care sector trialled a six hour work day. https://t.co/NVfznjt3gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But at least he didn't have a private email server. https://t.co/MezdrTozGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems like a big deal... https://t.co/MPQqYyCMw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an exceptionally interesting, thoughtful and well written piece. Worth a read. https://t.co/eTtwTvxaTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still magic to Saturday and Sunday... #saveourweekend https://t.co/Ms0TRBhKFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The morality of these people is disgusting. https://t.co/eo21qWXoqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, two hundred complaints, not errors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two hundred errors, given the real human cost, should give pause to the program. https://t.co/hwmVtluZg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The disgraceful predators here are the franchise owners who exploited the Workchoices law to steal from working peo… https://t.co/0mgjwQFr7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you serious? You're blaming unions for a franchise ripping off thousands of young workers? https://t.co/HMlAA4yZNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join your union. Help build strong unions. https://t.co/3tCr8GPIxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All fine with you, @JulieBishopMP ? https://t.co/ZyqsRoKqMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same sex couples can already have children and adopt. This is a very poor argument against marriage equality from y… https://t.co/MPDdP2T641]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobinmag what's the tune?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>