<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonCKNW @mattlee980 @SchintzCKNW980 good old Mr. Bundchen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonCKNW @mattlee980 @SchintzCKNW980 me right now https://t.co/1ldhhoJ0ED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly the best part about the #superbowl post game show was seeing that commercial that told me there's a Nyquil… https://t.co/FX4BOInSpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyletiney they're awesome, promise...

Until it comes to football. Hahaha. #kidding. https://t.co/0KWS1yI52J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am perturbed by this. Why you gotta do me like that Bailey? 😢😢😢😢 https://t.co/pfbJDv3xOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattlee980 @bnicholsonCKNW @SchintzCKNW980 and as a bitter @Colts fan I'm going to have to sit there and listen to… https://t.co/US92Ky1rR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonCKNW @SchintzCKNW980 @mattlee980 oh no NOT YOU TOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow @SchintzCKNW980 will be beaming from ear to ear. Already glad @mattlee980 has the day off, the combo would… https://t.co/DtP6o0ttc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djspencermusic not going to lie that was a massive comeback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst. Season. Ever. #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In happier news, @nerdist reporting there will be some kind of sneak peek of @Stranger_Things season two during the… https://t.co/prIVjAOHIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO NO NO NO NO THIS IS SO LAME. 25 centimetres?! AUGH! 😂😭🤕😣#snow #moresnow #stopsnowing #yvr… https://t.co/42cAkT3q2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not good news. https://t.co/E3m3m9EnPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess he will have to owe you one. https://t.co/08UScwuTlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#partylikeajournalist 
(Also glad you made it!) https://t.co/vyzWEBdZcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are some of the other bus routes @TransLink says are impacted. https://t.co/5bLygl3QQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransLink reminding customers of sig. delays on bus routes, incl: 5, 6, 8, 20, 41, 43, 49, 99, 210, 211, 229, 230, 232, 236, 95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RCYBC's Acting Rep., Bernard Richard, will release a report on an investigation into the life and suicide of a B.C. Metis teen on Monday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who is impacted by the #CanadaLine delays/tech issues...an update from @TransLink. https://t.co/XaSYvgEqHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are heading to and from @SFU's Burnaby Campus...take note: https://t.co/Favs7pKQ1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransLink says Canada Line service to and from stns on Sea Island/YVR is running, but is on a reduced frequency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#REELREPORT: The weather outside is frightful - so is the #boxoffice this weekend. Stick to the home releases folks. https://t.co/Yd7FfnmMrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it snowing where you are? Tweet us your photos! #vancouversnow #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[48 y/o man dead after crashing his car in Abbotsford earlier this morning. @Gordmac980 reports. https://t.co/ax82N6AY2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloveperks @RyanLmark @CKNW my tweet was from almost five hours ago. A lot can happen in that time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm screening A Cure for Wellness. (@ACureForLife_) VERY excited to see director Gore Verbinski back making horror/… https://t.co/acXsyM3qKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In North #Burnaby one plaza has already put salt down on its sidewalks ahead of tomorrow's expected #snow. @CKNW https://t.co/2HXwoQZn5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD says chgs Christopher Lee Boyda faces are re: Dec machete incident @ 29th Ave SkyTrain. Also a police-involved shooting. (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@vancouverpd says man facing chgs in Dec incident @ 29th Ave. #SkyTrain Stn, Christopher Lee Boyda. Man w/same is… https://t.co/Nt7a8PQuEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently they've been rescued, glad they've laid this egg to rest. https://t.co/oa9d5mMWre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@vancouverpd to give update @ 10:30 AM re: Vancouver's 2nd homicide of 2017 + Dec. 2016 VPD-involved shooting at 29th Ave. SkyTrain stn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When folks in #Vancouver were asked if they knew who @jjhorgan was, some answers: "a wrestler," "a comedian," and "… https://t.co/YVGYrgT9ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: @VancouverPD probe the city's 2nd homicide of 2017. https://t.co/gUlmOzZ3aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow to start falling in #MetroVancouver, #FraserValley by Friday morning. @Gordmac980 reports. https://t.co/iHW9U5sUya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wiartonwillie - the Groundhog based out of #Ontario - says it'll be an early spring; he didn't see his shadow this morning. #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you haven't had enough Asa Butterfield, fear not: I'm screening #TheSpaceBetweenUs tonight &amp; he's in it! Re… https://t.co/NvpWUiunVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonplittle @JHallCKNW980 fair. Same way I feel about that awkward version of Fahrenheit 451 w/Julie Christie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TSBCanada has deployed investigators to the scene of a tugboat sinking at Okanagan Lake. The operator died in the incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JustinTrudeau is abandoning his long-held promise to change the way #Canadians vote in federal elections. #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHallCKNW980 @simonplittle one can only hope....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HAVE MIXED FEELINGS ABOUT THIS: Dune reboot coming, to be directed by Denis Villeneuve. https://t.co/T9S8B7OC5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montreal's Mayor says a funeral service will be held tomorrow for three of the six men who died in the #QuebecShooting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't try parking at the meters in the Downton #Vancouver core either. SO many are coned off. I have no idea when the area reopens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, don't even try going down Howe today if you're going to be in the Downtown #Vancouver core. It's all closed off for crane work. -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EmilyLazatin980 guess what I just emptied out. #siopao #lunch #noms @NewTownBakery https://t.co/KniIyH3pTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD says it's expected to give an update at 1 PM today re: an attack that happened in Stanley Park last November.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the suspect description re: Jan. 26th incident at 9:40 PM involving woman followed repeatedly. https://t.co/aqQf137Ii6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransitPolice says she got on train, off @ Rupert. Suspect sitting near woman while on the train. Her boyfriend arrived. Suspect fled(3/3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransitPolice says woman got off @Grandview/Commercial. Noticed man following her. Waited for #SkyTrain. (2/3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransitPolice says @ 9:40 PM, woman boarded 99B bus @ Main/Broadway. Man seated nearby got up, stood beside her. Started convo (1/3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@translink issuing warning after woman followed repeatedly by man. Happened Jan. 26. Started @ Main &amp; Broadway, ended @ Rupert Stn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@StatCan_eng says real domestic product grew by 0.4% in November, slightly above expectations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course it was a mistake. Lol. https://t.co/ajlrJDq056]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc: "World looks @ Cda as beacon of hope, peace, not just b/c of diversity, but b/c we celebrate &amp; embrace it" #quebecshooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc in statement re: #quebecshooting: "...mosques are sanctuaries of peace and reflection. There is no greater violation."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc releases statement re: #quebecshooting. Says she is "shocked, saddened by tragic shooting."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JustinTrudeau: "Canada has long been a diversified country. We are compassionate, generous." Also thx world leaders who have reached out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JustinTrudeau speaking in the House of Commons, says the act that occurred in #Quebec last night has no place in our society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Thank you Jeff Lee for everything you've written and for all the great journalism you've given us. https://t.co/tDTzT1HM3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, @CityofVancouver to fly flag at half mast in light of #QuebecShooting. https://t.co/8wajvrxoRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#surreybc City Hall flags to fly at half mast today re: #QuebecCityMosqueShooting https://t.co/n0ZK1EG9Dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one wins with violence. No one. https://t.co/qstbJ0VDS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Muslim Assoc: safety of mosques in Lower Mainland "top priority" after #quebecshooting. @EmilyLazatin980 reports. https://t.co/sL2zGQ49Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JustinTrudeau will be travelling to #QuebecCity in wake of the attack on the mosque yesterday night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: Suspects identified in #quebecmosqueshooting that claims 6 lives, injures 12. https://t.co/sL2zGQ49Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS to announce this tomorrow. https://t.co/mhrkYy0QUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? That's what it takes? Dead businessmen change your mind? Not masses of vulnerable people you shot and kille… https://t.co/IB5uN4rYmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The spokeswoman w/Centre Hospitalier Universite Laval says "@ least 3 people 'between life and death.'" #QuebecShooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LaTourEiffel will go dark after midnight in Paris to stand in solidarity with those killed, injured in… https://t.co/oYmhHPt79T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning I caught up w/@simisara980 re: #boxoffice news. LISTEN: https://t.co/8Fz4bdmpSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc reiterates point from early this wk: "only 2 ways to fundraise" - to take donations from private citizens, or via tax $.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc: "The @bcndp are refusing to follow our lead [on donations in real time], and I hope they do." Says it offers transparency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc: "We are watching (@JustinTrudeau's) idea; we are making changes already." References reporting donations "in real time."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@christyclarkbc says she will not follow @JustinTrudeau's lead when it comes to cash-for-access evts, says "it's an interesting idea."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#REVIEW: The @adogspurpose film paws at straws, but is a bit fun. #reelreport #boxoffice https://t.co/OiTMTPYL33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw shucks! But the real question is do I pass @DuranCKNW980's pronunciation threshold? https://t.co/2zFODGx4cJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pardon

The State Department’s entire senior management team just resigned according to @washingtonpost

https://t.co/dCbd7D438C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SCC_eng has upheld a BC law that forces people to register before sponsoring political advertising during a prov. elxn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad I pay my hard earned money to ride the train only to have someone sneak behind me on my dime &amp; there's nothing I can do. @TransLink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screening controversial film @adogspurpose tonight in #YVR. My thoughts coming down Friday morning on the @jonmccomb980 show on @CKNW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisshak and I are in the new podcast studio at @CKNW today recording the latest episode of… https://t.co/zWz0a4fNSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've yet to watch anything involving Mary Tyler Moore, do it. An absolute pioneer in TV land (and more) for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP Entertainment is reporting that Mary Tyler Moore is dead at the age of 80.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmeyer_980 @JJLye980 HAPPENING NOW: I have heartburn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TravisVader's lawyer confirms his client will appeal his conviction and his sentence. The formal appeal will be filed later this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total number of int'l visitors to B.C. from Jan - Dec 2016 = 5,143,414.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BCGov says in the 1st 11 months of 2016, there were more than 5.1 million int'l visitors in B.C. 12% increase vs. same time frame in 2015.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Director Denis Villeneuve saw his 1st Oscar nod for Best Director for @arrivalmovie yesterday when @TheAcademy nods were presented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To celebrate its @TheAcademy nods, @arrivalmovie is getting a re-release in theatres on Friday, Jan 27. Will incl. 8 min. of bonus footage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More from the #TravisVader sentencing. https://t.co/RPqE09Clx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A judge has sentenced Travis Vader, the man found guilty of killing #Alberta seniors Lyle &amp; Marie McCann, to life in prison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal has beaten Canada's @milosraonic in 3 sets to reach the #AustralianOpen semi-finals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTimDickert visual update...I SWEAR I ONLY TOOK ONE. BALL IS IN YOUR CORNER DICKERT. #bostoncream https://t.co/H7spXhh8uV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newsroom just got a little sweeter this morning. Thank you @SchintzCKNW980! 
(I may be responsible for the missing… https://t.co/nlmWnfw3bA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacques Corveau, an ex-Liberal organizer convicted of fraud in relation to the fed. sponsorship scandal, has been given a 4-yr prison term.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@janetrfraser has been nominated as the @BCGreens candidate in Vancouver-Langara.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverPD searching for person who gave first aid to man who died in November 1st, 2016 stabbing. https://t.co/lu3Yx6mixL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dow Jones Industrial Average in New York passed the 20,000 mark. This is the 1st time this has happened. #business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people are dead and 1 is in hospital w/gunshot wounds following an early morning shooting in #PrinceGeorge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICYMI my two cents on @TheAcademy #Oscars picks with @jonmccomb980 this morning! https://t.co/PbdS8Kl9XZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>