<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece from a Syrian-Canadian Harvard student, including Lee Kuan Yew quote on how a US education=soft power… https://t.co/DOSW2wyOAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad, cruel story. Iran's population is the most pro-American in the Middle East. Trump is destroying this goodwill https://t.co/q0gPS7Me4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few leaders in American history have done more for Muslim-Jewish comity than Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators @SenJohnMcCain &amp; @LindseyGrahamSC: #MuslimBan "helps terrorist recruitment" not US security… https://t.co/xdAs2YDkzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Iranian refugees who've settled in the US over the past decade...hold Western values...have ferociously oppose… https://t.co/p0oleMNQp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands protesting now before the White House. Only 4% of DC residents voted for Trump so this is likely to be th… https://t.co/YFm29PYIew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ban also left Christians, Jews, and Baha'i from Iran stranded and vulnerable https://t.co/QjrFeUiJLc https://t.co/lyiVrfeMh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two images I'll always remember from the evening of Saturday January 28, 2017. https://t.co/afAEBDVCNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In 2016 only one-third of 1% of all murders in the US were attributable to terrorist violence by Muslim Americans" https://t.co/OgV9f0PheJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iranian emigres who left a hated Islamist regime can no longer legally visit the US? Please explain @KellyannePolls https://t.co/R4BPgTt8cT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're now detaining at the airport legal immigrants who risked their lives working with the US military… https://t.co/8dlO3bHs0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US suspended a program helping persecuted Iranian Jews, Christians and Baha'i, leaving them stranded and at risk https://t.co/QjrFeUiJLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Of the 3,252,493 refugees admitted to the US from 1975-2015, 20 were terrorists, 0.00062% of the total." https://t.co/1S3XcmJAeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortunately no Muslim ban prevented the talented photographer--Iranian immigrant Abbas Shirmohammadi--from emigrati… https://t.co/IbNafrhkpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reid Hoffmann: More than 50% of tech billionaires have "apocalypse insurance". @eosnos on America's anxious elite… https://t.co/XMT52cGWCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriots are proud of their country for what it does; Nationalists are proud of their country no matter what it does. Trump is a nationalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the duration of his lifetime Barack Obama will likely remain the single most admired man in America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump vows to totally eradicate radical Islam. Opposite is much more likely: Radical Islamists will mushroom during his presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been reading authoritarian speeches for the last decade and a half. This sounds like one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and the nuclear codes. Insightful and harrowing by @michaelcrowley https://t.co/Z4yBaxZTL1 https://t.co/9ZLEbJVSpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran's regime, not its people, have reaped economic rewards of the Iran deal. 90/110 agreements worth $80 billion https://t.co/yWdruJLl3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["8 men own the same wealth as the poorest half of the world’s population." And we wonder why populism has returned. https://t.co/yZYvtYPguz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many gems in this Obama interview on books/literature, including this wonderfully succinct description of Americ… https://t.co/ivwkZjeA6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Geographic's Genographic project: Iran's genetic makeup is 56% "Arabian", more Arab than some Arab nations https://t.co/6lCGVAUr8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neo-Nazi leader Richard Spencer diversifies his white supremacist movement with Iranian-American Jason Reza Jorjani https://t.co/AUXzW7G0Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says nobody cares about his tax returns but reporters. In reality 60% of Americans care:… https://t.co/3OPJYYGVry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're tired of arguing with strangers on the Internet, then try talking to one in real life." #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shiite Shakespeare: How the Rafsanjani-Khamenei friendship-cum-rivalry shaped Iran. My piece in @TheAtlantic… https://t.co/nTBYIlOhtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former US Ambassador to Russia (and @CarnegieEndow president) Bill Burns on how to deal with Putin's Russia… https://t.co/iM7SQFULGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Citizens of the free world don’t care about dictatorships anymore, or about the 2.7b people who still live in them" https://t.co/ln8mPXIRW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Longtime scholars of democratic decay believe Trump poses an unprecedented threat to US democracy. An important rea… https://t.co/kFYPai3R0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He has literally never read a book," said a longstanding Trump associate, "including the US constitution" https://t.co/eVPOBrc3kT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has @realDonaldTrump looked at the numbers of the Syria conflict? 12 million displaced, 500,000 dead. Big trouble!… https://t.co/umt8BVWmoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former Iranian official is unusually honest about the costs of Iran's Pyrrhic "victory" in Syria @JZarif… https://t.co/qrewjmP59N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stable, secure regimes don't take grandparents hostage; US citizen Baquer Namazi turned 80 in Iran's Evin Prison https://t.co/vky3Gpi9CA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those in DC still skeptical about climate change https://t.co/kJMDk5ES16 https://t.co/o9LLKxDq5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Research says when you put a bunch of millionaires in charge, you can expect public policy that helps millionaires” https://t.co/V4Xq36MTrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neo-Nazi leader eats at District Taco, dates Asians, has a Turkish chauffeur, and is protected by African-Americans https://t.co/nZ0bLWBFqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Clinton did better than Obama in 48/50 most-educated counties; She did worse in 47/50 least-educated counties https://t.co/Co5kJ8UgIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential Secretary of Defense General Mattis says that ISIS is an asset for Iran not an enemy… https://t.co/clS1rJmTvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February 2016: "Zarif said Tehran had no "boots on the ground" in Syria but only "military advisers."… https://t.co/ts6rZpMprc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess which images upset Trump: a) Bombing of Aleppo's lone hospital b) "Photos that show him with a double chin"… https://t.co/OX5GLdntrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I regret not voting. I never thought Trump would win." https://t.co/gnXfJ8Qxkn https://t.co/zLkD5e9AtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gwen Ifill was a national treasure. RIP. Condolences to @NewsHour family  https://t.co/ZhbSnTarxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be an enormous conflict of interest https://t.co/VLTIy1pcUk https://t.co/MPyF27yqQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coach of the San Antonio Spurs worries America might be Rome. https://t.co/s2KyUmbTM5 https://t.co/widma5LZUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gingrich paid $100ks by a Saddam-allied Marxist-Islamist cult that killed US citizens. Confirmation will be tough… https://t.co/5rejaX7BmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich (Possible Secretary of State): "I'd Tear Up Iran Nuclear Deal on Day One". https://t.co/zwrQxhQJnn https://t.co/DV1Cbm9qrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin prevented Russia from looking more like America; he sees in Trump an opportunity to make America more like Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fear that David Remnick is spot on https://t.co/ZwaHYIv4TP https://t.co/pO2A7uup9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US allies are utterly terrified. US adversaries-ISIS, N Korea, Iran, Russia-are celebrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real scenario: 1) Trump unravels Iran deal 2) World blames US 3) Iran resumes nuke program 4) No international unity 5) Israeli or US attack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This election has been really wonderful, I'm just sorry to see it end so soon." -No one in America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["America treated us so much better than our own country." My @TheAtlantic piece on autocrats, immigrants, and Trump https://t.co/cvBy3a47C8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the end of Trump's ghastly campaign, even Ivanka is embarrassed to be associated with him https://t.co/IsLYOrafrg https://t.co/R7NpUWIk2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Sedaris wrote this in 2008 but it aptly captures election 2016 https://t.co/hePervCDdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to @nytopinion for this outstanding weekly series about people living with disabilities. Another moving piece… https://t.co/XwpMsPRvWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those keeping track, Trump has now been endorsed by Putin, N Korea (https://t.co/HP5nRWh641), ISIS (… https://t.co/l6mxAKdYIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another dictator for Trump: Iran's Supreme Leader praises him for speaking the truth about America, defends him aga… https://t.co/JE2dTWz2qZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans dislike Obama three times more than they dislike Putin and Kim Jong Un https://t.co/3XQOWl9WAk https://t.co/ELaDUr5plu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Iraq war intended to spread Iraqi democracy to Iran; instead it spread Iranian theocracy to Iraq https://t.co/hxxMVwfHss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Iranian passport is ranked 190/199, worse than N Korea. Germany is #1. Afghanistan is #199 https://t.co/8xeL8rVnXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrians are literally being buried alive in body bags. Haunting NYT oped by Raed Saleh, head of the White Helmets… https://t.co/ePGF6d4uui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What rigged elections really look like (cc @realDonaldTrump) https://t.co/Cx6giru24s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's autocrat playbook: 1) delegitimize elections 2) threaten press 3) denounce judges 4) scapegoat immigrants/minorities 5) demean women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Globalization: The Ecuadorian Embassy in the UK stops an Australian from helping Russia interfere in US elections o… https://t.co/7H3FozkJK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statement from Babak Namazi, son/brother of Baquer and Siamak Namazi: "My father has been handed practically a deat… https://t.co/Kj9e620z2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran continues holding US citizens hostage. Mr Namazi is 80 and has heart problem. A total charade @JZarif https://t.co/Yf6lZpsnf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughtful response from Obama on why Washington will never operate like Silicon Valley (via @nacin) https://t.co/SBTYxcnO8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Siamak is so much thinner/paler after a year of prison &amp; psychological torture. @HassanRouhani encouraged people li… https://t.co/WeKY52AIyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This excerpt from the classic 1964 essay "The Paranoid Style in American Politics" aptly captures election 2016… https://t.co/LEi0AewOBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend Siamak Namazi, a US citizen, has now spent 1 year in Tehran's Evin prison, without charge. Tomorrow is hi… https://t.co/9hPB2xUCme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women who protested mandatory hejab were assaulted by Khomeini supporters chanting "Ya roosari, ya toosari!" (Cover… https://t.co/aUenGGKjSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Shakespeare's "Richard III" explains the 2016 Election https://t.co/S6T6lJ3fAI https://t.co/BGgEuZPb3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump packed his characteristic 1-2 punch tonight: Profound ignorance and pigheaded certainty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This captures it well https://t.co/0vKTlSQULG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Jeb Bush, RNC spokesman:"Trump Is the Most Dangerous Nominee on Foreign Policy of Either Party Since WWII" https://t.co/BsN3g0w2I0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Donald Trump a virtuous foreign policy is ignorant; For Gary Johnson an ignorant foreign policy is virtuous https://t.co/4Dcm09yD95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruth Bader Ginsburg says her English lit professor at Cornell changed how she read/write. His name? Vladimir Nabokov https://t.co/Hwj7BNPJ53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Iranian, Hezbollah, Iraqi, &amp; Afghan fighters encircle Aleppo 2) Russian/Syrian helicopters bomb it 3) US watches https://t.co/QhFwbpl6GF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One examination found [Trump] averages a lie or an inaccuracy in every 5 minutes of speaking" https://t.co/6YcdWgsisi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most profoundly ignorant man I've ever seen..." Prominent fellow Republicans on Trump. https://t.co/08byibFuEi https://t.co/GSsCi5JBHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Secretary of Defense Bob Gates on Donald Trump  https://t.co/KkUo9p7S3h https://t.co/go0ExMn2zC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A description of 1914 Cairo from Scott Anderson's 'Lawrence in Arabia' @SultanAlQassemi @MicheleDDunne @HamzawyAmr https://t.co/CRZzb69yZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran's dual-national political prisoners and their judge. The faces of civil society and uncivil society. https://t.co/AUQKjwlA4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful for both @JZarif &amp; @BorisJohnson. Imprison an innocent UK-Iranian mother from her 2-year-old for 5 years? https://t.co/WEJ6P3wBZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazanin Zaghari sentenced to 5-years in prison on secret charges. Outrageous even by Iran's low standards of justice https://t.co/hJmwQD2J97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also inarguable that Kim Jong Un is a stronger leader in his country than Barack Obama is in his country.  https://t.co/MBgdvg9FZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's unique about Trump's foreign policy is that he's both an isolationist and a colonialist https://t.co/A7MWUGUaMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's ignorance on foreign affairs is astonishing. He makes Sarah Palin sound like Henry Kissinger #NBCNewsForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After $1.7b US payment Iran not only didn't release US hostage Siamak Namazi, but they jailed his 80-year-old father https://t.co/21YyAJeW2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Omid Kokabee released from 5-years imprisonment in Iran. A profile in courage: https://t.co/UXqvkEil0R https://t.co/OR8Xd7u8rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allegations (from the MEK) re Iran's role in Syria. $100b and 16k Iranian troops commanding 45k Shia mercenaries https://t.co/Z9YR0YGdk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump advisor to @EdwardGLuce: If Clinton wins "We’re done as a nation. We’ll be overrun by hordes of young Muslims" https://t.co/J3jWpT5gmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islamic leaders from Egypt, Iran, and Saudi Arabia. And Denmark. https://t.co/ea6K32TUVX https://t.co/2fg9xuiTxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ISIS spokesman wrote on the ISIS-affiliated Telegram channel, Nashir, “I ask Allah to deliver America to Trump.” https://t.co/8FY1aRKLy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freed ISIS hostages recall Kayla Mueller; Painful to read how someone so good was subjected to so much evil https://t.co/2S4WKqtUqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-year-old daughter of imprisoned UK-Iranian Nazanin Zaghari ‘forced to wear sack on head’ during Iran jail visits https://t.co/ADZ2jzhkCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students &amp; faculty at American University in Kabul risk their lives daily for education &amp; deserve our full support https://t.co/GuxULCQ6Rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia militias tortured/killed hundreds of Sunni civilians. The enemy of your enemy may still be an enemy https://t.co/hOlG3oJCHf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>