<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CentristBeaver @PrisonPlanet @standardnews 15% obviously don't care, so it is a majority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @standardnews Unfortunately the SILENT majority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller He'll be sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Anyone with ANY brains knows your intentions are good #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AintLeft @stevenoons I agree it's his money and he can do what he wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenoons I know that and I am grown up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKouk it's probably what they lost from regular donors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pmlive Imagine what $1.75M could have done for Fr Chris Riley's Youth Off The Streets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust Now we have 3 people that are showing us the side of their heads. I can't watch. Please fix it.  #credlinkeneally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI DELIVERS CRUSHING NEW BLOW IN CLINTON INVESTIGATION #clinton https://t.co/Z72uD7DoPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_rebase That's probably the amount they lost in regular donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dodgierogie68 @RitaPanahi @SkyNewsAust @Nicholas_Reece @theboltreport He wasn't too bad tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust  sit #credlin&amp;keneally the same as you do with Jones&amp;Co. looking at each other excludes the viewer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Si707 @PeterWallaceAU His knowledge is amazing but I agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterWallaceAU @australian They see an election coming. No one complained when they merged County Councils #nswpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SelenaEvon @BreitbartNews @POTUS44 More than "partly!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorPayne320 it is lovely but we need our own Trump. ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorPayne320 @CharlotteRice20 @LegallyArmedUSA @FoxNews @TuckerCarlson @joseiswriting Tucker is THE BEST ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson @FoxNews Keep on laughing stupidity in the face. Love your interviews. #Tucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I doubt whether most people even know about Obama's ban on Cubans. #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikandynothem Thank you for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller the fault of Trudeau.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Chop their dicks off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking News Pro Trump Supporters Attacked At Anti Trump Airport Takeov... https://t.co/zC7Gvqqbyb via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec Terror Attack  - What They're Not Telling You! https://t.co/LMelBxpfNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @American_Mirror I wonder how much Press this will receive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 He grew up. Kids will do that to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts @australian @billshortenmp Deindustrialise the world is part of the NWO agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @scrowder Soros would have told him to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet protestors would still be paid to protest thru a strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holbornlolz @PrisonPlanet Lucky Blair isn't in charge now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller That's sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFoodNtLawns Totally at no stage was Moslem so Islam mentioned anywhere in the directive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Si707 he's enforcing a law that Obama put forward in 2011 and has already been passed by Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They're still working on Washington time, not Trump time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're doing such a good job the Dems heads are spinning and they can't handle it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian Didn't The Guardian have any news to report?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 Don't know but tradies and suppliers look after good builders as much as good builders look after them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 Yes we do, not that they get much from us because we are home all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 Maybe they did him a deal because he uses them on all houses that he builds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 SIL is builder and site super. Said he never signed anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 He was the builder. He said he didn't sign anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 my SIL is the builder, so whoever he uses. Didn't get them thru an Energy Provider.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 @SenatorMRoberts just checked. We didn't sign anything. P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oz566 @SenatorMRoberts Why are they getting a subsidy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts We have solar panels. We got no government subsidies??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Yes but it would have been more effective if it was done years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregmottola Trump is doing the same as Obama and GeorgeW did. They just didn't have a media that hated them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGTheMess @AllNewsAlliance Don't forget John McTiernan was here on a 457! #hypocrites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpsmithnews Oh that is so funny. Let's see...Trump v Bandt. Trump would send the little weasel packing. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usplaymoney @WegeSusanne @renomarky a lot of Freemasons on Hollywood.  They would all be on the same Lefty page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @Lukewearechange You know Obama could do no wrong. Maybe b/c he did nothing until the last few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek Just watched the repeat. He's brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WegeSusanne but then @TuckerCarlson wouldn't be special ðŸ˜ but we do want everyone to watch him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpsmithnews There's a lot of "family" reasons like this. Usually correlates with being pushed. Funny that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wmmII88 @AllNewsAlliance @Starbucks That shows why Starbucks want to give refugees jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we could have a President like Trump, I'm for a Republic! #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller And so he should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllNewsAlliance Agreed plus Trump showed who's the President. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet but theirs is real, ours is fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller And the Left argue about @realDonaldTrump temporary ban #fools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can they possibly do this? https://t.co/UM5T3TWQpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Totally agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller I find this offensive in a public space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump But FAKE NEWS won't want to know that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @BreitbartNews The true high road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illuminati Exposed - The Complete Truth: The Hidden Hand of Freemasonry EXPOSED #PraiseJesus https://t.co/TKKh9mglXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld You're a sick puppy lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan_1890 Abbott/Hockey budget would have been God but Senate blocked out of hate for Abbott. Turnbull is a do nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan_1890 Abbott tried. Turnbull has done NOTHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan_1890 Abbott tried to but the Senate blocked everything they wanted to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@linus2707 @GreensHunt @AntiSocialistOz Tony Mundine was a great man. How the heck did Anthony evolve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss Kenya: Trump Unified Entire Nation After Election  https://t.co/8m9Uw0UP3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller Has she been sacked or jailed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutfeld: Trump is treating the presidency like an actual job #TRUMP  https://t.co/3q2DBxQkjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillfromBendigo @GodfreyElfwick @POTUS "Woman!" I think she's off her meds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @JamesOKeefeIII what does it say of us that Conservative media have to meet in secret #MSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth About Trump's 'Muslim Ban'@Y7News  @JasonMorrisonAU  https://t.co/3P9iN3S8UL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Truth About Trump's 'Muslim Ban'@2GBNews  https://t.co/D2hMiE1fph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about the hundreds of millions who AREN'T there? https://t.co/E8lDSLp2qf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bolt_RSS @theheraldsun He's got that right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body Language:  Trump Family Dynamics #TRUMP  https://t.co/pjOSwcoAUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infolibnews @PrisonPlanet @CNN Well they are important to try and keep GW scam alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton I'm your little mind you might think I am, but rest assured, I don't give a damn about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton No it's not. Now go away and learn some facts before attacking people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton This making them illegals. They want our welfare payments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton That's where you're wrong. To be a refugee, you go the closest safe country. These people bypass many safe havens to come here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton sorry for the typo. See, I have good manners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton And imprison is harsh. They have every facility possible. They get treated better than our pensioners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton ILLEGAL economic refugees with no papers. They wait there until vetted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelegraphNews @PrisonPlanet Australia welcomes anyone who wants to fit in here but Moslems want to enforce Sharia law and WE OBJECT #TRUMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton per capita we are among the top countries for taking refugees but we are having problems with those that want to enforce Sharia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AranBurton I'm Australian and the Lefty Press would have you think we are racist. We are far from it#Trimp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @robreiner So Rob Reiner obviously doesn't watch international news. #TrumpMuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dodgierogie68 @realDonaldTrump He might be a man that doesn't break deals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Normac1211 @mpsmithnews @LeeroySmith68 If @TonyAbbottMHR  comes back he has to attack the Press like Trump did; it's the only way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WLTaskForce @wikileaks Plus look at the mess the ZuK is in right now b/c of refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking Saturday Update: Feminists Chant, "Allahu Akbar," at Women's Ma... https://t.co/wzwN0C140G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro Trump Democrat Turns On Obama's Policy Of Arming ISIS #TRUMP  https://t.co/S84WUQSpsa]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>