<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitefordPeter to put it another way if the debt was viable why would we need the ICL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitefordPeter who would buy them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmadchat the dude was like (I'll paraphrase) "some tea and scones and Run DMC and that will set the youngins on the right path"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmadchat I was having a go at the guy I thought her follow up point was valid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does this fwit think a music class is the way to deal with violent offenders? Where does #qanda find these people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is totes a labor Dorothy Dixer for Dan #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuuuuck. There's no righteous indignation quite like a boomer who doesn't think her premier is listening to her #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanieando @Rashidajourno @AngusTaylorMP they're actually my DVDs but you are most welcome to borrow them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinnybopper one of my favourite brewerys thier IIPA is awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanieando @abcnews I think it's good to see @AusChamber fighting the good fight but I (and I'm pretty they) know it will never happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[while I'm not sold on everything in @Adam_Creighton's op-ed this part is hard to argue with https://t.co/VCJgs6HbyW https://t.co/cgpVKeXTFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KHShan @stephanieando we know that's what makes that tweet hilarious having said that Arnold is a hero here too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau for $1.75M I'd be hoping for more of a majority than what they got too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonJCowan that's pretty much what I thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Linksastrology @MinhKular the gillard brookings thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myriamrobin yeah one would think he could've just spent the next 12 months obfuscating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattnomics @SimonJCowan while we're on this what do you think of his tax subsidy argument?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonJCowan I think the main game of the left right now is to whip themselves into frenzy about how Mal stole their election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattnomics I would have thought the main game here are the donations made by powerful sectional interests like unions and corporates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[find it difficult to be outraged by the $1.75M it's not like Mal's buying access to himself and were he a private c… https://t.co/jYqkpFSbg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen @acaderama @redrabbleroz west wing is the new edition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that look you get when you just got across the state line https://t.co/B8RHj1uFEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen @thmcmahon @mramclaren we should discuss the relative merits of hipster stock photos in agit prop instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen @thmcmahon @mramclaren I know. In any case I go to the pub for the express purpose of not thinking about corporate tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thmcmahon @NickMGreen @mramclaren chris bowen's wistful longing for a 25% corporate tax rate… https://t.co/YbSLbdAr2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkoziol one could argue excluding ppl from legal institutions on the basis of sexuality is also Stalinist and/or Fascist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...also concerned about how seriously they take sexual assault but if you think PML is all that matters far be it f… https://t.co/5WpfBEYlK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themetresgained @SimonJCowan they did I thought III was worse than II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut well I guess that's marginally less orwellian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckyquick83 @SimonJCowan you're referring to the SGC rather than super in general?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missmadchat that's a real show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSligar there's also dynamic considerations EMTRs only apply while you're eligible for a benefit a tax rate is for life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSligar it's not but there's more to a tax debate than just work incentives and more to an economy than just labour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSligar I'd hazard a guess it's the effective part that explains the distinction people make]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government facing a pensioner revolt https://t.co/59HbzjOkjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marrowing @amy_aej socialists just think a different bunch of people ought to be doing the rorting..most often themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinnybopper Limp Bizkit were shit, there I said it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabster0191 in 20 years time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westpac has just taken it upon themselves to offer expectant parents a (fairly modest) Baby Bonus https://t.co/27Xj6Ovpc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpotter98 @percapita @RecoEco better late than never]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oz_f If any of those pensioners have over a million in home equity I'm not exactly shedding a tear for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinnybopper some tweets are so good they don't need context]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @FijiSarah @SimonJCowan I'm outraged no one complained about retrospectivity when the taper went from $3 to $1.50.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice of @terrimbutler to finally find time for a genuine apology even if it took the threat of legal action to focu… https://t.co/FFAkDrxwnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you know, the pension changes that @AustralianLabor said they would "review" but made no commitment to reverse? @unionsaustralia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @unionsaustralia would these be the same pension changes that @AustralianLabor was happy to quietly bank at the… https://t.co/4dphev0OSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPlunky  so Apps is wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themetresgained professional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trinnybopper but that's the best part]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALeighMP @Treasury_AU Correct me if I'm wrong but wasn't this an earlier piece of work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know for a fact @Bowenchris that this "well-known ideological opponent of the stimulus package" is wrong? https://t.co/mMPWDwH9ve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDemography @CatherineDeveny because abortion law varies state to state?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny @DrDemography ..of the cost than they currently do (less child support, greater FTB expenditure etc...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny @DrDemography I understand my only concern is that if mum wishes to proceed with the pregnancy taxpayers will bear more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny @DrDemography ..suggesting is men ought to be able to op-out of the financial costs I'll admit there's a logic to that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineDeveny @DrDemography interesting...I guess abortion gives women an opt out of pregnancy and the financial costs what you're..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDemography @CatherineDeveny reasoning that male contraception is preferable to absolving oneself of financial obligations after the fact?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMGreen What did Rob Sitch do to get on there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the ABS Linked Employer-Employee Database at the Australian Labour Market Research Workshop https://t.co/ZUmPmQHpim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope that this is not true. If it is I'm a little concerned about our chancellor https://t.co/h87niZn3i8 https://t.co/eneK9warRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakeedbutler @GreenJ @GrogsGamut not saying that the gap in the graph is good I'm just saying it's hard to interpret on its own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakeedbutler @GreenJ @GrogsGamut or alternatively someone curious about the relative productivity of capital and multifactor productivity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a little trouble seeing the hypocrisy to which you're referring @terrimbutler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is objecting to extortion from a uni staff member under the guise of 18C the same as defaming someone on nation… https://t.co/VOC4yF0noV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themetresgained the hoth at at Christmas jumper?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Structural inequality https://t.co/q5H84ceNHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oz_f While generally in favour of market solutions in the context of sugar consumption I'm inclined to agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1petermartin @BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 same with fruit juice apparently https://t.co/I2Hyapdfgb https://t.co/7lNZdndoKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 @1petermartin which is in contrast to the carbon tax where compensation was paid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 @1petermartin if cpi was enough to compensate wouldn't the substitution by negligible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 @1petermartin why would you compensate? Isn't the whole point to hurt the hip pocket to save the waistline?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 @1petermartin one would think it will be at least as regressive as a tobacco excise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @beckyquick83 @1petermartin so why stop at drinks? the logical conclusion of this is banning carbohydrates altogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmreimers @SquigglyRick would the sugar tax be levied on cookies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick there's a fine line between well-meaning and condescending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevanShields can't wait for outsiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterPhelpsMLC I can hear the crickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a repeat offender https://t.co/2jheNOD7Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking fw to widespread condemnation by left wing feminists of Senator Cameron's demeaning comments re @SenatorCash https://t.co/yaFtIdifpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got home for the end of #qanda surely this is a contender for worst qanda ever excruciating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shhhhhh no one tell @GreenJ https://t.co/Lzm1z02HVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmreimers @pleasedontatme which was probably true when it was introduced though I suspect that's no longer the case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmreimers @pleasedontatme I would have thought the correct counterfactual is taking out inflation so not all of the 50% is a concession]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmreimers @pleasedontatme I think the rationale for the health and education exemptions is that you (partially) forgo direct subsidies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleasedontatme @davidmreimers on the grounds of double taxation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@australian there appears to be something wrong with the link to the story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirandadevine seems like a strange thing to bring into our IR system like PPL I would have thought better dealt with in social security]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one complains about retrospecifity when the goal posts are shifted in their favour https://t.co/jpD52FCipq via @JohnDaley_ &amp; @GrattanInst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the same policy but everyone's maximum eligible #ppl weeks goes up to 20 from 18? https://t.co/eij5LvBvK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausdataarchive we need to have a think about the social media strategy. We should aim for 720 followers by year's end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jc_cummins we almost had a Ferrari driving Opposition Leader https://t.co/R9LMHbw5gj https://t.co/Q8ADqXn3YU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut @DPlunky enjoyed your piece on the limitations of polling especially the comparison with sport data]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DPlunky @GrogsGamut better stop at "I thought X" and not write some insufferable simplistic think piece pretending to know what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut @thehill I thought the Trump candidacy would galvanise democratic turnout I was very very wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConversationEDU @PBtheUnbeliever @realDonaldTrump given the source I'll hazard a guess it checks out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep that wanka in the striped jumper is the last straw I can't do this #qanda anymore even if @herandrews is on the panel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonJCowan but that wouldn't be politically expedient for ol @DrCraigEmerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelTy8 @GrayConnolly how do those in the poor country win from that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddythecatlady you don't get to assume away entire groups of ppl in a democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddythecatlady these "...if only [insert demographic] voted..." hot takes are dumb af]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>