<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniejoly @The_CMPA The fact that modernization is seen as a risk tells you exactly why we are not globally competitive, and won't be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier @XGames At least Tom and Luke have done an amazing job with commentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adapt to pipe conditions with a safety run and xgames gold is yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so nice to watch @XGames with accurate trick calling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@microsoftcanada Why is it that the Surface Dial doesn't seem to exist in Canada? Are we that far behind the rest of the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DriveBC Meanwhile on the Coquihalla... https://t.co/TUKVOdCw3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternowak @globeandmail "innovation leader"? With a 5:1 dl/ul ratio? That's just reinforcing status quo, passive consumers not producers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another awesome day of #NFLRedZone. Thanks @ScottHanson for a Sunday insulated from Canadian broadcasting. Worth all those snow pesos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just @DriveBC 'doing their best'. Yikes. #cantada https://t.co/Aa1exxxp1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network upgrade time! Cat6 cable tangle level: Griswold https://t.co/d8gCx5kUqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arstechnica "As an actual artistic device, I'm in no real position to judge the merits of the Surface Studio". So why even bother?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@engadget corrupt sketchbags in Quebec? Shocker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CdnDemocracy This country can't even manage to enforce the laws it already has, so let's add more. What a joke. #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["we're doing the best we can" is the catch all for business operation in Canada #cantada #wontada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in #cantada for less than half an hour before laziness and incompetence overtake life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold, snowy and generally miserable. Perfect football weather! https://t.co/HHJKi5j5L8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another super diverse @cnn panel. And people wonder why the media didn't see this as even a remote possibility. https://t.co/cNCnn2MhVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The naivety of Canadians welcoming innovative, harder worker Americans into the country while our global competitiveness couldn't be worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything more pathetic than @cbc / Canadian media coverage of a US election? Embarrassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing a lot of claims of a "shocking" and "stunning" outcome. Have never witnessed a media so unprepared for an election outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Welcome to Canada's tech infrastructure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShiDavidi @Sportsnet 'Bautista is eager to remain with the Blue Jays'...  any evidence to support this claim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Guess you haven't been watching this season of South Park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cherald_works This perfectly represents the state of Canadian media. #boughtandpaidfor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSportsnet @reporterchris Thanks for the actual reporting, John.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC @reporterchris I guess $5.2b isn't enough to find reporters with the competency to identify players. #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a lot of sports. #NFLRedZone #WorldSeries #SNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More baseball!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple Revolutionary? It's almost 2017, just so you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottbaseball the most @Rogers move ever. #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank goodness for illegal streams. @Sportsnet expecting ppl to watch intl feed with Buck Martinez? #yikes #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I envision @JoeyBats19 vs the umpires for the rest of the series #alcs https://t.co/iIBH1dyP7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suck it @Rangers #swept #gohome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give Edwin all of the money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC all evidence to the contrary. Forgot last year already?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MStrooo6 you got this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NFLRedZone day is the best day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter but think of the ratings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNOWthegame Tried multiple drop points, all the same. Can't try changing sports because now I can't connect to the server. Just sits there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNOWthegame @smalltownsnow Are you guys going to fix this or should I just uninstall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vancity Thanks for the link. Depressing data. Helps to explain why wages remain so low, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vancity How about asking them why they wouldn't move somewhere they can afford?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mgeist People actually pay those settlements? I guess if you're that ignorant about the laws of your country you don't deserve any better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another gorgeous 32C day in Granada. Thank goodness for rooftop pools. https://t.co/KwdNRyN0GV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternowak Well put. In Spain now still going strong on my 25 euro sim card from two weeks ago. Amazing what competition can do to a market]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josierourke Might want to do some research first, if you care about things like abortion rights, productivity and entitlement. No better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darwin hard at work. #shootyoselfamerica https://t.co/U7zDkjvcye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the golden age of ignorance or entitlement? Perhaps both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35 degrees and sunny in Granada, home of the Moors
 #imsorrythecardsaysmoops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice little Thursday. Apologies to any Spaniards I've blinded with my non tanned skin. I blame the computer :) https://t.co/wC0vUTFieH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liberal_party @JustinTrudeau Because the children going hungry in this country don't vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD @chriskoconnell @TranBC  invite you to join me on the 210 commute to phibbs one day. You'll see drivers giving zero fucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD @TranBC you should try enforcement. Or is that too much paperwork for you? #unions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four glorious days in San Jose. Off to Almeria! I hear the @ACHotels rooftop pool calling my name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau If you actually believe that, we're in serious trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna be in Granada for Spain v Italy #euro2016 So pumped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau I guess values like hard work, productivity and innovation have no place in this country. Shameful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScanBC @pattibacchus lol, amazing what passes for a protest in Canada. #perspective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chamonix &gt; Geneva &gt; Madrid &gt; Almeria &gt; San José. Totally worth it. https://t.co/yeL9N7FbeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @redbull how about dedicating some of your athlete budgets to etiquette training. #douchebags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking on a bar patio, how I've missed you. #france]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My France-iest workspace yet. #café #painauchocolat #noncanadiansmokes https://t.co/MLRVJQswhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice little office for the week. #chamonix #arcteryxacademy https://t.co/tSmlog10S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@engadget Using astroprint with a pi for this already. Great cloud integration and interface. Worth a look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRTCeng Really? In that case you're doing a terrible job. How are those upload speeds? Oh yeah, still pathetic. #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work Chavez. I'd have thrown it at his head. That's a meaty leg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRTCeng How is it possible that your website is run out of one building? And you're supposed to be  a tech literate agency, no? #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgiastraight Any chance you could look into why expectations are so far from reality? Do people expect to own a Van home @ $72k/yr?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes @NYTmag And they say journalism is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Your intensity is for shit! Win! Win! Win!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly astonishing to see how many people are driving cars to a weed smoking protest. #sovancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc Guess this story wasn't important enough to be covered by our public broadcaster. Bummer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc I was thanking Vice for reporting. An American operation. How's the CBC coverage of this story going? Link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc Ah yes, the complacent smarm of the public servant. Vintage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattgallowaycbc If only we had a public broadcaster that participated in journalism. Thanks American info-news channel! #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six years of @43_Kadri? Boo. $4.5m for a third line (at best) center. Not how you build a contender.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRTCeng Your biggest failing. Half a billion in gov't $ for third world speeds. Complete lack of vision and expertise. #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Masters par 3 tournament. Best TV golf day of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels kinda like the Jays just got Raptor'd #nocalls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC pretty hard to care about such an uncompetitive tournament. Level of play was laughable. Attendance was pathetic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delissio die a horrible death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShawInfo Is this tweet from five years ago? #cantada #sofarbehind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternowak 4K streams available by chance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier But yeah, this surface experiment is just a test for justifying a surface book in an iteration or two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier Got my 1080p working to my liking. Curous about scaling a 4K to 2560xWhatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["...a lotta ins, a lotta outs... Fortunately, I'm adhering to a pretty strict drug regimen..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier @msonenote @surface On my list. Just have to figure out ideal Slack integration then I'm all set. Tried 4K out w/new dock?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier Took some tweaking but got it sorted. Surface experiment has been shockingly successful so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums up the innovation and productivity situation in this country. #cantada  https://t.co/RN2RZZyVzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier just the 3 for now. Running display port to HDMI but not really stoked on the picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozskier Any tips on best external monitor performance with Surface Pro?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews Worth warning ppl to stay away from PEI if they value wmns rights, like access to abortion etc. Fucking cavemen out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyshellParker @trennonpaynter Life's too short to settle for mediocrity and treat adults with kid gloves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trennonpaynter @MyshellParker No, I'll stick by it. That was progression. On a tiny jump no less. Got the grab too. Medal run in Oslo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myshellparker Against any relevant comparable (say, women’s snowboarding or men’s skiing 15 years ago), yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After watching the women’s medal runs from Oslo in pipe and big air, it’s pretty clear this sport is in a heap of trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicenews You guys might want to hire a copy editor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vancouversun The audacity to put a paywall in front of content you don’t even bother copy editing. #inserthyperlink #cantada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternowak The nice ppl at Tourism BC that organized the flight were not impressed (nor surprised). Probably standard operating procedure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peternowak Once flew out of South Terminal YVR to Trail. Was told ski bag ‘might not’ make flight. That was after charging the baggage fee.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>