<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Being emotionally attached to a married man/woman, holding on to the fact that you both are not sexually... https://t.co/Yy2rlzOgvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our Romance Story"
Join us as we bring you this month's edition of "Our Romance Story" by an awesome couple,... https://t.co/LZei4CcUd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Romance Story – By Lanre and Olusola Ogundare: FFA: Please introduce yourselves. My… https://t.co/bl1sqARxVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #Romance Story – By Lanre and Olusola Ogundare: FFA: Please introduce yourselves. My… https://t.co/4rNuiqLJ0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication and Friendship – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: One of the things we have observed in… https://t.co/QigBJKQYND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication and #Friendship – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: One of the things we have observed… https://t.co/un7RGCgJyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the things we have observed in marriage is that it matters who you spend time with. Couples often learn... https://t.co/MWbOqgp6MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. ...because we may keep projecting our pain in every relationship.#PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. Until we deal with past hurt, we cannot experience true intimacy in our relationships. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. They say, "hurting people hurt others", make up your mind to be a source of pleasure, not pain. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. Then come up with a plan to help others in a similar situation. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. Acknowledge that and appreciate God for the experience. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20. For example, making you more sensitive to people's pain and more determined to be successful. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Run your mind through the experience &amp; try to see the positive side,how it made U a better person. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @arihilam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. It is hard to pray for someone and hold resentment against him/her at the same time. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @arihilam @excelength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. Pray for the individual that hurt you. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts @excelength  @ChrisInspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. Ask God to help you, if you are finding it difficult. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15.To deal with past hurt,acknowledge that U are hurt. Nothing is as bad as covering a wound, it only gets worse. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. When past hurts are not dealt with, there would be a reoccurring pattern of pain in our relationships. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13.This is why it is important for your spouse to be able to express him/herself at any point,without feeling odd. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. If you are not happy about something your spouse has done, express how you feel. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11b. It also prevents you from accessing depths in your union. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11.It could make U build a wall in your heart that would prevent you from being truly vulnerable to your spouse. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10. Holding on to past hurt can deprive you of the chance of getting the best from your relationship. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9b. ...snapping at your spouse over what you think he/she is saying, which may not be. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. You may find yourself reacting unnecessarily due to past hurt;... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. This is why past hurts need to be addressed, else they will present themselves in 'explosive' ways. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7b. ...you'd be fencing out good people that can bring good opportunities and the most rewarding experiences. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. You'd end up feeling more hurt because in a bid to protect yourself from being hurt,... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6b. ...there are relationships that this cannot be applicable to. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6. Initially, I built a wall. That seemed to work with some people, but... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. I have had to learn different ways of managing them. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. The same can be said of my most painful experiences. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Personally speaking, some of my best experiences so far have come from interacting with people. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. If you interact with people daily, there is bound to be a clash of values, unmet expectations, rejection,... #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. Very few people can say they have not experienced hurt at different times in the past. #PastHurt #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and #control – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: We have been on a series on sustaining healthy… https://t.co/6qQZaTtjZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and control – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: We have been on a series on sustaining healthy… https://t.co/oy0ra7e7Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and satisfaction – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Our wedding day was one of our happiest days… https://t.co/XvRqgymkBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sex and satisfaction – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: Our wedding day was one of our happiest days… https://t.co/GIo9YMyT4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex And Your Physiology: Yesterday, we looked at your mind and sex. To continue the series… https://t.co/5yKdlSwzCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sex And Your Physiology: Yesterday, we looked at your mind and sex. To continue the series… https://t.co/Uw62edzkgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sex and your #mind – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: As mentioned yesterday, this is a short series… https://t.co/9vDsbfIsGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and your mind – Chidi &amp; Victor Akunna: As mentioned yesterday, this is a short series… https://t.co/dnC61qqhvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As mentioned yesterday, this is a short series on Healthy Sex Life.

One of the key elements of a successful... https://t.co/IL70Bt2YVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Your Family's Destiny: Freewill Vs Determinism

During my first degree, I was introduced to a course... https://t.co/94kNJxnXod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Work out your relationship. The only relationship we get by chance is a boring one" -Victor Akunna https://t.co/3vDUsuuhdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Your Family’s Destiny: Freewill Vs Determinism: During my first degree, I was… https://t.co/katuF5omHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing Your Family’s #Destiny: Freewill Vs Determinism: During my first degree, I was… https://t.co/POGqkxnFok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27. Building intimacy demands sacrifice. Support your spouse! #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26. Ties that strengthen their marriages from within.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. When couples stick together in these times, they often develop incredible ties. #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. Be there for each other when the going is easy, especially when it is tough.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. These are sure ways to connect with him/her. #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. Find out areas your spouse needs help and serve your spouse.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. If your words are the only words your spouse ever hears, let them be most rewarding and supportive.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20.It is fulfilling to hear your spouse commend you for the things you do and how you make life easier.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Be his/her greatest encourager.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. Let your words push your spouse to the next level.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. Do not get so familiar with your spouse that you speak to him/her with contempt.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16. Your words can make or mar your spouse.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15. You can also serve your spouse with your words.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. ...seek to make his life better and easier and see things change.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13. Rather than complain that he is a hard man, show him some respect and...  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Same would apply to women. #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11b. ...would lavish him with praise and pray for him often.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. A woman whose life has been made a lot better and easier by her husband... #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10.A man told me his wife reigns curses on him and nothing else, no matter what he does.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts @LanreAgboola1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9. Seek to make life easier for her.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts.@dare_benjamin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to destroy love, relationship or marriage from within is to focus on our selfish desires.... https://t.co/6Pqhp3kfxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8. As a man, do not leave the entire house chores to your wife, help out.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7. In marriage, there should be no need to enforce superiority or to subdue the other; you are a team.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6b. ...there is no fulfilment in that.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6.If UR wife is always sad,thinking of all the things she could have achieved without you in her life,...#ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5. Help your spouse to achieve his/her dreams.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4. Serve each other. There are different ways you can serve each other:  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3. Couples should learn to work as a team.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. Spouses deny themselves of so much when they work against themselves.  #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. One of the benefits of marriage is that two people come together to make their lives better. #ServingYourSpouse #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principles of an intimate marriage by Chidi Akunna

Kay and Gina (real names withheld) got married two years ago.... https://t.co/XI5PVAFMUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principles of an intimate marriage by Chidi Akunna: Kay and Gina (real names withheld) got… https://t.co/AuhLmLEujD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Principles of an intimate marriage by Chidi Akunna: Kay and Gina (real names withheld) got… https://t.co/BmkBo2nvr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A change in numbers (2016-2017) cannot produce the life you want

Hence, to make progress, you must begin by design… https://t.co/ZfGIFxC1J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27. 2017 shall be a year of boundless possibilities! #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26. When you are done developing it, display it and constantly return to it. Joshua 1:8 #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25. Please get every member of the family involved. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24. Commit to the process and the best interest of the marriage, rather than your personal agenda. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23. It's ok to disagree, but make sure you reach an agreement. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22. Address one or two issues at a time to avoid being overwhelmed. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21. Take some time off and get to work, experts recommend 2 to 3 days. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts @AyodejiJohnson7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20.To develop a family vision,ask God to show U why U are together as a couple.#FamilyVision #iConnectHearts @modupelanre @SuperSoulLifter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19. Do not exhaust all your time at work, church, helping other organisations, at the expense of your family. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18. Pay some attention to your family in 2017. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17. If they had known better, they would have done better. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16.Ignorance is expensive,your parents may not have had a vision&amp;probably never mentioned it,but get to work. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15. Some couples do not have a vision because they are not aware of it or its benefits. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14. Guide and protect your family and children from negative influence in your culture. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13. You rob yourself and your Family of so much when there is no unified vision. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12. Leverage on synergy to accomplish God's plans for your life and marriage. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11. God commands His blessings where there is unity - one  purpose, one vision. #FamilyVision #iConnectHearts @yomibisi @homebuildersng]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>