<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day, another cat-pile. https://t.co/ViYFhkc46v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thingsbydan I would like a whole Toots comic book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedimmick ah no, there was no box]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedimmick "perennially outside the box" wasn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ask nicely, I'll play Chesney Hawkes for you again. https://t.co/olSCR31DzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Debbos the band aren't playing though, it's just Pulp night, on ice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dis_graceful exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boygirlparty @WonderLilly @jaredschorr the back blurrrb is ok, but when they're blurrbing for 20 pages and you just want to read the book!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lsherrington1 I reckon he's good at it, reckon he's done a fair bit of skating in his time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boygirlparty @WonderLilly @jaredschorr it is ALL about the blurb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boygirlparty @WonderLilly @jaredschorr read the outside blurb, skip the inside blurb, read the book. Then maybe the inside blurb. Blurb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahNicholas there was a man scooting on a pallet truck in Manchester. I used to do that in Petsmart and Dixons. It was fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I... What??? I am so confused by this. https://t.co/7yu6Rog2HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahNicholas what news of bins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eggynewydd I'm sure 3 of them will, wouldn't trust the other one as far as I could throw them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanalbertt @birdiecanfly the owl, I love the owl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AHHH WHY AM I NOT IN PORTLAND WITH THEIR COLOURFUL MESEMERISING GLOBES??? https://t.co/ePZUshyLbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spillersrecords @DefyDesigns @TinyLittleMy @nijtables SWEET BABY JEEBUS YES. Vinyl please 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Bewitched was scary. There was one where the Devil came. Scared me proper that did" 
"Really? Do you mean Charmed?"
"Yeah that's the one."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarkaDaal it's like a gerbil with kangaroo ears and legs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airheadhell erm, meet the neighbours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airheadhell perhaps it's a warning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ILovesTheDiff @intercardiff @WelshGovernment can we us #alternativefacts here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themonsterist Past Pete saved it for you. How kind of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You all remember my golden Prince egg yeah? I got a 1st for it. Thank you, Prince.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bierkeller (national chain) got through to the Cardiff Life awards finals and Crafty Devil (local indie) didn't. FOR SHAME. #shoplocal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah. Imagination is the issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems that "be inventive" and "thingy" is an issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeltMistress this is such a happy picture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic I will invent an inventive thingy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic learning to drive and getting divorced 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madedotcom I LOVE IT. Could I have one please, for science purposes? I can, erm, see how many unused notebooks it will hold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic I love this course so much, best decision* I ever made.

*there are actually 3 that have this accolade. But it's awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic designing a pop-up shop. The word KINEMATICS is being bandied around in a most agreeable manner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading our current project brief. Enjoying the things that I have to think about. 

STOP! THINGY TIME. https://t.co/qDqN6aisHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeltMistress @Jontofski sounds like a comic strip in the making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one actually broke me. It's not often that human stories break me. Have a word with yourselves. https://t.co/vROCy2Vck4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm listening to @ChesneyHawkes. On repeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been instructed to bring scissors, masking tape, cling film and a scalpel. Sounds like we're making a horror film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to uni properly today. YAY! I have been bored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrregularShed WE LOVE YOU, STEVE ANDERSON https://t.co/WF89bKAHee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachael_ @Patreon YOU HAVE NO POWER OVER ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themonsterist @citizenhelene same, I have become addicted to refreshing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone going to the Cardiff march tomorrow https://t.co/MtZpj4lzJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Negative John! @ New Theatre Cardiff https://t.co/MLn8Tzk3L7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Set Fire To The Stars was wonderful. Even if @grafmcgraf did commit rodenticide. @ New Theatre… https://t.co/R5VgdbdR1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRIIIIIIIIIIIIO. TRIIIIIIIIIO. I want a Trio and I want one now. Tippy is well happy with epic… https://t.co/ZAo3jVcNgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's that lurking over there? It's John! @ New Theatre Cardiff https://t.co/CbIE9U6OpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gruffing (at @New_Theatre in Cardiff) https://t.co/vL6tSeHCiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sianz @heaper i want that chair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwardambrown Archer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equally fascinated and terrified by the US Alt accounts. We really are living in Black Mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, John Hurt 😢. That one's got me right in the feels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behold my can box fort! @ Crafty Devil Brewing https://t.co/kzGZBrvEn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuudBlog @BurgerTheoryUK @KongsCardiff can you bring me some? To the Cellar? Maybe a pinball machine too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, Tom. Ledge. https://t.co/XY7LFPdCKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nokhwe14 @AshTordiffe oooh in Wales we have "now in a minute" which is an indeterminate amount of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DefyDesigns yes, this. "you'll be out of a job" er, no because she's doing what we want her to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dusty_knuckle purse found, it was happily waiting on the table. Stupid purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYONE https://t.co/sD2ql96NsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElFarmaceutico are you on the list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for @CharcutierLtd in this. He's a real farmer. He deserves to win, not the guy who writes The Archers. https://t.co/yVyKPGTvDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elenacresci THIS IS HAPPY ALTERNATIVE NEWS IN THIS DIABOLICAL WORLD. 

Also, I really want cake now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! @gruffingtonpost mentioning @gavinfitzjohn and @KliphScurlock on @BBCRadMac. Both absolute gents. Next beer on me for you guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SF_Wales hi! When do continuing students have to put in for 2017/18 funding please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@presentcorrect it does light a cake! I went hunting! Happy now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@presentcorrect gah, what does the match light at the end? I NEED CLOSURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jontofski remarkable really. He had one ready!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful new @jontofski print ready to hang in the orange room! In good company with a bit of… https://t.co/ePmGZ3DA2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MammaTort I think so. Pickle's always had some arse about her. Monty is so chilled out. Even as a kitten Pickle was all claws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MammaTort Pickle does that. She smacks back and looks at you like she's going to drive a truck through your house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent the last 3 hours trying to be awake and alive. It's not happening. I have 5 hours to start engaging with the world. Ughhhh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardiffLifeAwds just as well I pressed the orange button then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardiffLifeAwds do you need supporting documents? What sort of things? I have only words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it, immune system, you give me a chest infection before 3 days work the weekend before going back to school. Cheers love. 😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OutpostCardiff Ghostbusters 2. https://t.co/zupnp8KxRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouting at cars. #cats https://t.co/bXbH4UNC1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a cat and it never goes out.... https://t.co/n7rHQOvLAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicahische it will always be a foo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See now, the thing with being good and having a big salad is that then you want a MASSIVE CAKE for afters. I have no massive cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My handsome boy. He's purring like mad. https://t.co/wJMZci76B4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Orange Ones are fascinated by a baby corn cob. Ohhhhh they love the corrrrrn. #IrishPingu https://t.co/Irfs5RByaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic I am impressed by their salad bar, which is why I went but then came back with a big shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic also the layout is weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorkomatic yeah but this is a supermarket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have gone to Morrisons. The shop is upstairs. I am confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elenacresci or a rejected Smiths track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesecook the baby has surely drowned, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamAlbumClub good gosh, is he still a thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonplotkin I imagine Frank would be similar to Trump, only standing on a box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonplotkin I would vote for Charlie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OutpostCardiff put me down please! 

Not literally, like I'm short and a terrible burden on my mother. 

Prize for guessing the quote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonnie &amp;  Clyde. I love this song but will always hear her singing "Ronnie Barker". @BBC6MorningShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamReesy that would be delightful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachael_ yasssss! Go team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachael_ 😕 should I eat the beetroot for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Theresa May (i. a. c.) and her puffa jacket need to stop. She's like the michelin man's nan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahNicholas I can still do Saturday Night 23 years after it was released.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Davies_ I can neither confirm nor deny that I may have ordered stamps because of reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always liked Mexicans. https://t.co/TgNtJOJdOS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>