<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Basil this ones for you...
https://t.co/LkYxAEtmGg

 #ausopen @7Sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is that Basil guy calling the match - doesn't seem to know much about tennis. No other past women Champions available? #AusOpen @7Sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was the womens final tonight. Why the last 5 mins about the mens final and a token 2 mins about the women? #AusOpen2017 @7Sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I pay income tax at the same rate please - less than 2% tax paid on earnings... #TaxFair https://t.co/DujBS8oUsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SAstorm #PowerOutages https://t.co/y7Bwsxqrwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithConlon @BOM_SA Approaching storm not too far away from #PortAdelaide https://t.co/05Ji5wdZo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Politics has become like reality television, which everyone knows isn’t really real anyway'   https://t.co/6YcNTbyD3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleBertie01 Only qualification to be a politician like these is self interest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofPAE your weed spraying contractors are disturbing the peace - working outside my window before 6 am. Radio blaring too #AhTheSerenity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat Empire's Felix Riebl on his song for Ms Dhu: a 'devastating' story https://t.co/L6hohHS8Y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play and Win with GooseChase https://t.co/fKeEg8KBhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bencubby @Ha_Tanya 'She smiled weakly'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Facebook When I reject the Groups you suggest on my timeline can these not be resuggested every day? Same for suggested friends/advertising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katefreebairn @TenNewsADEL How about this one of the rooftops in Port Adelaide tonight? https://t.co/0lWRZQEs4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sussan Ley apologises over Gold Coast luxury apartment scandal https://t.co/7JdtG5Kfk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved 'Days without end', looking forward to his session at #Adlww @adelwritersweek https://t.co/iHQJjIB48V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Government stuffs it up again.

https://t.co/TKvUUXuprK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, @lancereddick. Always enjoy your creative work. Thank you! Have a great 2017!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving back to Adelaide and being involved in a great @OzAsiaFestival in The Record by @600HWM #GoodThingsIn2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tools in power are going to regret their actions when the revolution comes. Here's hoping for peaceful change.… https://t.co/vCUuXP9PTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoubleJRadio the quality of your transmission in Adelaide is very poor. Scratchy sound. Been like it for days. #FYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eVent_cinemas unbelievable amount of advertising before Rogue One. Next time I'll wait and watch it on a streaming service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporations which don't pay taxes are the 'leaners' in our tax system. Stop persecuting and marginalising welfare recipients @thetodayshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The idea we could modify capitalism towards equality and social justice ...those are more or less utopian ideals https://t.co/tYVIAIZXyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed immersing myself in Days Without End by Sebastian Barry last weekend. #pageturner Excellent recommendation. @adelwritersweek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, Volunteers! #InternationalVolunteerDay  @adelaide_fringe https://t.co/7Ni0MhmiYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this #CuriousBeast in Rundle Mall yesterday. https://t.co/AKogVI0Fp1 @SAMuseum #Adelaide https://t.co/lknWEG3yuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop blaming teachers for falling results and give them the trust and time to actually teach https://t.co/LfF6kzFTwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#justice4refugees #bringthemhere #everydayheroes making a stand against inhumanity towards fellow human beings. https://t.co/C4rlaVXsgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Everydayheroes Thank you protesters for keeping the message alive. #Bringthemhere #humanrights #justice4refugees https://t.co/Sxqb6G86ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First visit back to #AdelaideOval  to see International Cricket in about 20 years. 99 runs to go for the win… https://t.co/GNy4HqZ6XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofPAE it would be appreciated if your workers do not vacuum the sidewalk so early so residents are not woken up at 6.30 am #noisy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbewart yes food is much overrated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbewart They will need to have a day job to keep playing at that level...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef  more voters abandoning mainstream politics for radical single-issue politics. Trend continues from #Brexit, #USA now to #Orange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAPowerNetworks @891adelaide why are planned outages not notified and why on Sundays when residents have a day off at home?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAPowerNetworks @JayWeatherill planned #outages on Sundays are just crap. Have them in the nighttime, not during our days off at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAPowerNetworks I can't do my washing or cook Sunday roast or  have a hot bloody shower. Why no notification? #plannedoutage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAPowerNetworks Thanks for this bloody outage on a Sunday. NOT. Why on Sunday? I'm home, I want to enjoy what I work for all week for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LennaLeprena @LemonbeatsCHNL @YouTube and mine...https://t.co/ZP6cDPCbag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peanutismint @SimOfTheNorth social conditioning via biased norms used by media and society both conciously and unconsciously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USElection2016 shows most people prefer a rich, racist, sexist  white man b4 a woman with relevant skills and experience.  #EverydaySexism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very happy to see #JohnMarsden on the 2017  @adelwritersweek program. Thanks for my program, @adelaidefest #Adelaide https://t.co/xqCcSlByMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see some terrific Netball live on commercial TV #WomenInSport  #9WWOS  #Fast5WorldSeries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition needs to abandon poverty politicking and fix its own 'welfare mentality' https://t.co/ARcyRczSd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More tests! How about helping kids have some more active, non structured, non graded play? #KillingEducation https://t.co/5lNgP3ByFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wwos the late Lyn Fulston. My first state coach, wonderful allrounder for Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems like a good time to ask: is privatisation of electricity networks ever a good idea? https://t.co/Lpd85LCNOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandisgate: this is an important issue so we will make it easy to understand ... and also delicious! https://t.co/RkmSuLlzaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliecorb @TurnbullMalcolm @sydneyswans @westernbulldogs @AFL Not one mention by PM of support for South Australians affected by the floods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive tree just fell down on St Vincent St, Port Adelaide. Lucky no-one under it. @abcnewsAdelaide #SAStorm… https://t.co/YNP3io8BoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambodia's Phare Circus - amazing acrobatics and humour. A huge smile after the energy &amp; fun of this #OzAsia &amp;… https://t.co/Z9sdJeiYPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was so great to be a part of The Record #OzAsia #Adelaide @600HWM  https://t.co/rxwfs7BAfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful, culturally complex and mesmerising performance. Loved it. #OzAsia #softmachineRianto https://t.co/HvsZk9jVFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OzAsia Festival 2016 — The Record | Adelaide Now  https://t.co/DyAzZnkyZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful night ahead at Elder Park #GoodFortuneMarket #OzAsia #Adelaide https://t.co/QI9KzbdsI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ResignInShame because we don't alway see or know the ripple effects of our choices - they can and do make a difference. #BringThemHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying a post-show wander at the #GoodFortuneMarket #ElderPark  #OzAsiaFestival #Adelaide https://t.co/wGm4cawymL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraGarcia_86 thats fine with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sun's heading down and the lanterns are beginning to glow... #elderpark @OzAsiaFestival #adelaide https://t.co/JhIY9ghVU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OzAsiaFestival weather has cleared, ready for the Moon Lantern Parade at 7 #elderpark #OzAsia https://t.co/n90WeXgMvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this talk about Turnbull vs Abbott just shows the #LNP are absolute duds.   #qanda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressed with the skill in the #AFLWomensGame a great sign of what's to come in 2017 #womeninsport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful words about the invisibility of women...
https://t.co/smZ3LhWrZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_DeWeaver @Captainturtle they have a beautiful song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahinthesen8 asks what has happened to Australia? 15 years since the Tampa shows detention is wrong. #LetThemStay https://t.co/aZOLroHHli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember ever heart represents a person held injustly and in abuse. #LetThemStay #BringThemHere #Adelaide #refugees https://t.co/Ar7De1HJll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearts put on line to acknowledge those held without compassion by our Gov. #CloseTheCamps #LetThemStay #Adelaide https://t.co/M23EW4tdQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Refugees #LetThemStay #EndTheAbuse #CloseTheCamps  #Adelaide https://t.co/3Hk31g2tXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We call on Gov to end the abuse, oppression &amp; our people to end indifference #LetThemStay #auspol #adelaide https://t.co/XeZXC77IYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Adelaide showing compassion and asking same from our Government. We all know about the abuse now #LetThemStay https://t.co/zEB2N2ZJFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compassionate crowd gathering on steps of Parliament in #Adelaide for #LetThemStay rally #manus #nauru #refugees https://t.co/GY4wKeCxvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost i have checked order and rest is coming from another store. All ok - thanks for your quick reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auspost only part order of A9T0006414 delivered. Where's the rest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TurnbullMalcolm cut the plebiscite, have a free vote in parliament and keep supporting our vulnerable #auspol https://t.co/L3Em0xO45C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cornesy12 Hey Cornesy, last time I checked Jen Williams was a woman, an expert in brain training, knows a bit about footy &amp; a South Aussie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nauru files: Labor pushes for parliamentary inquiry into abuse allegations https://t.co/kfqg3N1to1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abuse of children continues to be the accepted National pastime of Australia, backed by State and Federal Gov's #naurufiles #dondale #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NauruFiles: proof of an abusive, broken policy. Join the call for @TurnbullMalcolm to #BringThemHere https://t.co/OULHN9NLJM via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out! I donated to HELP FUND GARY FOR TWEED COUNCIL  https://t.co/Y70SrZVdoi via @gofundme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you really want to hurt me?

 #bettercensusquestions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's love got to do with it?  #bettercensusquestions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Census fails the arts
https://t.co/ewj6FChEFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna Torv #SecretCity https://t.co/7hMIvN61Em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people at the Port enjoying late arvo sunshine and great food at Fork in the Port @ourportadl #HartsMill https://t.co/FPxp5C0r84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did #MelissaMcBride not get an #Emmy nomination for her work in @TheWalkingDead ? #TWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone stating the #LNP lost votes in the election for any reason other than its awful policies is deluded. #auspol #LeadershipRedHerring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to investigate the Anatomy of a Villain with Marianne Musgrove #writing https://t.co/fqrgcKnn1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous Australians unfairly jailed due to racism in legal system – research https://t.co/oNKF65Hz4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper @3wombats  First *white* rock and roll star?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lonely Boys - Murray Island. #NAIDOCWeek 
https://t.co/WxjqSMYoIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LNP should acknowledge Oz does not like their policies, regardless who is their leader. Turnbull vs Abbott just red herring #ausvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut @faully33 seems like that might be a very big assumption!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlstefanovic Why allow so clearly a biased #LNP stooge air time on your show? Please drop Miranda Devine. Thanks Karl, you're a champ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antfarmer @DavidLeyonhjelm both, probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antfarmer @DavidLeyonhjelm probably the gun lobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi everyone. We need a change of government this weekend. Hope you can assist. Ta. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2LapsDown @toninicho @smh also sells lots of newspapers - vested interest of media has role to play too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like tax payers should own mines - profits would come back to 'shareholders' and be used to clean up sites. https://t.co/eolInI7k0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow those #LNP TV spots have @newscomauHQ as source for the outrageous statements against opposition. That's. real. solid. evidence. #lol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>