<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump poor buggers only wanted to go to a country with hope of a better future, but could end up in US instead. Sorry for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CricketAus It's a batting collapse ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CricketAus Playing like a team with one foot already on the plane home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #australiaday https://t.co/ov8vAq6Zgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump bit like the Mayan calendar. Lots of huff about the end of the world then nothing. Only so much he can do without Congress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We get the message Mark Taylor, you're surprised it didn't carry. Do t have to say it 50 times #wwos @CricketAus #gethimofftheair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisJay49 @AFL @WestCoastEagles They would wear the predominately blue against Hawthorn. That's why it is a clash strip not an away jumper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_bully Parmesan with melted butter. Been making it for years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @FOXSportsAUS playing classic @RaidersCanberra games, but what about the 1990 Easter massacre of Easts, Mal's 38 points haul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holden_aus Without a RWD V8 in the lineup, I will be sticking with my VF for a long time yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relaxing on a summers day with @thebeatles on YouTube. Still the greatest. When are you coming back to Australia @PaulMcCartney ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using an actors awards ceremony for your own political rant is tacky &amp; poor taste, whether you agree with her or not #timeandplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing we were back at Lammermoor Beach @Queensland enjoying the serenity https://t.co/HWSdzSlIwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So media is now telling "keyboard warriors" to leave Hird alone. Didn't see them camped outside his home, work, kids school etc. #hypocrisy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very angry @BeyondBank is charging nearly $300 to give back our own deed document. #ripoff #profitsbeforecustomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdbrown50 You got my vote already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial have long wished for a standalone VFL side playing out of Arden St]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial @Boomer_29 still remember @CLealiifano visiting my son when he has ALL, great bloke. All the best Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supercars can only wait to see what @OfficialHSV release post real Commodores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supercars @shanevg97 @holden_racing one rule for @888Official one rule for the rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial not too bad for a @MazdaAus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive will still call it Kitty Litter Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFL would of preferred the 2012 Brownlow to be listed as no winner, similar to when NRL stripped Storm of premierships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holdenman78 @MantelloHolden @holden_aus still love my MY14 SSV, you won't be disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerardWhateley @RicFinlay @abcgrandstand disgraceful &amp; weak as piss. Too many heroes, not enough substance. Where is a S Waugh when needed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely pitiful @CricketAus An embarrassment to the country to put in such a weak as piss effort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Bowen @bdbrown50 would be a great choice for 20. Give 29 a year off then give it to Ahern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial @lukemcdonald21 @GlennArcher11 so do you change your twitter name now? ðŸ˜„ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @petersiddle403 in the Test side. Aussie team needs more #shinbonerspirit @NMFCOfficial ðŸðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how is it inevitable? The @AFL schedule it, so unless they want it, it does not have to happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty in the words of Daryl Kerrigan, tell em all to get stuffed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion tough start with 4 finalists in a row then a trip to Perth. But not a bad fixture, &amp; rapt to finally have Good Friday footy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial should be locked in for next 20 years, but @AFL would never treat Roos that well. Guess the stripes are the wrong colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty @SammyHeraldSun then get shafted every year there after so Collingwood &amp; Essendon can share it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katestruth @NMOpinion because Pies &amp; Scum invented ANZAC Day, just ask them. The diggers just hijack their day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanhrovat @NMFCOfficial welcome aboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronDblack35 good luck at Kitty Litter Park, but not too much ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of talent for next to no cost, a positive trade period for @NMFCOfficial  The regeneration has begun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AusSportPolls should be investigated. Any Indian bookmakers involved?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he turns out as good as the wraps suggest, this will be bargain of the decade https://t.co/7hpIh0l1aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty @theheraldsun rumours won't go away because social media won't let them, &amp; wife tweet was probably a fake account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Bowen it's a big win for everyone if Hawks slide ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supercars @redbullracingAU @jamiewhincup what a surprise from Roland - his team are NEVER in the wrong, just ask him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supercars have a cry Roland. Whincup should of got a drive through so consider yourself lucky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holden_racing and 888 trying to blame GT. ARSEHOLES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supercars if Whincup doesn't get a drive thru for that, the race is rigged ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sortadunno @NMOpinion very true, we can only judge from the outside. Have never heard he spoken of like Carey, Riewoldt, Hodge etc though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion fine player but honestly felt he was never the inspirational on field leader the club needed, like so many of the great captains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial great effort by Shaun Higgins considering how much footy he missed. Huge congrats to Robbie Tarrant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmar69 don't have to earn spots at @freodockers , just ask Zac Dawson ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SENNews @NMOpinion Kieran Harper is my biggest disappointment from that list, showed so much promise but hasn't kicked on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesalbone just the thought of it is nauseating ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carn the Doggies, time to create yourself some history #bemorebulldog  #AFLGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukemcdonald21 did he get a ticket?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion which is why the Brownlow has lost some of its appeal, its now the Umpires Pet Award]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @majakdaw on Mark of the Year. Bloody awesome effort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial be lucky if any Roo gets a vote after round 9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs or Giants. Either way, someone new in the GF. Bloody awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westernbulldogs @AFL good luck Doggies, smash the arrogant scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_bully the kiddie fiddling Catholics are much better aren't they Pauline?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive let them have him. Every other club that's looked at him has passed when he failed the medical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion rebuild is good chance to freshen leadership too. Spitta is good player but not an inspirational skipper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion given opportunities &amp; forced to step up will make or break some players. Cunners improved when Spitta injured achilles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive if Lloyd thinks he should go to Brisbane, then he should definitely stay at @NMFCOfficial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion it is sad &amp; would be horrible to see him in other colours. Will be a very different side in round 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kwongtology @MiamiHeatFinest @onduties @316bbbd will still back them to finish above Essendon in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bestaflmemes @westernbulldogs let's hope it keeps rolling for at least one more week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersNRL will Mounties prelim final be played before? Or will it be in Shitney?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty throw up enough shit, you might get one right. Lazy journalism again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersCanberra don't care, just as long as it's a brutal game that goes to golden point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7aflgameday @NMOpinion but the season goes for 23 rounds so this whole discussion is as useless as a Brian Taylor commentary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing end to the season. Thank you to 4 @NMFCOfficial champions. Bring in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EssendonFC @GWSGIANTS @Kevin_Sheedy yes, never forget he came from Richmond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersNRL which means he will return in 2 weeks after the Green Machine have next week off #BleedGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersCanberra @giostadium @NRL @sydneyroosters will be there, gonna party like its 1989 ðŸ’šðŸ’šðŸ’šðŸ’šðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion hopefully see some Roos pick up MOTY &amp; GOTY &amp; a Norm Smith Medal this year ðŸ†ðŸ†ðŸ†ðŸ†ðŸ†ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µâšªï¸ðŸ”µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty @tabcomaumedia there is another game you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty of course, a footy free weekend in September. What a brilliant idea. NOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive yes it is, if only it would be produced more consistently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion neither. Time to move on &amp; accept the clubs decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive this is becoming ridiculous. They werent sacked, they didn't have contracts for 2017 &amp; club chose not to offer new contracts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SENBreakfast @NMOpinion Another rumour at this time of year. Very few actually end up true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion true supporters will stick around, the rest can go to Richmond &amp; get their Velcro memberships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thossian @NMFCOfficial sad to see them go, but time heals &amp; if we lose some "supporters" then they were never really Troo Roos anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heraldsunsport @superfooty @gilbertgardiner do you know if he was given that option but didn't take it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Boomer_29 @drewpetrie20 Dal &amp; Spud on years of amazing service to @NMFCOfficial Lets see you go out in style with a premiership ðŸ†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFOOTY opinions are like assholes, every1 has 1 &amp; most are full of shit &amp; wind. Different teams are favourites or can't win every week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markadamsiphone @FOXFootyLive I have been, and they are no worse than any other club. Maybe you need to go to games outside of Adelaide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markadamsiphone @FOXFootyLive very narrow minded view, every club sadly has fans like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty not even close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty definitely not, even Gold Coast deserve it more than that scum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty they will get it because they are Essendon. So many other clubs deserve Friday footy in 2017 before this mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@superfooty @Robbo_heraldsun The Duck still streets in front of Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMOpinion games are won on the scoreboard, and @NMFCOfficial have been very poor at kicking goals &amp; winning scores. Very dismal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial any risk of someone actually kicking a goal? Wasteful kicking at goal yet again. Most frustrating part of whole season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial and guess where it counts. Forward entries haphazard as usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMFCOfficial would not call that a dominant quarter. Better than the 1st but long way from dominating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @7AFL at least get names right? Leigh Tutor? Amateur effort by 2nd rate broadcaster #AFLNorthSwans @NMFCOfficial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will it be shown on @FOXFOOTY because @7AFL never show it north of the Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AusSportPolls hope the Boomers aren't thinking silver]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>