<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@wesnice Good luck with your permits! #hikerchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A15 #hikerchat Snowshoeing in the local mtns. Hoping to get to Baker w/ fresh snow! @TETONsports @Discover_MBS  https://t.co/tBqToWW6zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A13 #hikerchat Super thick mud, 5am screeching eagles and Ravens stealing our snacks @OlympicNP overnight along the west coast @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TETONsports He's learning abt better layering! And has noticed how much work it is to get out for a weekend together. #hikerchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8 #hikerchat Our best friend surprised us at the summit of Mt Whitney to celebrate our completion of  the JMT hike @fullvanfun #bestfriends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 con't I do make him pack his own clothes tho there have been a few trips that he's shivered....#hikerchat @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 #hikerchat I usually do the prep. Hubby hasn't caught on to all the details necessary to complete @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6 #hikerchat My husband @danpulsifer in full hiker beard. He's got the loudest, scariest yell I know! @fullvanfun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hugged the first tree I saw on my way down from Mt Whitney summit! #hikerchat @WidowVoyages @TETONsports @TheHikingDiva @bushwhackingfoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A5 #hikerchat I took a friend up Railroad Grade at Mt Baker. Not too long, good overnight location w/ explore ops @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TETONsports @k2rm Except when siblings didn't get the outdoor bug and whine and complain the whole time... :P #hikerchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 #hikerchat Excellent knowledge and experience with backpacking. More relaxing when I don't have to spend time teaching @fullvanfun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 #hikerchat Able to keep up with my pace, able to work together in camp, able to entertain each other @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2 #hikerchat All of the above! Always feel safer hiking w/ someone and can bring more goodies when can distribute the load @fullvanfun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I'd really love a furry companion one dat. Keep hoping for a pack alpaca. @TETONsports #hikerchat @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 I'm out w/ my hubby as often as our schedules allow. We went on a week-long hike within a month of mtg #hikerchat https://t.co/XtZyuMoRtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm here for #hikerchat. Popping in and out between work assignments! @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my @ParksCanada Free Pass today! Can't wait to explore our National Parks #hikerchat #parkchat #Canada150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gcouros Set them up in an edu chat so they get to connect with others right away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for hosting @Hiker_Steve &amp; @Bernardine. Look forward to the next one. G’night from the Left coast! #CDNHikeChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A10 #CDNHikeChat Always try to hit up a local craft brewery after a hike!  @Bernardine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hiker_Steve Dang! I’m not at home with my pirate gear #CDNHikeChat #Ahoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hiker_Steve @kristapetrie @MelodramaBabs Our last day was summiting Mt. Whitney, 14505’! https://t.co/aomfG72PTu #CDNHikeChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8 #CDNHikeChat "Walks long miles in high places” :D Still waiting for my trail name... @Hiker_Steve @Bernardine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kristapetrie @Hiker_Steve And catching the occasional view of the ISS! @NASA #CDNHikeChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kristapetrie @MelodramaBabs Hiked in the Sierras of California last summer. Crazy altitude high! Really changes hike speed #CDNHikeChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 #CDNHikeChat Was glad when Jasper Nat’l became a Dark Sky Preserve. Beautiful to mix stars &amp; mtns #DarkSky @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hiker_Steve @Bernardine Nope! Thank goodness for hiking poles! #CDNHikeChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Hiker_Steve @Bernardine Absolutely! I’m fast through the forest sections, and on the trip out. Slow down for the views and stop for lakes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6  Extra. Made it down from Berg Lake  (Mt Robson) in personal record best of 5 hours (20 km) #CDNHikeChat @Bernardine @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6 #CDNHikeChat I’m definitely guilty of being a hare! Tend to leave hiking partners in the dust... @Bernardine @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A5 #CDNHikeChat Looks like the cute sandpiper from the @DisneyPixar short! @Hiker_Steve https://t.co/NfCNV2DRr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 #CDNHikeChat Leave no trace! :P @Bernardine @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CDNHikeChat Good old blue tarp from @CanadianTire! Worth the weight on some trips @Hiker_Steve @Bernardine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 #CDNHikeChat Gotten good at stringing up shelter tarps here in the PacNW. Never know when it’ll rain @Hiker_Steve @Bernardine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CDNHikeChat @MelodramaBabs Def want to invest in a lightweight spinner or fly rod to take backcountry! @Bernardine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2 #CDNHikeChat Fished &amp; ate this summer along the JMT. Great way to supplement calories. https://t.co/y4V4gseaVg @Bernardine @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 #CDNHikeChat Lots of sea kayak opps on our coast. Bowren Lakes is really popular for canoes @Hiker_Steve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woot Woot! I'm here for #CDNHikeChat from just outside Vancouver @Hiker_Steve #BeautifulBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 #HikerChat Either somewhere local and easy or somewhere mountainous and snowy! Depends on weather and energy @HikerChat @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A5 @Wilderness1967 Definitely agree w/ burritos... all sorts of colourful ingredients rolled up together! #hikerchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HikerChat A7 Lots of @icebreakernz layers. Merino keeps you warm even when sweaty! @TETONsports @HikerChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RCGibby73 @HikerChat I love this reply. I think this is how I'm feeling these days too #hikerchat #optoutside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HikerChat A13 Hiking is a pretty isolated/isolating activity. It's important to connect and know we're not alone! @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again catching up late to #hikerchat. Wish I didn't have to be at work! Looks like it was a great chat! @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Flow397 &amp; @59NationalParks for another great #ParkChat! Just getting bigger &amp; bigger! #nps101 #FindYourPark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A11 #ParkChat Def hard to describe! Peace, joy, satisfaction, excitement… #oneofakind @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Flow397 In Mineral King hikers wrap chicken wire to keep our marmots #ParkChat @SequoiaKingsNPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@akonthego Been using @AlaskaAir pts to go to Cali. Maybe we need to start looking North… #parkchat @alaskatravlnews @DenaliNPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A9 #ParkChat pt.2 Hoping to go to Nfld this summer and get to Gros Morne Nat,l Park thx to air miles. @ParksandPoints #Canada150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A9 #ParkChat Plan the big trips years ahead and save up miles. Use credit for everything! @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8 #ParkChat I shared daypack tips on my blog last spring: https://t.co/QAcxJZgUcm Of course the 10 essentials most hikes! @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 #ParkChat We plan to snack lots and cook as many meals as possible. Camping in Nat’l Forest sites saves $$ too @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6 #ParkChat @NCascadesNPS, the American Alps, is a best kept secret! Didn't know it was in my backyard for a few years  @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 #Parkchat A lot of my fav hidden gems are a night or two into the backcountry. Esp high alpine lakes @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playoutsidegal @ParksandPoints @YellowstoneNPS I once woke up to a herd of elk outside my tent in Jasper Nat’l Park. Can’t imagine a bison!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissa_sue @ParksandPoints @YosemiteNPS Which road did you come in on? I love coming from the east through Tioga Pass #ParkChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 #ParkChat I was incredibly wowed &amp; impressed by Treeline Lake just before Mt Whitney @SequoiaKingsNPS… https://t.co/bfxEiCazp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true! @rscottjones A lot of great spots are in the Nat’l Forests &amp; Wilderness around the parks @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2 #ParkChat Off the beaten path, quiet during high season, special vibes https://t.co/zkuP5V68Q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please explain moose church! 
@MissouriHowell @59NationalParks @NatlParkService @GrandTetonNPS #ParkChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got into @YosemiteNPS last summer on my dad-in-laws senior pass! @melissa_sue @59NationalParks @NatlParkService @brian_heyman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 #ParkChat Planning on overnight hike so we could summit Half Dome and avoid the permit lottery @59NationalParks @NatlParkService]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m here from just across the northern Washington border! @59NationalParks @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please give @AltNatParkSer a follow! The folks behind this account are brilliant. #parkchat #hikerchat #nps101 https://t.co/Lgye4VgFOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FindYourPark photo challenge "This is My America!" Mine=@YosemiteNPS first view of Half Dome #parkchat https://t.co/ZxnU098hGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chiming in super late to #hikerchat but still love reading the threads. Hope I can participate proper one day @TETONsports @danjourneytweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 #hikerchat Lived in Edmonton, AB for 8 yrs. -20 day x-country skiing in Jasper was tough on the digits @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 #hikerchat I don't feel like winter's over yet! We plan snowshoe trips in the mountains thru April #PNW @TETONsports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hiker_Steve @Bernardine Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These made me laugh! #hikerchat https://t.co/o8VjLFNSPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your New Year's resolution to hike more? I've got some ideas and inspiration for you!  https://t.co/V04ngApjDJ #hikerchat #resolutions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @59NationalParks &amp; @Flow397 for the awesome discussion questions! Looking forward to next week! #parkchat @ParksandPoints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rscottjones @pubclub @DWoutside @Stars252525 @59NationalParks We often search for a craft brewery near our trailhead! #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A11 #ParkChat Seldom plan ahead. Got messed up @YosemiteNPS with that approach tho. Missed out on Glacier Pt :( @59NationalParks @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Flow397 @WildWithinHer Tons and tons of planning &amp; prep. I have some tips and ideas on my JMT blog https://t.co/slfS6cmuPK #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A10 #Parkchat 2/2 In Canada, Pacific Rim, Jasper Nat'l Park, and Gros Morne in Nfld are hopeful possibilities! @ParksCanada @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A10 #ParkChat If I get it all, then PCT thru Washington, lots of time @Discover_MBS and @NCascadesNPS 1/2 @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildWithinHer It was interesting planning 21 days of vegetarian backpacking food for the JMT. I think I eat better on trail! #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grovergirl72 I love the big indulgent dinner after a day on trail! #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A9 #ParkChat Have some favs that we reuse regularly. Love to visit Trader Joe's before a camping trip @59NationalParks @MissouriHowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JrRangerTigran @Flow397  I've been keeping track for the last few years. Hike, location, distance, weather, trail condition, etc #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8 #ParkChat Racked up 400 miles last year. Hope to break 500 in 2017! @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@59NationalParks Of course! But we only got to list 5 things... Really want a new multitool! #ParkChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 #ParkChat Also really like visiting Ranger Stns and getting first-hand info and looking at real maps #oldschool @59NationalParks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7 #ParkChat I spend a lot of time on @WTA_hikers website. Read hike descriptions &amp; recent trip reports @59NationalParks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6 #ParkChat A little. Now it's time to focus on #Canada150 and visit nearby @ParksCanada for free! @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@59NationalParks @Flow397 I find I can move a bit faster with them, and have saved my ankles many many times #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildWithinHer Aww thanks!!! I'll take you up on that for some southern WA exploring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Flow397 @WildWithinHer I hope the reservation system works this year! What a crazy mess last year. #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildWithinHer I'm up for it! Made it up Excelsior Peak on Mt Baker hwy Saturday in snowshoes! #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A5 #ParkChat Camera, tent, pack, fav boots and trekking poles! 
@59NationalParks @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WildWithinHer @Flow397 That's an awesome challenge. Still haven't ventured near there but it's high on the list! #parkchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 #ParkChat Training hikes in @NCascadesNPS on some of the super steep trails, like Sourdough Mtn https://t.co/TdmJBL8Bss @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramblRramblR Order your free DiscoveryPass now from @ParksCanada to streamline your visits: https://t.co/vfNU7oMw0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1zestytraveler Our mountain trails are steep for sure! Just keep walking and find as many hills/stairs as you can #ParkChat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 #ParkChat Always plan lots of hiking in the Parks so stay in hiking shape w/ the help of the gym &amp; snowshoeing! @59NationalParks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2 #ParkChat Def the weather! Tend to overpack for weather in the Pac NW and still sometimes get caught out. @Flow397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 #ParkChat 2/2 Canadian Nat'l Parks are free this year so hope to visit a few of those too! #Canada150 @ParksCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 #ParkChat Hoping to hike the PCT thru WA, so will likely visit @MountRainierNPS and @NCascadesNPS. 1/2 https://t.co/PbkApZBBZ2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>