<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cardiffste Not as crafty as you though. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man with salmon coloured trousers on the telly NOW!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sorry to hear about Roanne Dods. An inspiration who spoke to us with such honesty and grace at Culture lab in April. Always dancing ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done, Tom! SDUK in good hands. Thomas Hescott appointed executive director of Stage Directors UK https://t.co/lDIlm33V7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for your fb thread @sharonhafmorgan https://t.co/8QxxMCxvOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody mother******* awesome. Loved @WainBright tonight @TramshedCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewBulgo Watch Fawlty Towers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd you're always on the old pipe.  No wonder you can't think straight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news about @mbelshaw A class act and the first to come and say hello to me when I was on my nervous intro day at @CloreLeadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dollyrocket I think you've had some cowboys in, love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd @lucidtheatreco And what a celebration of theatre that will be!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great organisation - thinking about and active in all the important stuff... https://t.co/NVlsrcojbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody woke me up at 4am asking for a bucket of hay! https://t.co/uXEZ1EQ3Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a brilliant opportunity. Make the most of it while there are some places still left. https://t.co/DY0VsuKTa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd Do you also have a matching spitoon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great time at @BristolOldVic last night. Box office and FOH really friendly and helpful. Bar buzzing and a fizzy smart show &amp; cast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemengo Sorry to miss you. It was busy there. Next time. Have a great tour. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemengo Well done last night. Really enjoyed the show and you look good in peach. Did you really shit yourself or was that acting? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oslo’s International Ibsen Festival: Norway lauds its most famous son https://t.co/kiL25V0B5k via @TheStage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dude. https://t.co/RLrgv5cP6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewBulgo If it's Wales, one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campaign for better pay for artists and shake up of boards launched by national arts body https://t.co/1LMnkKmJhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the year of Roald Dahl that notorious anti-Semite and Nazi sympathiser who wrote books. You did know that, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffCripps @ArtsPro Thanks, Geoff. @Pibydd is fed up of hearing this stuff from me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the more who join, the more we can do for each other #joinSDUK https://t.co/3Npz0RKAjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong voices. Powerful words. This is directors together. https://t.co/KMs2B8Ju3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy tweaking last bits for @culturelabwales final weekend @FSCMargam Hopefully, just the start of things for our amazing group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity from SDUK. https://t.co/u2aQbsKweM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS renationalise the railways now. https://t.co/FMM3O5E1Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following on from my last tweet https://t.co/mIdHbGvDA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legoland. Please send help. https://t.co/gyY6IYrz6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blog what I wrote #SDUK https://t.co/HKo8eBHZH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: https://t.co/5KV9vEmlv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngharadLee @mattballsays @sargent65 @StageDirectors I'll be writing something up soon and other chances for us to get together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums up how I felt too https://t.co/kTo1zlqZF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw the glorious John Grant last night but I do love this guy -  Scritti Politti https://t.co/nDMIMH9Vd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelandlouise should see you through till the morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelandlouise treat it as a starter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The masses are really interested in what comes after capitalism. @ St David's Hall https://t.co/cqQaGAeXV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about the bravest and most resilient people tonight - Des and Doreen James. Hard to imagine their suffering. Good on you Phil Ralph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's spam mail dilemma - "Classic or performance - choose your boardshorts.."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The BBC Radio Wales Patrick Hannan Lecture https://t.co/US10FLJV2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @FestivalofVoice @scrittipolitti @johnwgrant and @Mbongwana_Star on the same night? Choosing which gig to see has ruined me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StageDirectors Details and how to register here https://t.co/KRmuriEmXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By Directors, For Directors in Wales...
https://t.co/KRmuriVXOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blown away by @ChrisSonnex talking about @GoodChanceCal today. #Theatre2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking @Theatre_2016 on Friday. Will be reflecting on @culturelabwales and leadership in transitional times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely solo set by Carwyn Ellis of @colorama_sound at @calanmaimusic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch @hangfirebbq Great friendly staff, buzzy atmosphere and totally delicious food. #Barrylove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so glad I joined @StageDirectors Directors are not all out for themselves. We can make a community and support each other #joinSDUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ace SDUK board meeting tonight. Really excited by how things are coming together and for the future directorstogether#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carwyn Jones on Creative Wales https://t.co/o7OmZzwFT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Llantwit Major Beach, South Wales https://t.co/EvrntkNNkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roannedods with the culture lab crew. https://t.co/DqMqCH2nSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just about to start another Sduk board meeting in these more than usually glam surroundings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Penarth, Vale of Glamorgan https://t.co/r2hfGpOERW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pork_pies @Iolo_Platfform @Simon_NTW @Milney_TV @laurahd Sorry won't be able to join you today. Have fun. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some fairness in this, but don't call it "brave" and "bold." It isn't. https://t.co/GP4RTQ7RDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[William Gaskill obituary - https://t.co/nvIYGY58cA https://t.co/FQdgfwFq07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talked about Bill with my class of @YoungRWCMD students only last week. Urged them to read A Sense Of Direction. Unique &amp; uncompromising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud to say I was taught by Bill. 30 years ago but I have thought about his teaching nearly every day since.

https://t.co/XCu8T4IXIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StageDirectors Sorry I had to dash. Was really enjoying the discussion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd my fave... Not. Congrats on the house. I hope it's not in a "bad area!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd not pressed send yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't listened to Blackstar - can't - since last Monday but saw this and have to the Strauss 4 Last Songs all day https://t.co/IdM11WoTqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay. That's enough. Can everybody just stop dying now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My David Bowie, alive forever

https://t.co/WnfmJGA2QZ

Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived. Wowie. https://t.co/p1zfhTdq9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already love Black Star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really proud of SDUK for this... First standard contract for assistant theatre directors launched https://t.co/FoH7L98jv4 via @TheStage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcareywilliams There's a lot of good looking wood on that set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is happening and will be good...https://t.co/JIqvBospoU Take a look. https://t.co/Yl5YV1gO7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mister Potato is coming to town. Allegedly. #fiveyearolds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted for our big boss in the #NewYearHonours Well deserved and now we know his middle name! https://t.co/YQwxm2uQxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcareywilliams Derby and the bike shed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So a theatre is offering mid-career development to anyone with over 5 years experience. That's about right - 10 years for an entire career.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilly Harris was here. https://t.co/j1R7YiXbvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want for Christmas is my two front teeth... https://t.co/W7r5vbKKBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd This is balls. He's tried saying stuff like this before. Does he think we don't know what goes on in England?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arts Council of Wales hit with 5% cut https://t.co/STzHAZTTRa via @TheStage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a Cardiff-based actor, theatre-maker, creative make sure you take up this incredible £5 offer on Saturday. https://t.co/NyJ4ETV0rD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV satirist John Oliver responds to Paris attacks with 'a moment of premium cable profanity' https://t.co/jIp5nkyGQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to tomorrow's conversations with @dollyrocket @Shaz_Casey @kwasserberg @garethlloyd @sandrabendelow #producersplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking out "Artists/ Producers/ Mentors / Mentees" on National Theatre Wales Community: https://t.co/JrKmJ93wv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffCripps Ha ha. Very good. I fear I would lack in compliance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Arts Council of Wales chair search continues https://t.co/PwClirNdhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click on Wales » Blog Archive » The Centre-Periphery Game https://t.co/BNy3WUdJ6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDUK Masterclass - Jeremy Herrin on 'Collaboration' https://t.co/piizS3KAxy via @lizholmesod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers quantify the intrinsic value of culture | News | ArtsProfessional http://t.co/s3orxNNLwQ via @artspro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd Words I never thought I'd find in the same sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week Nigel took me up Leather Lane and I quite liked it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Trueman: Are we at risk of forgetting the plays of the past? - http://t.co/nvIYGXNxl2 http://t.co/N2zM4IHQVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things Mrs H says #771 Me: Omg. That was amazing! Mrs H: Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahd You mean in front of the fridge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papertrail_org @StageDirectors Great that you are on board, Bridge. #directorstogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Poshcosh it's going to be the nationals. Nowhere else for it to come from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arts_Wales_  #investmentreview implies radical change may be required even of companies that have retained their revenue status. Hope so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the lack of any significant change in numbers, it looks like the national companies are going to have to take the brunt of the cuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to see @earthfall lose its revenue funding in @Arts_Wales_  #investmentreview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't bear guff about "winners and losers" in commentary on today's @Arts_Wales_   #investmentreview announcement. It's not a competition.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>