<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[State Dept. reverses visa revocations, allowing previously banned travelers to enter U.S. https://t.co/LtdtdU5Km8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Things They Won’t Tell You About the Flint Water Tragedy. But I Will. | MICHAEL MOORE https://t.co/Z1g9eunAmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Considers Taking Legal Action Against Trump's Immigration Order https://t.co/qbfQlvXkDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s rallying cry: fear itself.  Beware, Trump's fear-mongering is prelude to war-mongering.  War magnifies fear. https://t.co/p1IbTF3UvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad we have 3 branches of government. Judiciary stands up to Trump! GOPCongress adopts Trumps values, not Americas. https://t.co/g5bsjK1FuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The so-called President bashes Judge who blocks unconstitutional ban.  Trump used Roy Cohen playbook. Shame on Trump https://t.co/JzRsSVIhay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eric Trump’s business trip to Uruguay cost taxpayers $97,830 in hotel bills to promote his dad's business interests  https://t.co/NWAZMiIPdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent: Federal judge temporarily blocks Trump’s entry order nationwide https://t.co/FGLRbpNHeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Children play in rice paddies hit by drought, photo by Gary Braasch, at SEJ &amp; Wilson Ctr presentation tonight. https://t.co/PIH6Bz8EFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comic-in-Chief approves raid from dinner party instead of situation room, failing to provide basic leadership. https://t.co/0tYOz4DVr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Star father Khizr Khan: Congress, voters should resist ‘Muslim ban’ https://t.co/nPm5x5JSHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration can not survive 4 years without a war.  Trump knows this.  Trump WANTS to start a war. Stop him https://t.co/n9Hn85ZPsL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American public will hold each these warmongers personally responsible for the evil they inflict on our children https://t.co/qQCPxfVLBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disturbing spin by a White House that repeatedly lies to Americans -- yes Americans -- about basic facts. Trump lies https://t.co/qQCPxfVLBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/sJEgRN3yCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags - The Washington Post https://t.co/4aP47lj8rZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence interviewed by Judy Woodruff tonight.  Pence falls back on expression "I believe" again and again.  He refuses to address any FACTS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance from within: Federal workers push back against Trump https://t.co/oMFZz26AZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump firing Sally Yates isn’t the big story. How he did it is. Trump follows footsteps of mentor, Roy Cohen. https://t.co/9Hnj4Pr3Gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My family saw America's best and worst; Trump's refugee ban takes us back to the worst | The Charlotte Observer https://t.co/NyCWkASuuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please read this: this is exactly what happened with Hitler.  The German aristocracy thought they could control him. https://t.co/2zPypIBMVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican Fausts, via @nytimes This is EXACTLY what happened in Hitler's Germany! https://t.co/2zPypIBMVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy-Cohen-in-Chief: Trump’s Falsehoods Make Foreign Leaders Ask: Can We Trust Him?, via @nytimes https://t.co/8ZSLiS4CGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liar-Bully-in-Chief: Trump’s Falsehoods Make Foreign Leaders Ask: Can We Trust Him?, via @nytimes https://t.co/8ZSLiS4CGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks promised to hire thousands of refugees. Will give my friends gift certificates to Starbucks! https://t.co/3OvjcTAx4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and White House spin personal damage inflicted by his orders as if he's following a script from Orwell's 1984. https://t.co/GtJpVe4dAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 'Roy Cohen' move by Trump: attack opponent's personal integrity.  Will he go after the federal judges next? https://t.co/Wg6ajDgqws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sacks defiant attorney general https://t.co/BThgkUyHBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US acting attorney general defies Trump immigrant ban https://t.co/7AbftBoj8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm proud of our former president, the ACLU, many lawyers and all the protesters standing up for our precious American values.  Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legal community has shown themselves to be very generous.  They have gotten out there and helped a lot of immigrants stuck in airports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope the diplomats continue to work for us and our American values! https://t.co/XyexVCPHcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angry Americans lash out at Trump for being a coward and stoking fear.  He is a liar-bully-in-chief! https://t.co/sH4eEm3bpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying Spicer must go: Diplomats opposed to immigration ban exercise their freedom of speech.  I support them.   https://t.co/GztTt1PSoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lies again &amp; defiantly says ‘all is going well’ on immigration order amid chaos, while Obama backs protesters https://t.co/9vV8EoBfrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama defends American values.  Stands up to Trump who verbally attacks protesters and own admin staff.  Fantastic! https://t.co/L8o4Exvka9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent! State Department employees protest Trump policy!  Dissent memo circulating in the State Department  https://t.co/DXfDPTxWJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will profit from his ban: Who Hasn’t Trump Banned? People From Places Where He’s Done Business, via @nytimes https://t.co/kagLdoyUzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent! Obama rejects comparison between Trump’s immigration policy and his own, encourages protests https://t.co/fMbOjTHRRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Muslim Ban Is Cowardly and Dangerous, via @nytimes https://t.co/OAf6L9ShkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samantha Bee to Roast Trump on Same Night as Correspondents’ Dinner, via @nytimes https://t.co/njjylb2vkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samantha Bee plans an anti-White House correspondents’ dinner. Will journalists go? https://t.co/cyTbtA08ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACLU: Delay Sessions confirmation vote until ‘Muslim ban’ is stopped https://t.co/BkSFLEraob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The American Civil Liberties Union raised more money online this weekend than it normally gets in a year - Quartz https://t.co/SWkvicPLDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[via @npr: This Week In Trump's 'Alternative Facts'  https://t.co/2q3hunG1MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the media, shutting up is not an option https://t.co/NVKEXf5gsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the rookie federal judge who halted Trump’s refugee deportations — to save a Syrian https://t.co/NQ4FIChbv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump uses Roy Cohen approach to bash Sen McCain and others who used their freedom of speech and conscious to oppose him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order: White House stands firm over travel ban https://t.co/733jjUwAey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Who Blocked Trump’s Refugee Order Praised for ‘Firm Moral Compass’, via @nytimes https://t.co/4isn6KGrxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Excellent article from the New Yorker.  Worth reading. Orwell’s “1984” and Trump’s America - The New Yorker https://t.co/4t9XFLWIOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Mind of Trump: The leaks coming out of the Trump White House cast the president as a clueless child  https://t.co/hjzWIOquMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countries where Trump does business are not hit by new travel restrictions - The Washington Post https://t.co/i0VRAiEsAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identity groups must UNITE &amp; oppose the emerging Authoritarian government.  What are the democratic principles &amp; values that will UNITE us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the ACLU executive director said, "This executive order must die on the vine."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That judge is brave. I anticipate that Trump will go after that judge big time.  That is the Roy Cohen approach he learned so well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone thought the Germans were too sophisticated, too.  Will, in nine months we may no longer have the freedoms that we cherish.  So sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my father's lifetime it happened in Japan, Italy, Germany.  Few people believed the Germans would follow a clown like Hitler but they did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Blocks Part of Trump’s Immigration Order, via @nytimes https://t.co/h0HOPGmwwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Judge stays deportations; Trump order barring refugees, migrants from Muslim countries triggers chaos, o… https://t.co/MdOstyRnDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it surprising how quickly an authoritarian administration is taking over the US. Let's hope we can build on the Federal Judge's stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facing intense criticism, some Republicans are speaking out against Trump’s refugee ban. Paul Ryan and Mitch McCon… https://t.co/TaJJPi0SM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence now supports religious intolerance.  Shame on him!  Pence joins Trump in thinly disguised ban of Muslims. https://t.co/03Isu9ELlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence looses credibility: lacks moral center. Americans appalled at how easily he flip-flops on important issues. https://t.co/R3Vz9RSpH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump needs a war.  Otherwise Trump won't last 4 years.  He knows it. We need to stop him now!  All political identities must UNITE today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware TRUMP's PLAN to DEFEAT ISIS!  Slippery slop to Trump Administration taking us into another bloody, messy war.  Don't be a lemming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Liar-in-Chief, Lying White House Press Secretary, Flip-flopping-lack-integrity GOP build their case for war, DON'T BELIEVE THEM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Immigration Ban excludes Muslim countries with business ties.  So what are Trump and GOP's real motives? Wa… https://t.co/ZesOTPETBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a leader who can unite identity groups based on the shared American values that Trump and GOP are trampling for power and money!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's directives today provide the opportunity for identity groups to unite; for example, immigrants, persons with green cards, scientists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only sane response to people like Trump and Pence is for all identity groups to UNIT and fight politically!  https://t.co/R3Vz9RSpH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political identity groups must UNITE to stop Trump's Christian Crusade before he escalates his war against Muslims and people start to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Trump is preparing the groundwork for sending troops into the Middle East -  The Trump Crusade. Did he get Putin's blessing today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes us more vulnerable.  List is arbitrary.  Radical Muslims come through Pakistan and Egypt who are not on list.  Yemen is not a source.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just banned 134,000,000 people from US. Everyone opposed to Trump, no matter what your identity politics, must UNITE politically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more identity politics.  The only sane response to Trump is for all persons concerned to UNITE!  And to become involved in POLITICS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detained Iraqi released from JFK airport https://t.co/Jhbtv8wgQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green card holders in US legally or trying to return to US are impacted by Trump's ill-thought out directive. Serious blow to our economy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every bully I know likes to hurt innocent people: Trump is no different, Stoking Fear Around Globe, via @nytimes https://t.co/h0HOPGmwwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Change March to Descend on Washington in April | InsideClimate News https://t.co/3PMykHnTB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars for April 29th for the People's Climate March on Washington.  Join us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, causing unnecessary pain and anguish, is no Good Samaritan: Refugees Detained at U.S. Airports, via @nytimes https://t.co/h0HOPGmwwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Mexico wall will destroy lives, Berlin mayor warns https://t.co/i4wvsPVEqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order prompts Google to recall staff https://t.co/0gCpqrrSuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eleven Nobel laureates, thousands of academics sign protest of Trump immigration order https://t.co/xVrATV7A9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian in Chief?  Sad! Is his next directive a crusade?  Sad and dangerous and stupid. https://t.co/jzbheDMOOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIAR IN CHIEF!  President Trump’s first seven days of false claims, inaccurate statements and exaggerations https://t.co/pfa7rK5LyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump and Mexican president speak by phone amid crisis in relations that Trump created. Dangerous!  https://t.co/Jrhju4u8PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kennedy defused crises, Trump creates them. Sad! Why Trump can’t simply build a wall - The Washington Post https://t.co/lJhK8sbkDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subscribe to InsideClimate News Email Newsletters | InsideClimate News https://t.co/gj0zoWYW6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSNatParkService now has 1.2M followers.   https://t.co/iU09sz1lJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s immigration orders will make private prison companies filthy rich – VICE News https://t.co/AZ4TbnTbwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured Park Service to back up his claims about inauguration crowd https://t.co/reg8YpaOPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there.  Join us! https://t.co/m6yrEGWOSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico president: 'We won't pay for wall'- The only way to deal with a bully is to stand up to him.  Sad day for US! https://t.co/xHZdL24vSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Censor in Chief: Trump administration backs off plan to scrub climate pages from EPA website https://t.co/2bhHd3fxZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace protesters climb 270-foot crane in downtown D.C., disrupt traffic https://t.co/mfcK38DbDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idiot in Chief: Trump’s absurd claim the 2012 Pew report researcher was ‘groveling’ https://t.co/P3nxihebVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s definition of ‘voter fraud’ appears to include his own daughter and top adviser https://t.co/rN0vEFMSi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEJ's Leakers Guide. Please circulate widely.  https://t.co/cPinAas80I]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>