<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennEngelken @CaneLibrary Wonderful idea. I love it.  Great promotion of reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hype is Real.

Join your friends. Download MileUp and automatically earn rewards for every mile you drive.… https://t.co/y5Z4iy7K8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Come join us 9:45am and 5pm 2014 N. Church St. , Jonesboro, Arkansas to Worship in Spirit &amp; in Truth.  Bro.  Jamie Barber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theobserver @langstonwertzjr Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pafymneob7  Check out Math &amp; Science @JPSMathSci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jloganwxguy You know that it's ok to be wrong and it be warmer, right ?  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPSMathSci Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Awesome.  Thanks for sharing the pics. Looks great.  Will have to try it sometime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Absolutely not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sprivettKAIT @jloganwxguy @malmjordan @Region8News A wonderful crew. Awesome photo. Keep smiling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan What school will you be at? By chance the School of Hope? Well, it's actually in Fairdealing so I  guess not.  :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan I haven't been there in far too long.  My favorite place was always the Journeyman.  Not even sure if it's still there now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Bro. Jamie Barber will be bringing the messages tomorrow. Come join us 9:45am &amp; 5pm.  Praying to see you there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro 3rd Saturday Singing tonight 6pm at Immanuel Missionary Baptist Church.  Come join us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OverDriveLibs @KCLS @SeaTacAirport Way to reach the community.  Have a wonderful weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joinairhr I found it. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joinairhr Is this available for Android?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jloganwxguy @BryanAMcCormick reach for the stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick That rumbling isn't thunder,  it's my tummy. Gee, thanks.  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Wow. I never expected that.   Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity for class K-5. https://t.co/pjP80UpXCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jloganwxguy @Region8News Can you choose another sign?  :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayers please,  for Bro.  Jamie Barber and his family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Ibotta and get cash back! Install using my referral code and you will get an extra $10: https://t.co/pxiEjodZ3J.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonesborobma District WMA meeting scheduled for tomorrow at Walnut Grove has been canceled.  Please help get the word out. God bless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrawingPenciI You sure make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badazzrd76 Anyone you know? https://t.co/ubNeW99dmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Prayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Happy New Year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews prayers for his family and the force.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByMikeMooneyham @postandcourier Great article.  Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm running late @OrganicValley, I'd rather give up #Breakfast. https://t.co/tn84bgaxIh #OrganicBalance
https://t.co/FW7M6bL4VC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Prayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LongmirePosse @netflix @LouDPhillips @kateesackhoff @cassidyfreeman @Adam_Bartley @ucrosspop25 I love this show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick @kfvsnews @Ahansonkfvs @TommyDawson88 @MKBurgessKFVS Merry Christmas and a very Blessed New Year!  What a beautiful group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Cloudy and sprinkling in Nettleton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro 9:45am tomorrow Bro. Jamie Barber preaching.  Christmas Dinner following.  2014 N. Church St. , Jonesboro, Arkansas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Bro. Barber's will bring the messages tomorrow,  Christmas Dinner following a.m. service. Come join us.  2014 N. Church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Perhaps,  it came our way?  Jonesboro, Arkansas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Great job. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray for Anthony and Mary Pennington in New Mexico and for Neighborhood Mercy Church to continue to impact lives and multiply there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Happy Birthday Blessings,  George. Have an awesome year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFDaley Have missed you Dr. Sweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Boreanaz @BONESonFOX Ya'll are so great together.   Why end such an awesome thing with a wonderful cast? Thank you for the memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pejvahdat @BONESonFOX I  love this show and it's deeply depressing that  it's ending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrinceWmLibrary So cool. I  hope everyone in the area takes advantage of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan @JordnHowington @icecube I  didn't know myself and still don't have the details although my kids school me daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Join us tomorrow 9:45am &amp; 5pm.  Bro. Jamie Barber will bring the messages.  2014 N. Church St., Jonesboro, Arkansas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Having a great day with family in Whitewater.  Hope yours is good as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPSMathSci Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Batten down the hatches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Happy Birthday Blessings,  Shad.  God bless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTRCyclones Looking forward to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray today for John and Louela Page in Cambodia and for new leaders to be developed and for people to come to Christ there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Brr. Hold off the rain. Heading that way Saturday.  At least keep White Water dry, until noon, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPSHurricane @JPSMathSci Congratulations Mrs.  Douglas and Mrs. Lichucki.  Wtg!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keenacrenshaw @SockwellScience @JPSMathSci Cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPSMathSci @HubbellNancy @latonja68 There's always something happening at Math &amp; Science.  Love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Thank you.  I  love these specials.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisJacksonSC @ryanvaughan @wxbrad Great capture,  but so heartbreaking.  Prayers for you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BONESonFOX Say it isn't so! I  love this show and have been watching it on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AHTD Amen to that. I can't believe the number of people driving around with them off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faithclubdotnet Amen. Have a blessed day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray today for Justin and Crystal Owens, missionaries in Estonia, as they continue to learn the language and minister there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dorismckeown1 Heylo,  stranger.  How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Happy Thanksgiving to you and yours.  God bless ya'll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Not mine. Sweet potatoe or apple or pecan pie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Prayers for her family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeliciaBoltonTV @Region8News Welcome Daisha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Thank you.  Heading that  way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heads up elementary teachers. https://t.co/oQu7pKckQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laceysherrod @ryanvaughan Beautiful.  I  have family there .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My baby girl, Megan, has her own wheels. Look out everyone!  Love you Megan. https://t.co/2wFJMg0AMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TriPeaksApp I  love this game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrickingKaos Me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RussellDWalker @ryanvaughan Great catch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jloganwxguy @JGrayKAIT Great photo.  You're beautiful people with wonderful smiles. Have a blessed day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPSMathSci Snack Day will be a week from tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick Anytime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanAMcCormick So sorry for your loss.  Will keep you and your family in prayer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro  Brotherhood tonight,  6pm at Immanuel Missionary Baptist Church in Jonesboro.  Come join us. 2014 N. Church St.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lichuckik @april_ramer Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Region8News Prayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro  Bro. Marvin is in room 112 at the hospice house .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Please keep Bro. Marvin 's family in prayer as well.  We love ya'll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayers are greatly needed for my dear friend and former pastor,  Bro. Marvin Tate.  Afternoon going to hospice.   @IMBCJonesboro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play Solitaire TriPeaks!
https://t.co/TP5dwmEHda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTRCyclones @JPSHurricane Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayers please,  for Bro. Marvin Tate in room 3217 at St. Bernard's for dehydration.  @IMBCJonesboro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OTRCyclones Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click To Give @ The Breast Cancer Site https://t.co/YNmxYf6YQa via @po_st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryanvaughan Welcome to the club.  Now, is there an app for this to initiate correction, or possibly immunization?   : -)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshHarvison Prayers for all involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaaSowSow Most definitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMBCJonesboro Prayers needed for Bro. Pat &amp; Sis. Diane Spriggs and their children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMA of Jonesboro Association Meeting Center Hill 7pm tonight. @IMBCJonesboro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BKLYNlibrary Cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Child_Neurology Anytime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@accessfreely Wonderful.  What a fun idea. Enjoy.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>