<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneSeyd Bike ride downtown was 25!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comforted by fact I wasn't the only one today! #biketowork #cycletowork #bikeyvr https://t.co/3Hb6sWlkw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add to that overwhelmed Cap/Marine intersection and this new development. https://t.co/cR38XLzMgv No consideration… https://t.co/JniEvSwJmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just look how it's disappearing in the @NVanDistrict . Each old house demo'd sees mature trees wiped out. So much f… https://t.co/TDJ5U8tSGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cypressmtn what happened to your mobile app? Old version doesn't work and nothing on App Store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestJet how come I can't find the city I'm flying from to check in online or on app. Makes no sense!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraJMcGuire @StarbucksCanada whenever I order tea it's with 1/3 cold water!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvrairport i was in the area of gate 78. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvrairport Time to upgrade your wifi. Can't handle the volume!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christyclarkbc your current plan so far off the mark.  https://t.co/647KSoB6wB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rush hour at #scienceworld makes you think ur in the Netherlands! #cycle on! https://t.co/TER89Jz7Gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it even legal to have dog in lap while driving?  https://t.co/Eg18j68nLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A complete shame and profound lack of leadership.  https://t.co/KfrS2qYZvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fond memories of taking the kids when little and lying on a blanket up in the mountains. #PerseidMeteorShower https://t.co/0SzCLkVjgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver @ParkBoard Nice job on the trim! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no limit to how ridiculous it can get.  https://t.co/t6EIMmwZGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver @ParkBoard corner already so dangerous. Needs attention again https://t.co/IDkTIBBegG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophielui They're everywhere. Hope ur okay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree w need for dedicated lanes but, here, cyclist should have waited imo  https://t.co/OqivlKVX3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sierra_BC I think it's insane considering climate change will move production north]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 women out of 17 photos? Really? @JaneSeyd @NorthShoreNews  https://t.co/paLmZ3nILE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophielui we'd be poorer without you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A recent quip I heard. "Newspapers were a way of communicating data using dead trees" Ouch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markattisha @Annakozniuk @JKozniuk I also agree. We're all proud and grateful for her longstanding contribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markattisha @JKozniuk What's the news? No link]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkBoard Please brush. Everyone was ducking and dodging after the weight of rain. Blackberries are dangerous! @TranBC @CityofVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver Right where the coloured dot labelled 6 is. Thanks. Took eye quite a while to recover. https://t.co/RoPDPBYu0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TranBC @CityofVancouver Serious trimming needed on causeway bike path. Got hit in eye by branch just after entering Georgia eastbound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TaraJMcGuire make sure you plant some garlic this fall. Can buy seed at Pemby slow food cycle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@vancouverpd more practical to ticket drivers who threaten cyclist safety by cutting through bike lanes.  https://t.co/tfVRTxPR2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CyclingSurgeon logical but likely not practical. Interested in other potential benefits of intermittent fasting. https://t.co/CWcOQoMqR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally some rain for #Vancouver. Collective sigh of relief from plants and #gardens all around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JaneSeyd great read;my sentiments exactly. Community character lost everywhere. btw, what's with RWalton? #edgemont a wasteland 20 yrs ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic, such a spectacular setting and he's face down in his phone.  https://t.co/4U4hO3V65C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeHeartLocalBC Show us a honeybee then, not a bumblebee although they're important blueberry pollinators, too. https://t.co/KGTBOaBFoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah. #leavethephonealone https://t.co/hTIi5cSpIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Strava partners with urban planners to improve city infrastructure for cyclists and pedestrians. #CommutesCount https://t.co/FXHB5Mfy2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's progress! #leavethephonealone https://t.co/J3T6C1pyoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So stoked for my first Tuesday Night Race of the season @deepcovekayak #kayakracing #NorthVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the servers can keep up.... https://t.co/hTSUG4ImF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So close to #cycling my first #centuryride. Wish I had realized. https://t.co/iLqIdlJsfy #strava]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must-see film #themessenger  https://t.co/pwSLwjs402]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great summary of current reality. #millenials  https://t.co/aK0ej1sO66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sections of the piece would be indistinguishable from a Michael Pollan book" @michaelpollan https://t.co/sgjCmHR6PD #Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimated cats kill 3.7B birds annually. Birds bite back! https://t.co/rooVPsK0gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was struck by car on 10th in front of VGH years ago. Good location to get hit, I guess, but scary nonetheless. https://t.co/yTg7WenAGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've wondered/worried about this while commuting. https://t.co/SIdRReM7E6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelpollan I've read this before! https://t.co/VnyhhdF06T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We wondered why we lost power last night. Must have been scary for him! https://t.co/KZwmqHnZ82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime northern agricultural land will become ever more important with #climatechange https://t.co/ymOZyxo9Zk #SiteC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baffled why we're building new dams when US is tearing out. Better alternatives for next 50 yrs https://t.co/q3yr4xACrL #siteC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is creative and awesome!! #nodistracteddrivers #putdownthephone https://t.co/hhixHxFcZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinireland You should also check out https://t.co/CVOyW2Gep7 Sad times, indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Shore 2 @NVanDistrict. Mature trees on older house lots gone as redeveloped for max sq. footage. Enforcement? https://t.co/LQH07fB5oZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling even better about jumping on #FrenchsKetchup bandwagon! https://t.co/NhEYFRXKNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw last weekend. https://t.co/T2dWzkaPcV Sobering, depressing testament to environmental decline. #migratorybirds of my childhood disappear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple demonstration of the power and value of #socialmedia https://t.co/s82Uyze3vb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSpedalpushers Such a peaceful, stress-free ride to work this morning. It's kind of sad, really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoutmagazine Thanks! Been wanting to see The Messenger. Would have missed it w/o your notice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A biker's guide to street harassment. https://t.co/6Epq9nNfTV #bikeyvr #safeinthesaddle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe # of people who bag their #doggywaste then toss into bushes. Who does that? Pack it home people! https://t.co/0saInwMZLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD u guys need to spend rush hour time on Nelson @ Mainland. #redlightrunners #speeders #nomanslandforpedestrians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly and ironically #darwinian @Keri_Adams  https://t.co/IXkvNhWCgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real estate market affordable to majority of Vancouverites?  https://t.co/4b9qiBQfAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themessengerdoc @BirdStudiesCan Nothing in Vancouver. How disappointing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSpedalpushers They've already done so. Quick response!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No planning but i'm apparently endorsing #pinkshirtpromise . Good cause! We've all felt it one… https://t.co/bSlSeLYcfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One step forward from the already two back. https://t.co/9I5srxliJk #kcups #weshouldknowbetter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icbc Can't believe how many drivers on phone I dodge while I cycle to work. #dontgetthemessage #dropthephone  https://t.co/mfVYMuJS3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now there's a special day I can really get behind! #NationalMargaritaDay #tequila https://t.co/ZTMFWJGf9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSpedalpushers just b4 E-bound upper levels /penny hts exit off cap rd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder couldn't find the way @northvandistrict @NSpedalpushers Workers dumped it the bush. https://t.co/GvzDMLTgmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a seriously wet week of #cycling home from work. Looking forward to a break! https://t.co/ubUZHeCqC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa! https://t.co/oKxeK8cXSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofLdnOnt hashtags too!  Try #LondonON instead of obtuse #LdnOnt as many others in London already do. Own your brand! @lisatimo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisatimo Just saw tweet ref'g London &amp; immediately hated handle. Came up with same as you &amp; searched it finding your tweet. Great minds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisatimo @londoncomms @CityofLdnOnt Me,same reaction. No offense but poor handle imo. #wastedbrand

 https://t.co/DoLF9ALYXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[toxic pesticides again? A lot of innocent tourists have died this way. @globeandmail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for visit to @vanmarkets  #wintermarket #winterveggies https://t.co/h0lFgYDbof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kettlebrand this bag was so stale yet BBD may 19/16. Disappointed https://t.co/D8fyYPwajd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCVancouver what's with ur ÔTA broadcast? Audio constantly breaking up. Only u guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TranBC @NSpedalpushers  sure but feedback provided was for west side. Monitor should ride it at commuting speed to understand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So on point. As cyclist I battle every day #distracted drivers encroaching bike lanes. https://t.co/nTV1WMVpaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NSpedalpushers @TranBC It's a nice piece of work. Feel safe, secure and no pedestrian conflict.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TranBC @WeAreHub Eastbound side, last pullout/bend before leaving causeway. Thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great service. I'm registering my bikes! #logitorloseit  https://t.co/IZEpm8kIhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NVanDistrict Who's art in background, please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In1960s US 90% kids living within 1 mile got to school under own power. Today, 31%. Inactivity epidemic. Canada?  https://t.co/skcxD4btzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TranBC Causeway great but here #Cyclists need &gt; concrete on right to bank between #obstacles. @WeAreHub #bikeyvr https://t.co/gkX7BzEAKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaraKozan @erinireland @Sonia_Faruqi My hero @JoelSalatin figured it out for all of his animals. Is there a Canuck version? #grassfarmer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyclingSurgeon Good one. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VCHhealthcare I think it might be better said that UBC validated upon request what the BC Aboriginals had already discovered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another argument for the home-cooked meal.  https://t.co/HWDtT38ykA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust us", they said. Oops! #GMO goes wild so, in other words, no containment. https://t.co/TQzIswWZHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to read this twice. "prevalence of #diabetes in Canada is now slightly higher than in the United States." https://t.co/EqyipM4i1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I laughed out loud! https://t.co/l2b1UOXtvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityOfNorthVan I meant why in parking lot broad daylight. Fact was injured makes sense. They are common NV bird thx https://t.co/7PC8Q8Igbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityOfNorthVan Saw Whet Owl. Too cool but why there? Hunting something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posit will make we cyclists safer. No competition w #mobilephones, #makeup &amp; #breakfast Seen &amp; dodged all #bikeyvr https://t.co/fpV8UDMG3b]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>