<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at Dublin Heuston Railway Station - @irishrail in Dublin https://t.co/FKcyO4lg0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John @Romero's Irish [Galway] Adventure https://t.co/TMs1UTKoHx (@noclipvideo) cc @ei_westregion @IDAWestRegion @galwaychamber @galwaycityco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SteveColeBooks You obviously saw Trump coming in 2006 - not to mention audio recording by Stephen Tomkinson; Gran… https://t.co/LJ9aVUzhze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent stuff @patrickc and @eoghan https://t.co/EQYEKmLTSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistors come in all shapes, sizes and colors. Be a part of the resistance. #resist https://t.co/IrZT8LXdwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep calm and trust the process" w/ @BillAulet #mitedp #lasttweetfornow https://t.co/iiRPyjQ1CD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won a Tim beaver mascot for most prolific #MITEDP tweeter! Thanks @BillAulet https://t.co/W9kSJeNt3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Roberts @mitsloan tells us how entrepreneurship was fostered as a field of study at MIT. "Innovation=Invention*C… https://t.co/OXS4CbQJkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TY @BillAulet @EshipMIT/@annm_maxwell @MITSloanExecEd on a super educational/well organised #mitedp: One of the bes… https://t.co/oqgnBIi8YD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isabelle Bettez @8DTechnologies recalls some of the highlights from @MITSloan #edp2008 https://t.co/s3YHcOsmuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our last day lunchtime guest speaker is Isabelle Bettez President and CEO of @8DTechnologies #mitedp @EshipMIT… https://t.co/F5wpm3eIyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When God made time, He made a lot of it." - Irish saying quoted by my fellow Irishman @BillAulet #mitedp https://t.co/En8oMUuRKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forthcoming from @BillAulet - @edXOnline Entrepreneurship 103 and on @Amazon for pre-order the Disciplined Entrepre… https://t.co/fmwc1V68eF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a pitch: When you are asked a Q, you should emphasise with them, and close the loop (did I answer your question)? #mitedp @BillAulet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Results of public vote at #mitedp - who would you invest in (Whereaball) vs. where would you like to work (GameOn)… https://t.co/sLrWsVzEnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw this entrepreneur on the subway this morning in Boston's Downtown Crossing #mitedp https://t.co/OJ96m45FnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mitedp Panorama shot from the final day of the Entrepreneurship Development Program 2017 at MIT https://t.co/kuinm5Hq3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now up is winning team from our session, Loop, FKA Wear It Out - a wearable that gives piece of mind for people wit… https://t.co/UwSLVbwROg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First up at the #mitedp final presentation session is https://t.co/D6YFRp3LvA - tracking device in kids' shoes - us… https://t.co/pkAl3sjzTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to team Wear It Out / Loop! #mitedp @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd https://t.co/8tG6uUeFF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RajeshReddyyyyy @EshipMIT Thank you very much Rajesh #mitedp @BikeWarning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the last one is Commuti$e at #mitedp in room 345 @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd https://t.co/mOUtDpjey1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next up at #mitedp is Wear It Out - nice slides @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd https://t.co/x8Rpj3nfiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First team up in the big room is Connectivate #mitedp @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd - connecting qualified scientists w… https://t.co/iiI0rXpvRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the @tech_innovate Fellows for running a fantastic ideas and design thinking session today! https://t.co/Inthwt5VQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the final teams at #mitedp. Go team @BikeWarning ! @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd https://t.co/Jh46nYOnib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our esteemed judges announce themselves for presentations on the final day of #mitedp @EshipMIT @MITSloanExecEd https://t.co/Gq7jNsHtjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BillAulet - you weren't kidding. We got the Irish food today! #mitedp @MITSloanExecEd @EshipMIT https://t.co/RLUGGw5Zix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The #1 rule for a startup founder is don't run out of money" Jeff Fagnan @Accomplices #mitedp - yes! https://t.co/wi3wQ5t5E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Revenue is not a leading indicator, it's a lagging indicator" @Accomplices #missiondriven #superpower #marketdislocation #deeptech #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm on board of 17 companies, 5 with &gt;$100M recurring revenues, too many for a VC, but glad to be involved, enjoy it" #mitedp @Accomplices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few they missed... Still, everyone can learn from mistakes for the next time around! #mitedp https://t.co/voM4OSfK1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... I remember going to an Odeo launch party in SF, 2005 ... @Accomplices #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failing and entrepreneurship, they go hand in hand. Learn from mistakes, apply that next time around" Jeff Fagnan #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AngelList, DraftKings, InsightSquared, Freebird, Vesper are some of the case studies being presented by VC Jeff Fag… https://t.co/fpCpnr7k96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It takes 8 years to build an overnight success." Jeff Fagnan @Accomplices #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Fagnan/@Accomplices: founding investor, 22 companies each north of $250M, 5 companies at S1 IPO #mitedp -&gt; 100 investments last 3 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A quick no is the second best answer any entrepreneur can have." Jeff Fagnan @Accomplices #mitedp https://t.co/lmgkipDD4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @BillAulet! #keepcalm #trusttheprocess #mitedp https://t.co/FtW0CYITg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@billaulet "How the Irish Saved Civilization" #mitedp (with apologies for the bland food and Michael Flatley) https://t.co/pEWRY3l5iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another recommended book by @BillAulet is "Venture Deals" by @bfeld #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice interview @joehas! Learning lots here at #mitedp... Must catch-up for a call soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rate my VC #mitedp https://t.co/DqqXngkMaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point by @JudeCook @ShareIn. Is there less difference between crowdfunding and angel investment in 2017 as com… https://t.co/3ghtX5pSQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of finance department and professor at @MITSloan is now up at #mitedp https://t.co/m0slPoHMQN @aschoar https://t.co/xQPM4RMKh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hockey stick on @BillAulet screen for our Canadian delegation - translates to shinty stick for the Scottish… https://t.co/qJxdwFMhnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book recommendation from @BillAulet for #mitedp class - The Power of Habit by Charles Duhigg https://t.co/JZNmHZ1mn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's sad but this Lego wall in @cicnow this morning made me very happy #mitedp #findireland https://t.co/V0J4grGDWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's LTV and COCA time with @BillAulet #mitedp https://t.co/Arun7TnW8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AirCIC - airbnb-like service for @CICnow companies who want to rent them out - current experiment! #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a good community member, make good use of spaces, encourage people to use private/public space most appropriate for them #mitedp @cicnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@cicnow: You pay for min people associated with office plus per person fee. Encourages density within space. Invigorates community. #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Places that have a bustling innovation community aren't a target - picking places that are nearly there. Rotterdam has a @cicnow hub #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[200 staff altogether in @cicnow - 90 in Cambridge, with people in other centres in Boston, St Louis, Miami, ...… https://t.co/ejh1kVKNXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very highly staffed model in @cicnow - means knowing clients personally, relationship managers: 900 companies and 9… https://t.co/3p6AkkCu9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @cicnow Cambridge Innovation Center for a tour as part of #mitedp - getting ideas for the @portershed too https://t.co/OIQClcS8P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope that my #mitedp tweets are much better than deciphering someone's scrawled lecture notes @EshipMIT… https://t.co/uFb44OE5y2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found the 360 degree camera we need for our @bikewarning project at #MITEDP https://t.co/36K5Hw1Mn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are having a mini Robbie Burns night at the #mitedp main dinner - Graham recites @grahamfaeforres https://t.co/UnhObkJkMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add value before extracting value. Spend money on free content. Don't ask every qn on your form before you let peop… https://t.co/E7DaoyINV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Dublin: "Why would we have gone anywhere else? Our R&amp;D office is phenomenal. We do real feature work there."… https://t.co/0dgEcDtydP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Godin quoted by @markitecht - "Turn strangers into friends, friends into customers, customers into salespeople" #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hubspot's SaaS product is updated 300 times a day - no wonder Gerard Butler is freaking out! @markitecht #mitedp https://t.co/hXONl4W4pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Inbound is matching the way you market and sell to the way people shop and buy" -- Chris O'Donnell @markitecht… https://t.co/IAI3k3GSGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone in big company who does not understand core customer is unlikely to know how to create/capture value for them." @sstern_mit #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["24 steps/entrepreneurial strategy are great for this [corporate intrapreneurship]." @sstern_mit #mitedp @24StepsofEship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Should companies break out of their crazy bureaucracies? Yes. Motivate employees on creation and capture of value." @sstern_mit #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Big company has resources, capabilities: can pursue multiple paths, all at same time. Don't face startup constraints." @sstern_mit #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Entrepreneurs have been extremely poorly served by adapting big company strategies to startups." @sstern_mit #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would like my workforce to have an entrepreneurial mindset. Called diff things. Intrapreneurship. Internal venture." @sstern_mit #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day an employee shows up, and the only reason they are there is a contract, is a wasted day @sstern_mit… https://t.co/lAZK26Wn3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Stern's favourite slide - you can't have both the human and the horse as customers @sstern_mit #mitedp https://t.co/lhg1JSxD2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Stern, who teaches Entrepreneurial Strategy at MIT, is taking us through the topic now at #edp2017 lunchtime… https://t.co/We31EcRbAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland Export Treemap by Product 2014 from Harvard Atlas of Economic Complexity https://t.co/VRQhvX4IKn cc… https://t.co/1w36WswuLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor old startups have a very high rate of interest in the first year(s)... @ce_tucker #mitedp https://t.co/NvTYA26Kso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ce_tucker Is the average lifetime of a customer in your gaming example about 2-and-a-half months then? #mitedp https://t.co/sU9k6tQjNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! Got the same answer as @ce_tucker... #mitedp https://t.co/7gqby3k7Sj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LTV is a prediction of the net profit attributed to the entire future relationship with a customer @ce_tucker… https://t.co/uaqiSg7DYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Company: 'Let's let everyone have a 4% discount off everything'. Don't do this, focus discounts" @ce_tucker #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stunt_penguin LOL! You do know I have access to all the CCTV in the building right? .......................................................]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The compromise effect @ce_tucker #mitedp https://t.co/HOnZLSdLKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some reason, according to @ce_tucker, engineers love taxi meter effect-based pricing #mitedp @EshipMIT… https://t.co/TtYWLp1Xki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the most innovative companies fail because they can't be innovative around price @ce_tucker #mitedp… https://t.co/0FEDUkzcuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at MIT Jack C. Tang Center for Management Education (Building E51) in Cambridge, MA https://t.co/r5WlaPriT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stunt_penguin Well spotted! That was a deliberate error of course... *cough*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Origin of the name for MIT Delta V is ΔV/t = A (acceleration) #mitedp #accelerator https://t.co/3bnLkck25p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Time EIRs at @EshipMIT will have been involved in startups that have scaled up *very* significantly @MITTommy… https://t.co/QxDtSbLHqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honest Broker Policy at @EshipMIT @MITTommy Plus: Program Pillars =&gt; Head: Knol, Hands: Capability, Heart: Mindset,… https://t.co/2Js5bLDpCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a great overview of the Martin Trust Center for @EshipMIT #mitedp Serving all MIT students across all school… https://t.co/UQH2dmOxub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More nuggets from #mitedp "Never have meetings in a startup with more than five people" ... "I want customer IP; gi… https://t.co/lOENUv1y2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maria_yianni @EshipMIT I think they are @BillAulet's "Go Fetch" socks #mitedp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When new tech comes along, successful companies build from the ground up as opposed to retrofitting an existing sy… https://t.co/UVgvPzNPl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Interesting is worst four letter word you can be told. Nothing actionable. I still recoil when someone says it."… https://t.co/Nboo0ZY0mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Myth: X was in the shower, they had an idea, and it led to a multibillion dollar company. That has NEVER, ever hap… https://t.co/eXNplNVEhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who was Richard Cantillon? The Irish originator of the term entrepreneur! @BillAulet @annm_maxwell #mitedp @EshipMIT https://t.co/a1j80GhHWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why large firms can experiment more compared to startups - as a result they can be more intrapreneurial (with CEO b… https://t.co/6lAcvsQfoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Big data is not enough. It is hard to separate causation from correlation. More data you have, harder it is to gue… https://t.co/NwUCqil0kC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You'd be surprised how many Kickstarter projects are being run by Fortune 500 companies, not under their own names… https://t.co/dudZbf2QMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mitedp [disciplined entrepreneurship] "process is what makes you avoid the Segway story, which is natural tendency… https://t.co/xy6E9Lx271]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lean: lots of experiments, see what happens. But don't sequence properly, you run out of resources. Need experimen… https://t.co/sBgD83I8Qx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>