<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinThornber @Jeffugee   Sigh.  People who use phrase "Ponzi scheme" on Twitter generally have no idea what it means. As here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRentoul @Richard_Carr How does Chaplin's idealism make its history "dodgy"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impact of Angela Merkel's refugee policy on crime and unemployment https://t.co/fO7QKKJgeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For ‘speaking truth to power’ to have any effect, power has to be interested in listening". Richard Mottram: https://t.co/rxsZmsPS4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays @Guy_Stallard Wasn't disagreeing with you but with Cooper framing of debate (which she knows perfectly well is wrong)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays @Guy_Stallard Yes. Not criticising you; but my "weary tone" reflects irritation at Cooper remarks - rehash old, incorrect points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays @Guy_Stallard in particular, as blog says, we know a lot more about migration impacts than when (this round of) debate started!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays @Guy_Stallard Not objecting to sensible fact-based debate. Claim we've not been debating this for years is absurd, as you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays Agree. But on basis of facts not (mis)perceptions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulStocker5 Not sure what you're referring to - but most recent data is Annual Population Survey - on NOMIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A(nother) debate on immigration: how about starting with the facts? New blog: https://t.co/VYoWHYN7hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulietMEvans Indeed. I make this precisely this point in the section on public service impacts. https://t.co/RbPDupLHgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxelltrotter They're not all totally clueless you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbeetroot "including also by calling in @jk_rowling to curse Barnier &amp; Tusk" was dropped at late stage of drafting..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billwells_1 @IlvesOtto ??? That's the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8inkcartridges "including by legislation as necessary to mitigate the effects of failing to reach a deal." ie "we'll think of something"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit paper para 12.3 suggests govt recognises risks of "train crash Brexit" - but has no idea yet what to do abou… https://t.co/wmnfFHOk84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit White Paper: "In any eventuality we will ensure that our economic &amp; other functions can continue."  Reassuring...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwest @IanDunt @NickCohen4 @fatwheezybloke  (not saying not an issue - complex &amp; difficult. But facile generalisations get us nowhere) I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwest @IanDunt @NickCohen4 @fatwheezybloke  (Seriously Ed, we both know theres no strong empirical support for this in UK. Why deny it?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwest @IanDunt @NickCohen4 @fatwheezybloke Not really in UK as you know. (See also Shaggar and Somerville)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwest @IanDunt @NickCohen4 @fatwheezybloke Is there a reason you're ignoring actual *UK* evidence ? :-) https://t.co/OiI1pfymph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwest @IanDunt @NickCohen4  Ed is surely aware that empirical papers with UK data give very different results to US literature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Government groping in the dark... while Opposition is in disarray". @Usherwood on why we're still all at sea despi… https://t.co/82J3lmkihZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkGregoryEY thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdportes @mjturner1975 @StrongerInNos Figure 4 here https://t.co/Qq9YzBH8DD shows a version of this (x-country)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjturner1975 @StrongerInNos Yes, Or pop  growth and GDP pc growth. Which is exactly what the IMF research does. (as multiple regression)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrongerInNos [try comparing your chart to a simple chart of population growth!!]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrongerInNos [sorry, first term minus second term. Cancels except for 2nd order (negligiblle) terms]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrongerInNos Wrong.  You are charting [GDP (t)/GDP (t-1)- 1]  divided by [GDP (t)/p(t) /GDP(t-1)/p(t-1)- 1]. Do the math. GDP cancels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdportes @StrongerInNos @notayesmansecon ie, despite your labelling, there is literally *no* information/data on GDP in this chart..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrongerInNos ?? As a matter of arithmetic that's just population growth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erskineandrew Nothing quant I think because we lack good data on self-employed (a problem for lab market econ generally not just migration)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impact of immigration to UK. My evidence to @CommonsHomeAffs summarises the evidence from my &amp; others' research:  https://t.co/TFq7BQlbzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_bunker @dynarski @JustinWolfers @JayCShambaugh 4 pages surely too long.. 1 tweet. Economy is growing bigly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK negotiation objectives: I will be testifying to the @CommonsEUexit at 9.15am.  https://t.co/fRIwMgaFiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriciaQuinte9 Maybe try this? or is it too hard to use google? https://t.co/TDxBgKzQWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billwells_1 @CommonsEUexit that's non EU not total]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billwells_1 @CommonsEUexit What is actual quantitative evidence durations are increasing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chakrabortty ??? This can't possibly be true, right?? https://t.co/NzfeIaV63F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_lilico @DanielJHannan True - diminishing returns to establishing what we &amp; our followers already know. But historical record etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_lilico How many examples of @DanielJHannan mendacity do you want? I've got all day.. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems @andrew_lilico has an alternative definition of "impeccable". See, eg, https://t.co/b9StHta71j https://t.co/OdhaSKvex6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanJakobB @StevePeers &amp; 3 of downloads are from me! [but NB you can view in browser without downloading]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testifying tomorrow to @CommonsEUexit on EU nationals here &amp; UK nationals elsewhere in EU: https://t.co/qTIPT14m34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BharatWarrior @TherealNihal @UKIPCANDA You do attract some pathetically inadequate lonely men, Nihal. I'd be worried....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewEdgar_CB @ChrisGiles_ Try reading the paper. It's in English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Diatom1000 @DanielJHannan Ah, now you're just tweeting meaningless nonsense.  Try English next time. Muted. Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Diatom1000 I make statements that are factually correct &amp; evidence-based. You &amp; @DanielJHannan make things up. See the difference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @cjsnowdon @K_Niemietz Complex issue. Plenty of scope for debate/interpretation.  @DanielJHannan contribution is #fakenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @cjsnowdon @K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan Note also claims about relative vs absolute wrong over any time framd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @cjsnowdon @K_Niemietz I am *not* claiming poverty getting worse. Just that @DanielJHannan is making up his facts again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @cjsnowdon @K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan Yes. Uptick bigger for children, which is Blair/Brown target.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan  Latest figures show increase in relative poverty for both population as a whole and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCShipley @K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan  The ones about UK trends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Niemietz Fake news?  Child poverty rises by 200,000 on previous year, official figures show https://t.co/RE1mpOY8RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan And claim "this definition is now showing steepest fall' also nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Niemietz @DanielJHannan Latest UK data shows a rise in relative poverty. Not a fall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fuzzfoster  Yes, that's precisely the #fakenews strategy at which @DanielJHannan is expert. Important to challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatwheezybloke @DanielJHannan It makes statements (not matters of "opinion") which are demonstrably false. How is that "reasonable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lefties" love #fakenews says @DanielJHannan, cleverly inserting two entirely false statements about UK poverty tre… https://t.co/jCv2iNSQzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Niemietz I assume you notice  @DanielJHannan cleverly inserted two completely false statements about poverty trends. Satire lives!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanbeattie Given my legendary tact &amp; patience, I'm an obvious choice, but the phone has unaccountably failed to ring..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanbeattie I thought your view was that they could sit around drinking tea for two years?  Not bad for £160K+  ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VeraTensTXL Read the paper, which has actual data &amp; evidence, before you "disagree".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_lifto_g @TherealNihal ?? See you've given up - that's entirely irrelevant to  @TRobinsonNewEra's anti-semitism, as you know. Muted. Bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RPShah_econ  Don't bother. @UKIPCANDA isn't into "objective proof" (or facts, evidence or data) - he's made that quite clear to me before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_lifto_g @TherealNihal See you're proving the point on literacy, &amp; @TRobinsonNewEra has made his hatred of Jews quite clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_lifto_g @TherealNihal Illiterate neo-Nazis stick together, I see.  Sure @TRobinsonNewEra welcomes the support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TherealNihal Expecting followers of noted racist @TRobinsonNewEra to be anything other than, er, racist is a bit optimistic..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dnancy1 @TRobinsonNewEra @HoCpetitions Alive, but evidently no more sentient than ever..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danbarker @GeoffreyB thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impact of refugee influx to Germany on crime (very small, petty crime only), lab markets (none) &amp; support for anti-… https://t.co/cmdp3J69WM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, racist neo-Nazi sympathiser @TRobinsonNewEra is illiterate.. https://t.co/wNIhqQPdyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chakrabortty what's the score now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hadrians_Head @NickCohen4 the point is that  @DanielJHannan 's claim is entirely false. In a column about fake news! Beyond parody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffreyB @danbarker Closest is Munz and Werding , Journal Pension Economics 2005 for 4 countries. Some OECD work relevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juanincognito You'd think @DanielJHannan would lose power to shock. But even in an article about "fake news" he gets simple facts wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Left loves fake news" writes @DanielJHannan  https://t.co/uAAwpmD2R8! This statement is fake news (ie, it's si… https://t.co/akgoQoelZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dlknowles Indeed. Not really an excuse. I read it last night and tweeted within minutes that it didn't make sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dlknowles Yes. This contradiction was obvious last night. Yet UK press reported it (mostly) uncritically.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even the possibility that we might be forced back to WTO rules would destroy value" (in UK financial services) says Andrew Tyrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is complete nonsense to suggest that the detail needs to be closeted in secrecy" says Andrew Tyrie - will be writing to Carney, Hammond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticking to commitment to reduce migration to tens of thousands will carry economic cost says Andrew Tyrie @UKandEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To suppose we can replace all this [EU access] with Antipodean trade deals is moonshine" says Andrew Tyrie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key test for Brexit is whether it preserves close to current levels of access to EU market says Andrew Tyrie to @UKandEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reversion to WTO rules immediately after Article 50 conclusion in 2019 would be "train crash Brexit" says Andrew Tyrie to @UKandEU  event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would a successful Brexit look like? 4 economic tests. Me &amp; @anandMenon1 in @guardianopinion https://t.co/xZgCyw0Bwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirHusband Yes.  It was explicitly designed as a "Muslim ban".  @andrew_lilico is being laughably, dangerously naive here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I said - Government statement about Johnson "deal" doesn't reflect either what Order says or what's happening:   https://t.co/7sBLDSL6RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueEgAl @defunked Not surprised to see @AdamPerkinsPhD attracting  antisemites &amp; racists like @defunked &amp; you to my timeline. Muted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching our @UKandEU  "Four Economic tests for Brexit" report today with Andrew Tyrie MP 12pm at @KingsCollegeLon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politicalhackuk @WoodClaudia Yes. On face of it FCO statement is flat out wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulFScott @nytimes .. Which given there are no flights to US from most (all?) of those countries would make no sense..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakubKrupa @SMerlChest @peter_daly @SamCoatesTimes my guess FWIW is even consummate professionals in FCO are clueless &amp; making mistakes..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SMerlChest Yes. This *directly* contradicts UK gov statement.  @JakubKrupa @SamCoatesTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulFScott it says "regardless of nationality". On face of it, directly contradicts EO (and common sense).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt claims  US travel ban doesn't apply to *anyone* flying to US from UK. Anyone believe this? Has US confirmed it… https://t.co/8gpHmKQaX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamCoatesTimes @JakubKrupa @SMerlChest Have you read actual text of EO?  Not consistent with UK statement.  Confusion (at best..)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PickardJE [in particular, bullet point 2 of the UK statement is completely inconsistent, esp given @yarotrof point]]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>