<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How You Can Push Back on the Trump Administration - Moms Clean Air Force https://t.co/EGkkvkA4uD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals On the Edge of a Nervous Breakdown - POLITICO Magazine https://t.co/2iIVzGJr7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of Fake News, Op-Eds, Satire and Journalistic Errors | The Huffington Post https://t.co/TxunZVBxkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Ways to Take on Trump | New Republic https://t.co/13LBgWU62K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The growing case against Scott Pruitt's nomination to lead EPA - The Hill https://t.co/cWLrDxmbJW via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Battery Revolution Just Reached Critical Mass - Bloomberg https://t.co/uvZJ335d2n via @nuzzel thanks @kevcirilli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | President Trump, stop implying that Americans on welfare aren't working - Washington Post https://t.co/2r2DwmaiWI via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Canceling Tesla Orders Because Elon Musk Is Advising Trump - BuzzFeed https://t.co/bBe041Sd85 via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile advertising drives strong Facebook quarter - USA TODAY https://t.co/GFDh8kupBz via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Syrian Doctor with a Visa Is Suing the Trump Administration - The New Yorker https://t.co/nFhu9EIpPR via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is 'fake news' a fake problem? - Columbia Journalism Review https://t.co/0OtiFu49a1 via @nuzzel thanks @mikeyavo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eichenwald: Neil Gorsuch is supremely qualified, and must not be confirmed - Newsweek https://t.co/6NpCmRVTAO via  @mjfrombuffalo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge in L.A. orders a temporary halt to Trump's travel ban - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/ooWGTxQ2bv via @nuzzel thanks @gfriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Post: Mis-readings | Civicist https://t.co/t76b07N9qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Science Panel to Hold Hearing on "Making the EPA Great Again" - Scientific American https://t.co/eFsyimBWC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nestle to move U.S. headquarters to Arlington, bringing 750 jobs to the region - The Washington Post https://t.co/7WmU0exRuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TRUE &gt; Did Neil Gorsuch Quote Henry Kissinger in His Yearbook Entry? : https://t.co/zbGCcmSxg6 https://t.co/szcPrL2e3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angela Merkel is now the leader of the free world, not Donald Trump | The Independent https://t.co/6NhqctBRxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot possibly confirm Judge Gorsuch before the election - The Washington Post https://t.co/6klzvor208]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarnerVA As a VA resident and long-time supporter, you must filibuster the SCOTUS nominee #StolenSeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner As a VA resident and long-time supporter, you must filibuster the SCOTUS nominee #StolenSeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenKaineOffice As a VA resident and long-time supporter, you must filibuster the SCOTUS nominee #StolenSeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine As a VA resident and long-time supporter, you must filibuster the SCOTUS nominee #StolenSeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheldonforRI @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a RI resident (Block Island) I ask you to vote no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWhitehouse @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a RI resident (Block Island) I ask you to vote no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJackReed  @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a RI resident (Block Island) I ask you to vote no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenKaineOffice  @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a VA voter (22046) vote NO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine  @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a VA voter (22046) vote NO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarnerVA  @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a VA voter (22046) vote NO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner @AGScottPruitt is not qualified to be @EPA administrator.  As a VA voter (22046) vote NO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenShelby  We need an @EPA Administrator who puts people over polluters. That person is not #PollutingPruitt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Messy people are happier than neat freaks—and more productive too — Quartz https://t.co/Pe5gJvM7WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Committee Advances Price and Mnuchin Confirmations With No Democrats Present https://t.co/YcwSZH2rIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[altMBA update via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - After more than a year, I ... https://t.co/2pkLWe5RDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Hamilton (Original Broadway Cast Recording) by Various Artists ♫ https://t.co/DpGDi9IruU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“President Trump Is Winning” @slaby https://t.co/XY0hMMeNPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A majority of one walks away from his keyboard - POLITICO https://t.co/5Cgle0Fbsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#sotus was Obama's #StolenSeat @TheDemocrats must block #MaximumHardball cc @SenSchumer @POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But when will you abandon it? via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - Not if, but ... https://t.co/AEfPk6tXXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Budweiser 2017 Super Bowl Commercial | “Born The Hard Way”" on YouTube https://t.co/6LvF2AmXAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I have to hand over bank and social media details at the US border? – Naked Security https://t.co/clPSOgex4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happening NOW! @LCVoters Flash mob at @SenJohnBarrasso’s office to stop #PollutingPruitt from taking over the EPA #RejectPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NRA Has Been Moonlighting as an Anti-Immigration Group for Years https://t.co/jFs4tHzUa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @SUPGVNetwork's Tweet: https://t.co/9oyCr9mu6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos's Nomination for Education Secretary Clears Committee - New York Times https://t.co/AG1VLU3eKk via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to keep your secret activist Twitter account a secret - Boing Boing https://t.co/tDAl8zhwF3 by @doctorow via @nuzzel thanks @normative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NRA set to go on offense | TheHill https://t.co/eJLSq7P4q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Facebook Instant Articles a flop for publishers? | ClickZ https://t.co/etTlFo4mPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed it by that much via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - I got to the gate ... https://t.co/3tKDhX7gel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time for the Democrats to wage all-out war against Trump? - Mother Jones https://t.co/MAIVjZAFwo by @DavidCornDC via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quinnipiac University poll: Almost half of American voters support Trump's immigration order https://t.co/7b7wd9wT9e via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From order to disorder: How Trump's immigration directive exposed GOP rifts - Washington Post https://t.co/mzWX5otPc7 via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#deleteUber is NOT #Resistance 

It is stupidity 

#justsaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the chaos caused by the people &gt; the chaos caused by by @realDonaldTrump ? Fuck yeah!   #MondayNightMassacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people deleting Uber? A Trump backlash the company didn’t deserve — #deleteUber Quartz https://t.co/lCzliq1sVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angry Republicans lash out at Trump for not consulting them on travel ban - The Washington Post https://t.co/mvELhg1kI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Simple Ways to Resist Like a Mom - Moms Clean Air Force https://t.co/FBoHmiNnEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This chart shows the top 10 origin countries for refugees adimtted to the United States in 2016. https://t.co/WcKm4a61ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Dems will filibuster Trump’s Supreme Court nominee - POLITICO https://t.co/SeouObOEcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ACLU's Huge Weekend Donations Haul Shows Twitter Activism Can Work - WIRED https://t.co/Px7JNj4zQf via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What has the U.S. government learned from Fred Korematsu? Nothing. - ThinkProgress https://t.co/G9NN8qqjA9  thanks @timothywjohnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartland voters shrug off global outcry over immigration travel ban - CNBC https://t.co/0uDhRxCowH via @nuzzel thanks @mmurraypolitics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team won't back down - Axios https://t.co/J7P87eeHMG via @nuzzel thanks @JGreenDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where your elected officials stand on Trump's immigration order and Cabinet picks - Washington Post https://t.co/2D4nxVdVY5 via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists Baffled by McConnell and Ryan's Ability to Stand Upright Without Spines -  https://t.co/iXyNE7UpJN by @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters Grill Democratic Senator About His Vote for Trump's CIA Chief - The Intercept https://t.co/g1RjE6q6rJ via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advocates Urge Delay of Sessions Vote to Examine His Role with President's Executive Orders and Proposals https://t.co/VpoyB51IBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs executive order requiring that for every one new regulation, two must be revoked - POLITICO https://t.co/Qdp3xaix37 via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a top conservative radio talker lost his audience and faith but gained a new perspective https://t.co/nwSUu4i12o via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brushing up your mobile &amp; digital skillset with online learning (aka the MOOC) | ClickZ https://t.co/qv3g8ga4Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Troublemaker Behind Donald Trump’s Words - The Daily Beast https://t.co/fC3ZlTER9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Rules for a constitutional crisis” “Rules for a constitutional crisis” @lessig https://t.co/RIN8MRwzxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYTimes: No, Trump, Not on Our Watch #fuckingwall #muslimban https://t.co/WR6uuQCusw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make believe problems via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - We focus on them ... https://t.co/rc96avmj9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage over Trump's immigrant ban helps ACLU raise more money online in one day than in all of 2016 https://t.co/2bpfrN2sAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dc protests #muslimban #MuslimRegistry #blm #alllivesmatter? https://t.co/gDVhzAlZd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A $20,000 Match Offer On ACLU Donations Today – AVC https://t.co/OCX6fUgSBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just donated to 'A Safety Net to Keep Pets in Their Homes'. Give $1. Change a lot. https://t.co/VBwZ6bYJUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friction and traction via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - It's fashionable ... https://t.co/3zP6PlPIwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying We Shall Overcome - Live by Pete Seeger ♫ https://t.co/a2cYNWrXAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying This Land Is Your Land - Live by Pete Seeger ♫ https://t.co/ocubJ0RSAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philadelphia Inquirer's editorial board goes there: Trump's first days resemble those of a dictator https://t.co/Mf253yxuRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a Dem backbone?  Anyone?  Anywhere?  Someone?  Somebody?  #DNCforum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Recalls Staff to U.S. After Trump Immigration Order - Bloomberg https://t.co/Z7uH4jLxDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Politics of Cowardice - The New York Times https://t.co/761kYXox1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Navigating Climate Change in America's Heartland - New York Times https://t.co/yKvleR7ouB via @nuzzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['How Do I Get Back Home?' Iranians Turned Away From Flights to U.S. - New York Times https://t.co/q0AUyG2P9f via @nuzzel thanks @iSheyman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little National Security Benefit to Trump's Executive Order on Immigration https://t.co/fS2oBITBsw via @nuzzel thanks @CahnEmily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Visa Ban Also Applies to Citizens With Dual Nationality, State Department Says - Wall Street Journal https://t.co/qDCCyHmmMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran to ban US citizens in response to Trump's order - CNN https://t.co/URqtfjrM47 via @nuzzel thanks @iSheyman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Muslim ban excludes countries linked to his businesses - NY Daily News https://t.co/s0y1cIVNI6 via @nuzzel thanks @UKProgressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitol Hill mom directs thousands of anti-Trump activists with texts sent from her living room  https://t.co/zMw65sHvhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans and Cybersecurity | Pew Research Center https://t.co/U87aPj3sbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats have the power to stop Trump. All they have to do is use it. - The Washington Post https://t.co/twYPBFrqzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Groups to Trump: Here’s How You Can ‘Send in the Feds,’ and Actually Make a Dent in Urban Crime https://t.co/it5ZVgpVXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the right amount of data via Seth Godin's Blog on marketing, tribes and respect - The digital ... https://t.co/6fzG9aqtTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Key Elements For A Big Analytics Driven Business Impact https://t.co/HFijnW7vOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to use cleaner, better energy? Get up to $25 free when you sign up with @ArcadiaPower https://t.co/Zcu9MRI1LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch "Democrats won the most votes. Why aren’t they acting like it?" on YouTube https://t.co/k8jhNjZozJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top download from any federal site right now is Park Service report on climate change - Washington Post https://t.co/IXM1sKp275]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>