<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Xi takes the global stage (at Davos, but elsewhere too) as others vacate it through their actions  https://t.co/qLdvzjYcXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a Week, Trump Reshapes Decades of Perceptions About America, via @nytimes https://t.co/tY8bc8edYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chicken dances: Chinese New Year around the world via @TheEconomist  https://t.co/TjeVz5XZfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China stakes a claim for globalism without liberalism https://t.co/Wl2CO0byAj via @FT@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the annals of Presidential history it will be said that George Washington never told a lie &amp; Donald Trump never told the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The anti China, anti trade economist at the heart of the Trump administration via @theeconomist  https://t.co/iT9A0sxJFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to have a chapter in this fine volume https://t.co/aYw4cpiqLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to my PANZ colleague and Vice President @thkukutai on her appointment as Prof of Demography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrBob317 makes you glad your Scottish Bob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcapie not today - it's a great one to be inside and working, not so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great privilege to have Kiwibank Local Hero Shona Murray as a role model and teacher &amp; as my aunt and friend  https://t.co/gBU99a5Mlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really outstanding i/v with Prof Sir Richard Faull on @radionz this morning. Loved his reflections on collaboration &amp; leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @asianewzealand Chairman John Luxton on being awarded CNZM for services to dairy industry in New Year's Honours 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hard task of measuring how many very old people there are in the UK. It turns out people lie about their age... https://t.co/P0FZk1e5Eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving listening to @DianaKrall excellent album Wallflower this Boxing Day evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 21st century Cambridge Spies or just professional jealousy?  https://t.co/9xjiz7GjhJ via @FT #Russia #Intelligence #Cambridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzinitiative great work from a great think tank!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to have appointed Allen Tie as National Director of International Student Ministries of NZ https://t.co/HuOE0RLGJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lengthy but thoughtful lecture from my favorite satirist Ian Hislop #privateeye #hignfy #orwell  https://t.co/ZhWqn2ViE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very impressive and capable young New Zealander, who I had the pleasure of working with in Track 2 diplomacy, thr… https://t.co/3i6imGUr3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s collision course with China https://t.co/VEC4nuD12k via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The decline and fall of the BA; or a transformation of what it is &amp; how it's taught?  https://t.co/mobHk19YdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year of the demagogue: how 2016 changed democracy https://t.co/ZzkOVBp5FL via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to have chapter abt Irish, Samoan &amp; Korean migrants to NZ &amp; their interactions w/ Christian church in this book https://t.co/aYw4cpiqLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT Person of the Year Donald Trump https://t.co/ENAvEDDyg3 via @FT &amp; with Time's endorsement too next thing you know he'll be President...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea poses a clear and present danger https://t.co/gP2rwQEK8p via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English will be NZ's third Catholic PM after Savage and Bolger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting questions &amp; thoughtful answers on English's active and formative Catholicism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A damming - and excellent - editorial by @DomPost on the Rebstock inquiry into MFAT https://t.co/XGZsfbOJik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build that wallaby: Australia and Trump via @TheEconomist @LowyInstitute  https://t.co/gbcoygtrYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter diplomacy: upending the old order, one tweet at a time https://t.co/azCmjIiCNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials warned NZ govt that foreign students were lowering skills of immigrants https://t.co/qVPuc0sS7w https://t.co/CJsJ5xv7IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great piece on new New Zealanders in Mt Roskill by @JohnJCampbell on @radionz superb thoughtful journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Christchurch and Dunedin longitudinal studies are national treasures says Kibblewhite #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacPherson: the strength of the debate is fostered by diversity  #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kibblewhite: even economists are emotional beings. #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MacPherson: the fundamental role of policy is to reinforce or to change behaviour  #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kibblewhite: investment approach one of the most exciting things happening in public policy anywhere in the world #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kibblewhite: building knowledge base is essential for now and the future #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kibblewhite: data won't tell us what to do no matter how much we have. We need to turn it into policy advice. #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kibblewhite: new policy acronym EIEIO #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No self interest here then ... https://t.co/Q4U8Oy5Ka0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average no. of authors in social science &amp; economics papers has doubled in last 10 yrs notes Julia Lane #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trip down memory lane as Julia Lane recalls LEED at @StatisticsNZ #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great question about how we can explain limitations of big data (normally found on back of piece of paper) #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof Julia Lane from NYU admits, excitedly, that she is geeking out talking about big data #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Lane (an economist) from NYU cautions engineers and computer scientists against over/under counting data #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong emphasis on 'what can we learn? rather than 'what do we know?' in Nina Terrey's presentation #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nina Terry bringing a strong social science and qualitative design lens to influencing policy and behaviour  #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to talk by World Bank lead economist reminds us we often learn more from our failures than our successes #GEN2016conf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Policy makers often overestimate how useful &amp; imp their programs are (David McKenzie, World Bank) #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great presentation by Struan Little on success of behavioural insights in Inland Revenue understanding its customers #GEN2016CONF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Unimatrix_0 Twitter asked me if I wanted to translate your tweet from Dutch. Hmmm...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you were still a pollster @Unimatrix_0 ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was on the TV was moving but the TV wasn't even on.., #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to hear of the death of actor who played Manuel in Fawlty Towers. I had a boss who replied 'Que?' to any question asked. Truly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi @RevHelenJacobi @StMatthewsNZ @auckanglican an auspicious day to mark it on! Congratulations and blessings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will Trump mean for South East Asia? - BBC News @asianewzealand  https://t.co/qGKUKF1jD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Settlement to Super-diversity: The Anglican Church and NZ's Diversifying Population Journal of Anglican Studies https://t.co/aHJNpDzXSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to spend time in fellowshjp &amp; encouragement w board &amp; senior staff of @tscf_nz &amp; CEO of Scripture Union. Imp partnerships for ISMNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: China’s chance? Economic leadership https://t.co/HqkUBPxUot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving to my American friends, family &amp; colleagues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MFATgovtNZ @NZinVietnam first there was Kennan's long telegram, now there is Manning's short song. Diplomacy history in the making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Will Trump Trade Policy Actually Look Like? Three Possibilities, via @nytimes https://t.co/22U8VsipH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Asia thinks about Trump's TPP reaction https://t.co/z3ryWlHzIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was 5 yrs ago that @asianewzealand had 1 of its first Track 2 dialogues in Beijing &amp; with my successor… https://t.co/iCpuvaZeVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All good thoughts and best wishes to my colleagues @StatisticsNZ in Wgtn. I've been in that building 100s of times &amp; sorry to see its damage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently reading an article in @TheEconomist titled "shaken and stirred". Very apt even if it is actually about espionage #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there I was thinking it had been a while since a shake in Wellington... #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new iPad app for @TheEconomist is superb: clean , modern and readable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thoughtful &amp; insightful i/v with Gavin Ellis on understanding US election &amp; the role of media on @ninetonoon #USElection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Lady Liberty  https://t.co/PUf30sROC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two simultaneous quakes of 4,7 are enough to wake me up. Great rolling coverage (as it were) on @NZStuff #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Economist | The Chinese in Britain: Raise the red lantern
https://t.co/RkZK8KV15B via @TheEconomist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best line on @radionz today: Kim Hill, having been informed of the storm due after the earthquakes, asked "when are the locusts coming?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand earthquake: Tsunami follows powerful tremor https://t.co/O0bDNLFH66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb coverage by @radionz during the night. Professional, calm &amp; informative. A great asset #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With his keen eye, prayerful heart &amp; global scope Paul Windsor laments for America (written before Election Night) https://t.co/fCfY7js3pC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the dangers of America first https://t.co/nzWuhcWijv via @FT@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: Quote of the day https://t.co/URF3y60BuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elinanoor and look to the Philippines too, electing Duterte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might Chinese Trade Explain Trump’s Success? https://t.co/ZR6Sbj8V2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trending emojis tell the story of upset Clinton supporters https://t.co/jA8oMEfxaH via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Latinos And Asian Americans, Take Exit Polls With A Grain of Salt https://t.co/emHjcTINeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: The World If... Donald Trump is President https://t.co/03WO7B61BI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: Talk in trade: TPP’s Asian cousin https://t.co/ZwmxD6ftZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This delightful cartoon on trade might appeal to you @StephenJacobi @charles_finny  https://t.co/4skSHNpTjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China’s strongman rule sets a test for the west https://t.co/9iYqKUlGyi via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Chinese Christian is on track to be the next Governor of Jakarta. Extraordinary.  https://t.co/ihxajtaZwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see one of the first @asianewzealand Track 2 dialogues established still going strong and relevant as ever https://t.co/3MXYL0hBaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @AucklandUni's Stephen May on this fellowship. Great to work with him on @asianewzealand's forum on Asi… https://t.co/cCEgOLVDoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news for the Korean economy  https://t.co/iaBjCloYEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this thoughtful Godpod: digital technology &amp; how we approach it as Christians: https://t.co/syfGhy65bf https://t.co/hUlih72CyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International students "join the police" | Victoria University of Wellington https://t.co/nAUUyUvSeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great @InsightRNZ funded by @asianewzealand https://t.co/b8OOIf4omh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From The Economist Espresso: Grey ink: Vietnam’s lawmakers https://t.co/ysqPwnMBI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Britain's new immigration policies are bad news for international students there  https://t.co/HbvWMTjCg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ian Hislop: satirist the British establishment loves to hate https://t.co/MDeeiahBC4 via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell Aunty Wainwright!  https://t.co/69cZcgDkPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How racist is NZ?  https://t.co/ieMfOAvOWt https://t.co/Zm9KXZmWkq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>