<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[No but seriously how's $1 million bet guy doing now? #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performances &amp; tweets re: @melissamccarthy &amp; @ladygaga = pretty entertaining. #SNLSpicer #SuperBowl #girlpower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry neighbours. #sorrynotsorry #Superbowlhalftime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES #Superbowlhalftime #MillionReasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🔥 #SuperBowl #Superbowlhalftime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No @SavvyAuntie #sleepover weekend is complete without a trip to @MastermindToys! Done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I missed the segment last night but all caught up now. Hell yeah - @melissamccarthy for press secretary. #SNLSpicer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a fan of tattoos but this https://t.co/Zodsd7IGjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Organized religion has a lot to answer for." #Unholy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw @dianeflacks &amp; @baharehyaraghi in #Unholy &amp; I have so many thoughts. But mostly, Oh. My. God. An incredible, must-see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I'm sure I'm the girl version of #SheldonCooper. Without the science genius. Must be why, as a non-TV fan, I love @bigbangtheory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This aired last night https://t.co/YTotEoC4Mq &amp; #SickKidsVS Broken Hearts out tonight: https://t.co/7UydYHeBAr. Love it when the stars align]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now if only we could fix your egg &amp; get you a profile pic @lcskf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW your fave ntl news anchor says u gave them exclusive, rare, inside access &amp; u made it happen. Whatta team, me &amp; u @lcskf!  #girlcrush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're grateful to Xavier's parents and to you &amp; your crew. #HeartMonth https://t.co/jzQ6XmaMow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although once unheard of, partnerships like these are the way to go for the NFP sector to continue to thrive. https://t.co/5F7hgFYodx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing @ParamountFoods. Love it when successful entrepreneurs are also philanthropists! Family. Community. https://t.co/5e9H1z3Onn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was day 3 of 3 shoots. This story to come soon (ish)! #heartsurgery #3Dprinting https://t.co/quQMW5FQaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only one could donate one's passport to someone in need. I will not be using my US one for the remainder of its validity. 🇨🇦 #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having day where lack of open comms among colleagues is making my head pop off. When u work in Comms u think it's plain &amp; simple. But no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rdelaet Glad to hear you enjoyed the talk &amp; your family had a positive experience here. We're biased, of course, but it's a special place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well! Looks like you guys lit up #ldnont a little wee bit tonight, @LoriDavison6 @carlosthethird &amp; @therealmcmiker. Nicely done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah! That's right! Not to mention covg in 17 countries... : ) https://t.co/fsd6x4bNK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific initiative by @MLSEFoundation https://t.co/adXmsUmdEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinner @fatpasha was DELISH! Thank you for the great service. Me &amp; @anfarnell will be back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the privilege of spending most of today in Dr. GVA's OR ... and just wow. https://t.co/2PBzy1QVfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up and at it dark and early again today. Always a little surprised by how many people are out here already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an early start today. Something cool is brewing! Chase. Pitch. Land. Shoot. Today is day 1 of 3 shoots. #lovemyjob #butnotmornings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 20+ yrs I don't know if I've gone to gym on Friday. But I'm irritated &amp; raging &amp; I had to release that energy somewhere. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This headline https://t.co/hdXYSpCpY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for today's gift to @sickkids fr @VancityReynolds...a boost for city's Ego Meter in @torontolife! Oh, &amp;… https://t.co/YB08HShGgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mojorising Yes. I need the t-shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow talkers. I can't even. Give me your headlines, people. In a lot of meetings lately with people who deliberate over every word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to @StJude for scoring a mention in @Hasbro #TrivialPursuit 2000s edition. That is very cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got new PC at work &amp; waiting 4 new iPhone. But highlight of work day? Seeing this in PR brief: Need guests to feel serious amt of #FOMO. Ha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished reading all the guidelines 4 #IABCOvation &amp; #CPRSAce award entries. Lots of writing work ahead. Will be worth it. #SickKidsVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of all I have done in my life, I am most proud to be your dad. -- #POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God how I wish this was the beginning and not the end. #PresidentialFarewell #ObamaFarewell #POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved the profile story on you, @docdanielle in today's @TorontoStar Insight (no link yet). Also enjoy you on @CBCTheNational health panel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring is an overused word. But this story about what @jimestill is doing for humanity really is just that. https://t.co/eQ4TxZSj9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just bought a CD. Like a real music CD. (I also read a hard copy #newspaper this am, like I do everyday.) #olskool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @TheSocialCTV for re-airing our favourite show of the year! #SickKidsVS https://t.co/7UvSuqimyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent time this wk @multipastaa &amp; it's incredibly touching how people miss dad, hearing how they loved &amp; enjoyed him. It filled me up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What part of our brains allows us to sing old Italian love songs we haven't heard in years? 'Cause can it be used for sthing else?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning. It's the last day of this terribly awful, no good year. Let's do this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget your and you're, its and it's. It's New Year's Eve, people. #apostrophe #nye2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made an early morning hair appointment on a day off because...? #morningpeople Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some best days off = catching up w/ old friends, being a lady who lunches &amp; walking around town w/ my tunes. Just don't call me a lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll remember our patient, Kael. @CBCToronto profiles his physiotherapist Ryan: "Kael taught me more about myself… https://t.co/ZvhzFazECr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have wanted to see @Mirvish #ComeFromAway SO badly. No idea why I procrastinated getting tickets. Now they're sold out. Boo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlie is 'right where she should be' says mom, thx to complex heart surgeries. More in @SaultStar… https://t.co/x17IkNUhb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 yo nephew: Are you coming on our trip?
Me: No. You're going on a family vacation.
Him: You're part of our family! Come! 
Me: 💕💓 Melting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI Dec 24 Toronto Star A1's cutie patootie Naya &amp; twin Milayna celebrated their 1st Christmas in hospital:… https://t.co/WhsgYTsTKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa was here! Who didn't catch him with the cookie drone? I'm looking at you @hart_andrew https://t.co/0B9tQ4CAqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checked outside &amp; yep, it's chilly with a chance of milk &amp; cookies.
https://t.co/fHDYGoi3z0 #santatracker #DLWS… https://t.co/S1nWicJ3RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has #HomeAlone replaced the fireplace channel? I'm 💯 okay with that. Just asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @TorontoStar front pages. Beautiful work - thank you @jforani &amp; @rlautens https://t.co/sRT1dvtPOu… https://t.co/ZBmRZ7vLim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you know me, you know I love sending &amp; receiving mail. So, thanks 4 the cards. But, those that don't mention dad… https://t.co/YoeAeFTP0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great profile on Helena - an awesome VS ambassador. Be proud @capjkkirk! https://t.co/2O69SRZ2F9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Reynolds could say yes, indeed. Interesting read in @CharityVillage on the impact of 'star power' on charities https://t.co/sn2qJ5diYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we are a year later with Kathryn &amp; Ella, joined by Minnie, closing out the 30th anniversary @NEWSTALK1010 Radi… https://t.co/qAqKBNaSn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Menaal, a.k.a. Minnie, who met Alessia Cara yest.That machine? Connected to an artificial heart keeping her… https://t.co/pNgNNsOD5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We sure enjoyed watching Jadyn teach @JayOnTheRushTO to dance &amp; sing a jingle she wrote to make the phones ring… https://t.co/HVXMYqJZsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have sthing that changes the sheets? 'Cause I hate changing the sheets. https://t.co/VbuNa4qv0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @alessiacara @Duracell for a wonderful visit today &amp; for your generosity! You're welcome to visit @sickkids anytime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out @Canuckscribe #Brampton https://t.co/tXvPvE7WBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI Former patient @alessiacara visited us today &amp; Duracell donated $180K to @sickkids! VIDEO: https://t.co/VbO2LaAyB6 THX @AzzuraLalani!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to celebrate Duracell #PowerImagination 10th annv. @alessiacara made super fans v happy! AND Duracell don… https://t.co/SjWpQk1AG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning. It's another celebrity day at SickKids. Gosh this is a great place to work in PR. #tistheseason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I work at SickKids = I get the #flushot. You should too. https://t.co/ojiedvlcEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@i_am_gemma_ We're going to miss having you on our PR team. Thank you 4 your hard, excellent work during an exceptionally exciting quarter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yrs ago, b4 @multipastaa, my dad was in sales @ Unico Foods &amp; called on this acct. We often got best tix 4 Mirvish… https://t.co/1uRozuo3s5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, even in @ELLEUK - https://t.co/YXMBAKHnGe  Thanks @KatieOMalley__!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan Reynolds - the gift that keeps on giving https://t.co/pXXs5D2kf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the explanation. I got a nice (tho slushy) morning walk up from Union out of the delay. https://t.co/IWo3x6oUXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm impressed Go train just left the station on time on this first messy Monday morning. Just wish they'd dim lights like early am flights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously. I don't think this guy can be any sweeter: https://t.co/LaFQLNtbKn #CriticsChoice #EntertaineroftheYear Tribute to @macgra23 too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New fave song alert: The Greatest by @Sia feat @kendricklamar https://t.co/wjTrmRaYhB For the dance beat, lyrics not so much. On repeat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our giant milk &amp; cookies 4 Santa are still on the helipad; they're just covered in #snow https://t.co/fHDYGoi3z0 #SickKidsVS #onstorm #dlws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for supporting #SickKidsVS Barrie's 1500 https://t.co/ZFkrXNPdrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umm no thanks, Facebook. I am not interested in the year-in-review video you made for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted at the @CFtoeatonCentre #SickKidsVS https://t.co/couwVptaMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, thank you, @YouTube for the nod to our #SickKidsVS Undeniable spot in top ads of the year https://t.co/40mZWXLDCI fr @Marketing_Mag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also. Apparently I'm OK w/ buying 98 items 4 niece &amp; nephew w/o looking at prices. But I'll take 2 buses &amp; 2 subways home to avoid Uber $.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not #christmasshopping unless your feet hurt, you're sweaty hot, so tired already people can you walk faster, and omg so hungry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this by @nkeung https://t.co/KW4n0D7A9K. Hits close to home &amp; reminds me of @multipastaa. Mom &amp; pop shops = quality, community, love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a surprise birthday party to celebrate the @MapleLeafs centennial! Our therapeutic clown Ranger Ray joined t… https://t.co/PDZPckf01X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @LeighNaturkach! Important read. https://t.co/Saf4heEQtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showed 6 yo niece our giant milk &amp; cookies surprise for Santa. She gets the helicopter bit. But she'd like to know how cookie fit in oven!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids need to find Santa, yes. But Santa needs to find kids, too. WATCH what we did to ensure he finds our patients:… https://t.co/bPKNQqFmid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're making sure Santa finds our patients. Watch surprise we've made just in time 4 #nationalcookieday https://t.co/fHDYGoi3z0 #SickKidsVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andylassner Our little patients worry how Santa will find them in hospital. Watch this: https://t.co/fHDYGoi3z0 #SickKidsVS Missing Home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcy113 Aww, thanks so much! It's been a thrill to work on this campaign. A privilege for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankfully no medical emergencies requiring @Ornge during @CityNews live remote. The special delivery has arrived!  https://t.co/fHDYGoi3z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In yet another first, we're broadcasting live from the @sickkids helipad with @stellaacquisto &amp; @CityNews because..… https://t.co/8aUa7jdYRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Cda's lgst daily paper runs mktg pics on A1, top am show runs full :90 spot, &amp; Ryan Reynolds comes to TO, neve… https://t.co/5M76kbABq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune into @BTtoronto tomorrow am for the latest from @sickkids! #SickKidsVS https://t.co/FssRSKwlWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[250 @sickkids staff had an exciting time on set w/ @VancityReynolds - who should be famous simply for his kindness… https://t.co/4hZrGlIXCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha - I was just thinking... what should I tweet to explain why I'm already on the road and it's not even 7 a.m. ...… https://t.co/utArH8QojC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You guys are awesome! Thank you @dothedaniel &amp; @GracieCarroll for your support. https://t.co/N9nHz9BOWx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>