<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BilboRocky just rain here mate in Ashton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmptraffic i have sent them a tweet since but no reply yet. Thanks for your help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmptraffic @merpol I agree but it's everytime I've been near it. Is there any cameras up around there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MerseyPolice can somethin be done about Haydock roundabout before its 2 late? Is deadly dangerous and only a matter of time till some1 dies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmptraffic ok thank you. Just every time I'm there i see a screaming match. It's deadly dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmptraffic is there anything can be done at Haydock roundabout coming from ashton? Someone is going to be killed there soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic https://t.co/iTAwY1nSkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredyTheRed fully agree mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barring any injuries we should start the same XI again next week and pile the pressure on Liverpool and the rest of them #MUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great end to the first half hopefully we can carry it on and get a few more goals #LEIMNU #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PayetForward that would be great as a shirt next season @ManUtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on United #mufc #MUFC_FAMILY https://t.co/MsAJdWBOmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a fan of the colour grey but I luv this https://t.co/1caPaB4QfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@man_utd___ @MrStephenHowson I'm sorry but Rashford has to be our #9 even ibra leaves unless he goes off the rails that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Bates__ I'm with you on that mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bignev38 exactly mate difference this season we're actually playing nice football not boring #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyLouLou69 I watched it tonight and actually missed the question (kids carrying on) but heard him say united. My God she needs a slap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the title is gone for this season, just can't see Chelsea fucking it up so I'm hoping that they do a proper job on lvl tonight #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeBurgess1 hope you have come back to carry on where you left off mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicsmy true yeah almost forgot about that. 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicsmy I would be to, that shower of shites are getting their faces everywhere at the min. Won't last long tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicsmy I'd cancel the whole thing right there. Sky scouse scum 😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What no big fine or big ban for #Wenger after the gbh on the official? Wonder what Mour would have got? Prob hangin would have bn brought bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is our kid @PhilGuest yesterday morning 😂😂😂 https://t.co/jmeFWNKitI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sairachoudhry @NoOffence_2 can you try and organise that there is more than 1 series a year please luv, miss it for 11 months 😔😔😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FullTimeDEVILS @UtdFangirl if Merson was a race horse he'd have been shot long ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 I just went for ibra so you can test their spelling 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 christ yeah, maybe just see what name they can and matching number in stock 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 women don't understand mate. My missus got mine for me so I know I've a good one 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoifeTurner 😂😂😂 trying to poach fans now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 there's also Scholes kanchelskis Sharpe best the list just goes on. Get your own name easiest option 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 last one I got was Rooney, couldn't pick any1 now, luv Herrera mata Rash ibra degea and thats just from this team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UtdsBestFriend it's grand mate, water off a ducks back just still surprises me how ignorant some still are just hope that 1 day he'll learn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allan7MUFC @YorkshireRed2 too tough to call that mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UtdsBestFriend I never got a fre ticket either Only time I get a free ticket is rugby matches were my career gos free.That fool has no idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UtdsBestFriend it's berm deleted now, I have a disability myself and I need help with stairs and such like so need to bring some1 with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashtontownafc hi, I have an 8yr old boy who is mad into football and looking to join a team. Just wondering if you have any spots open pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManUtd @AnderHerrera @Fellaini @BlindDaley @HenrikhMkh @LukeShaw23 really hope Shaw gets his chance soon, best LB in the GB when unleashed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any word on the @FA doing anything about Wenger shoving the 4th official yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garty1965 @whentheseaguIIs @FA sounds about right, they always back the ref's. To soft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuanMataMufc87 I agree mate can't Slag mata off for 1 bad game. Mkhi has had 2 games where he could have done better. Pogba as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRedDevils20 I'd luv Kroos bit can't see that happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRedDevils20 can see us going mad in the summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRedDevils20 personally a replacement for Carrick has to be priority imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Memphis @ManUtd best of luck pal, hope to see you back to your best soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SemperFiUnited don't make them like that anymore #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanBarr73 I was 1 of them mate, he's proved me wrong abdominal if I ever meet him if apologise straight away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BAKERMUFC1999 that's got to be a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike87_MUFC I'd be more worried about Rashford mate, we start buying top strikers then Rash might not get his chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sairachoudhry @AbbottVision loving the new series #NoOffence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antiballgame @jameswyatt3212 that's for sure they would. Imagine what they'll be like when they end up 6th in may 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameswyatt3212 @antiballgame for me is between Evra and RVP coz LB is a problem at the min and RVP could still offer us something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garty1965 @photosofootball because he's superman 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that it for #Sherlock ? Will they make another series? Please say yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Magic_Memphis abs Milner on the other side to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C7MUFC I know, dying to see him back passing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy with the line up, think we can really get at Milner with our pace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antiballgame @JoshGI97 just what I've been thinking mate, excited for the kick off now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreativeMartial @PaulRedDevil bar Rojo  (coz of injury) that's the team I want us to put out on Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was really hoping for Shaw to start but no sign of him. Hopefully he'll be back really soon now #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2 boys after their hair cut https://t.co/XEduNR7rZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely loved #Sherlock again. By far the best show on TV. #BenedictCumberbatch and #MartinFreeman are without doubt my fav actors around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juckylim that's for sure mate, need people around the team like him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juckylim him and vida def had at least 1 more season in them. I honestly think he will come back to us in some capacity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juckylim yeah it does mate, luv the lad. He def loves the club too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball can you please get shut of @PaulMerse a joke of a pundit.if he were funny then I could understand but he talks such b@llix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juckylim personally I can't see it but maybe as a coach of some kind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Memphilosophy Kroos, we need to find a replacement for Carrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelanieSykes suffered with that and a chest infection over the Xmas. Still on the mend but def loads better now. It's a curse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redarmyunite @HeyMkhi22 ever seen the equaliser? Or Jason Bourne or looking for Eric. All class films]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Phelan sacked, since he signed the contract they haven't been the same. Shame coz he had a great start to the season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomaswjones86 haha it would be funny mate, not sure if I will tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pa_Ward1 he's def not a happy camper at all can see him walking away next season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GothamOn5 are you going to be showing the new series anytime soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henry_shyboy he can play in that holding role. Also drop Herrera back and put mata in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orafa2 wish you were still with us mate, miss your passion #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really can't believe Felli gets the nod ahead of some of the talent we have in the squad. Blind, Schwini, Jones, TFM to name just a few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched looking for Eric, one of my fave films ever. Makes me glad we have Zlatan in our team, closest thing to Eric we've had #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wobblybollocks I agree mate, for me he could even cover for Carrick so he could get a rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danutd7 @johnchefysmith1 @DodgeLRC @wilsonmufc25yrs @Inza786 @patto1992 @mufc99treble @mo_mayat_97 @RavNorris @MuFc_Sam92 merry Xmas all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damiontucker23 fair play to you mate, hope you find them. Happy Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to all https://t.co/AjGs4S7cmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mufc_Monkey I'll keep my eye open for them now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mufc_Monkey cheers mate, unfollowed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConceitedSpud @MrStephenHowson @StatmanDave it was by far the best ever performance from any player I've seen. Dragged the team 2 the final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheUnitedLink I think he could still make the grade yet imo, hope he is loaned out and comes back stronger #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoeDino I like him to mate but think his time is up. Would loved to have got Kroos but can't see that happening now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenHazza he's turned our season around. Never thought I'd say that but he's made the difference for Pogba too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our biggest area for strengthening imo is  a replacement for Carrick, never thought I'd say this but he's been massive for us #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike87_MUFC I agree mate bt what annoys me the most is managers cant have there say on them without being persecuted Their jobs on the line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickthespinner @AbbottVision dying to see season 2, when is it out do you know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder would @FIFAcom go mental if our fa's all told them where to go now after being fined for wearing poppies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiSkyman1979 is because come the end of the season they ain't even making it that high, then they are going to lose sanchez and ozil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She loved it https://t.co/7dKsNkhnLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tia's first Christmas play https://t.co/rpSQTocHHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdavidhaye @TonyBellew hope Haye batters him. No offence to Bellew but always been a big fan of the haymaker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to say I'm loving watching #Zlatan again. He is just unreal &amp; I think the perfect role model for our youngsters. Like what Cantona did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nevthompson12 I do think it'll be a tough game, always is down there but all going well we'll get another win &amp; make some ground on top 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samuelluckhurst I have seen his name on team sheets but never seen him playing since he left us #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samuelluckhurst is he the lad that left us and joined Tottenham after a few months out abroad?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>