<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@theborowalk Ah me, same as it ever was...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theborowalk Damn, I'll be covering the Ashbourne Football match that day. #pancakeday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea and I went to see Tango Fire at the Peacock. Stunning dancing from Argentina's best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjchubb if they can stay with them till half time they'll have a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoisinDubhComed Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is disgusting! https://t.co/bWawTGl5Uf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjchubb New England by 5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great fun tonight at the Comedy Store, I got to be King Aldread, an ice skater, and to work on a cruise ship! https://t.co/bsXrKUBm8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very proud of my MP. https://t.co/Hu4NPT2r09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Randy Newman - In Germany Before the War - Album Version [HD]
This was going round my head in Whitehall last night. https://t.co/sBsxdXzXGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrea and I were 20 feet from he speakers tonight. @SadiqKhan and @ShappiKhorsandi where my favourites. https://t.co/Or01pCiGsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just back from Whitehall, great to be with so many likeminded people against fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawksbee and Jacobs daily - Monday, January 30 | talkSPORT https://t.co/tdXKnwyr32 via @talkSPORT
Had a lovely time today with the boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SogsSaunders Can you still score from the half way line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHawksbee here's that goal I was telling you about. https://t.co/RmYWOewSWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FCFleetTown @FarnboroughFC @abufton39 @tSHandJ If you'd listened I gave him a whole heap of praise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BennettArron @Foyles Definitely not going back then! Their loss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Foyles why aren't you accepting cash at Waterloo? Just lost a. Customer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At TalkSport tower. I'll be on @tSHandJ around 1.15.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The petition passed 1M. President Trump will love that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm also going to this later. https://t.co/jEscqrDBvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on the Hawksbee and Jacobs show this afternoon, on TalkSport. 1.15-1.45. Looking back at the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philchatterley Cheers, but I think I'll leave it to Cumberbatch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So why not Egypt, Turkey and Saudi Arabia in the ban? Is it because you have work going on there? Tad unfair?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my flaming cock Andrea. #chinesenewyear https://t.co/3vVbh16UEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1-0 down at half time. It could have been 4, if wasn't for @abufton39 Hello, it's 1-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home game against Chalfont St Peter. https://t.co/XtQdpUvrYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy lunar new year. If you are Chinese then enjoy your flaming cock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Perth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has he got duck shaped gloves on? https://t.co/rUyser8DqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw Manchester By The Sea, hell of a film. Casey Affleck is stunning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's Barabas? https://t.co/MEJoSyROXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinmoorhouse Aldersh*t, we call it in Farnborough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tSHandJ Skin care from Roots Number 7?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afcmark1 @Ed_Miliband @paulwaugh @HuffPostUKPol And that doesn't make you feel queasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afcmark1 @Ed_Miliband @paulwaugh @HuffPostUKPol There are so many things I'd like to ask her to say. But I fear she's already on his team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afcmark1 @Ed_Miliband @paulwaugh @HuffPostUKPol I would ask her to ask him to grow up, and stop behaving like a spoilt child!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afcmark1 @Ed_Miliband @paulwaugh @HuffPostUKPol I would have her say that we will not be involved with anyone practicing torture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's what I call a courgette! https://t.co/cRbnZFcRfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie friends, did the WACA become the Furnace? Or is it a new ground?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmafreud Happy Birthday! Have a ga eat day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone should tell the Dad in that Quick Quid ad that that toast is going to kill him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's best parking award goes to this guy. https://t.co/NNWfYttN5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nova Scotia village hosts one of the smallest women's marches, but it's still mighty https://t.co/MMUve3ZUhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved episode 22, of @theimprovathon 
It's amazing they're still going! How much Rich Energy must have been consumed! Good luck for last3!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at Wiltons Music Hall for episode 22 of 25. @theimprovathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timbojos @BraddJaffy 
This might explain. https://t.co/smOQkWmihE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to @improfthrones for a great night. I've just woken up! If you get a chance, pop down to Wiltons Music Hall to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all going on in Highbrow, with the elvish tree of knowledge. #throneofgames https://t.co/nvifQ2wBn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to start my third show of the night with the Imprvothon guys. It's 3.15. https://t.co/OMks9C2vF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gil Scott-Heron - The Revolution Will Not Be Televised (Full Band Version)
For my friends in America! https://t.co/httzFiAQFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm off to see @aJimSweeney later if anyone has any messages. Taking him a new batch of medicine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAndyPT It's back on now, I was at the cafe and realised it was dead! Soz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theborowalk Annoying ain't it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost 5-0. Looks like we're going for the playoffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're 3-0 down at half time. Mind you one of our centre halves is still on his way on the train. Blinking cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another new ground. Royston who are top v @FarnboroughFC who are 2nd. https://t.co/KtG9hBAgwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished reading Dead Air by Iain Banks. A roller coaster love affair between a shock jock and someone he shouldn't have fallen for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicciardini Have a good one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davejohnscomic Bunfight at Joe Corals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davejohnscomic Stick on your CV mate, you'll be doing cowboy fillums within the year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grace_Smart You give em hell sweetie! Go pop a cap in their ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nasty place to get hit by a javelin! https://t.co/jGcE9NsfkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was nippy though. https://t.co/agjDcLXiea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great 4-0 win over Barton Rovers by @FarnboroughFC Great performance and a clean sheet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RalfLittle Came to see the show tonight. Top work sir! Thoroughly enjoyed it. Lots of good laughs. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed #DeadFunny tonight, a fine cast in a dark comedy, if you get a chance, go. It's on till Feb 4th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see Dead Funny with @MsAndyPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN I trust CNN more than I trust you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight I'd to guess I was a cat behaviourist, in a dog kennel, in a kaftan with the hanger still in it using the orange from Jaffa cakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the closure and down grading of 66 A&amp;E &amp; Maternity homes, since 2010 has something to do with the present NHS crisis? FFS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Train companies @VirginTrains &amp; @CrossCountryUK aren't providing facilities for disabled customers https://t.co/GxTVk1Jw76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quentyquestions @FXMC1957 He doesn't look happy about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland His calm, dignity. His sense of humour. His love for justice, his wife and his country. How cool he is in any situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bostock's Cup
Just watched this again. Some great memories. I played with these lads! https://t.co/2fApCja1oF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we'd beaten Swindon Supermarine, Welling, Whitehawk, Stourbridge, Northampton &amp; Wycombe, we'd be away to Spurs, 4th round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a joy at the Store tonight, Romanian bell ringing, Nando's, the cas of the Antique Candlebra, and kangaroo gymnastics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theborowalk It was flipping late! But why did they let him get in the box?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2-2 draw in the fog. https://t.co/OOxpr5u0sF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tidy little ground, Doom Bar in the Clubhouse. https://t.co/KqF8D7Pf7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another new ground. This seems like a good deal if you live in Potters Bar! https://t.co/747BX7uGeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arthur_Strong Not bad, I got 12. You should ring up one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arthur_Strong Coffees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful low half moon over the Willesden shunting yard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aJimSweeney Sorry to hear that Jim. I'll be down tomorrow mate. See you then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josielawrence1 Any chance of opening emails?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @itvracing please don't explain how odds work. And stop that bloke shouting in the ring too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very happy new year to you all! I hope it brings all you desire and more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmichaelsmiley  You forgot poof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home from the pub, I'll sleep for a week. The volunteers at Crisis this year have been a joy to work with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to my last shift of @crisis_uk 
Always the hardest. There will be tears. But hopefully a lot of smiles too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, off to the Store for the last Players gig of the year, then on to shift 6 at Crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shift 4 was lovely. 253 guests, 7 dogs, 105 volunteers. Bit cold on the gate though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grace_Smart Great ceiling on that one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen the future, its name is Thistlecrack! Going to be the story for the next 4 years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[253 guests. Busy night. Now to sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too excited to sleep, with Thistlecrack taking on Cue Card tomorrow at Kempton. I'm going with Thistlecrack. So, off to shift 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@managerboardout @MsAndyPT 3 minutes! 3 minutes late! I know you love briefings, but 3 minutes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooked @MsAndyPT and I a full Xmas dinner. https://t.co/rNUtrFCnJ8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>