<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I recommend reading the Reluctant fundamentalist at this point in history https://t.co/uJ4fkGayNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughing - introduction to episode 8 of a series of unfortunate events on @Netflix has Lemony Snicket talking about fake news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canva thanks - I was sure I was missing something obvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canva sometimes in layouts I just want to see the grids - not have to scroll through all the lovely layouts is there a way to do this fast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Junior art teacher took this today and was wowed! But We need to share this with older students too. https://t.co/WpTE92h8QG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to Our Chemical Hearts by Krystal Sutherland https://t.co/nvmJ3NuqxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Burn Baby Burn by Meg Medina https://t.co/qLXx4rH21l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelVanRiel some of the save library campaigns use dire photos of old/fusty books - should focus on community more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Make America Kittens Again’ Chrome Extension Replaces Donald Trump With Cats https://t.co/op64TjemHK  for you @BarryBaughan ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fivefoot3 @Meg_Medina was lucky @Auckland_Libs had ebook so I was able to read theirs before committing to our own copies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not sleep at all last night so I've read Burn baby burn @Meg_Medina - an absolutely fab teen novel. Ordering library copy+ebook today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We bought every title in the Big ideas simply explained series last year - they are essential for any secondary lib… https://t.co/1vGOsQsmCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ @bridgy_s Ooooh thanks....I think that's the one @GelaNeely had seen....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK tweeps - recommendations needed for the BEST biographies on David Bowie for a High School Library? @bridgy_s @StephEllisNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love it if @PenguinBooks_NZ would reissue titles under Raupo/Reed imprints especially Treaty House by LeeAnne Orams. Needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of my daughter who received an offer of place for the conjoint degree she desperately wanted after receiving NCEA results yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Holding Up the Universe by Jennifer Niven https://t.co/RwdnC1cU2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSIROhelix I had a quick look - is it available outside of  Australia? - we are in NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @CSIROhelix any plans to have your magazine available digitally or online archive of past articles? This would be brilliant for schools!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Moo by Sharon Creech https://t.co/KjV7H5s26c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Wet Cement by Bob Raczka https://t.co/h591MIi8oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Six Dots by Jen Bryant https://t.co/CefW66vwb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Stepping Stones by Margriet Ruurs https://t.co/5hQAiZ4GeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What The Trump Era Will Feel Like: Clues From Populist Regimes Around The World via @forbes https://t.co/sSxChXqPDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to The Queen's Hat by Steve Antony https://t.co/coN0JM83Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to be able to purchase ebooks for my students without having to sell a kidney to fund it first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't fit in every author - if you still want students to know about them then we have to be able to offer backlist and duplicates in digi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling so frustrated at publisher limitations on ebooks for school libraries. Smaller shelf areas in modern libraries = less physical books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool! This has worked so well in the UK on the tube :) https://t.co/9fO8lSxOjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting how ebook borrowing up whereas book industry always doom and gloom about ebook sales. Sell more to libr… https://t.co/tZjzsHXYUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ I'm a cataloging geek actually - it feels therapeutic. Loving the changes to the Oliver UI too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ I realise I need quiet time to work with metadata there's a lot that can get missed if you try to hurry. Authority files etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ yes mostly! Have 2 new units this term in JS but also we identified gaps in some MS/SS units last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ I've done a big order for term 1 K-13 books, all in Oliver acquisitions &amp; catalogue, hope I get to focus on curation next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US political situation has completely derailed my holiday reading. I don't even live there but it's hard to focus on anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeDyckman @802jdf858 ohhhh. I guess if you eat enough that the toddler didn't finish ...you get addicted huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeDyckman @802jdf858 what the? Do you peel it to go on pizza etc or is it just a snack thing? Need photos of lasso use IRL please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to When Friendship Followed Me Home by Paul Griffin https://t.co/PqRU6xEkz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be fun #snapchat https://t.co/N7dwpF4aYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnUncivilPhD @jgrovum @GaryRSilverman unbelievable - this is like nazi Germany - perhaps that's what Trump really meant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeDyckman @802jdf858 what the heck is string cheese? Americans eat some funny foods!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarperNZ and the preordered the ebook too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarperNZ yes just ordered a copy today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to Hoot Owl, Master of Disguise by Sean Taylor https://t.co/ZgTvCt35M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well worth a read #gender #diversity #learnerprofile #openminded https://t.co/xKGV1pctBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmazonVideo Im in NZ have recently subscribed - why cant I watch season 2 of the Man in the high castle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardDarrow I'm up to episode 3 east r trying to build a computer that can read a floppy disc from a new IBM great detailing/props]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unable to view S2 of man in high castle I've started Deutschland 83 on @LightboxNZ have u seen this @RichardDarrow ?https://t.co/n4QrErDtOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiLibrarian Can you imagine what it must be like to be living there? (we feel this bad and we are in another country....). Sickening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pilsch @AmazonVideo it's been interesting reading about the life and works of Philip Dick too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playbythebook @38_degrees fantastic necessary initiative Zoe, but could they not use a better photo perhaps with people/community?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Through season one of the Man in the high castle on @AmazonVideo loved it once I got into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that an accusation we could level at Trump? https://t.co/GbGwJl29jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ @Flipboard this is the short link https://t.co/0qVGyw5Scf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ a fab teacher and I collaborating on @Flipboard on Fake news - has meant a lot of interesting reading but less time for novels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ OMG that's what happened to me last time with two! They will be brilliant my dear! 💪💪💪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auckland peeps - you can download the January issue of @NatGeo on gender via @Auckland_Libs @zinio app. I'm also buying extra paper copies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every teacher needs to get their hands on the January 2017 issue of @NatGeo mag. Whole issue is about gender- it is fascinating reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ I've done my first book order and spent at least 3 days on Oliver tasks, e.g budget, stats, metadata tweaking for ebooks.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karyngra @StephEllisNZ @AKeenReader could be individual ones but could display in a place where students could see...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Thank you Meryl. https://t.co/tzcXtvpua7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ happy new year to you! I've not been sleeping so not feeling v. Rested. Back to work next week. How about you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BridgetLCM @nerdybookclub the Serpent king is amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephEllisNZ @karyngra @AKeenReader fantastic post Steph! I'd have to do one sheet for seniors but wondering about staff....#thinkythoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineBusby ended up binging as it was like a book I couldn't put down! It's complicated in parts w lots of characters/relationships]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marked as to-read: Amina's Voice by Hena Khan https://t.co/xCPOteQ9o7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is a mail delivery! https://t.co/bSvYu67MEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristineBusby have you watched Marcella?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting - buying less DVDs now but worth hanging onto literary adaptations and just keeping 2-3 apple DVD drive… https://t.co/Ud2QmI4nTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisawiltshire4 @Purbrook_Junior @watchsted Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@langwitches thank you for sharing - I'm going to sit down and try and work through this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennygadget @penguinrandom @randomhousekids @randomhouse these all cost us 77-80 NZ each for one copy one user early readers thru to adult!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennygadget @penguinrandom @randomhousekids @randomhouse in NZ this title is embargoed for 90 days then 24 month term + hardback price 😣]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to How I Live Now by Meg Rosoff https://t.co/dELbqLotBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ Thanks had one this morning from https://t.co/foEiqvPWaR wasn't addessed personally and was full of links for changing passwords...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @SparkNZ do you have an email address for forwarding spoof or phishing type emails re Yahoo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 of 5 stars to The Boundless Sublime by Lili Wilkinson https://t.co/aZecI1wthQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be useful -prompt for looking below the surface when inquiring into culture and heritage #pypchat #mypchat https://t.co/WPL4V9rfLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an information literacy task for librarians to use with students (but try it ourselves first) - is this quot… https://t.co/frYpfkALOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buffyjhamilton I'd be fascinated to see a list of the book titles and details - to see what was 'worth saving'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buffyjhamilton Having just weeded 500 nonfiction juvenile titles prior to Christmas consider that prof judgement needed not just algorithm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinda proud of the eclectic nature of what I've recorded : Check out My Year in Books on Goodreads!  https://t.co/0VfgVAEpyu via @goodreads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 of 5 stars to A Monster Calls by Patrick Ness https://t.co/mwMtSEz4Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Librarians need to widen 'page to screen' connections to cover TV and not just movies! Not that we'll see all of th… https://t.co/71uCGQvYlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gypsy_librarian do you have Pit? Great for older kids, teenagers and adults, noisy, uber competitive fun (and over quickly!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is dignified, this is Presidential. https://t.co/8kqwlHBIgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I missed this earlier in the year but good holiday reading. #informationliteracy #schoollibraries https://t.co/3w7ps4dNBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are about to start an eagerly awaited final part of a trilogy.... but can't really remember how part two ended #toomanybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I confess to trying this and also another folksy remedy: rubbing the feet with cut piece of garlic... https://t.co/MdvuI1w6FE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent the day reading stories tagged #fakenews head spinning from views/opinions from all sides. Great learning opp 4 media studies students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I moved the furniture in my bedroom to create a peaceful summer reading nook - it's been two weeks and I havent sat… https://t.co/Yqv6Z8o7wq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playbythebook ..children's non fiction. I'm trying to find a space to write up thoughts on the role and relevance with recommendations pt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playbythebook I have not blogged or reviewed for months due to heavy workload and life with teenagers but I've found a new respect for pt 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playbythebook I've only read Bone sparrow and Wolf hollow so I will seek out the others - thank you for sharing this thoughtful collection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@playbythebook everything you have loved...if it's an advance that is good - gives us something to look forward to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mat_at_Brookes @tygertale Fantastic choices - I have seven of your ten which makes me think I must order the others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought provoking list from contemporary authors: The Most Important Books of the Last Twenty Years https://t.co/C5NnOyEJmP via @lithub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite publishers for the PYP Library and classroom. I've added a few we don't have to the must purcha… https://t.co/6TYtVHvIWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These trends apply to NZ/Australian school libraries too. https://t.co/e6zIMku4rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenStower1 do you think this is accurate? I wonder if the stats for reading 1-2 times are even that high?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>