<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how we beat Trump. https://t.co/cwDpASt2Ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuheritage I remain hopeful it will improve. Is Top Gear dead, do you think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just look mental. https://t.co/EkCSRqG92j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's going on with Goodman's eyebrows? https://t.co/v1PweNSA47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A week ago I thought Australia was probably the best place to keep safe from Trump. How quickly things change... https://t.co/N5EAIcXnSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveGorman Take that, Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NivenJ1 Fear the eggs. They have tainted vodka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw, they even got a copper each! https://t.co/xM6jgGwTua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tokyorich Apple Tv is ace. The Plex app is the best media server I've ever used.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched an emu crap on a pigeon. Beat that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexwinterstv @CardiffCityLive @WelshSportLive Yep. Reminds me of this though: https://t.co/kJ8ZBPZJSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan He's the worst. A travesty of a human being. https://t.co/vOICtYAL7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan "What, you mean the video in posted a link to? Why yes, yes I have" #I'manidiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan Adam Green's version is nice though, strangely. https://t.co/dgJCz7JhHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyathan Have you seen the video? Love is such a creepy peado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Han__James That's one for the wank bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new album from @RoseDougall is utterly gorgeous. A ray of light in dark times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenLOHara I must have watched it every 6 months for 24 years.  Dumbfounded to have missed this simple fact!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Han__James @realDonaldTrump I wonder if he's ever bothered reading it? His ghost writer has nothing good to say now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martin_carr @petepaphides Wot, no Popassheadsets?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profanityswan Saving it for the sequel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenLOHara Re-watching Princess Bride again and have only just noticed it's actually a Christmas Movie. Mind. Blown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followed. https://t.co/nTnbNc04nN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power cut in Queenscliff but not Manly so our road is all dark but the next one is bright. Weird!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Did you bother to let them know in advance Don?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt  squarespace there didn't seem to be any risk of confusion. Still, there are better things for me to worry about I'm sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt I do get that, and obvs I understand commercial realities, but at least with something like the airline or...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt Ah yes, fair point. You certainly talk about your opinions of them a lot though, which isn't all that different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt No problem with sponsorship at all, but being paid by the same people u could be reviewing is a bit iffy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt Not sure I like the Sky sponsorship on the pod. Doesn't feel very independent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBW_BFF If it's good enough for Indiana Jones it's good enough for me! https://t.co/taSlAdwfIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Burgess Adore 20/20, but never been sure about Jardine's jumper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt Does that mean Marvin was Sutcliffe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt Well quite. Plummer is clearly Macca, softly spoken Travolta is Harrison and shouty Jackson is Lennon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @SpookyClowns "Here's your one chance, fancy". Gold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexwinterstv The Common Good Collective is run out of Windsor. https://t.co/CdUhBbHx4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing that ever happened to audio books. @StevenToastRADA https://t.co/PX3umYUr5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onewordnodots Ha! Whoever wins, we lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beavis &amp; Butthead sequel is off to a dodgy start. https://t.co/rlObz4TLGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame. I was looking forward to torrenting this.

https://t.co/hYXbNxBsrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's what I call a President. Hold on folks, the next 4 years could get rocky. https://t.co/XlfsVznMVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tokyorich I feel the same, but not everyone has twitter/follows Trump, so they have to find out somehow I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @NetflixANZ Good luck! Don't watch Housos...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd I only wish @NetflixANZ could get hold of some more content. Their library is shocking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @DanielaPhillips If memory serves, Ainsley is packing some serious meat. I have Comic Relief to thank for that knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aced my Citizenship Test today -hopefully within 6 months I'll be an Aussie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBW_BFF where are his balls? I think he should see a dr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josie is OK with fireworks on the TV, just don't let them get any closer. https://t.co/nRycluiRo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year! https://t.co/DJLH6wOIZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomdark If you don't have it yet let me know - I can Dropbox it to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charltonbrooker Sorry man, but I'm in Aus so had to torrent this year's Wipe. Can you please nominate a charity to receive an apology $10?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear 2016 Grim Reaper, just an FYI, Mike Love is still alive. Lives in Lake Tahoe, CA. You know, in case you're not… https://t.co/qBa7CefKxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JammyTheC No, sadly my phone always deletes them after they've been listened to :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JammyTheC @empiremagazine Glad I live down under and listened to it before the Sarlacc got it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nouseriously @neilhimself  The Night Circus by Erin Morgenstern, definitely :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empiremagazine Phew, glad I'd already downloaded it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycchan Keep your dragon glass close at hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickcarr1 @realDonaldTrump Yeah come on Don. The people have a right to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_price01 Frankly even if she was, where would the surprise be in the headline "Berkshire millionaire votes Tory"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstabb Ha, sorry. Won't happen again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomstabb Can't Hurry Love by The Supremes and The Concretes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got properly pissed on for the first time. Thanks Finn, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mad twat, no they wouldn't and what the crap has it got to do with you anyway?! https://t.co/DEyQBNMQV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never had a song become so poignant over night before! Thank you @EdHarcourt.   https://t.co/sTNxPYL3wz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QMagazine This version of the app is at least the first to work properly in the 4+ years I've been using it. Baby steps...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QMagazine Just found out @theGLC are playing the @BANGFACE Weekender. Safe clart, that will be spectacular.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petepaphides In Cornwall the discos only played music that also had a video. Ghostbusters was everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election results are so frightening I'm fairly certain I'm actually in an episode of Black Mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @DanielaPhillips Absolutely right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaPhillips @Jedshepherd He's right to do so on Queeg, but probably not on the mechanics of birth...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @DanielaPhillips Not in the version I just listened to ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd Why on earth are you trying to argue about birth with @DanielaPhillips?! #nevergonnawin #womentalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghbonello Arrived today - Josie loves it! https://t.co/e5qXXRYLEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warrenellis I've already stopped wasting the time left to me by washing up and showering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilhimself Thanks for the Q&amp;A @SydOperaHouse - I've just started writing the weregoldfish story u suggested to the 2 kids in the doc ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guilty. https://t.co/uITwD3tKLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZipposCircus @Jedshepherd Well, certainlky not as cool as Norman Barrett ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TheRock, can you please have a word with your sponsors @UnderArmour? Their blood-lust makes you look bad.  https://t.co/W7pMHIJ6TP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @ZipposCircus  What a bunch of clowns...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thevandykeparks Has he indeed, the greedy scamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when can @MichelleObama run for President and end this nonsense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaPhillips @Jedshepherd I could prove it with an etch-a-sketch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: the kidneys. Sorry @Jedshepherd, @DanielaPhillips is absolutely right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd I'm not sure this is as exciting as the headline makes out... https://t.co/77Wtgrzab3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every moth in Australia seems to be bouncing around my ceiling. I'll look forward to hoovering the daft buggers up in the morning :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No mate, you're a wanknozzle. Deal with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell of a day. Hangover, bacon, Ante-natal classes, then a massive Oktoberfest fancy dress piss-up, now home to watch The 3 Amigos. YES!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@broadly @SaliWho Generally worth taking any article that quotes from Goldman with a massive pinch of salt, but still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hypocritical obviously, but still, nice one Arnie. https://t.co/4cBLGG9uax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love seeing dolphins on my commute in the morning, though I do wish I was in there splashing about with them. https://t.co/oMLaoBYwL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedshepherd @DanielaPhillips The laughter in series xi is all wrong, right? Sounds piped even when it's not, &amp; laughing at the wrong jokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepooluk @emilyrbakes That would fuck me right up and I'd DEFFO end up in the wrong one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had mobile phones for about 17 years and this is the first time I've ever cracked a screen.   Bummer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesjammcmahon It's features pretty heavily in series 2 of The Trip, so someone somewhere sure does!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when iPhone launches were full of surprises.  https://t.co/FVKVVSnOzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone else doing the pub 2 pub race in the morning? There's a bottle of whisky on each table at this wedding, which doesn't bode well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at a Lebanese wedding and the only words I've understood so far were: social media and judgement day.  Does that mean I'm saved?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameschant Its the bollocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out there's no way to buy a shovel and gloves without looking like there's a dead stripper in the boot of your car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empiremagazine What's wrong with the #podcast ? https://t.co/ywJangcgcM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>