<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRiley007 @kangamaker Think it just walked quicker than the rest of the walkers. ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredrickCrews @rtralphy Several years ago had lunch with 12 Racing diehards most with kids in their 20's-30's. None of the kids were fans.ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonBanksHB @TonyAbbottMHR Emboldened by the Polls. #I'llbeback https://t.co/RWgjuIwtHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonalford08 @tetrickracing Would have won by panels.#lovetheleanðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashbrennanphoto @ChrisAlford5000 @alisonalford08 Needs to get the lean working for him. #canwebetonthem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ljayes Let's wait and see shall we. I trusted and believed a confirmed liar once before. I will never do it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @smh I guess it means OUR  Refugee's taken by USA won't able to have their families visit.Should we now be sending them there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacificPonies @GuerinSports Champion Trainer. Best ever by any measure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thepunter80 @HRVinformer Of course it should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe The fenceðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTABSports @kylegalley Not sure if it was 10 minutes or not but late generally was the theme of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTABSports @kylegalley Ran late all day mate. Horses were regularly jumping shadows in the prelims with late scratchings/gear changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegalley Not sure we can blame Sky for today's performance. They didn't put the meeting on a track where horses repeatedly jump shadows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcarroll99 I thought Harold Steptoe was dead. ðŸ¤”ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henriettacook @theage How many millions of dollars did it cost to come to that "bleeding obvious" conclusion?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef @SimonBanksHB To see the real issue first hand look at Canberra suburbs in Molonglo Valley. % investor ownership is staggering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JollyBleek @realDonaldTrump Sophisticated strategy like that would take some working around! Might even involve re-routing the transfer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsBouquet @pedestriandaily Says now it was "satire". James must have told him to spell it as I doubt he would have known.#ðŸ¤¡senator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull Not arguing that at all - there seems to be a belief that Mark's an anchor. I disagree. If was it'd  be easy to list slaughters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPugsley @SeanyCull @rufusoungblood @codywinnell @BlakeRedden @PoggaSalter Bit harsh-if was that bad name 5 Group 1's lost due to drive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaintFrankly Economics 101 - the costs of Tariffs are invariably passed on to the consumer. Mexico won't pay - USA consumers will.#ðŸ¤¡Optus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAmerican22 @ItsBouquet And I'm not racist. I'm a huge fan of Mexican workers. I'll employ them on building my wall's South side.#ðŸ¤¡potus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAmerican22 @ItsBouquet This will be huge. We will employ millions of min wage workers. It will be the hugest wall in history. Huge. #ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @JWGOP @GlennThrush Welcome to Trumpland where Urban Myths lead to multi-million dollar spends. #ðŸ¤¡inchargeofCircus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull @HRVinformer Good decision if the same logic is applied next time it occurs. #won'the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenc59 @SeanyCull Should be both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull They should be required to go inside but last time I looked at Rules you weren't allowed to restrain inside markers. #ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm @MichaelSukkarMP @POTUS Except for TPP that is. Oh, &amp; also the Refugee Agreement.And then there's the propensity to lie. #ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKouk @guardian The issue is how a family on the $88k income get firstly a deposit then a mortgage to buy anything in Sydney? #buckleys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beneltham @TheKouk Let's say you could buy a 3br house in Sydney for $600k. How can a renting family on household income of $80k buy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colgo @TheKouk Let's say you could buy a 3br house in Sydney for $600k. How can a renting family on household income of $80k buy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @GrogsGamut @samueloakford @Reuters I wonder if Manus and Nauru will be on the list? #bringthemhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan @GrogsGamut @maggieNYT And this supercilious, superficial buffoon will be the leader of the free world for the next 4 years.ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRVnews Aren't you counting B Hancock's 3 wins in succession on Koala King? Three of the best drives you will ever see.ðŸ´ðŸ´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jotoolesyd @JohnWren1950 @LennaLeprena @chriskkenny They forfeited the right to be called a credible News Service years ago. #refusetobuyit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @LennaLeprena @chriskkenny The primary role of the Media should be to hold all Parties to account - not to be RW Cheerleaders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apgath68 @brian_kiesey @gothevikings Is there a "Statute Of Limitations" on calling back Group 1 Prize Money? Must have expired by nowðŸ˜„.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenc59 @AdamTABSports @superracing @GuerinSports It's a very quick front line if they all plant the foot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brian_kiesey @gothevikings Could be worse - seem to remember a big production Hunter Cup draw that wasn't handled to well @apgath68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamTABSports @superracing @GuerinSports Some chance Hector could be in front of Laz after 200 metres if Major Crocker charges out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe @SeanyCull Unfortunately their restricting/banning practices encourage people to cheat. I understand completely why people do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharpman87 Interesting that Skinny elected to bring it to Melbourne first up. Obviously knew it went well.ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe @CraigNottTrots  I'm not sure how hard it is to open an account there. Craig will know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots It would be dq'd for certain if the race was ran in Europe and I'd imagine some would have discarded their tickets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots The emus will be in their element in the PMU Agencies recovering the winning tickets the punters threw away. #disqualified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegalley I'll bet he doesn't go twice. #oncebitten #twiceshy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut @AlexJamesFitz Is that the NFL or The Premier League?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Bricky @PaulRowse1 And 3 wide around one bend and off the fence around 2 which equates to 62.8 feet extra distance travelled.#amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly @AusDebater People are protesting at what Trump has said he WILL do.For the World's sake I hope all his promises were lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny @edeales He's not a journalist FFS - he's the Leader and President of a Country where ALL Citizens need to feel included.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSyvret @ItsBouquet @couriermail That Policy of reaching out to Corey, Eric and co has really worked out well @TurnbullMalcolm. #ðŸ¤¡circus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 @LennaLeprena @POLITICOEurope And they become even more "Fair And Balanced"! #newsðŸ¤¡s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe Just watched Cobram and then went to the Stewards Report assuming there would be an adjourned enquiry.ðŸ¤” #blindfreddys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mleppard11 @AdamTABSports @benkrahe If Lenny is right and Laz can sit outside him then he is the best we've had in many years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyAbbottMHR Multiply disappointment by million &amp; might be close to how families felt after your "credible information" proved to be crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe Are you suggesting the Drivers should be miked up for duration of the Meeting so we can get the COTs straight from horses mouth?ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany I guess they should follow the lead of President Elect given the way he has worked on bringing the Nation together. #ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mleppard11 Rule #1 for Trainer/Drivers suspended - never put on anybody who steers better than you. For some it's a tough Rule to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane @AngryGranny1 @LyleShelton Great to see the believers Tax Deductible donations to his Organization being put to good use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Globalgallop @Racing That in itself is enough for the Industry to move a Vote Of No Confidence in them. Clearly don't see crisis we face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESIaustralia @corisel Ask your mate God to reproduce "loaves and fishes" trick Kevin &amp; turn LNP's funding into amount that'll fund Gonski.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahinthesen8 Can't wait for a push to ban face scarves and sunglasses being used to hide the identity of these bigots. #notmyAustralia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deemadigan @brisbanetimes Obviously time to ban beards, sunglasses and hoodies as well to prevent people hiding their faces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gothevikings That's dreadful bad luck mate. Hopefully a temporary setback and he can return sound and better than ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @mohamad_sowaid @JakeQRyan The vast majority of Australians (and all decent ones) will welcome your children as true Aussies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @guardian What's happened to our Country? We now bow to the racist abuse of bigots hiding behind our flag? #notmyAustralia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riracing @gothevikings Presumably Gov's acting on recommendation from the Industry Board. No wonder punters are leaving for Sports betting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots I doubt it would have been on their SkyChannel equivalent because of the clash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots @benkrahe I see the Vincennes Starter waited for the Melton race to finish before starting the first there.ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe I believe it has been published and is a matter of public record. I'll see if I can find the link. The percentage return is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe Yep. We will get more from the French out of Race 9 (if it's moved to 11.15) than we will from the TAB for first 4 races tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickHooper70 @CraigNottTrots Even right now is not to late. Move it back to 11.15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots Don't see why it would be out of our control at that time of night - I suspect no one bothered to check what time R1 was on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigNottTrots I see we have scheduled a direct clash with Vincennes Race 1. Staggering incompetence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe Given little chance and crapped in. ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRiley007 Lenny versus Lazarus looks a terrific match up to me. Throw in Smolda and it's a fantastic contest.ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRVnews @KerrynManning Seem to remember a couple of those providing me with plenty of fun.ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP As opposed to you and your colleagues who boost Queensland tourism and jobs through your Tax Payer funded holidays. So selflessðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farrm51 Perhaps we could get them all on the same plane and hope for a miracle. #manchesterunited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz @lyndalcurtis @realDonaldTrump Or as a decent person would say "Stick your inauguration tickets up your arse Trumpeter". #ðŸ¤¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull Forget about "great" - I'd be over the moon if we could crack it for competent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull If we hold $100k on a race we "get" $3.65k. If we hold $50k we "get" $1.83k. Decisions on Cups format shouldn't be made on t/o.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull I disagree - I strongly believe great horses do attract new support if they are marketed properly. Should be all about the horse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull Agree completely. They should be pref draws - with the method of preference determined by HRV according to the Acceptors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull Devil's advocate - reduced turnover on occasional Country Cups shouldn't be consideration. How many people came just to see HJJ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thethoroughbred One of the best. Thought about becoming a catholic to get his tipsðŸ˜ƒ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gothevikings @SeanyCull Most of them used to be on track Tarax ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyCull @LukeKrahe Nearly all would be free on Bail to work until convicted. Think everyone's entitled to Court Day then life if guilty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharpman87 @SkyRacingAU A split screen to show horses walking around behind the stalls? WTF!ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Forthleft2 To keep the Mexicans out? ðŸ˜ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanOnselenP @RDNS_TAI Plenty of jobs require extensive travel-how many of them allow 3 Employer funded Business Class Family Reunions p/a?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_haigh @ChrisCoons Not sure he is Bruce. If anything, he's shoring up his base with his 140 character rants &amp; dividing USA even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanOnselenP Agree about it being a beat up but the issue must be why we pay 4 families to go. Will Sky pay for your family to come to Syd?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshBBornstein @TheKouk You think your stupid? Wanted to see wife on birthday when working away and stupidly paid 4 her &amp; 2 kids to visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benkrahe Sounds like a losing night - I find I empty the fridge when things get real dirty. #fatbastardtonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozpsych @Forthleft2 @rodcub @unionsaustralia When we have more unemployed than vacancies Job placement firms simply provide more applicants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robgreenwood1 @messengernews Jack O'Loughlin of the @AdelaideBite is one you've missed. Has a chance of being something special.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workmanalice @SimonChapman6 Just the sort of intelligent MP's we need running the Country. #not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HastingsFred @benkrahe @racebk_com @leighjones0212 Does it come with an endless supply of Coronas? #ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigspeculator You forgot KnightpistolðŸ˜‰#90metres]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>