<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@theintercept @ddayen Dems should have blocked votes on ALL the nominees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trevornoah oh they're are not the same @POTUS is quick slice of guillotine, @HillaryClinton is a slow roast on a spit over a campfire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForeignPolicy Looks like Russians know history and geography about as well as Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign leaders and Wall St execs call Trump’s businesses to reach him, now we can too. Call White House Inc. https://t.co/hQB4Vrt3sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amiraminiMD we. are. in. BIG. trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maddow - what are you doing?  Stop. Warmongering. Now. https://t.co/AqbXXhjsGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald ya think ?! Trump not 1st President to implement unconstitutional powers.  How do I know ? I read The Intercept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KameronJdevine @adamjohnsonNYC I bet the pay is better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory Maybe &amp; hopefully he will pull troops because it's really stupid &amp; provocative to have US troops on Russian border.  C'mon #Maddow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders it's not the first time... more like a continuation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts Love that U are doing this-but wish U had been stronger- enforced law with more vigor when you had chance-now we're doomed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Bank subsidizing fossil fuel projects--- NOT HELPFUL, but not surprising https://t.co/yVUxpTGqr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @UCBerkeley I detest what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it (or something to that effect) -- Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greg_Palast @SenSanders Love these guys https://t.co/wrJe4ChcGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJEnglish @AJENews great news ! @Greg_Palast- @POTUS wants to watch your documentary - #BestDemocracyMoneyCanBuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFPvGP I don't want your crap on my Twitter feed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FearDept How about a big bubble over the land so people don't fall from the sky ?  one can never be too careful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you #Seymour Hersh https://t.co/RtZtVsNrb0 by @jeremyscahill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me cry: 14 Senate Democrats fall in line behind Trump CIA pick who left door open to torture https://t.co/YRLRUBLjdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjohnsonNYC it can NEVER be explained.  It's pathetic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hey, it's just aboriginal land......@JustinTrudeau #NoDAPL https://t.co/mdcdX5xlAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning! Created by Imgur user Fejetlenfej-geographer &amp; GIS analyst w/ lifelong passion for beautiful maps, https://t.co/vm2SdxaT4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hella Cool Signs Oakland #WomensMarch https://t.co/8eWERFA7IC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As glaciers literally crumble around him, pianist plays elegy for Arctic-it works as elegy for everything else too https://t.co/y9P1GcREiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like a great place to be right about now https://t.co/uAYQh9A7eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingpost &amp; Spicer earn 4 Pinocchios for false claims- WaPo for Russian Grid Hack &amp; Spicer for Lowball Crowd Size https://t.co/4YGMjd7RTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, THAT Corey Booker, the media's darling (@washingtonpost) if he is the future of the Democratic Party, then it… https://t.co/yx1wYdKqqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation imagine what would have happened if u had properly covered @BernieSanders' Presidential campaign?  u ignored &amp; dismissed him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl(s) On Fire https://t.co/D4w5ezkwTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Dakota Reps introduce bill to allow motorists to run over &amp; kill protesters obstructing highway-if "accidental" https://t.co/zdm7h7rlXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whadda Headline !   "World Erupts in Revulsion" as Trump Becomes 45th US President  https://t.co/kmMNTImf07  #Revulsion is my new word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFbae UC Davis-I'd recognize that photo anywhere-Injustice reaching boiling point-leaving people w/ little choice @clairecmc doesn't get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly @claircmc it's not "angst" but intense anger at the perfidy of our government.  I don't think anyone in Washington is grasping this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairecmc "unAmerican" as in George Washington and the other rebels under his command ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all my shameless shallowness-that's one damn beautiful dress https://t.co/sPdH5DilWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GadflyMorse @theintercept @theoceanlawyers this makes me so sad.  Back to watching The Godfather Trilogy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending Inauguration Day watching Godfather Trilogy (yes, even 3) - just seems appropriate somehow https://t.co/yg3Ii729Bq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidsirota hired by David Brock?  You lost me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ontheotherhand yeah, glasses, wild hair ?  I remember him.  I hear he is still fighting the good fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DNCdebate lobbyists, corporate money, superdelegates will stay.... nothing is going to change.  No lessons learned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama exempted Military from climate change regs- despite his public pro-climate rhetoric https://t.co/S6uk3n0pgU via @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Obama, US pumped most oil in 43 yrs- despite his public pro-climate rhetoric https://t.co/S6uk3n0pgU via @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama invested $34 bil to promote fossil fuel projects in other countries-despite his public pro-climate rhetoric  https://t.co/S6uk3n0pgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremyscahill Interesting comment ?  I think it's a deliberate smear.  NONE of the dirty dossier is "conclusive"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is NOT America-National Guard Deploys MISSILE LAUNCHERS At Peaceful Protesters at Dakota Access Pipeline site-https://t.co/8QlpUHliDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ending rough day on high note -Why #NikolaJokic is the BEST Passing Center in NBA- a must watch! @JokicNikola15 https://t.co/ZPdPX4Wg8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FearDept @washintonpost I can't be "sober" when I "look" at this-- where's my wine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DeVos wants corporations to profit w/taxpayer $ for public schools, her brother #ErikPrince is good model- made profit w/taxpayer $ for war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker and Big Pharma Dems Have No Excuse for voting against lower-priced life-saving drugs  https://t.co/vYTGBwMLOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news!  @Snowden I hope you are next https://t.co/telNxunMYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water rates have gone up 41% since 2010-US Households That Can’t Afford Water Could Triple in 5 years  https://t.co/cl7qcgmYkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RollingStone I liked it better when she was Gertie.  Double sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a fine how-do-you-do. Libyan Haftar signs agreement w/ Russia to build 2 military bases @Tobruk &amp; Benghazi https://t.co/W31uBye0EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RollingStone I liked it better when he was Heathcliff.  Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their smiles disgust me. https://t.co/hzk0RQsQBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Adm Orders Completion of CA Delta Tunnels- project supported by BigAg, opposed by enviros, fishermen,Tribes https://t.co/h6jlstdH24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Hands Democratic Party Over to David Brock &amp; Billionaire Donors- no lessons learned https://t.co/IE0Yysq6wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asking for proof sounds reasonable https://t.co/d4zexLb8He]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fracking in Oklahoma causes earthquakes-- among other things. https://t.co/urpy1PKDkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somethings I just don't understand.  Has our Constitution been torn up ? https://t.co/XAggAVowvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stukuls @FearDept @zerohedge @nytimes goes to show you how good the Deep State really is-- if they can fool even @FearDept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stukuls @FearDept @zerohedge gosh darn.  Is the NYT publishing Fake News again ? https://t.co/0aCbQBtYF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Halloween Crack" is pretty scary https://t.co/dNhTrtVVGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FearDept - What are you up to now? US Marines Land In Norway For The First Time Since World War II    https://t.co/wokEw4sgzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning Before And After Pictures Of The California Drought And Devastating Rain Storms | Zero Hedge https://t.co/4BXHq0o3nH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrWarrenBuffet Yes. Wind farms are great.  Your explosive Bakken oil trains are not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 8 richest men worth more than HALF of the world's population https://t.co/hl9MtKOUAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RT_com Crosby, Stills and Nash told us this in 1969 https://t.co/Nzpw4xUCd0 and we got to get ourselves back to the garden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch he's got a nice signature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama had "most sophisticated &amp; well-funded ($18 bil) human-expulsion machine in history of country" Yes, his legac… https://t.co/Ox7b2y80KQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FearDept @MrJonnyJames Wait.  I thought YOU were in the command room directing the Saudis ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @GadflyMorse Who hired #ChristopherSteele ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukewSavage @ggreenwald oh well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker - we are not letting you off the hook for your despicable vote against lowering prescription drugs https://t.co/mD8Js4QRUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on a roll.... https://t.co/d45FNARU0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US decline to banana republic accelerates w/ Trump's son-in-law Kushner in White House https://t.co/UEHsbfYe2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why indeed. https://t.co/Q3fKOFmShl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[best analysis of claim that Russians hacked DNC-conclusion: too many inconsistencies and holes in official story https://t.co/cQRZq0067q v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our planet is dying https://t.co/RwAZliGBnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker-- so much for your phony FDA standards defense https://t.co/ulHIICEgWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker and your vote against Bernie's amendment to provide lower cost medicine is also outrageous--there is no… https://t.co/CxnL5bPTyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau I think you mean your commitments to the fossil fuel industry #NoKXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning America, how are you ? https://t.co/aOqRWEC05v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JANUSZCZAK @GadflyMorse I must be in the Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antarctica’s fourth biggest ice shelf is on the verge of collapse https://t.co/7OZaC0MGKB via @grist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Truth revealed by WikiLeak disclosures influenced election-Americans didn't like Podesta calling you a "dick"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illusions in, delusions out. Algorithm and Blues: Why Hillary’s Moneyball Strategy Failed https://t.co/FZxlfCLiUS by @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alas is right https://t.co/cA5qzNgwWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I call BS: Homeland Security's attempted hack of GA voter rolls likely inadvertent  https://t.co/YYyrQfJi1i via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election interference? The U.S. has done it in 45 countries worldwide https://t.co/CLW4vW3rvJ https://t.co/TXTpG3TyZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLU @POTUS sometimes serving your country means exposing government wrongdoing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. "proof" of Russian hacking is going "poof"  list of IP addresses likely innocuous https://t.co/5LXr9f8wWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth 'On the Edge'  as Disastrous 2016 Goes Down as Hottest Year on Record - https://t.co/YDwe6IehQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicahZenko 3 strikes in Pakistan seems low, but accurate?  https://t.co/AyMAzhoXHD  as reported by our own trustworthy CIA (wink)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lancet study: Living within 50 metres of busy road raises risk of dementia 7-11%  https://t.co/AD5Anyzlk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald you did a great job-- thanks !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coming American Supergun - from science fiction to reality - quite frightening. https://t.co/2A48MSGWET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[loosing faith in @frontlinepbs and it's blind faith in agencies that have repeatedly lied and deceived the American public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California's drought: less hydropower, more natural gas=more climate pollution-CA needs to speed up solar and wind https://t.co/CJQRd3iIJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost  needs to do more than "discuss" bogus Russian hacking stories-- it has sadly lost it's credibility. https://t.co/Wl2M38WZcL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>