<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The next step for Airbnb is to commit to better hiring practices and representation so this is no longer a thing: https://t.co/xd6BzLEGeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where government(s) sometimes leave us wanting more, communities and companies stand up.Thanks Airbnb, we need more… https://t.co/3hr2ycWth8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual assault cases have been deemed "unfounded" (didn't happen) higher than all other types of crime. A+ reporting https://t.co/9Q0upxHzMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those energy bridges" are just pipelines. Chris Alexander, just say pipelines. #cpcldr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justin_Ling am I being shamed because I'm not moving to Saskatchewan? #CPCldr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Lemieux saying that his healthcare policy will come from the heart? #CPCLdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data visualisations: W.E.B. Du Bois on African-American history in the US via @openculture https://t.co/IPaahcUEfS https://t.co/YX43TyuIUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you wait your turn, do everything right, go through "random security checks"? Just a reminder that brown skin i… https://t.co/Qakw7MYj8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks. The Ace of Base song "All that she wants" is about a per-child-subsidy in Sweden!!! https://t.co/1bKsIVgcIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does journalism look like in the Trump era? Reuters explains via @thewire_in https://t.co/pmUxxjBnUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The consensus on Desi Twitter is that La La Land is a Hindi movie but too short" via @seesomething https://t.co/PD92zIXDvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But he said it. https://t.co/0SUsj8ADqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard pass: https://t.co/OviCFTE2bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mrinalinid I am so glad to hear this, needed a reason to check out the show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonXIX I had a viral tweet about fascism once. All you can do is mute your mentions and drink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even more jams: 100 songs for 100 days after the Trump inauguration. The Toro Y Moi from today is A+ https://t.co/5JZXAFTh8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markwwilsonmd ugh so right. Irony is lost on some people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People telling J.K.Rowling &amp; co. to stop talking politics: the word derives from Greek 'politiks' meaning issues relating to or of people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know LRT stands for Last Retweet but can't help but think everyone up in here is a transit policy wonk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @TOYouthCabinet and @_rileypeterson gets a shout out at #civictechTO 🙌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty cool. Orders in council now on the web h/t Ontario Digital #opengov #civictechTO https://t.co/urRITf16gV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm a recovering literature PhD student"
"I want to make a difference"
My favourite introductions at #CivicTechTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more employers know about this the better. Moving out of the (often literal) basement is hard. #YouthPanel :https://t.co/bLn0ffsg0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Most American Thing: https://t.co/MnDHpeLPgP via @jiatolentino https://t.co/eN8Ry6DDmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More jams: A playlist of tracks from artists and immigrants on Trump’s banned country list #MuslimBan https://t.co/cwSYP5ezNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians thinking of donating to ACLU, consider giving to the Islamic Cultural Centre of Québec (or both!) https://t.co/lHcCLm1ZII #SteFoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone who knows Quebec knows that the devastating Mosque killings aren't surprising via @thewire_in https://t.co/3BSs8MbdYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why are we even having this argument?" https://t.co/ZJlFqdp7E9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This album is on loop for this part of the #resistance. #MuslimBan https://t.co/8LxBDLJ91O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't give your prayers if you use legislation (Barbaric practices act for one) to undermine and target othe… https://t.co/xjMXGlTMYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please direct me to the email address or phone number of who asked that question. I have some...words. https://t.co/JSnWTP1GUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends in the US, here's a resource to take action. https://t.co/L7mhXpwr2u
You can: 
1) Email (there's a sample here)
2) Lobby
3) Vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator @ratnaomi on what Canada's policy response to the #MuslimBan should be in addition to our tweets: https://t.co/8cd2OhaA4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La La Land is the English Ae Dil Hai Mushkil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @MichelleRempel I agree there aren't two sides but the assumption here (that there isn't a stringent policy of ve… https://t.co/fyjalxXJGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just emailed my MP, @Bill_Morneau, to urge him to denounce the #MuslimBan. If you need help emailing your MP, please DM me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glynbowerman Sent too! I better not be added to yet another listserv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart is heavy today. Thinking of my grandparents from Karachi. My friends from Iran. Every Muslim in the world. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story. Just. Thank you and hoping for the best for Brahim. https://t.co/o7NpLLFlbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to go to America illegally? Do you know how difficult the vetting process is? Jesus. https://t.co/a3lAxCpbXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After hours at City Hall: Toronto star archives #TOpoli https://t.co/9UqMGtbrYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you make two good decisions, make it to vote and work to elect progressive councillors that show up to work… https://t.co/ITTy3w32MY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dir. of Equity &amp; Diversity at the city: "If I had immigrated to America, as a Muslim woman, I wouldn't be able to do this work." #toyouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm @TOYouthCabinet's Identify &amp; Impact Awards and tonight, I can see minds turning, young people thinking about running for office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm A Member of Trudeau's Liberals &amp; I Think The Gov Should Decriminalize All Drugs. A+ Leadership by @beynate: https://t.co/HuhULk4IsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadySnarksalot @stateofthecity yea I'm hoping to make a dent this weekend. Don't tweet anything interesting please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started using Twitter likes or hearts as a bookmarking tool and now I'm super overwhelmed with things to read. What do other peeps do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baileygreenspon I mean might as well eat great food and ruin our health, the gov is already doing that to our bodies and the next gen's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What do you mean working at City Hall is not like IRL Parks &amp; Rec" - Not me, of course not not me again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm joining a yoga," says dude bro in my streetcar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never studied policy (traditionally) but my transit policy is mandatory reading for a seminar at my alma mater. Policy is for the people 🎉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired after attending the Women's March? Now, run for office: https://t.co/HzInbc22cX #witopoli #canfem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving my $ to @rgay, who did something (pulled her book from the firm that's publishing Milo) that I'm sure lots o… https://t.co/cK3M0HyJKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@namshine @nadinetkat exactly, not okay to create a situation where one has no other option and then shame it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@namshine, @nadinetkat and I assure you this is not true! We're apartment kids and we turned out fine (right?😩)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadinetkat yes! We are fine... 

Learned how to ride a bike in a parking lot and public park. It was fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which I have things to say about protest music ft. @ANOHNItweets's jam.
https://t.co/p79EvwNdkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davescrivener omg literally crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thread: Team of 💯🙌🌟 just iterated a dashboard of progessive organizations and their calls to action #nptech https://t.co/1qi5kb7U2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning I'm at a training with these wonderful people: #Flint https://t.co/q12doG0wVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part three: Inauguration day is now a holiday in a country where Columbus Day is a holiday and election day isn't: https://t.co/S7K2W4w2jK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part two: American Sovereignty Restoration Act of 2017 would end the country's membership in the UN https://t.co/4Qr6kmf1iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week in Trump's America part one: Trump makes it harder for women to get abortions https://t.co/SK52M2Jmac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BLM TO Live: "if we're not in agreement re: black lives, indigenous lives. That's not an opinion. It's racism." #BLM https://t.co/6Ik22wUYi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were lucky, says Lisa Lucas @nationalbook, to have a reader in President Obama. Here's how Trump can make a dent: https://t.co/6pVROgD5oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing justice to an inspiring weekend at the #womensmarch by reading this. The work goes on: https://t.co/jotD9MsuMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok. Best #WomensMarch in Toronto Sign award goes to https://t.co/7J8MrEzySb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch in Toronto https://t.co/vRWgXqu2DU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Toronto is at the #WomensMarch https://t.co/LT5UlAnJrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is everyone at a bar right now? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In second place for Best Obama is Dad Obama with "Is this thing still on?" https://t.co/a3xXraS5PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this song is basically ripped off of Genovia's national anthem from Princess Diaries #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skeptical about people &amp; organizations who are business-as-usual today. It's a luxury to not be scared today #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daibyday this is my fave gif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks are spending an evening, voluntarily, to debate billboard taxes. These are my peoples. #GenderEquityTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Poor services for newcomer men. That's something a gender responsive budget will try to resolve." #GenderEquityTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now talking Kerala. "It's a special state," indeed.  #GenderEquityTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GenderEquityTO was launched in South Africa when I lived there, in the 90s. Now I'm talking about it at home in Toronto. Full circle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing room only (sorry!) for tonight's #GenderEquityTO budget townhall talking services that we use everyday and… https://t.co/5GQJJvbnc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something I'm reading before the Women's March this weekend: My dad's interview with my idol Angela Davis:… https://t.co/3c6QXMYI0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundried tomatoes are delicious, don't @ me I know who you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great read on how the government can get digital. First gem 🎉: There’s Always Room to Improve via @BrookfieldIIE https://t.co/TLngUHc3DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jillian_LeBlanc @SamaraCDA I'll be there too! https://t.co/00M9LzY4n2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadySnarksalot LOL. "All on merit" as if we would can't fathom that women are hired for skill &amp; qualifications 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to this to talk deferred TCHC spending &amp; how it leaves women vulnerable to abuse #GenderEquityTO. Join me… https://t.co/g8CXJHk2yT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davescrivener @jasonwagar most countries too! My friend's UAE dog's passport asked for the dog's last name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two great conversations to follow here (what's the #FF for hashtags?): #MoveTheDial &amp; #YouthtalksTO https://t.co/a5tZl8poV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India will explore a universal basic income program this year. Taking a page out of Brazil's playbook: https://t.co/7gA4pR7vBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love. Vogue on the women marching on Washington:
https://t.co/hTgakuH8rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since reading this piece, I have thought about it often. 
A Predator I Can Understand: https://t.co/wMLvLCdYDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending all one's disposable income on skincare and books is what adults do, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just really tough to read this. So many displaced for a "revitalization" with no end in sight #TOpoli https://t.co/nGX7LjVRfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every headline in 2017 should be preceded with "A Series of Unfortunate Events:" Bonus points for alliteration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday on Twitter https://t.co/DnlAVq5V2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it feel like to be on time for work, #TTC? #SnapTheBudget https://t.co/XgGSUo3RNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giant, printed tweet a la Bernie Sanders in our very own #TObudget committee https://t.co/PQzgaBEj31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_layton @TOYouthCabinet @TNGleason Knew I was going to like this tweet when i saw it being written in real time on the live stream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite Obama is community organizer Obama #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a champagne-flavoured Lindor truffle is this how the Kardashians feel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craughingirl The next four years: clearly stating that you are taking a water shower]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>