<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavalia: "This is the biggest tent in the world."

London: "I've seen bigger."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is extremely shitty news. https://t.co/Efg9Do67dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshalederman @CBC From this moment forward, all my hiking photography will be captured whilst wearing tapered military trousers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His wrist hurts. https://t.co/95uPbKHIFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about my eight-year-old son's gambling addiction.  

https://t.co/vRLHHZlAQH https://t.co/mPGKtH7eRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: They're in the White House. https://t.co/0mMgj3HssK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seconded. Mark shot our GlobalNews.ca #sorry spot that won an @PromaxBDA award earlier this year. https://t.co/X252LAX2t4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlfieLau Yes, but can't say before they do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of talent leaving the Sun/Province tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alex_ruiz Let's hope the Trump chapter is a short one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised this isn't written in Crayon. https://t.co/EkLSv0XClM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladurantaye @MontePaulsen @NeilCBC Really only inconvenient for those peddling islamophobia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess we've reached that part in the movie where we all watch our televisions in disbelief?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, @SuzyPatrick: any way we can organize tea cupboard so tea doesn't collapse on me like caffeinated Jenga every time I open door?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay tuned for Dick's new travel show: White Hoods. https://t.co/Cij2R8mxi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when people talk "types" of terrorism, like it's some kind of grape variety. How do you like your hate? Room temperature or chilled?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guessing it wasn't a Syrian refugee who shot up that mosque in Quebec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm too lazy to cut this down. https://t.co/bpiDzY9Pbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For sure @realDonaldTrump will hate everyone knowing he's afraid of stairs so, whatever you do, don't tell anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally installed my son's @MonkeyLectric's on his bike and shot a long exposure of him riding Vancouver's seawal… https://t.co/oP95dbu4Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was going to fly out of Seattle to India, but now direct out of Vancouver. Avoiding U.S. for foreseeable future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really thought I would hate La La Land. But I thought it was terrific.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troll's restaurant owners die days apart after 52 years of marriage https://t.co/QGJJGSophx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When deuces are wild: https://t.co/b4D9Xkm1Nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Trump's executive order to strip the Jamaican 4x100 relay team's 2008 Olympic gold medal was a bit much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're blowing a bag of Tostitos, you're too drunk to drive. https://t.co/NDII3VLIu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's why Donald Trump's suits look cheap even though they cost thousands of dollars https://t.co/GgIJ9CesVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus LOL - yes! I'd forgotten how wonderful it is to just stare at a baby sleeping. Bliss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting times, indeed... https://t.co/IE7egu8GMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most if not all world problems can be linked to people who stand-still on subway escalators.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighbor is spending $14-billion on a wall. What an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess college kids are paying for the wall. #tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the FB memories feature: My son at peak pro-yodeler cuteness, circa 2011. https://t.co/thNdqzSjoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning! https://t.co/lo0tDOjjXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son goes international. 

https://t.co/V2qQ7F8Hss via @guardian witness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LCEMusic @CFOXvan I'm supposed to tell you it's for me - and RON COLDHAM, who I work with here at Global.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't there a cure for the cold yet? Related: I have a cold.

#mancold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus Thanks Chris!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch “The Mary Tyler Moore Show (Opening)” on #Vimeo https://t.co/YWhTOmDSjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good! | "INAUGURATION DAY" — A Bad Lip Reading of Donald Trump's Inauguration https://t.co/qTNNruBvrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you guys seen season four of Black Mirror? It's set in America. Bleak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four more journalists get felony charges after covering inauguration unrest https://t.co/mNfCP5hIHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: this week's column stinks. 

9. Deuces Wild https://t.co/EzqirDBfbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth a read. | Let's Talk About How Bell Fired Me After I Asked For Mental-Health Leave - CANADALAND https://t.co/JS8ljIFPeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LCEMusic @CFOXvan Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Badlands National Park downgraded to "parkette."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leader of the fact-free world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weeddude There's a tracked-package joke in there somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody have any vintage @CFOXvan stickers I can borrow for a project I'm working on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apoocalypse Now.

https://t.co/EzqirDBfbF https://t.co/jylPVwnYxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class(ic). https://t.co/3gF2TRnsBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roads on YVR's westside are crumbling. Potholes everywhere. Along Spanish Banks? Brutal! Dangerous for cyclists, tires etc. - SAD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Told my daughter women were marching today and she raised her fist in solidarity.*

*It's possible she's just pooin… https://t.co/qllj2usAiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a good day for toilet humour. https://t.co/P35J3pS87e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He fixed climate change on his first day! HERO. | All References to Climate Change Deleted From White House Website https://t.co/xUPIbFAhiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Mirror is fucking stressful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow marks 20 years since Grant Hadwin cut down the Golden Spruce on Haida Gwaii.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKieltyka A poo and pee pun in one sentence! Well done! And thanks for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzbishop Not that I need help with the symbolism. But apparently many people do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzbishop Wow - that is powerful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianhinkle I'm super excited to shoot it. I missed it last year by hours in Varanasi. But now I'm going to Vrindavan/Mathura, its epicenter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally @JerrySeinfeld gets his break. | Seinfeld teams with Netflix for stand-up specials, more... 

https://t.co/VkYd3PbuF0 via @thr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weeddude @BuzzFeedNews Only if the daily brain-storming session is called Rusch Hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's got two thumbs, is going back to India in March and will be doing a travel feature while there for the Globe &amp; Mail?

Hint: it's me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never seen someone use a teleprompter to write. https://t.co/5RUBKiAKWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A worthy tribute to Kingsgate Mall: https://t.co/4h4kDzBg5n via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not Russian to any conclusions. https://t.co/TqHhaGqRj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are not a storyteller.

https://t.co/4AHDbbUXb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess now we know why it's the right to BEAR arms. 

#DeVosHearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think "bashes" is misleading but she's certainly squirmy and full of shit. https://t.co/bYRNQyFtIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant. | Young Thug - Wyclef Jean [Official Video] https://t.co/3SENYroiVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a writing whiz so urine for a treat. https://t.co/34p57Jsk0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get a green light for a cool script you wrote. https://t.co/sVOdQSbdfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about my son's insistence on sitting down to pee. 

https://t.co/73qnTLMIXv https://t.co/Rwypq7FjpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani Yair is fun to watch - but that wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyric of the night by Majical Cloudz:  “One thing I'll do, if it ever goes wrong/ I'll write you into one of my songs..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last thing you'll see in Vancouver is a driver waving at you just before he runs you over. We are polite to the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ropes. | The North Face: Alex Honnold - El Sendero Luminoso https://t.co/IODnEkc38Y v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wreck Beach, British Columbia [01.14.16] https://t.co/PK4Kec7HGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bricoleur @sophielui Dont't worry, when we win we will buy you a sense of humour. But it's coming  out of my kid's cut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophielui He likes Set for Life. We're going to split it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reading John le Carre's memoir The Pigeon Tunnel and it's really informative. For example, I've realized my life is dull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not too young to gamble - I'm too young to collect the money when I win." 

- London Rhys McRanor, 8.5 years old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applaud snowboarder's use of inflatable backpack in avalanche. I use orange arm floaties and hope for the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brennanleffler @CTVW5 A wee nippy out today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the menu: Penne pasta with chorizo and a dash of frustration https://t.co/1M4KH6bzFr via @vancouvermetro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When next week's column is already done. https://t.co/CHamN5HiIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slowly going broke booking camping sites for summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish staring at a baby was a workout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About 250 Facebook shares of my handful of Big Squeeze stories over past month or so. More to come...

https://t.co/unc41S4HTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a story on getting my son ready for school in the morning. Think of it as a presidential digestif.  https://t.co/2IGXFW6El1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man can speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerMoleMom Good for her! Well done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerMoleMom He's excited. I think he was expecting another eight year old though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerMoleMom Yes! I managed to get off Twitter for a few minutes to make a baby with @SuzyPatrick. LOL. How are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying Netflix's London Spy. Really good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KillerMoleMom It would be weirder if you all woke up in different cities and had no idea how you got there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccacoleman All good. Took a couple days off at birth. Getting some sleep. @SuzyPatrick on baby duty; I'm on London duty. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Monday is next week. In Canada, it's the day everybody's @TimHortons Xmas gift cards run out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebeccacoleman Congrats! You have a book. Woot!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>