<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@goss_ie @connell_fiona she's coming back! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31 days without online shopping ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼ so tough working in PayPal not to but finally stuck to a New Years resolution #Gome ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goss_ie @GmailMahony @NessaCristin there they are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manginahun I meant to skip a December one year apparently I obviously just forgot then ðŸ˜³ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging by my time hop it's clear I really really hate pre season ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @denisemcactress on DWTS ðŸ’ƒðŸ¼ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Stepbrothers. What a bloody movie ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think you're grand until preseason starts. Then you go to the opposite of grand ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barry1217 It's absolutely hilarious ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AoifeLacey99 from what team?! ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did they let him on telly with that tan? ðŸ™ˆ Also Des Cahill is so cute I could die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Don't make unnecessary journeys' I'm so happy this is getting more airtime ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndoSport can I have your autograph @StueyL11 ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All support welcome on the night! ðŸ§ðŸ§ @Peregrinesgaa https://t.co/s9WxHO1Z6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJennifer @manginahun Ye Mango it's defo not camogie anyways ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing Dessie is the cutest man alive right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck @JudgeJennifer today in the #Bluestars game. Representing ðŸ§ðŸ’™ @Penguinettes @dublinladiesg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dayno1 @Penguinettes Thanks a million ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manginahun Pam is life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona @digitalspy Once there's no dancing ðŸ¶ he'll make me watch I'll pass on the message!Mercedes and Gary Barlow, what a combo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember Nadine Coyle lied about her age and got throw out of the band 'Six' ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #Reelingintheyears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movie selection on telly has been brutal all Christmas. Bloody joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im really gonna miss eating rings around myself ðŸ˜«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_harte11 @manginahun think of how much fun 2017 is gonna be ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robbie Brady is such a ride ðŸ’šðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ªðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've literally been refreshing all forms of social media every few minutes, you know it was Christmas holidays ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kieranoshea24 my first time ever watching it tonight! ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here anyone else watching The Snapper? ðŸ¤” #loleveryoneonsnapchatis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manginahun @emma_harte11 All the gangs together ðŸ’—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack Dawson is an absolute ride #Titanic ðŸš¢â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cracker jokes are the best ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish One Direction were still together what a band ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Emma Thompson opens the cd in Love Actually ðŸ˜­ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseRedknapp You were incredible throughout the whole show, hard luck! Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When they tell you your foods not ready and you've to pull in at the drive thru Mcds is literally the most heartbreaking thing ever ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the next 72 hours I've two gigs, a 5 KM Santa Dash run and a Penguin sesh. Jesus it really is December ðŸ§ðŸŽ…ðŸ½ðŸƒðŸ½ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gavin James, The Coronas and Damo Dempsey in the next two weeks. #cantbeattheIrish â˜˜ï¸ðŸ’šðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time a carpool is shit and creepy aka Madonna I just rewatch the Adele &amp; One D Ones to remind me of how good the can be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing show in the Gaiety tonight, @davygcrowley you are deadly #RobinHood ðŸ˜ðŸ‘ðŸ¼âš”ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlsnightintv Great show guys, love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help Sent, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help Hi my card is being declined but my balance online shows there's money in my bank account,is there an issue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think you're watching great Christmas films and then Miracle on 34th Street is on ðŸŽ…ðŸ½ðŸŽ„#Thebest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My toughest decision at the moment is so I watch Home Alone 1 or 2? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @gavinjames Winter album is top notch, perfect addition to the build up for next week #3Arena ðŸŽ¤ðŸŽ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fav ðŸ˜ visiting the reindeers ðŸŽ„ðŸ’— https://t.co/Rq5jGf5b8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not emotionally equipped to deal with the Gilmore Girls ðŸ˜¢ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJennifer I'm on the last ep of the new ones, sobbing ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manginahun staying in tonight is key prep for DecembEEr ðŸ»ðŸŽ…ðŸ½ðŸ™Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Louise Rednapp so much I might cry ðŸ˜­ðŸ’—â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howlett87 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ basically doing his leaving cert like come on!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate 95% of the characters in Home and Away yet watch it religiously every day ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeillJCullen Gets ya right in the feels ðŸ’‘ #Couplegoals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxi man tried 2 bring us 2 a strip club last night. Me 'oh no we just ate 2 courses' The girls 'eh Jen we wouldn't be stripping' ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜³#Warsaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unagi episode is definitely one of the best Friends episodes, never gets old ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garymoore1406 can we bring Amelia?!?ðŸ’™ðŸš•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished all 7 seasons of Gilmore Girls, never watched it before. So excited for the new ones now ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJennifer they messed up our orders &amp; then drinks machine was broken we ended up asking for a refund &amp; going to Burger King! ðŸ˜°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally howling at a League of their own ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally had the worst Nando's experience ever there, can't believe it #neverthoughtI'dseetheday ðŸ˜µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss the hurlers being great. Remember G Mag led out the hurling All Stars ðŸ˜¢ðŸ˜¢ðŸ’™ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The full back line is weak' PLEASE #GPAAllStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DL_6 Ye it's a tough commitment isn't it! Would love to survive even one weekend ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona @IndoEnts YES! Also says Elton playing in Cork, I'd say that'll be unreal ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone going to Bieber tonight please not piss him off so he doesn't cancel tomorrow ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ brilliant!! Him going 'I'm going to your concert tonight' like wasn't even playing last night COME ON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisNewman @connell_fiona he's just on bloody Grafton Street!! ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is by far the worst hangover of 2016, I'm gonna have to skip Christmas ðŸ˜Ÿ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is Niamh Mangan and why has she not contacted me today? ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm dressed up as lego today #inbits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to watch the last two eps of Sex and the City, I'm still fairly locked. I'm sobbing now, love me mates #mates #huns #friends ðŸ‘¯ðŸ‘­ðŸ’—ðŸ’•ðŸ’žðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona @Independent_ie Jesus! That's a great couple he seems like good craic &amp; she's a stun ðŸ˜ðŸ’‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Niamh_Hynes Penneys! They sell the caramel ones now Niamh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never seen Parnell Park as busy in all the years I'm going ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually can't cope with Molly Weasley today ðŸ˜­ #totesemosh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona @dexterthe7th @JustJared deadly! Is it me or do all the girlos at the start look like they're using a snap chat filter?! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmabergin1 Thanks Emma, it was a great day. And let's just say DJ Vinny won't let us near his karaoke anytime soon ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bolandjohn3 thanks Big John! You should have seen the performance we gave Sunday night with DJ Vinnys karaoke, I'd say we're barred ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent_ie @GavMoore8 this will inspire you ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bath and a few eps of the Gilmore Girls to celebrate the offseason ðŸ‘¯#nomorecamogie ðŸ™ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nessa Byrnes hungover on twitter, I can't think of anything funnier #hilar #gas #lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dc_suitcasegirl @MeganDM13 as I said before, the door is always open for you xx ðŸ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very proud captain today ðŸ†ðŸ§ #winning #TheDreamTeam #WelovecamogieinOctober https://t.co/X6Zhkf3W31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New found love and obsession for Louise and Jamie Rednapp ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinladiesg @LeinsterLGFA @kildarelgfapro @Peregrinesgaa @Penguinettes two former Penguinettes playing here! #memories ðŸ§]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @TCDGAA is defo one of the funniest twitters going #Bloodybrilliant ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ well I was taking a full length selfie so you're not far off ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen a woman wearing a Christmas jumper ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael B Jordan is such a hunk #Creed ðŸ˜ðŸ’ªðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when the Dublin hurlers used to get nominated for All Stars ðŸ˜”ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@connell_fiona @playbill @KChenoweth @JKCorden oh sweet Jesus! James is the guy that just keeps giving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbiewilliams surely there's a Dublin date in there?! #RobbielovesCroker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dayno1 @garymoore1406 @Hill16Army definitely, incredible photo ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJennifer eh Judge that's such a happy sad movie!! I've defo cried more than once ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Thursday I've watched my Dad get married and won an All Ireland. Love my Dad, love Dublin #reflecting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our full back line is weak they said. And the Mick Fitz gets MOTM &amp; we win the All Ireland ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only cure for hangovers this bad is a Dublin win. Hon the lads #COYBIB ðŸ’™ðŸ’™ðŸ’™ðŸ’™ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I'll have to stretch and foam roll after my performance on the dance floor last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any way of undoing the IOS update? It's awful ðŸ˜ŸðŸ™„ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeganDM13 I've been buying mine since 2010 &amp; it's the best investment ever!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>