<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's simply called historical context. You're reading a little too much into this... https://t.co/qJWtiGxUCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a-MAZING https://t.co/g3L08T6zGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I endorse this. cc: @wolfblitzer https://t.co/zSBPbO0UQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Israeli government apparently emboldened by the support it's finding in the Trump administration https://t.co/10FSmMm8lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night in the East Room of the White House, President Trump announced his nomination of… https://t.co/R1JBjglDw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @realDonaldTrump picked Gorsuch for #SCOTUS -- and kept it a secret https://t.co/ZjaZIATGng https://t.co/YY8PpUpiec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump made his decision more than a week ago -- a half-dozen top aides kept it close to the vest. Tic toc: https://t.co/ZjaZIATGng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Gorsuch-- "Wasn't that a surprise?" @realDonaldTrump says https://t.co/hiZBr1EyYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scene in the White House's East Room as press &amp; guests, including GOP senators, gather for @realDonaldTrump's… https://t.co/vIUKjrPkzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump friend &amp; fellow billionaire Steve Wynn named RNC Finance Chair https://t.co/iKXpFOXmVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec today said "no American citizen will ever be targeted" by US. White House now walking that back. WH spox… https://t.co/C1xUq3bse4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @KFILE: Bannon in 2010: "Islam is not a religion of peace. Islam is a religion of submission" https://t.co/aRdvL6ULRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer just now: "That's not a ban." The President disagrees: https://t.co/jeyVRWzaIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To outsiders, Bannon's NSC appointment was startling. But to Trump administration insiders, it's a natural next step https://t.co/7cGvMcmzjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except it's pretty laughable given how much Walmart has contributed to outsourcing to get to deliver lowest prices… https://t.co/JmGEGZODZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw an ad from Walmart touting itself as a boon for American manufacturing. Marketing for the Trump era.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec just said @POTUS "went out of his way to recognize the Holocaust." He's referring to a paper statement released by press office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@netanyahu will come to the US to visit Trump Feb. 15, @PressSec announces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowy scene here at the White House today: https://t.co/M7cvWv0Wde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Sunday morning feel good vibes: https://t.co/wQvE4qSyBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS's immigration ban is sowing chaos &amp; confusion as its impact ripples through airports &amp; foreign capitals: https://t.co/wDHvr3w1OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More reaction from Trump supporters: https://t.co/IhHFGooVW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reaction from some Trump supporters to Trump's ban: https://t.co/3NybeaSRkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've been affected by @POTUS @realDonaldTrump's immigration/refugee ban, tweet @ me to share stories. Others, please RT for wider reach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UNHCR-IOM joint statement: "The needs of refugees and migrants worldwide have never been greater..." https://t.co/tqTsuF06vp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With just a few quick strokes of the pen, @realDonaldTrump on Friday banned more than 134 million people from the US https://t.co/cLNtjIXprW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7-country ban likely just a first step, a senior WH official told me. Criteria for adding more countries? "Not… https://t.co/lorDqcsFkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking down Trump's executive order banning entry to people from 7 countries &amp; suspending refugee admissions: https://t.co/cLNtjIXprW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior WH official: Admin will be "very aggressive" in weighing more countries to add to ban. Criteria? "Not going to take any risks"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump banned refugees on Holocaust Remembrance Day -- Jewish groups are panning that decision: https://t.co/iEyYMpofDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerRyan commends Trump for suspending refugee program, banning citizens of 7 countries for (at least) next 90… https://t.co/pZqfPqx7eO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH official: Trump executive order immediately bans people from 7 countries for 90 days--&gt; Iran, Iraq, Syria, Sudan, Libya, Yemen, Somalia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the section of @POTUS's executive order pertaining to refugees, Syrian refugees in particular: https://t.co/0A0mbKeEkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And somehow, despite this, the text just got blasted out by WH https://t.co/nLTOjbnPCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway just now, 2 hours later: "We are not revealing what he signed today." (Per @danmericaCNN) https://t.co/yTzFVNusiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely part of a strategy-- hard to make the case not to report what we know though. But important to note that… https://t.co/1EXpTFcJ3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So for all the coverage of their contents, we don't know exactly what's there. Or how impactful they are. Or whethe… https://t.co/aIQa6OK3MT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 hour ago, @POTUS signed 2 executive orders. The White House still hasn't distributed text of those orders or provided details on contents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signed 2 executive actions today, but beyond the title, we don't know exactly what the documents he signed call for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just signed executive action on "rebuilding the Armed Forces." Unclear exactly what's in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@carlbernstein answering @potus calling media opposition party: "You know who's the opposition party?...The truth is the opposition party."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to interview @SheriffClarke for a story I'm working on. Here's the response I got back, via Milwaukee County… https://t.co/Oh9rWfRFsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says his Defense Secretary James Mattis, who opposes torture, would "override" him on the issue "because I am giving him that power"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK PM Theresa May says she conveyed Queen's invite for @POTUS &amp; First Lady to head to UK for official state visit this yr. Trump accepted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InspektorClouse This tweet was based on what Sean Spicer initially told reporters. The story was then updated when Spicer later clarified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonBlais85 thanks! It is a pretty neat sight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of another long day...but wow, I don't think seeing this every day will ever get old… https://t.co/t9qyZLiRd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump &amp; GOP Congress planning 20% tax on imports from Mexico to pay for border wall https://t.co/d6gcYoTdQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporting from the White House: How @realDonaldTrump is getting GOP on board with border wall &amp; moving forward  https://t.co/atV0QG3X76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump seems to think his newly-minted CIA Director Mike Pompeo would be at the GOP Congressional retreat. No, he's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine One taking off with @realDonaldTrump &amp; staff on board for the first time https://t.co/5CvP0S95hT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump boarding Marine One for the first time: https://t.co/2ZhzAgQt4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan just repeatedly referred to border wall as a "fence." Almost seems like he made a point of saying fence repeatedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No word on what exactly, just that it will be "big." Refugee &amp; 'extreme vetting" orders will come later on https://t.co/mJ8QjGawED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS won't sign exec orders on refugees or terror-related immigration bans tomorrow. Instead, he'll act on trade, per senior WH official]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHueyBurnsRCP @realDonaldTrump or a fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RandPaul, in Congress, on TV, in a turtleneck: https://t.co/igaaZq78I4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanctuary cities, explained https://t.co/bwfJ5pVluG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The definition of a border "wall" in @realDonaldTrump's executive order: https://t.co/zW3OsEvtER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY AG calls @realDonaldTrump executive orders threatening to strip sanctuary cities of federal grants "unconstituti… https://t.co/nsgqNYfNLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of his Cabinet officials have signaled opposition to reviving torture -- Mattis has done so strongly -- but Po… https://t.co/ftEdlEKS26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump also reiterates that he wants to "fight fire with fire" and said he believes torture works, but will rely on… https://t.co/Dau4KWAnZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump says he asked top US Intel officials if torture works &amp; says their answer was: "Yes, absolutely.” https://t.co/iyZK0FdeWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @gwhatchet is a standout student newspaper, if you ask me, and it's got  fresh new website. Check it out: https://t.co/olUOsKxki4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT So he's still using his old Android phone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman named Haberman talks to POTUS!! https://t.co/sRf0zPSWjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's Spicer tamping down poss of fraud investigation: "Anything's possible...it was a hypothetical question" https://t.co/N6nkgj44jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @PressSec saying "maybe we will" launch investigation, but that focus is on "putting Americans back to work" https://t.co/spCvIwrCe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After reporters followed up on Spicer saying maybe there would be an investigation, Spicer said anything's possible… https://t.co/Wobz5HJPNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems Trump decided on voter fraud investigation on a whim. Yesterday @PressSec chided reporters for taking him seriously on the possibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH spokeswoman Sarah Sanders says more details on Trump's proposed voter fraud investigation to come later this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The president believes that" millions voted illegally in 2016 election, @PressSec says, but provides no evidence to backup his claim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go again: https://t.co/HLayTLhSkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Trump executive actions on pipelines today: moving Keystone XL &amp; Dakota Access forward and mandating pipeline materials come from US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New White House. New pictures. @realDonaldTrump inauguration pictures lining the walls of the West Wing: https://t.co/iwSZw0mIfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong piece from @PhilipRucker @AshleyRParker &amp; @mateagold on Trump's first days at WH -- &amp; the swirling turmoil https://t.co/2JfV4i6Ol0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway appears to blame media for new Secret Service protection: "Because of what the press is doing now to me..." https://t.co/EJFnp3VGz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer on Trump's reaction to #WomensMarchOnWashington: "I think he has a healthy respect for the First Amendment."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer, who started first day berating media, now says: "I want to make sure that we have a healthy relationship."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer: "My intention is never to lie to you" https://t.co/1IUE7EOXuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer: "Yes, I believe we have to be honest with the American people. I guess sometimes we can disagree about the facts."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer said 7 Obama nominees got confirmed on Day One. Was actually 6. Trump  got 2 on Inauguration Day https://t.co/XKZ5g93wdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer says @POTUS spoke with Egyptian President el-Sisi -- discussed visit to US in future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer says President Trump will reconvene business leaders he met with today in a month. And then on quarterly basis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press has begun to gather in the White House briefing room for @PressSec's first official WH briefing https://t.co/NRMlKcCw9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President George W. Bush also issued an executive order reinstating the Mexico City Policy days after taking office https://t.co/1KaaqsEfkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@marcorubio says on Facebook he's voting for Rex Tillerson -- making Tillerson's confirmation increasingly likely https://t.co/8tTz8VOfGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS to withdraw the US from TPP, step 1 in radical reshaping of US trade policies: https://t.co/cFFTGuhaRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this was a first... https://t.co/GcA3ZX9Lcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS: President Trump to withdraw from TPP today via executive action, a senior WH official tells me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is up &amp; tweeting: https://t.co/MwHyokniCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mikeallen points out the lead Trump could have had: https://t.co/VYGiSQJiGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sens. Graham &amp; McCain will support Rez Tillerson's nomination. McCain said that would only happen when pigs fly. St… https://t.co/WLDMBE1Qa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNBC is airing old "Celebrity Apprentice" episodes featuring President @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently not-- despite swift apology &amp; correction https://t.co/P6AeTJLQV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it wasn't. Trump just as focused on crowd sizes as president as he was as a private citizen during his campaign https://t.co/H0F8DvAeEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pictures that don't show where the crowd ends. About half the picture is VIP seating, for scale https://t.co/BtWAjjSlGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the #WomensMarch in DC has flooded way off course. This is H St NW in DC's Chinatown https://t.co/UgJ89mg9n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Uber driver just now: "All these women and I can't get one number!" #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My view earlier today as @POTUS delivered inaugural address. Can you spot @BarackObama? https://t.co/QLQsJYscYq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>