<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Building a Wall of Ignorance, via @nytimes https://t.co/78yM3Qcl8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Youth Group That Launched a Movement at Standing Rock, via @nytimes https://t.co/XhjyYUMqaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angela Kerins loses her case for damages against the Public Accounts Committee (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/6eEqcXFtBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel’s Hard-Liners Want to ‘Go Big’: Annex a Settlement, via @nytimes https://t.co/YndFGXauNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump fires acting attorney general for defying travel ban
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/OgjkMGLnSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want them all to stay #celebritymasterchefIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kitsgirl1 I was thinking cat vomit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 Thise Afflecks are a talented bunch! The son was amazing too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 Me too *music* and many tears were shed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 I have, Nell. It's really good, heavy going at times but outstanding performances from Casey Affleck and Michelle Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BlueJay is a little gem. Mark Duplass and Sarah Paulson are both wonderful #Netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His last Grand Slam 5 years ago at Wimbledon *in awe* @rogerfederer #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Match point #FedererNadal #AusOpen2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3-3 final set, each broke serve in 5th #FedererNadal #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobfoxer @rogerfederer It's superb, fast serves, short rallies, killer shots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the score line: #FedNad 6-4,  3-6, 6-1, 3-6 and so far 2-3 in 5th #AusOpen some amazing shots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aussie open into 5th set. Federer playing brilliantly, Nadal has break in 5th but Fed about to break back #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live From the White House, It’s Trump TV, via @nytimes https://t.co/Rq6tjyd18Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thread worth reading https://t.co/3Z6wvShf6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another crisis, another minister dodging it - Gene Kerrigan https://t.co/ldudZdXOkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobfoxer @SaturdayRTE For sure Bob and it's a lifeline for many in rural Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good stuff in Hennessy Portrait Awards too #NatGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The light is beautiful in Dublin this afternoon. Speaking of light, it's the last few days of #Turner in #NatGallery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have taken trains in Italy,Germany, Denmark (heavily subsidised) and England (privatised) Far superior, efficient and good value in former]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus Eireann is a subsidised public transport *service* it should not be expected to run as a normal business and make a profit @SaturdayRTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would Sinn Féin want to be in govt with Fine Gael? Makes no sense, totally different policies @SaturdayRTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Hurt. I remember his incredible performances in Midnight Expess, Alien and Elephant Man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm doing a Friday double, now for #Trainspotting2 wooooooo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The premise of #Denial is very apt right now. Truth and lies, ahem *altenative facts* Also most films with Rachel Weisz are worth seeing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh God, Joan Burton and Brian Hayes! Is there nobody else? #pknt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured parks chief for photos to prove 'media lied' about inauguration crowd – report https://t.co/yzZBZGLCf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doomsday Clock moves 30 seconds closer to midnight as threat of global annihilation grows https://t.co/71dKp0rj2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it okay for a stranger to pay for your first-date dinner because he’s a man?
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/nqlFIvkQgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NettyKealy It's worth the monthly tenner even just for House of Cards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NettyKealy It's on Netflix x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NettyKealy Hi Netty, it's a bit bizarre so far! Brilliant acting. Jim Broadbent and Whishaw really excellent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started watching #LondonSpy Ben Whishaw is brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bitter_lemons @guardian Yes, for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump says torture 'absolutely' works: 'we have to fight fire with fire' https://t.co/RldVJEzD1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reaction On Decision to Join the EEC - Throwback to 1972 https://t.co/ALD1AGOM0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GCraughwell @realDonaldTrump Oh what now? #NotInMyName]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke the Panama Papers story. Here's how to investigate Donald Trump https://t.co/SmMRwXQeHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turas Nua sounds a bit like Scientology #Liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspirational: 'I baked cupcakes to fund my pilot lessons' https://t.co/aUIznhH8O5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government signs off on €2.2m salary top-ups for TDs and senators https://t.co/K6qaJQa9CU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s first bowel movement in White House twice the size of Obama’s, Press Secretary reports https://t.co/orLhmcwjhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene-Modified Ants Shed Light on How Societies Are Organized https://t.co/QLqy3TbqS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lion is so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+#LaLaLand for director and OJ for best documentary #Oscars2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Michelle Williams for supporting actress and #LaLaLand for soundtrack #Oscars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't seen all the #Oscar nominated films yet but I'd be surprised if Casey Affleck and Natalie Portman don't win. Outstanding acting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithihartery Questions and answers, Paths to Freedom and Nighthawks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good profile piece on @ClareDalyTD in today's @sundaybusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump But the media reports "fake news", "ratings are false!" When did you change your mind?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doesn't every country put its own interest first?" Asked #Marian I have two words: #BankDebt

Our Govt supports the EU and the 1%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CNN needs to take a lesson from #Vinb https://t.co/NFpggSuWZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Kerrigan: It's been a hard right turn for the worse https://t.co/5pFCeX1tFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's #Finegaelness https://t.co/FxEUY8FdXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 True but scant compensation! There's always next week....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 United were worse!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh @Nell496 How did that happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland Also liked "This must be the place"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland Emma Donoghue "Room", John Banville "The Sea", Maggie O'Farrell "After you'd gone" Love Irish writers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland John McGahern "Amongst Women", John Boyle "The Boy in Striped pyjamas" Brian Moore "The Doctor's Wife" Colm McCann "Transatlantic"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 Ha ha moving fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh @Nell496 1-2 crikey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Auster: ‘I'm going to speak out as often as I can, otherwise I can't live with myself' https://t.co/4jYbByQ2JP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintan O’Toole: President Donald Trump is an authoritarian and anarchist
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/j1Y7Y2ZVJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could have been @BernieSanders thanks @DNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, this is what the Govt wants. Pit one group against another and they get off scott free, we should support each other and form a plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+subsidised and, because fares are low and services are good,public transport is used widely #Liveline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus drivers blaming free travel for reduction in their pay. Surely it's low Govt subsidy that's at fault. In Italy transport is heavily +]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would @HighNoonNT George have a problem with a 64 year old man having children?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing that David Quinn, he of Iona and Breitbart, doesn't love the Democrats #Newstalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McManus on what Kenny did not tell global elite
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/Cxv6a918p4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libor scandal: the bankers who fixed the world’s most important number https://t.co/EbXdP2IyWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would we be angry, eh? https://t.co/vvtOXMJN8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianKeyes That's brilliant! Well done you x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmcgrathtd @FineGael @fiannafailparty No response? Seems they're only interested in us at election time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, @AXA_Ireland I'm assuming, since I haven't heard from you since yest, that you want me to take my business elsewhere? After 15 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan's rising child poverty exposes true cost of two decades of economic decline https://t.co/gvm2upd1XC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewstalkDrive Car insurance companies operate pretty much like a cartel, stratospheric quotes this year. Claims down per Michael Noonan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight men hold as much wealth as half the planet combined (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/DHpSfJKT9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AXA_Ireland Could you follow me please so that I can DM you the details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vinnynau Absolute nuts! They need to be seriously regulated @AXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vinnynau Me too. Was told they *have* to put 20% on all premiums this year. Nonsense! Price gouging a compliant consumer base]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mmcgrathtd @FineGael @fiannafailparty What's happening about insurance premium increases? Are you going to let consumers be gouged again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamreilly57 I'm sure that's part of it. And Setanta. But, as usual the innocents pick up the tab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+Insurance companies can do this because we let them and we have an inept Govt that only cares about reelection. We have to shout stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @AXA for years and years, never claimed and they are putting a blanket 20% increase on all policies this year, regardless. Moving!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[+They tell us that inflation is low, consumer price index 0.1% lower this year. What is CSO measuring? We are taken for fools #CarInsurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't continue to accept this cartel-like price gouging. What is Govt doing about it *silence* @AXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CarInsurance quote nearly doubled in 2 years. Never claimed EVER. Clean licence for 20+ years, full no claims bonus. Hopping @AXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 Probably a fair result, Nell. We both played well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's some advice for Mourinho: Play Rashford, he changes the dynamic of a game #IShouldBeUnitedManager #manliv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? No Rashford. Fellaini FFS #ManULiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 The half time hairdryer hasn't had the desired effect! COME ON UNITED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nell496 You're playing well, in fairness (we'll getcha in 2nd half after the drubbing from Mourinho at half time) 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw #MeetingswithIvor today, an Alan Gilsenan doc about Ivor Browne. Really excellent, moving and honest. Opening in #IFI on Feb 10th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A powerful piece from Gene Kerrigan: "Freeze them out of it, said the honest man" https://t.co/iLQI1tSFmq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>