<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlchadha @peelschools They help us translate policy to classroom practice. They reflect what Peel Ts are doing to support policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlchadha @peelschools 

Monographs and AssessPeel guides are here: https://t.co/4vfCO88bjO https://t.co/zXkGuu75LA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the GRASPS. Great way to articulate authentic #assessment #AssessPeel https://t.co/Y3o18hEh58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What else could you add to this list? the pros and cons of traditional assessment? #AssessPeel https://t.co/AkFgrtYTRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need some AfL strategies to check for understanding &amp; readiness to learn? #assessment #assessPeel https://t.co/cBdUL3Lk7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you know about the value of a student centred portfolio? Share your ideas.

Student voice and choice is nec… https://t.co/lAm9fAtqiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t give one mark to all Ss for group work or as Dewey says…

#AssessPeel https://t.co/pj2Du2i0b9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlgonquinT Of course you want to Goolgle Formify it! #AssessPeel #PeelABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students’ conceptions about fair assessment of their learning — Equality &amp; equity are diff in assessment #assesspeel https://t.co/pNDkHd68iT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful chat led by the dynamic duo @teachpatten .

Thanks for all the thoughtful assessment ideas! #PeelABC… https://t.co/Ilq6IoGXuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlchadha I think this is reflective of secondary context. Work in progress. #peelabc #Assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miss_Salituro Here is a copy of the missed work form: https://t.co/0jpUCmEEki #AssessPeel #PeelABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petrychkovych Just say no to penalties when we can invite another learning opportunity #peelabc #assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider Ss learning and social emotional needs when making instructional and assessment needs. Students at the cen… https://t.co/4kluzQU6xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airamxmaria @AmitMehrotra78 Self reflection drives learning! #peelabc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharronHuxley The book puts students at the centre. #assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler Hmmm. Interesting. We approach it a wee differently here. Each goal must have knowledge and skill. no… https://t.co/9djTfvc9Yn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler 2nd try.. "We are learning to apply design thinking to a text form for specific audience and purpose" #learninggoal #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to reconnect with you and your assessment thinking tonight #PeelABC #AssessPeel https://t.co/lb7Xz8SvDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready for #assessment chat tonight at 8.15 pm? #AssessPeel #PeelABC https://t.co/DZR8ZMAeNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to do some learning with you tonight at 8.15 pm! #AssessPeel #PeelABC https://t.co/b2k4AhKDRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready for tonight? #PeelABC 8.15

#Assesspeel https://t.co/RB3HWxuENa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you are getting ready for tonight at 8.15 pm. Here are our prompts. #PeelABC @teachpatten https://t.co/chFZ8dPqr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New month, new #PeelABC. Eager to start the convo w the dynamic duo of @teachpatten.

Find all our chat prompts her… https://t.co/6WCidTdkrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler What about “apply design thinking to create a ppt’? Adds in competency. #learninggoal #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serting clear goals with criteria supports students to be life long learners and reflective little dudes!… https://t.co/cmfsCpIBoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedding #assessment processes so all our learners have access #assesspeel https://t.co/BMEpTbydsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sidebyside folk ready for some #assessment conversation? #assesspeel #peelabc #peelsln https://t.co/7dVL188MbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markboard @albertfong @GignacMs will it allow for most consistent more recent? When I checked it out, didn't meet GS police #assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GignacMs Lots of ways to leverage google apps #assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKrstovic @ForestAvenuePS @KAEdwards1 Sharing #learning goals to empower our learners. Now i see it! #assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready for some collaborative assessment learning @Briarwood_Buzz #assesspeel https://t.co/L5Nr15MVV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assessment as Learning in motion. effective motion! #AssessPeel https://t.co/W3pTTEF3wA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feedback from colleagues that will feed forward = invaluable time. #AssessPeel https://t.co/o03yhhbJ4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffbeaudry There is also a @CAFLNetwork  conference at that time too. #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MashelleKaukab and I are excited. We have decided it is going to be a Book Do! #AssessPeel #EngageMath https://t.co/2daZNhoB5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kindergarten curriculum now loaded for the Student Learning Notebook! Whoop Whoop!  #AssessPeel #PeelABC @LizUgoEYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s a learning map? Where does the idea come from? Part learning progression, part descriptive criteria.… https://t.co/3hO27XstWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s talk assessment as pedagogy &amp; shift our view to see how it can drive learning. Huang &amp; He (2016) #AssessPeel https://t.co/pl2kMsPqlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cshiffman @BrendaDawnLamb @PeelSchools Push past compliance to real learning.  #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's renew our focus on Learning Skills and Work Habits. These skills will empower our  modern learners.… https://t.co/ffnNCSd4bP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both Ts &amp; Ss are a part of the formative assessment feedback loop.  #AssessPeel #engagemath https://t.co/0VdZNiexUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do you take time to reflect on student learning? T reflection promotes S reflection. #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we giving our Ss time to reflect? Are we modelling this for them? #AaL #metacognition #reflection #assesspeel https://t.co/NQIeN5JuBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we use all five senses to better observe our students? What would that look like in your classroom? #Assesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assessment for learning. 
Triangulation.
Include students in the assessment process. 

#assesspeel https://t.co/Diiq9gyK2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Observing Ss in the process learning allows Ts to serve their needs through feedback &amp; questioning. #AssessPeel https://t.co/vUPwXxOgCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we become more wise to student learning? 

Observe.

#AssessPeel https://t.co/yFhVRTkGxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still deducting late marks? What strategies help to avoid this penalty? 
1. Non-evaluative homework
#AssessPeel https://t.co/FLo1n6X7hT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do we need to do to help students? Assess with the purpose of learning in mind. #AssessPeel https://t.co/34XDA3PWHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is why Ts must embrace our mistakes. #reflection leads to learning. Teaching = complex. #Takerisks #AssessPeel https://t.co/kXBW7lcc8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of learning in a PLC. What in assessment do you want to learn to change in your practice? #assessPeel https://t.co/jhsNFoiz69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful visual to share &amp; discuss with Ss to help them value and READ feedback! #AssessPeel #PeelABC https://t.co/lvOKwIidoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphic to illustrate #formative assessment. What do these ideas look like in your classroom? #AssessPeel https://t.co/GGhN3ChwRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanRidler51 We are leading a #PeelABC (book chat) in June on @susanmdrake book. Perhaps you would like to co-faciliate the conversation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always building on existing &amp; supportive assessment practices. Do more of good, less of not so good! #AssessPeel… https://t.co/CBTLMTIkEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanRobertson Let me know if you want to explore that in an inquiry w colleagues in the spring 2/2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanRobertson Great curiosity Refocusing on learning skills &amp; work habits develops sense of self-regulation...helps in 'owning' learning.1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VPLoiLam Experienced Ts value their own explorations. Try it out is the best permission &amp; encouragement to give! #PeelABC #assessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PeelABC prompts are here: 
https://t.co/bVFu9RGAa6
@nluinen
@jenniferpagniel
@AlgonquinT
@ms_e_demeter
@MmeJBrosel… https://t.co/SUcfA6QUkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PeelABC prompts are here: 
https://t.co/bVFu9RGAa6

@Ms_drury
@Ms_salituro
@gillianKajg
@Trinh_babbles
@missusrq… https://t.co/bDHrdFljf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PeelABC prompts are here: 
https://t.co/bVFu9RGAa6

#AssessPeel
@petrychkovych
@airamxmaria
@mkkhela
@mawpalgrave… https://t.co/oS0VwyMpgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for the #GSNH #PeelABC prompts? 

https://t.co/bVFu9RGAa6
@teachpatten @myrondueck 
Starts next Wednesday a… https://t.co/D9fPlRkG1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to sign up for our next book with @teachpatten @myrondueck 

https://t.co/RKwP7Zq0DY

#PeelABC… https://t.co/WNL4XUF67L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the wonderful chat tonight! 
Wonderful facilitation @MashelleKaukab 
@MatthewOldridge
#PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3. Set a professional goal and reflect on it. Share experiences with Ss. 

#PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3. Ask Ss to write an email to parents telling them about their learning. #PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2. Ts need to provide clear success criteria for Ss to use during reflection. #PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2. For reflection to happen, provide choice... in person, vlog, blog, tweet. #PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2. Ts need to provide multiple strategies for Ss to use during reflection. #PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1. Asking Ss to include evidence in their reflection requires thinking about their thinking &amp; product. #PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1. Asking Ss what they would do differently is impt part of reflection. 
#PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1. Shift convo from what Ts need to cover to what Ss need to learn. Brilliant statement @mssackstein

#PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1. Everyone needs a plan for reflection. Ss, Ts. Ts need to help Ss create a plan 2 work toward mastery. #AssessPeel #peelabc #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for Feb's #PeelABC?

https://t.co/RKwP7Zq0DY

#AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk 

Facilitated by this fab duo:… https://t.co/n9JD9kWCdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for tonight! 

@MatthewOldridge
@mssackstein

#PeelABC #AssessPeel #BellLetsTalk https://t.co/twYI2owV7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrDWiwchar Making students a part of the assessment process. Giving voice and choice. #AssessPeel  #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using observation to ask the question that will lead to more visible thinking, a student question or feedback.… https://t.co/uVRElUrThF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True or False:
You must change your learning goal every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What strategies can you share to help others understand how to effectivley triangulate evidence of learning ?… https://t.co/qcbmbEdlyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What conditions do informal teacher leaders face when working to support assessment? #AssessPeel #teacherleadership https://t.co/q1PAPtDdGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assessment literacy involves developing skills, knowledge &amp; principles that align to support Ss learning. These are… https://t.co/Yz4fPvf0d4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still working on getting Ss to understand the #learninggoal &amp; #successcriteria so they can self-reflect. It is impo… https://t.co/OPJoQVfVqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating valid and reliable assessments that celebrate learning results in increased student and teacher efficacy.… https://t.co/12RVgReiwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoachChirakal Just saw this. I don’t agree with all, but might be helpful in your #assessment convos #assessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenApgar @beepreemo @MeganHaessler @mlchadha @MatthewOldridge @MissHarperClass Nope. Peel has its own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenApgar @beepreemo @MeganHaessler @mlchadha @MatthewOldridge @MissHarperClass Created by our own fabulous developer w lots of T input]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenApgar @beepreemo @MeganHaessler @mlchadha @MatthewOldridge @MissHarperClass We have our own SIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susancampo @taravento Thank goodness! I was wondering what else you could be doing on a Fri night! https://t.co/V1MOdISTSc 4pm #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s only 7 am but I am already excited for tonight’s #PeeABC meet-up at 4 pm! @MsHLye 
#assessmentisfun
Who wants to join? #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlchadha @MeganHaessler @MatthewOldridge @MissHarperClass @beepreemo Amazing overview! Thanks Monica! #asesspeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beepreemo @MeganHaessler @mlchadha @MatthewOldridge @MissHarperClass Eventually. S version lands in March.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beepreemo @meganhaessler @mlchadha @matthewoldridge @missharperclass Teacher app now. Student app to launch in March. Connects to our SIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beepreemo @meganhaessler @mlchadha @matthewoldridge @missharperclass Created in house. Not sure where $ came from. Would love to show it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mskwhitford So glad you are making time on your Wednesday nights to share your assessment practices with others. #AssessPeel #PeelABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganhaessler @mlchadha @matthewoldridge @missharperclass @beepreemo   Triangulates, uses learning goals and success criteria. AWESOME. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganhaessler @mlchadha @matthewoldridge @missharperclass @beepreemo Tool for eportfolio &amp; assessment. Curr &amp; GS aligned, uses levels 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddrmanic So terrifying. Perhaps she needs to revisit the PISA data and make some informed decisions. #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmesmiley Ah, Madame! Missing you in our chats! #PeelABC #AssessPeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristaharris19 @royal_orchard @mrswilsoninpeel What AaL strategy are you using? #reflection #assesspeel]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>