<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[15,000 words into my next scifi novel. This one is about AI. Not Terminator, don't worry. Or at least not yet. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been checking out Refind too and hope it catches on. If you're curious, here's an invite link from moi:… https://t.co/0Y6YDGW9Mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s no doubt Thiel helped NZ’s startup ecosystem. Still feels like he bought his NZ citizenship. Wouldn’t be so… https://t.co/qx47lGZl2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time for a new humanist movement in tech; something less selfish and more humane than transhumanism? https://t.co/6IVvX9uf58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBattlefisher hi Michele, that sounds fascinating. My email is richard AT ricm.ac. Let’s talk more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Case For Humanism In Tech https://t.co/6IVvX9uf58 In which I argue for a new kind of humanism in tech (&amp; I don't mean transhumanism!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great progress! Looking forward to reading it. Is that the title of the novel? https://t.co/5ioTKPJAuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree, it's up to the media (incl we the people) to solve this -&gt;“The Information War Has Begun”by @zephoria https://t.co/vas7pdv5D3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make America’s Robots Great Again https://t.co/OLHgMxtXEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go indies. The artist runs their own store, fans can follow them. Superb model. "Digital album sales grew 20%, trac… https://t.co/Fyql9UMTjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Double the benefit, because he gets to avoid our earthquakes by not actually living here. https://t.co/VvnDriNrTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really good episode -&gt; Recode Media: How the press can save itself in the age of Trump (Jay Rosen, professor, NYU) https://t.co/BLayjNQ9hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once interviewed David Gelernter and he was one of the most thoughtful people I've ever met, so he's anything but… https://t.co/mtYojN7JId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TECH COLUMNIST AVAILABLE. I'm looking for a home for my new tech column: https://t.co/Iq3LPJSlcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in! Call to arms by @johnbattelle to take back Internet publishing from platforms -&gt;We Can Fix This F*cking Mess https://t.co/z5lxUYr8wR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “When Both Tech &amp; Humans Fail Us: A Tale of Lost Luggage” https://t.co/wCzb6W0Prx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my readers in the UK, my latest book is on special this week for just £0.99: https://t.co/LZZpjY52qR #KindleCountdown #sciencefiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yikes "Shot directly through Magic Leap technology on 10/14/15, without the use of special effects or compositing.… https://t.co/Jy4c72VzmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My top tech trends of 2016:
1. VR
2. Conversational AI
3. Social Media Jumps The Shark
4. Automation
5. Pokémon GO
https://t.co/8EHH2F4YzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My top tech trends of 2016. Especially interested in yr thoughts on #3: social media jumps the shark! https://t.co/8EHH2F4YzE #yearinreview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last chance to buy my latest book at the special offer of $0.99. The #KindleCountdown deal finishes later today:… https://t.co/qzL72geF32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats Ryan &amp; team! One of the good guys in the twittersphere, so well deserved. https://t.co/yKnJmhoUBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Completely changed the way I think about VR." A happy Presence customer! Buy now for just $0.99:… https://t.co/Jk4v8yuMBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmelville @lancewiggs one thing I’ve learned as an indie author: Amazon gives you great opportunity, but it’s the same old terrible UI! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmelville @lancewiggs If you go to 'Manage Your Content and Devices’ then check ‘Country Settings’. Switch to US &amp; you should see the deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmelville @lancewiggs It’s just on US store (although supposed to be on UK too). Also looks like you need to be logged in to see it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An update on Presence sales, early details about my next book, plus a teaser about a new tech blog I'm developing! https://t.co/irwOZoP5mM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limited time offer: buy PRESENCE for $0.99. #ScienceFiction about the future of #VirtualReality. #kindlecountdown… https://t.co/fxUbfhOUxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I second that. Amazing work @iceandy &amp; co. https://t.co/ET4voOF1Xn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bernardchickey @tmurphyNZ Congrats, the new news site looks great...and much needed in NZ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CyberMonday deal today on my scifi novel, Presence. Just $0.99 for a limited time only! #kindlecountdown #Kindle https://t.co/LX8wfHQvEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honored to be interviewed for @NetHistoryPod. Lot of great stories here about early blogging &amp; founding of @RWW. https://t.co/sPfkbdlxpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's someone who's doing the #indieauthor job right. I'm still in the early days of this, so I have a ways to go. https://t.co/HDjrvo9tkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This French futurist magazine ponders what Facebook will be in 2050. Features an interview with moi, whose novel is… https://t.co/YFr0Lkq2EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought https://t.co/Qkl900iuSi from @Namecheap for $24, instead of paying Wordpress $250 for it a month or so ago. 2017: blogging is back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just like the politicians, our job was to listen, and we talked instead." Spot on. Listen up, Twitterati. https://t.co/PPwU4jYY9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marshallk congrats Marshall, Mikalina and Tyler!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GeoNet continues to provide amazing service. Its latest blog post calls for "24/7 monitoring centre to respond to t… https://t.co/l279NfCvbN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmccormick, a @ProductHunt feature awaits. https://t.co/mAg7x3wqhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently they were rescued, which is good news if so: https://t.co/pDlpdj76yb https://t.co/sB2XEW9NZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree! -&gt; "new laws with powerful sentencing for those who loot during periods of civil disaster." https://t.co/EADzRjVHIm #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not one, but TWO live blogs. Does that count as exponential? ;) #SUNZSUMMIT Sad to be missing @SingularityUNZ, but… https://t.co/YD3fdM2uR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley was worried about the wrong bubble (via @BIAUS) https://t.co/V78kMkhdHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sfrielick good point, will keep an eye on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ditto. Still trying to assess situation in Chch. Most of the news coverage seems to be about Wgtn. https://t.co/udaU8SOLUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["magnitude 7.5 severe earthquake has struck 15 km north-east of Culverden at 12:02am". Woke us up in Lower Hutt! Ts… https://t.co/WEN0jRLUfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great show, incl challenging the media -&gt; Open Source with Christopher Lydon: Seeing Red in Trump’s America https://t.co/oZdh03FK7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Twitter was technology’s gift to him in that he could keep leapfrogging ahead of any fact check." Trump biographer https://t.co/0m0EPqp1dC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what my novel is about! -&gt; Virtual reality powered by our minds? '10 years from now, it will seem obvious’ https://t.co/XnjAVefbIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see initiatives like thetrustproject getting more discussion after election. https://t.co/NN6VLdsLPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddt until the AI starts building the next generations of itself! Not too far off that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craignewmark I think @timoreilly was suggesting FB &amp; Goog are capable of inventing a truth algorithm. Or at least ways to detect falsehoods]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As well as a truth algorithm, I'd like to see Facebook, Google et al work on ways to present diff points of view. A 'pov spectrum' tool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great suggestions here: "build algorithms that take into account “truth” as well as popularity" https://t.co/ErlNIZaMEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing this year's (!!) sci-fi big movie -&gt; Ted Chiang, the science fiction genius behind Arrival https://t.co/F4kiEKE9yU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiffrMedia I saw that you're building a product, which is def what's needed. I'd suggest crowdfunding approach, to get $$ + users/support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh sh*t... Like Bowie, he produced an amazing album before his death. Give it a listen today... https://t.co/3yhxsS0VSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiffrMedia do you have an example of a counter opinion from one of those researchers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We need to embrace, even relish, our legacy as malcontents and troublemakers..." https://t.co/8fqFuypt6V via @cjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The media industry needs to take responsibility for its role in producing spectacle for selfish purposes" @zephoria https://t.co/N7HXG7d66V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now there’s a great word: Homophily (i.e., "love of the same") is the tendency of individuals to associate and bond with similar others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The rise in influence of social media, particularly Facebook, have contributed to greater polarization and homophi… https://t.co/8xw8OgozZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure it's no accident that this thing has just one eye. The state of social media, folks. #selfishmedia https://t.co/UMiedelQ0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to hearing more about this. https://t.co/HwG9uvaIds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legacy of Doug Engelbart should always be celebrated. Happy 70th to SRI. https://t.co/S3RmqAxyAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great post by @fmanjoo. I'd add that our industry must build better listening tools. We have too many talking tools. https://t.co/F5cUo4vAAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aza starting with not misspelling your name Aza! Sorry :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aza absolutely, please keep me in the loop and I'll help if I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be great to get more smart people like Asa experimenting with new social tools. I'll try and come up with ide… https://t.co/FGTmBYT1Eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps it should also react by building new tools to replace our useless 'Selfish Media' tools. We talked too much… https://t.co/dp52hqLeSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News media is broken (and social media too, in my view) -&gt; A ‘Dewey Defeats Truman’ Lesson for the Digital Age https://t.co/1PtcdB53hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left = comedians, right = President; "reality-based  community [...] is what I based most of The Colbert Report on"… https://t.co/MY7vXr0L2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes have to say that's been great. Also I'm a huge fan of their podcasts. Just think their live odds tonight were r… https://t.co/BTULPGVAX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to agree with this. He forgot to mention that the Twitterati amplified (and added insults to) the exit polls a… https://t.co/205K1mTM9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other side of the coin. https://t.co/9XwrjFtfRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxogles @FiveThirtyEight yes, they're not yet counting Florida. But they'll have to review that policy in the aftermath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT's "best guess" is now 94% probability Trump wins. @FiveThirtyEight still has Clinton ahead at 50% chance. Love the site, but c'mon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time @FiveThirtyEight has Trump favored to win. NYT currently has his odds at 87%!! #holyshite https://t.co/mStHK6kEeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity I recently re-read Heinlein's screenplay, er novel. Now that's a masterpiece! I liked the movie too, when it came out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly right! While I don't claim my novel is hard SF (or anywhere near as good as Snow Crash), I tried to extrapo… https://t.co/5AxVqaBX5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a month since I released Presence, my debut #scifi novel. Here are my learnings so far… https://t.co/WKF6Ck3DUm #indieauthor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest @BretEastonEllis podcast is up and this time it took him 38 minutes to let his guest talk. Gotta be a record :) Great monologue tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to agree with this. I recently upgraded my tv and was very disappointed Apple TV couldn't play UHD very well. https://t.co/j2d3liXIlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliotpeper @tacanderson what about you Eliot, any genres you think should have their own Amazon categories?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliotpeper @tacanderson well I’d prefer LitRPG had its own genre, so I could leap up the Cyberpunk charts! :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tacanderson it was a great image :) But also I'm fine with it being a romanticized past scifi term, it's just not relevant for today's sf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For #indieauthors, finding the right subgenre @AmazonKindle is a challenge. Esp when the best match is a 1980s term: https://t.co/jbyWAgBAwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The term #cyberpunk went out of style in the 1990s…so why is Amazon still using it as a subgenre of #sciencefiction? https://t.co/jbyWAgBAwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hadn't used Vine in a few years, but I did some great vids of my (now sadly passed) cat JackFrost back when. https://t.co/UQTVkpTste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was hanging out for an Air update, but this is disappointing from Apple. It's almost twice as expensive, when por… https://t.co/wV9dNSfKBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This roundup needs updating, @MacRumors: https://t.co/odWUInlTu7. So much for all the rumors around MacBook Air getting updated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re a member of #KindleUnlimited, you can download my scifi novel PRESENCE for free. It’s about future of #VR 
https://t.co/6aSZFeREfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyL_Owen @GGadney @SarahSuch Congrats Amy. But where can I buy your book? I can't find it anywhere on Amazon or elsewhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Needle-Free Dentistry" my fave. Yes please! -&gt; The 12 Most Important Health Innovations Of The Year https://t.co/sJ7SqpccQp via @Berci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mathewi @BillSeitz that would work great if it went very granular; e.g. best sci-fi novel about VR (it would be Snow Crash of course!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great deal for both. I regularly use Wirecutter for shopping  -&gt; NYT buying The Wirecutter for more than $30 million https://t.co/4dUcIOP2j6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrowing story Taylor, but thanks for putting it out there so others can learn. Hope you're doing well these days. https://t.co/AorXsYJxbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent, looking forward to this! https://t.co/ZYXKO40BkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WIN 1 of 5 paperback copies of my beautifully designed scifi novel, Presence. Enter @goodreads:… https://t.co/y2YTJyhTwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan_Rowinski I still haven’t worked out how to do that economically, given my constant Geographic challenges.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>