<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalidBugatti then she's trippin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn this is me tho https://t.co/Utp0CHoU5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeratjilani @Yilmzx @NzoJilani what you call him now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asyed1995 bet I'll make sure you won't see another day after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close call.. who knew what woulda happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm walking to my car after class and this white girl comes up to me randomly and asks me if I was Muslim, I replied saying "nope." Phew 😓]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn I feel this on another level 
mtariq01 add me on snap holla https://t.co/vDyLSOe4qK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lion was such a good movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao this is live af. I love that guy 😂 https://t.co/JuLUohbMbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlafield tbh it's pretty hot rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ahoss24 @SameerIrfan2 wtf is Donald trump the dajjal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaanezehra SC it so I can watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJ_10Q @MaryneeLahaye that's so live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 hours until this game set match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeratjilani you and my moms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeratjilani these girls w followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But get likes, they think they're poppin but nah bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of these girls who have a little extra followers and get a few extra likes have it in over there head. They say the dumbest shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, I really want a @Nukdabomb jersey... 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how the Justice league would feel as trump as president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too. Fck it https://t.co/ZeZ9UZAH1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthew McConaughey needs to fr make a quick come back to romcoms..genres dying without him real t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate twitter sometimes man. always bitchin about something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Saadrahman21 I honestly don't mind man I'm just excited to see the two in the finals. But if I HAD to choose I'd go with Federer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus v Serena nadal v Federer wow. It's late 2000s again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg I've been waiting ages for a Federer v Nadal match. Never thought it would happen again 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeratjilani your so hot when you say big words 👅💦💦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; Found treasure during juvie https://t.co/YFFsvy5iej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Roberts in the 90s was fiiiooooioinnee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Akhtar @asyed1995 find this man a girl broooooooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for suits tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kash102892 @Complex I swear I thought it was t pain for a few seconds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AishaZamann @_Levantine this is so cute 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aestheticmadz I'm one of the Houston feminist hoes that didn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn I wonder how many of the these Houston feminist hoes marched for women today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald trumps first day in office and already uniting people #womensmarch really is making America great again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DizzyNotScared that's alotta carbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abe Lincoln thinking about resurrecting 😭 https://t.co/HgaTrLWvDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They really gotta promote this shit right now 😳 https://t.co/HIAsUIYCJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Donald took that shit like a champ 😭 https://t.co/kj7UHApW43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the most live guy I've seen after retirement 😂 https://t.co/AirEbVTxxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asyed1995 your future wife about to future leave you after reading your twitter timeline 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed sheerans the nigga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfaoo this is the funniest shit I've seen 😭 https://t.co/StJ0J5KvGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao that's def uncle drew https://t.co/u94EI5cig8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameerIrfan2 @J4CKMULL lmfaoooo bc he's tall skinny and slender we all look and move alike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asyed1995 you're a wizard Aamir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOOOOO Sameer felt so guilty of eating a pizooke so this nigga went home and FORCED himself to puke I'm so dead 😭😭😭😭😭😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zaman_Azhar @SomeDudeRJ how'd it take you so long bro my eyes went straight to the controller smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfaooo this is funny as shit "Real Housewives of ISIS" https://t.co/Ux4q68L1Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was so beautiful to watch https://t.co/55P4Uffs6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMSOJANJUA he's probably a germaphobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamshaChisty how's your winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmaooo his built isn't fair https://t.co/68eDgPNj1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lmfao Waleed this the funniest shit I've seen 😂 https://t.co/YGrI51EZzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronda Rousey took those punches like a champ tho.. she did not wanna fall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarib940 LMFAO fml imy come back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahmedaly_18 lmao my dudes looking at some booty at the gym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn I'm wondering why coach wouldn't have them help.. https://t.co/yFmJjFP56E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameerIrfan2 lmfao ur such a fob 😭 ily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like to point out that kobes kyries mentor..he must be proud https://t.co/rStZapEH11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They played lebroms song and he wants in!!! put the man in!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Hibakhan @thehorrorpics what the fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mahekkkhan ofc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMSOJANJUA he's a YouTube star, probably made the situation bigger than it was. Another thing for people to cry about on social media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidrahabibkhan @Mediaite ya guess we have no way of knowing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably what really happened https://t.co/6JS4RO5vS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mute option on twitter is clutch af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw she apologized :') https://t.co/Ll0hcUKsGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao delta got fucked lmao played with a dude w a bangin YouTube account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaanezehra @HBCU_Roundtable Shaanes always ready to throw hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMSOJANJUA the show canceled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Real_SalimShady what channel in paki do live sports come on bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaanezehra @AIDSgov @Africa @aidspatient it's not a joke when you have it 😪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaanezehra millions of people suffer every year Shaane. And you're here making jokes @AIDSgov @africa @aidspatient]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I panicked, but remembered it was water proof and left. It. There. 😎😎😎😎😎😎😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just dropped my iPhone 7 in the toilet 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalSherry ow ow ow it hurts so bad 😩😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tehaumaster @TheWalkingDead @WalkingDead_AMC @AMC_TV oh god that pose ooooooohh god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_rizwaan thanks Rizzy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baseeratj imy brat we need too!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man Chris brown cuts it up in his new video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamalSherry thanks I will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SameerIrfan2 LOOOOOL accurate af 😂 thanks brotha I love ya man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebrownboi97 LMAO! Thanks bro 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingtaha19 thanks buddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJ_10Q 😂😂😂 thanks man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asyed1995 lmaoo I'm looking forward to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battlafield he fits the role way better from what it seems. He's much younger, I think he'll be a lot closer than the other two were]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carol is such a fckin badass on TWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahl_b10 "ur man" Sahl bro we get it. He's your neighbor smh 😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke Waltons doing a decent job as coach good for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the rocks instagram. Everything on there's is motivational af. I love the rock in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaanezehra apparently the official UH brown people party/ hangout planner...😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live af. How it should be. https://t.co/N9QbwX4Ga4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaadAziz94 😂 lmaoo I can imagine you laughing while people stare at u like "fcks wrong w this guy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J cole spits in that clip man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone ever act like they got a funny txt but really you pulled ur phone out bc u didnt wanna look like an idiot laughing at your thoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most simple inventions that have the biggest effect: back scratchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeratjilani @S1dharthM what the fuck Seerat?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>