<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary how the simplest of fundraising ideas can connect with so many people. Congrats @macmillancoffee. https://t.co/HKCNBjE5ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of an era. @GrantStottOnAir will be a big miss @forthone. A radio and panto legend. https://t.co/xoHVBYlQ9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant programme for budding business people. https://t.co/9CKhG5AQAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity to join the board of @TeamWestLothian. They do invaluable work in promoting the area. https://t.co/o0n9G8bdZT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scvotweet At this rate you will have to move the event from the SECC to Hampden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved recognition for Roger and the team at the Penicuik Community Alliance after years of hard work. https://t.co/zU2K9d4Hda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite defeat, an unbelievable effort from all involved @Bonnyriggrose81. Let's now go on and win the Junior Cup. https://t.co/T6XLIqTsjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks As a manager you plan all week &amp; create a perfect tactical plan. Must be soul destroying when players don't execute it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an uplifting story. Another example of residents in a community delivering vital services. https://t.co/76F2hTwWRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some amazing cafes doing incredible work. None more so than West Lothian's excellent @lardercooking. https://t.co/P2nPdaP1vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I always suspected, having more connected communities and reducing social isolation benefits the economy. https://t.co/HJbVgZW3kW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophyRidgeSky Fair play to John Bercow. If I was sitting in the chair all day, I would also try and find ways to keep myself amused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cat_Headley Indeed, I fear the next #indyref will be fought through the prism of asking people which institution they feel closer to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cat_Headley As someone who voted Yes, I would most likely vote No this time. The case for independence is far weaker economically now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BroadcastMoose Don't know when you find time to rest, Moose. You are on the Breakfast Show every morning and a footie match most nights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting times ahead. Would love to be a fly on the wall during these negotiations with the EU. https://t.co/mq78QOd6R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see the Scottish Government continue to support communities and the third sector. https://t.co/JXrDRQqdCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Previously worked on a project that faced many difficulties. The response from @socinvestscot was always supportive… https://t.co/hbYoVak8aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing moment. Richly deserved award for Joe Biden. https://t.co/8Gx6IGGqH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent blog highlighting the importance of befriending in reducing loneliness and isolation. https://t.co/IZbzJ4be9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic article in the @LocalPeopleLead newsletter from the team at @Scotregen looking at alternatives to SIMD. https://t.co/389dyR967p.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations. It looks like an excellent and well attended event. https://t.co/s2EpF8h9I2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incredibly thoughtful and personal piece. The number of people affected by mental health issues is growing. Govt… https://t.co/ueg14UTI9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality advert. I loved watching Football Italia on a Saturday morning. https://t.co/VCxmsEDsZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news for Scottish communities. https://t.co/D6MX8uCiAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love a roundtable discussion with Barry, Kris and @GrahamSpiers on PLG. Graham's book on this subject is outs… https://t.co/50vPyDjQ2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bonnyriggrose81 Will the tickets be available on any other day. I can't make it to NDP today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to think that three of the biggest pop stars of the 80s, George Michael, Prince &amp; Michael Jackson all died before they were 60.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very late to the party on this, but this article analysing the history of community regeneration is fascinating. https://t.co/2BL5Lm0PiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bold move from Michael Sheen. https://t.co/mryB4cyyC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever puts together the #bbctw opening and closing videos deserves an award. The Snowman video with Aled Jones is tremendous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Tman10 The system doesn't help him, but he is essentially a striker who doesn't score any goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFC_Charity @alzscot Heard all about the amazing work that Football Memories does at a meeting this week. It is a fantastic project]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terracepodcast @DuncMcKay A truly outstanding piece of writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very thoughtful piece from Martin Sime. Communities have to play a role in delivering social care. https://t.co/YPjcfKPveR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading this. https://t.co/BXUdW4aDfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BT Sport proving once again it has the best football coverage. @chris_sutton73 is spot on that Cathro deserves a ch… https://t.co/uSrcD9bAzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great topic from @MichelleDewbs. Technology is changing the workplace. Politicians need to look long term to re-skill people. #thepledge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCrawfordBBC Hope you'll be at the game to produce another one of your excellent videos, Kenny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some top tips from Tim from @WoodlandTrust on the art of fundraising. The story of their project is so inspiring. #communitiesinthecentre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some incredible opportunities available to communities through the new Community Empowerment Act. #communitiesinthecentre @Dtascot_COSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all involved with @Bonnyriggrose81. A well deserved win. Dumbarton were lucky not to have lost the first game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very depressing to discover that the new Hearts manager is younger than me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone who criticises politicians should watch #MPsBehindClosedDoors. Every week MPs help people with complex problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks Much improved performance today, but classic case of goals changing games. Aberdeen well on top at the start of the 2nd half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaudrupsHair That was one of the newspapers favourite transfer rumours. Every season Jess was supposed to be signing for Rangers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pieandbov Nothing Cammy Bell likes better than a penalty to save.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainDale Could an argument not be made that he was already preaching to the converted in that constituency. 69% voted Remain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great win for the Lib Dems in Richmond. Though, surely not a vote against Brexit when 69% of people already voted Remain in that area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSportScot @KCrawfordBBC All of these videos from the Bonnyrigg game are outstanding. Gives a great glimpse of the atmosphere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRock All your success is thoroughly deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@90sfootball Best programme on a Saturday morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks Very strange tactics today. Aberdeen are wide open. Forrest ran for miles unchallenged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryHassan Nothing better than an afternoon watching junior football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terracepodcast @DuncMcKay Outstanding piece. Listened to the podcast last night &amp; almost choked on my water when Chic suggested Jim Duffy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic news. https://t.co/NWT189kby8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomCommentator Good luck with the launch. Looking forward to reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrymcculloch1 Remember that guy who called in a couple of weeks ago and predicted Brown would return after speaking to him at a function.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange to hear Jeremy Paxman giving his thoughts as a commentator rather than an interviewer, but really enjoying his insights. #theagenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsabelHardman Look after yourself and get well soon. As a self confessed political geek, I always enjoy your reasoned &amp; balanced analysis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland Rangers are only two points behind Hearts with 27 league games left. So, now is definitely not the time to get rid of Mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland We'll see, but Mark deserves the full season to try and get second place. October isn't the time to sack him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland Even if they are well beaten today, there are 27 league games left. If they finish second, he gets another season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland Untenable is a bit strong. An assessment will be made at the end of the season to see what progress Rangers have made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone would think that Nick Clegg is still leader of the Lib Dems. Heard far more from him on Brexit than Tim Farron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant comments from Tom Hanks. https://t.co/4VPKZaDIhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An absolutely riveting interview. Very jealous of @JananGanesh getting to have lunch with my favourite director… https://t.co/xtpyPWNFOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A triumphant return. #StillGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks Being a Gers &amp; Scotland fan I hope he develops, but he has to improve his concentration levels. A mistake never seems far away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks It shows the lack of talent in Scotland if he's considered to be the future. No pace &amp; flounders without experience beside him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling inspired after speaking to some incredible people at the @WL_SEN dinner. Thanks to Fiona and Colin for the invitation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pieandbov Should be a good game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A truly inspiring day spent talking about the social benefits of sport at the @HolyroodEvents conference. #sportcomm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing to hear the work that @HibsOfficial are doing in trying to tackle health inequalities in Edinburgh. #sportcomm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a Labour supporter, but this is quality from Tom Watson. Rightly citing the highlights of the Labour govt. https://t.co/8EtShiGbJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland Excellent. Good to hear a positive story about Scottish football for once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There won't be a better game all weekend than Dunfermline v St Mirren. The epitome of end to end football. Thank you @bbcalba.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only hope that Labour has now is for Theresa May to call a quick General Election. It will be the only way to get rid off Corbyn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great work from @btsportfootball here. They prove again that their football coverage is much better than Sky. https://t.co/KZDQlnlxg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some unbelievable quotes in this article. Not sure if Barton is just being honest or is trying deliberately to get… https://t.co/YIq2NtwNDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every ground should have this pre-match. https://t.co/GKzvD40okV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprised that Joey Barton is up to his old tricks. Always worried that he would ruin the balance of the team both on and off the park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No doubt there will be an inquest about the state of Scottish football following Celtic's loss. Fact is that the financial gap is too wide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure that it will have the same format, but can't see #GBBO working on Channel 4. It is the quintessential BBC programme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time watching a full episode of @ThePledge. A really fun format with a relaxed way of talking about current affairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pieandbov Really surprised at their slow start to the season as they have experienced players. Finished last season strongly under Rae.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks Central midfielders and wingers by the dozen, but no commanding central defenders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know why anyone is surprised by that Senderos red card. He has been making the same mistakes his entire career. #OldFirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is undoubtedly the best episode of #ScotlandsGame so far. Wonderful archive footage of Scotland games from the 80s and 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks a fantastic cause and well worth doing.  https://t.co/ivz4wSfJat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holmleapark @FitbaHacks @RangersCulture Reyna put in an unbelievable shift as a makeshift right back during the 1999-2000 season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant to hear about the fantastic food and gardening projects being delivered by @greenerkdy. So many great ideas to ponder. #dtas16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating opening plenary of #dtas16. Some eye-opening stats from @nourishscotland on the levels of food insecurity in the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbaHacks Another brilliant guest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing that development trusts are generating over £21 million of trading income. A huge contribution to local economies. #DTAS16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An inspiring visit to @wcdtgarden. A great way to kick off #DTAS16. https://t.co/37pmHSQdPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again the needs of television more important than the fans. https://t.co/gVaixNsSd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New favourite podcast is @fitbahacks after binge listening to it over the weekend. A must for anyone with a love of Scottish football.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to read the book that Jeremy Corbyn will inevitable write about his time as Labour leader. #traingate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekMackaySNP @scotgov @StirUni I went to Stir Uni. The grounds are stunning no matter the season.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>