<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryback22 fancy going one on one with my mate @thomo7483 he reckons he would get the 1-2-3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This transfer window has been so underwhelming would love for us to sign a dominant CB and an out and out goalscorer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 @OrangeBunnet you no seen the birds in it bunnet???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 it's gutting we never seen them go head to head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 orton deserves another push he is better than he has been getting recently! But that cunt cena????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 but to give that cunt @JohnCena  another title is the biggest joke of the lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 not overly bothered Orton won, but this whole Goldberg continually embarrassing Lesnar it's a joke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 @divybhoy1888 reptile bastard of a boy he is but still a good cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 @Shaz_15 @KirstyBryce I can't do it anymore I'm in a bad bad way! I can't even remember going home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 he is up there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So had to go to opticians today so took the bird to M&amp;S cafe for a early lunch! Ya fucker need a loan after that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iammcintosh na doubt it I unfortunately rate your full back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iammcintosh ha ha ha ha aye that was start of last season before he had to defend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 he must be injured he isn't even on the bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@albl75 the only thing I think he offers is pace, his crossing is abysmal, not overly skilful. But I hope he proves me wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 in fact he is like a man down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 he looked decent going forward last season, shocking defender but offers nothing at all now playing at a higher level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@albl75 he is a better option than MOH, he has better control, skill, more of a goal threat! Don't think Waghorn is great but better MOH tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously don't see what MW does in Tavernier!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And MOH starting ahead of Waghorn is a mystery. Has hardly played him all season can only think he is putting MOH in the shop window]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Hodson injured?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markbrownser @thomo7483 @Karen_Conway doing the smeato while singing the sash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 here we go again head buried in the sand again! come back to the real world! 1.8m for a striker who doesn't score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 should have been a great signing just look how he plays with Burnley! But MW system is flawed but no cunt admits it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 Garner, Signing on fees Barton, Senderos, Kranjcar! Rossiter wages cunts no been fit in years! All adds up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 naw but are not performing as well as they should be &amp;we are spunking the money we are spending on not good enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 I am a realist not a dreamer when a player performs well I will praise them but I'll slaughter them if deserves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 here I've no heard you commenting on the return of your Mickie James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 when they haven't seen him anaw but claim to watch all his games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 @ClaireyMac24 naw you get all excited if we sign sum cunt nobody has heard about because some boy on the internet said he is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karen_Conway @thomo7483 @markbrownser I shall be making an appearance after trainspotting 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 hardly if they are not good enough I will say rather than make out they are quality and they are also under performing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 aye he is lazy but he is better than anyone else we have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORTDrive Nonsense you are talking about Mourinho Adrian! He has won 23 trophies including 2 champions leagues!! What has he to prove?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT the owner of Blackpool sounds totally and utterly delusional! The quicker Blackpool get rid of the better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 aye I agree! It's in a mess the now depending on Taker, Goldberg and Lesnar for Rumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueBoyRFC72 exactly the point I've been trying to make! He should be given a bit part deal or even a player/youth coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS but we should be getting more out of what we have a 2-3 high quality signings make the difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS Aye I'm not saying they aren't im saying there two main players were there major signings which have taken to the next level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGPBFB he offers more than MOH, has more quality than Garner, Forrester seems to pick and choose when he can be bothered so best option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS I'm not saying they ain't a good team but it's Sinclair and Dembele who make the real difference with there quality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkovanbasten &amp; let's be honest he hasn't been a world beater his career just a good solid pro so should be achievable for better quality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkovanbasten he should get a deal but as an impact player we should be signing someone better and a younger age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JorgAlbertz1872 I don't think the system fits the players. Joey Barton is a prime example of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JorgAlbertz1872 MOH offers very little other than pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGPBFB and Miller did score two goals, first one was a cracking ball from Waghorn and 2nd was quick thinking on the part of hyndman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CraigGPBFB I think Waghorn is lazy but I think he offers something that nobody else does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkovanbasten  I do feel it's sad reflection on the rest of the squad if it wasn't for him and hill we would be in a terrible position]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkovanbasten we can't keep praying that his age doesn't catch up on him because it happens to everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parkovanbasten im not saying he hasn't been good but this give him a 2yr deal, most important signing is crap, we need to replace him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS they not as good as everyone thinks,they made 2 major signings that make difference. We should be getting more out what we have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JorgAlbertz1872 also true but I felt it was a Waghorn who changed the game, should be starting as he offers another dimension we don't have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS you are joking? Some of the performances have been horrific it's a sad state of affairs our two best players are over 35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've nothing against the man but we need to be building a new team not revolving it around a 37yr old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JorgAlbertz1872 he did, but he done nothing at all before that, even missed a decent chance which he didn't even connect with the ball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS and I haven't overly rated him as a player his entire career I think it's a reflection on how bad the rest have been]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WATPLOYALS he is one of the few but it's time to start looking to replace him rather than keep relying on him, his legs will go soon enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 that is a sad reflection on the rest of our mid. goes missing in games then gets injured if hull bid 1.5 I would drive him myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't understand this love in for Miller at minute. He is 37yr old we need to look to future and it was Waghorn who changed the game on sat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 would you pay that for someone who offers nothing, shown nothing other than gets injured every 3rd game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no danger Hull have bid 1.5m for Windass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DS_dieci @talkSPORT they won't be able to attract a better manager, they are a striker, CB and a GK away from being a good team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT what an overreaction for today regarding Liverpool, it's a bad spell nothing else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 I might come over and watch it if I'm back from the opticians in time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 are the mighty Broxburn at home on Saturday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 I can't believe I just seen that Paul Scholes only got 66 caps for England that's a tragedy. Best English player I've seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 @ClaireyMac24 they do cracking cheese and ham sandwiches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireyMac24 @thomo7483 that would be better as it would keep out the wanks in brox as it is higher class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireyMac24 @thomo7483 I have told him about 18months ago it was a Tesco and I stand by my information]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 @ClaireyMac24 doubts about what ha ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 mate your presence much drive the house prices up in that postcode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyBryce wee Sherlock with a skinhead https://t.co/MQW611i3YK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 here mate your bit must be the best area in Brox, Tesco, pub, Chinese and a bakers and your neighbours have the Benefit of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not ideal another Loan but need another CB as we are hopeless at the back and he is better than what we have even if he is 18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 sound and I have arranged for taxi kirsty to collect us from a public house later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeys93 I'm no even going there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 a week on Saturday our mission to Edinburgh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And they wonder why Scottish football is a laughing stock. The state of Rod Stewart doing the cup draw fucking embarrassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 and he has a Celtic tattoo on his ankle absolute tit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divybhoy1888 I'm working and would rather go swimming with sharks than watch that shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divybhoy1888 you going to watch that horrible shower of terrorist sympathisers today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divybhoy1888 no worries hope you are dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 rough?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 some boy walked into the gym has snp badges all over his bag, goes into change and he comes out with Republic Ireland top on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireyMac24 9.30am at pure gym don't be late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 good day yesterday that man smeaton?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spanisharjenrob I was going to cash out but thought fuck it nobody will blow it as all the teams were up by at least 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aston Villa are the officially the biggest cunts in world football 2-0 up the coupon was up and they go throw away  a 2 goal lead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertford I thought he was shocking until he scored as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 good son pished!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomo7483 how's the brox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's a sad state of affairs when a 37yr old keeps bailing you out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know we won but that was woeful, took going 1 down to show any kind of urgency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our centre forward is never in and around the areas he should be either it's all about fucking possession around the box it's a shambles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There keeper hasn't had a save to make!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not even surprised in the slightest can't defend cross balls and we create fuck all. We learn fuck all it's fucking grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must be the only team who when we break, we actually slow the play down when we get to the edge of the box]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't even think there has been a shot on target yet. Severe lack of quality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is some grim stuff can't believe only 22mins gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha ha wtf is that https://t.co/yiKVqWCJjB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>