<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@kachninja @KamVTV Well the @SenateDems are doing our job for them.  We will now be able to put EVERY Trump candidate in office!!  Good job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I truly believe he is a VERY big part of all this Senate democrats idiotic moves, as well as the "protests" which a… https://t.co/LYblvHRACh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce AND was an Obama move before he left office.  They should be sent back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC @Clear_Honesty And the CA police let them get away with all!  Stood by and watched - 1 arrest!!  CA is totally out of control!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems - THE PEOPLE WILL REMEMBER and we are fed up with your obstruction.  VOTING YOU ALL OUT NEXT ELECTION!  Get ready!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if those coward @SenateDems are getting their pay check when they are NOT DOING THEIR JOB and boycotting hearings? #nopayforthem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPuma2072 No, I believe in telling the truth...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPuma2072 oops - but you like the good stuff!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Latinos4Trump16 I disagree. we NEED SCHOOL CHOICE because the Fed Dept of Ed has totally destroyed the current education system!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrPuma2072 OK - you're talking my generation Mr. Puma...   Some good ol days &amp; some bad ol days..... ha ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hummmm --- Me thinks Obama is behind much of the democrat's blowing themselves up now!!  Fine... So much more to vo… https://t.co/vbGpbvzNp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needs to happen!!!  The democrats are so out of touch with the American People and need to resign or be voted OUT!!! https://t.co/GxbZJMZrwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bfraser747 This is horrible.  Our immigration  system always was about people coming in needed to assimilate. 8 Yrs of Obama changed it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is a "strange" person. https://t.co/GddtsMJqfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coffeeblogger1 I'll follow you cause you are not Starbucks!!  Thanks for following me.  Look forward to your tweets.... with my coffee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi - but then again, maybe U don't even know what is in the Constitution since you and the democrats seem to skirt it constantly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi Supreme Court Judge interprets THE CONSTITUTION.  Not 2 stop people from drinking water, breathing air or eat food - idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heritage I'm sure it is on @POTUS "to do" list!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw  (D) Joe Manchen on @FoxBusiness ACTUALLY putting down Harry Reid &amp; some of the other "current" Democrats for their actions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leaha_Luv @ThePatriot143 @PressSec He sure changed his whole view point after becoming President!  Guess he remembered who votes for Dimms!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarsLarsonShow Great questions!!  Especially about the forest's.  It is time for us to use our own wood instead of letting it burn!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @jaketapper  You guys are getting pretty well known with Trump fans! https://t.co/16Te9rp8Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jojoh888 @carrieksada Hopefully the remaining REPUBLICANS will stand up and stop this. CA is so out of control!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolinagirl63 @LifeZette YES WE DO. Tried with McCain last year-big money won apparently.  WE PLAN TO REPLACE @JeffFlake w/ @DrKelliWard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffFlake You are going to be replaced in 2018.  Between you and McCain, we in AZ sure made a BIG mistake!! https://t.co/bQR7MoU8KE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After all - he is staying in DC (not because of his daughter's school), but to interfere most likely with his "shad… https://t.co/Lj4ZoUl9yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many of you think @BarackObama is behind all of @TheDemocrats slow walking, interfering, &amp; subterfuge of R new President? Me thinks so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems to me that this dork is about as illegal as George Soros!  They both incite anarchy.... which is ILLEGAL and… https://t.co/JGRWBp7bLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And can we STOP the current illegals taking welfare and every other free stuff!!???  Especially CA! https://t.co/iWROXsAE63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ I think they are just afraid, because Trump is a PRESIDENT that does something.  They sucked up to Obama and he did NOTHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CassandraRules @CamilleGtine @TheDemocrats These people are acting like High School Kids and better wake up- some will be gone in 2018!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats need to get their "crap" together and start doing their jobs.  Lot's of states who vt for Trump will be voting you OUT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ @CBSLA Fine - no federal money, no help for anything!  Hopefully no voting  either!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexisinNH @Rockprincess818 @ScottWalker If they R not doing their JOBS - they need 2 resign or we need to get them out of office! #BanDems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America was always about brining in legal immigrants and assimilate to be part of this country!  I am more worried… https://t.co/I0ezGYaUfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats - obstructionists. Anarchrist @georgesoros should be put in jail. Did anyone see Republicans do this against Obama?  NO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer - did you cry for the hundreds of thousands of Christians that were killed in Syria + which Obama did n… https://t.co/PE1K7Eh5f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruthSeeker____ @YouTube  The Governor in CA specifically stated that illegals could vote.  We heard it, and all you had to do was pay attn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rockprincess818  Was @SenSchumer crying when hundreds of thousands of CHRISTIANS were killed in middle east because Obama did NOTHING?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer - How many Christians in Middle East  were killed by Obama doing NOTHING?  ARE YOU CRYING FOR THEM?  Stop your lies and help!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeTurner212 @RealJamesWoods @realDonaldTrump @GOP @seanspicer @FT SOROS needs 2 be REMOVED from our country, just like Europe &amp; others did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1VirtualPixie @KNP2BP @newsmax  KICK HIM OUT OF THE COUNTRY!  Europe and many other countries did after the destruction he did to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChuckShumer What do ya think???   How you going to vet??   Never mind, you just continue to spread your lies. https://t.co/SlJjIfKdhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov @FoxNewsSunday - Chris Wallace..... maybe you should read this!  And then start telling the truth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChuckSchumer - you seem to be more concerned about everything except AMERICANS!!  How much more terrorism do you want to see?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Westxgal @bfraser747  - Gee --- and we were thinking about a vacation to Iran..... ha ha ha!  Probably would never be able to come home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pastorbones @KNP2BP @nytimes My question is .. Are the lobbyists still giving money to bribe Congress???  They sure seem to get rich fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls GREAT job on @FoxNewsSunday!  You have a tough job but you do it WELL! You GO GIRL!!!  We are all behind you &amp; President!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @PJMedia_com America needs to BAN SOROS from our country.  He is funding the Anarchy.  Europe &amp; other countries have BANNED HIM!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKStahlUSA  I read that even people in her state don't like her.  Hopefully she will be one of the many democrats who don't get elected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenBookerOffice  - YOU ARE A SENATOR  Do you even KNOW WE HAVE LAWS ON THE BOOKS? Immigrants come to the USA LEGALLY not illegally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weimer_suzanne @jstines3  The bottom line is.... We have laws!  We need to work within our laws.  People come to our country legally only!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCoon4 @CamilleGtine @BreitbartNews Soros was kicked out in Europe and other places, and SHOULD BE BANNED FROM THE USA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow - I need to tell all my friends to not vacation over there!  And we were so looking forward to it!!😎 https://t.co/vntMVuceXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is well today? https://t.co/XeyFVYMAcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConstanceQueen8 @TruthFeedNews  - Whatever!  Like CAIR above board anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trish_regan  - Didn't think LIBERALS believed in Religion!!!  They seem to constantly stand AGAINST it - except Muslims????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @billpostmus  And yet he has ONLY BEEN IN OFFICE 1 week!  Nice going Jake- still putting out stupid untruths.  Get over yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Democrats @HouseDemocrats  It would be really great if you bunch of liars decided to do the right thing for our co… https://t.co/hhOkZO9S63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi - HOW MANY WOMEN AND CHILDREN have come here from Middle East???  All we have seen is young single men going to Europe &amp; US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can't believe it is 31 years ago!  I remember exactly where I was and what I was doing.  So sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPartyOrg So they"repealed" O-Care how many times? But NOT ONE REPUBLICAN worked on a REPLACEMENT? They only care about re-election!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tamara - thank your for sharing your article.  You were blessed with one baby. BUT your other baby is with GOD. Tha… https://t.co/YkgRIMOvZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sorry to hear that.  But you did the right thing to continue and you have a wonderful child now!  God Bless! https://t.co/JGO5yddOv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretBaier  @"Leslie"-EVERYONE has access to BIRTH CONTROL-free or low cost - What is wrong with Women not using it if they don't want baby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs Why did Republicans NOT work on a plan to REPLACE O-care? After they "repealed how many times?" So now they don't know what to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElishivaAhmose My favorite -   Rush @limbaugh  But I agree with you - I never watch mainstream either.  Do like @LouDobbs  - Fox Business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @FoxNews  So then they can't vote... right?   #TheDemocrats will never again be in the White House!  Go for it CA!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElishivaAhmose When Barbara Walters was there, it was halfway good.  But even SHE is now saying it is disgusting and doesn't watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForTrump - did you get my message?  I am not a snowflake, I live in a town called Snowflake.President Trump is the only one to use name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheDemocrats - #HouseDemocrats  are so out of touch.  This is why they have lost SO MANY seats in States, House &amp;… https://t.co/WaRjVl6BYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am NOT a snowflake.  I live in Snowflake, AZ!  I voted Trump and believe he is the only one to USE HIS TITLE! https://t.co/ur9CZnxmhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForTrump  I don't believe you should be using "President Trump"  Please change your ID and let our NEW President have his title ONLY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shezz1511 @KNP2BP @QThePinkYoshi @soccermom818 @LeahR77 The get free everything, medical, welfare, jobs paid in CASH - pay no taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell I thought Trump Administration  could fire them and replace???  Guess not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom AND they already built a wall on their Southern Border!!!  So that's a lie from them!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaySekulow Shouldn't the Mayors of those Sanctuary cities be fined or go to jail for NOT FOLLOWING Federal Laws and outright ignoring?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePatriot143 @TruthFeedNews The MAYORS protecting them is AGAINST THE LAW!  They need to go to Jail!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_America1776 @CamilleGtine Maybe she should go to the Middle East to practice what they do!!  Women are so loved over there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjauthor @graycsam Prayers for you and your family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @RichardGrenell He needs to go to jail with all the other Mayors ignoring the laws of the Federal Government!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell Any Mayor protecting illegals - Sanctuary Cities, should be put in JAIL  for NOT FOLLOWING THE FEDERAL LAWS!! Enough already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Sanctuary Cities protect the illegal criminals - I think the MAYOR should be charged with not OBEYING THE FED LAWS! They should go 2 jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One item the NEW Dept of EDUCATION needs to stop!! https://t.co/ciIsFM0eKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Obama, being an Imperial president walked all over the laws on our books.  Why he is celebrated is beyond me!… https://t.co/Tg2iutB4Rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillPowers9  It is time for @ShepNewsTeam to leave FOX NEWS and move to @CNN - @NBC or any other liberal channel!  He acts like a democrat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asamjulian @jaketapper You might check out California Mr. Tapper.  THE GOVERNOR came out and said he would let illegal's vote!!  Check it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, as long as they are "rich" and the rest of the little people are struggling for jobs and better pay... they ar… https://t.co/n7JUBEndY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomFitton - unbelievable - We need everyone to vote - but it needs to be LEGAL. That means Voter ID!!!  But we know there is so much fraud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just keep digging themselves into the gutter.  958 den seats lost in St. Legis. 10 Senate, 63 House --- all in… https://t.co/VXbcoml7Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cure, as far as I am concerned, is to send them to every socialist country around the world.  I'm sure they wd… https://t.co/BBgu1usvOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @KamVTV @realDonaldTrump @POTUS We need to SMASH the GOVERNMENT UNIONS - i.e.: Vet hospitals, and all other's - Need to fire!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain  is on the WRONG side of Americans!!!!  You can add @JeffFlake  &amp; @marcorubio  to that side ALSO!! https://t.co/mYaAsR4PJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Telling the truth is all that is necessary!!  You did a great job and I believe informed so many more people!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hlOWtQ5Ml1  Everyone needs to read this.  Very scary @LouDobbs @DineshDSouza @AnnCoulter @realDonaldTrump   Pass it on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harleysandguns @tponews  - Yes - DEFUND Planned Parenthood.  American taxpayers do not want to support killing babies in womb!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardGrenell  - Well at least 62,million will not be watching!!  Who cares!!  I'm a bit concerned abt Fox News - I prefer Fox Business!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reince Good job on @FoxNewsSunday - even tho #ChrisWallace seems to think he knows everything! Pictures wrong &amp; on TV saw the real numbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday #ChrisWallace - you might want to read your FB page.  Apparently most of USA despise you and your view of #PresidentTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @DHecei @realDonaldTrump She is so great and loved her singing.  Beautiful girl!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>