<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer falsely accuses Iran of attacking U.S. Navy vessel, an act of war https://t.co/LIkTOraziI by @ZaidJilani @AlexanderEmmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch in His Youth: 'Fascism Forever' https://t.co/JDRGjC2mob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Longtime Doctor Says President Takes Hair-Growth Drug https://t.co/M4ofk0zSBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator asked Pentagon chief to give the war court his copy of CIA ‘Torture Report’ https://t.co/D1SUvBXb6X #TortureReport #Guantanamo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Picks Anti-Choice Federal Judge Neil Gorsuch for Supreme Court https://t.co/fFvHuVRGIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargotWilliams @micahflee @theintercept About OnionShare: How to use OnionShare to securely share private data  without leaving a trace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargotWilliams @micahflee @theintercept About #Tor onion services: How to host hidden websites using Tor onion services]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargotWilliams @micahflee @theintercept How to use BitTorrent to share your data with the public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How scientists can protect their data from the Trump administration https://t.co/moB2RM8c1p by @micahflee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In secret battle, #surveillance court reined in #FBI use of information obtained from phone calls https://t.co/b6OehJIDOx by @JennaMC_Laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennaMC_Laugh @ryantate yes the CURTILAGE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Blind Faith?" To Probe the Digital Defenses of Targets, the #FBI Turns To a Special Program https://t.co/NdgKehUWeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden loopholes allow #FBI agents to infiltrate political and religious groups https://t.co/eOtntYZ24W by @coracurrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #FBI has quietly investigated white supremacist infiltration of law enforcement https://t.co/6Zu3kADEUK by @alicesperi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In secret battle, surveillance court reined in #FBI use of information obtained from phone calls https://t.co/b6OehJIDOx by @JennaMC_Laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite anti-profiling rules, the #FBI uses race and religion when deciding who to target #profiling https://t.co/Ar8xg6J3Sb by @coracurrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undercover #FBI agents swarm the internet seeking contact with terrorists https://t.co/7H3tKJ8G2j by @coracurrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the #FBI conceals its payments to confidential sources #informants https://t.co/602tL5OQku by @trevoraaronson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When informants are no longer useful, the #FBI can help #ICE deport them https://t.co/A0GhSZKHOS by @trevoraaronson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #FBI gives itself lots of rope to pull in informants https://t.co/X5q8Nwbtrb by @trevoraaronson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret rules make it pretty easy for the #FBI to spy on journalists https://t.co/1FkM1U4WEM by @coracurrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret docs reveal: President Trump has inherited an FBI with vast hidden powers https://t.co/Bi1wNgsTDK by @ggreenwald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter really cranking out the "promoted" tweets tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump Is Already Showing Signs of Major Disrespect to the U.S. Military https://t.co/yoVzRfKHIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hill staffers secretly worked on Trump's immigration order https://t.co/AiiIbda779@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @MazMHussain reminding me of the first "reports" after the Oklahoma City bombing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in Quebec mosque attack depicted as a Moroccan Muslim. He's a white nationalist. https://t.co/IzRAkVWG4X by @ggreenwald @mazmhussain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library of Congress Card Catalog @atlasobscura https://t.co/Bmas9MQdRs Thanks for mention of my 1994 story on Gophering into LOC catalog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama killed a 16-year-old American in Yemen. Trump just killed his 8-year-old sister. https://t.co/4BhcbBDX1x by @ggreenwald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As protests escalate, Trump retreats from barring green card holders #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/NSJSsa9eDn by @RobertMackey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one for #Guantanamo in Yemen raid: Pentagon clarified that US service members had not taken prisoners https://t.co/MUy4pyqq0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made in China https://t.co/Be8ppOGPyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trevortimm when will the color codes come back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Mo Farah: ‘Queen made me a knight, Donald Trump made me an alien’ https://t.co/h8uUHA6dK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should officials resign when the government goes crazy? https://t.co/vrxGOgSwjO by @maassp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal court halts Trump's order barring Muslims after protesters swarm airports #MuslimBan https://t.co/TONBB5Y6fu by @RobertMackey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees Detained at U.S. Airports, Prompting Legal Challenges to Trump’s Immigration Order https://t.co/YlpMpDgCjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Coalition of Scientists Keeps Watch on the U.S. Government’s Climate Data https://t.co/rh6KrYJCqx by @AlleenBrown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bsnidermcgrath no, Margot Fonteyn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon Takes Control via @jeffersonmorley https://t.co/TiteKWg7Zp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compromise doesn't work with our political opponents. When will we learn? Chelsea Manning @xychelsea https://t.co/qfG6pqFyMK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration choosing to replace several senior State Department diplomats https://t.co/k7m8kcFJn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government scientists at U.S. climate conference terrified to speak with the press https://t.co/kO9Cg6mOyL by @fastlerner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned https://t.co/MpIGAriazu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guantánamo in the Trump era moves ahead in slow motion #Guantanamo https://t.co/C1ge4Miolg by @MargotWilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists' March on Washington: What is the Scientists' March on Washington https://t.co/Pstn2GbELS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's New #CIA Director Enters a Maelstrom at the Agency https://t.co/f9eM0x1O4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today on the playlist at RADIO GTMO #Guantanamo https://t.co/LjITqfP9sU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kentucky's new fetal pain law, like most abortion restrictions, is based on junk science https://t.co/5qOTsA0Xk2 by @chronic_jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We recognize that we are collective agents of history and that history cannot be deleted like web pages." --- Angela Davis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonLeopold @bensmp I was interested. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please start this March now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are these "enemies?" https://t.co/RGkpNkfolk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are those little kids?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The site also lists the brand names of Melanie Trump’s jewelry lines sold on QVC https://t.co/R3vti6FwWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Threat Embedded in Trump's Angry Address via @jeffersonmorley https://t.co/Wc50Q6Vxk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal list shows President Trump was Sworn in next to his VIP donors https://t.co/lOfslsdSaz by @Schwartzesque#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post reporter thrown to the ground by D.C. police at violent protest https://t.co/arLIHWbbPt by @AlexanderEmmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Reasons Congress Members Are Boycotting Trump @alternet https://t.co/56dUjgEPeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major fake news operation tracked back to Republican operative https://t.co/FmI1tzHYcc by @RobertMackey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the White House press office had left the administration by Thursday and could not be reached for comment https://t.co/lnU9W4ieWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intercepted Russian Communications Part of Inquiry Into Trump Associates https://t.co/U4ddxKrYN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room for Debate: Whistleblowers Will Need to Be Brave, Reporters Must Be Open-Minded by @betsyreed2 https://t.co/Y6jpUowTYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Fight with the CIA Is a Danger to All of Us https://t.co/aXWF78ttP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's Schmidt met with Kushner in Republican outreach https://t.co/EqydgD8Bp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google was overwhelmingly against Trump, now it's trying to win him over https://t.co/DgEh3BiHgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Serves Up the Latest Chapter of Racial Backlash by @jeffersonmorley @alternet https://t.co/hoxkngd7Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Swedish Kings of Cyberwar https://t.co/dt9wCcsWv8 via @nybooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyQuintano @EricLiptonNYT knows a lot of other stuff though https://t.co/VgSO1pZNnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering Marjorie with love @TimothyNoah1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now 45 detainees in #Guantanamo; the last time there were fewer than 55 was 1/15/2002 @coracurrier @carolrosenberg @charlie_savage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drink Here Until 4 a.m. During Inauguration Week #DC https://t.co/Mn7yjQCBGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The horror of the Iraq war, one hundred years from now. https://t.co/ZbNxFzWq9i by @coracurrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewacole @the_intercept don't miss this!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgreensit they don't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Investigative Reporting Outlets to Follow https://t.co/yHolIWWrpy via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MazMHussain citizens asked “what do you think of the United States?”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Complaints describes border agents interrogating Muslim Americans, asking for social media accounts https://t.co/NMgVuDyAHd by @mazmhussain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @BarackObama, please grant clemency to @xychelsea #timeserved #FreeChelseaNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Spy Who Wrote the Trump-Russia Memos: It Was Hair-Raising Stuff https://t.co/cv0Aie0QzD via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea Manning Describes Bleak Life in a Men’s Prison https://t.co/ynDDmheSHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeland Security pick Gen. John Kelly failed to disclose position at lobbying firm on ethics disclosure https://t.co/4wYSUen5mW by @lhfang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 15 years, prisoners at #Guantánamo face more uncertainty than ever https://t.co/jFCpMzI4Wo by @AlexanderEmmons @MargotWilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spokeswoman for Trumpsaid in a statement he had not yet decided for certain if he would form a presidential commission on vaccine issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump asks anti-vaccine activist Robert Kennedy Jr. to lead panel on vaccine safety https://t.co/zSq64VSZNE by @RobertMackey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women visiting New York City jails describe a pattern of invasive, humiliating strip searches https://t.co/Y3HmOFPP9W by @aintacrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Guantanamo review board decision for indefinite detention of Moath Hamza Ahmed Al-Alwi, Yemeni, ISN28 https://t.co/scxWjO61Zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet Confirmation Hearings https://t.co/gQJANRH7Re #senatehearings @theintercept #liveblog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crimes of SEAL Team 6, an exclusive investigation by @theintercept https://t.co/3CUMkZTe3u by @matthewacole #SEALTeam6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many gowns available. This is DC not Hollywood! Trump says DC dress shops are sold out of inauguration gowns. Wrong! https://t.co/AQdIoJplTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alykat She still can't pronounce my name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Break With Precedent, Obama Envoys Are Denied Extensions Past Inauguration Day https://t.co/nSKbsV3OGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GrizzlySteppe report: @micahflee shows that much of the evidence presented is evidence of nothing at all.https://t.co/ATrUr6GF3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL @micahflee "Does this mean that I’m an elite Russian hacker and I just didn’t realize it?" https://t.co/WgSZ4AlzDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. government thinks thousands of Russian hackers may be reading my blog. They aren't. https://t.co/ATrUr6GF3Y by @micahflee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the expert Jack Abramoff is talking about corruption on CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't think we're free in America" – interview with civil rights attorney Bryan Stevenson https://t.co/fTjRtOW5yC by @alicesperi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianstelter best of new year wishes for you and your family!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald he's a "member" of the DNC? or is there a card that Democrats carry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twelve must-reads from The Intercept in 2016 https://t.co/OPMGOdEnC3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>