<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax season boy ya car rented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swea i swea, ima keep it real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoke fruit punch, we off it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorties be funny as hell thinkin im gone spark them up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC got alotta different types of people. Everytime i step out i see something new]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course i split my lip rite before the weekend over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the bottom of the bottom, it was nothin under me https://t.co/EFp8g2ogJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned my lesson last year, ion ever wear clean sneakers to house parties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study me, see the clarity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So selective with who i let get close to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You hear me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im 🔦💡in ball now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do ya thang just dont step on these all white g fazos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play the cut so well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aint heard from maxout in a grip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see how corrupted i am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live orchestra aint no joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernard Herrman wave lord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to switch time zones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need them bags in pronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can be educated for oppression or for liberation. It dont determine your future but that shit definitelty puts you in a certain mindset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believing is a concept, and state of mind, i only accept facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ion believe shit, show me facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday i wonder what comes after death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long live yams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We was raised different, i grew up on tough love. Honest but supportive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me goin to B&amp;B is like me going to the cafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn i miss them eastside summers when briant had the water ices rockin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont take the genuine relationships you got for granted...once you lose those bonds you wont find the same kind ever again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunt man, spielberg, shootcha good side. Straight to dvd, rated R like hood fights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I been stayin to myself the social life crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trappin it out till the lease up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cant help what you born wit, but its on you if you die broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get off ya ass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pack came in rolla wood to see what the gas like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[raw sex top 10 most dangerous things lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn... shitted on my mood. RIP to shordy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fw wit all the niggas that keep it real wit theyself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ion pray to no god so who got my sanity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never cared for approval !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never spoke on shit i aint did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitch this charlie's angels, i want all three]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that girl, she gone be around forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was so eager to find someone to hold me down in high school...&amp; i did but both of us got paths to follow. hope they meet again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No resolution but i know exactly how ima handle this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding concepts, learning perspective....all underrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only niggas that keep it ah 100 understand this lingo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock goin up. Bitch invest in me. 📈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont fuck with college. And yall too systematically oppressed to realize its a scam..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never bored enough to play twitter games. Chalked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's about your impact. nobody can recreate those memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I aint never adapt to nobody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its funny how niggas re-create themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We was made for each other. We both know it. Circumstances just makin it hard for me to show it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saddest part is when you think somebody understand you but they dont]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addicted to my flexin you cant live w/o me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mah Bro down the road i know he maxin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am i wrong for making light of my situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realize how lucky i am for even gettin a chance to make it out. Still evolving,  still fucking up, still Messy https://t.co/60fOd5TzhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont go where you aint from. Thats how you get x'd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delaware so fuckin corny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall niggas so fake, cuttin up for the social, dont forget we know yall niggas in real life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets really keep it ah 💯. Ian connor got most of yall niggas hip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think of shit like this when im high, foh. Yall aint eva gone find out https://t.co/zE0Kwifn5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bape &amp; supreme chalked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know you ah bitch just stop pressin ya luck, lucky as fuck that i kept it on tuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything real lil bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get better at shit just to prove a point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They dont acknowledge your potential until you start getting clout smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip my hat to all the niggas who aint got they family around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you actually think Tommy Hilfiger said that racist shit in 96 you a dickhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come home find out my right hand and my lil niggas booked smh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shit i buy is timeless, it cant ever be lame cuz ima be the one wearing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall joe every major release then decide its corny when mf's start wearing it.  what did u expect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Niggas in Wilmington dont even know what strains are. Yall niggas be smoking regular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yall put broken heart theme on everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still trippin. Aint no love for the other side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9-1 

We doin numbers this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been bitter since the day i found how shiesty the world is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trill as shit, cant deny it, we different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put niggas on game, dont need credit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She like it on camera, adalina rose her stamina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most you niggas be frontin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free maxout man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aint heard from t roy in a brick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigga tried to hit a lick and missed, try run and i caught em like a fish💥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP to shordy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna know where ima go when i die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling Embarrassed gotta be the worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ion speak on shit i never did, so you can't question me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#freecrack https://t.co/NKg7I21XS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cant stand when niggas pray before games. You cant pray for a win nigga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get in the shower wit this gold on, ima die wit this gold on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[grown ass men walking roun wit a flannel tied around the waist smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You drew that line so ima cross it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It be funny as shit seeing niggas i scorched at the gym on campus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck nigga what did you really think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im tired of niggas watchin what i do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we dont fw cops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im too real for all this shit. Deception my worst enemy. It the reason we all here]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>