<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@canonstevejones no, that's your flawed interpretation of his actions. Your opinions and analysis are not 'facts'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grangecardiff OK thank you. That design looks impressive. I'm very glad to hear the cafe is staying open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know whether the Black and White Cafe in Grangetown, Cardiff is closed for good, or is just being radically renovated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigraceking @nightingaleitv Lol. I can't say that's ever happened to me watching 3D. Vague disappointment watching football in 3D though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigraceking @nightingaleitv And those TV Times glasses weren't really that much inferior to modern 3D glasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hayley____ Hayley ❤️'s Rover. Nah, that's not going to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Warnock is exactly what Cardiff City needs at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaker Bercow is calling a LOT of SNP members to speak, all of whom are making more-or-less the same point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's very bright and well informed on constitutional history and parliamentary procedure. https://t.co/71NDwnDE1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hayley____ It depends what the name is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightingaleitv ITV used to show 3D films as long ago as the early 1980s, usually late on Fridays I think. Glasses given away with TV Times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canonstevejones No 'but', truth is truth, and lies are lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erm, Bill Pertwee was never a Dr Who........... https://t.co/Gni4Trai6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually DON'T support the measures President Trump has taken on Muslims, but that doesn't give me the right to report on them dishonestly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no 'Muslim ban'. Any journalist who uses that phrase is being utterly dishonest and is a disgrace to the profession.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is Robert Mugabe on a State visit to Britain in 1994. Not many MPs questioned his human rights record: https://t.co/vmwGOQcVCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is President Assad and his wife on a State visit to Britain in 2002. Where were today's protesters/MPs then?: https://t.co/eReplR9wkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the grandstanding we saw in Parliament today did not take place when dignitaries from China, Saudi Arabia &amp; others visited Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's also not forget Ed Miliband's support for the bombing of Libya in 2011, which plunged a successful country into warring chaos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainlee Mandela effect = people young at the time misremembering his prostate health scare in the 1980s, which he recovered from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, it's a wind-up..... https://t.co/24m9XQiq8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really, really hope this is a parody account for The sake of your sanity... https://t.co/JOzolX3Bpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is papers like the Daily Mirror are dying. Their readership consists mostly of elderly people who don't know how to use computers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thinking knowing what you're protesting about, why, and what you're hoping to achieve, would be a good start. https://t.co/NtoqZ14aMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I bought the Daily Mirror, I'd now be boycotting it. I'll refuse to buy it for others if asked. Its standards ha… https://t.co/lU8VhD14bS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mentality of the protester.... https://t.co/2QATxKBtVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archiebland I was sorry to hear about your dad, a man I had a great respect for, especially during the LWT era. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am completely opposed to torture - it doesn't work, and it would make things much less safe for American and possibly British troops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITV should move #Peston to a live slot on Sunday nights and drop Sunday mornings, which are already overcrowded with Marr, Neil and Ridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the Brexit vote in Labour heartlands in the north and in the Welsh Valleys - that counts for more than party membership #Peston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDoughtyMP I'm glad you're consistent at least. Thank you for answering honestly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Peston just said 'most Labour members' wouldn't want Article 50 triggered. Maybe, but not the case with Labour voters #Peston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael van Gerwen is in a different class to everyone else now, even when he's not at his absolute best #darts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDoughtyMP So would you sign a petition to stop President Xi Jinping or King Salman from being granted a State vis… https://t.co/oA5xNxfVuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really possible. The BBC couldn't get its hands on any horse racing rights for several years for starters. It's… https://t.co/mPlX8ooqhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice how quickly Barack Obama's policy on Haitian refugees has been forgotten...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder whether Stephen Doughty was quite so active when the likes of Assad and Mugabe &amp; several Chinese president… https://t.co/pEIj8v61Y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump has not banned Muslims from entering the USA. Just so you know....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terrific night of #darts ahead on ITV4. The best four players on the planet have made it through to the semi-finals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris180Mason Agreed. They've been hired because they're 'names', not because they're good pundits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewClarke19 He certainly is, Andy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leeselby126 The judges got it about right for me. I hope you're OK Lee. I feel sorry for you today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pistol147 @RealCFrampton The judges got it about right for me, but huge credit to both fighters. Let's have a third bout!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The judges got that one about right. Both Santa Cruz and Frampton are a credit to boxing. Let's have a third fight in Ireland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best wishes to Alex Lester and Janice Long for the future. Axing live programming on Radio 2 is an absurd decision by BBC management.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImAndyMcColl I'm glad to hear it, Andy. I've admired his work for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris180Mason terrific ITV coverage as always Chris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Serena Williams. It's phenomenal and she's been around for a very long time now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganbootITV hi Megan, I replied to Andy Collinson's email but haven't heard from him since. 3 of us to do a conference call next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never recovered from the year Man Utd didn't participate. Plus top 4 in Premier League getting into Champions Le… https://t.co/yqNRllcBdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs were very fortunate to win. Wycombe put up a good fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kermogant came back to haunt Cardiff City this afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir John Hurt was a superb actor. I particularly enjoyed him in The Elephant Man, 1984 and The Alan Clark Diaries. A sad loss. RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoundLike @BBC There's not a huge amount he can do for 'retribution'. She's one of many who asks him absurd questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoundLike @BBC Nah I think he was only having a laugh with that remark. He's used to daft questions from pro-establishment journalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_Occomore @SocialistVoice @TelegraphNews I tweeted that article very widely earlier this evening. He's been treated disgracefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annispice @CSquireMagazine Thanks for pointing me in that direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoundLike @BBC There's a serious institutional bias issue for sure. Ian Katz, ex-Guardian deputy, is editor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for clarifying! Ha! Ha! https://t.co/BPCpvEgret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annispice I can't stand the bloke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldGeezerAl I rarely drink when in the flat on my own...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GwenSteph88 I certainly hope so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't 'SURVIVE'? This guy is beyond absurd. https://t.co/riX4c9zr1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James O'Brien is an awful presenter of #Newsnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilomenaPound @TelegraphNews I hope he finds radio work elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wirelessradiouk Brian Matthew is in good health and is available for work. A good fit for The Wireless? I think so. Go for it, I say!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilPurnell Well, most BBC management these days are Islington elitist types who don't have a clue what ordinary people want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GwenSteph88 It's possible another station could snap him up. Age UK's online station The Wireless would be a good home. Shameful BBC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GwenSteph88 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@socialtechno No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Graemethedean No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPPW3000 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMediaRock No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JAJRobertson No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuieBurley No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulsummers55 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bonzodog25 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndharrisck No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mynony No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilPurnell He's back to health. Dropped against his will: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ric9871Ric No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vbb9871 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FloClucas No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@what2weeks No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilomenaPound No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxFalconScott No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guydixon5 No, not ill health. He's been dropped against his will. From the man himself: https://t.co/V3TifbEYiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGB Tony's under-used by the BBC at the moment. Most of his radio work is on commercial stations these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGB Thought so :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGB Most likely scenario - Dermot O'Leary gets a Saturday breakfast show. SOTS moves to a new off-peak slot with Tony Blackburn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGB John Birt? What's he got to do with it? He's long gone. Don't you mean Tony Hall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuddyGB To be fair to Tim, he's effectively reading Brian's script, so can't make it his own. Tony a likely successor in new slot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowrangler @SocialistVoice Erm, Man U were top for so long largely because they brought through a lot of academy players. Work it out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowrangler @SocialistVoice I agree football has less connection with the community nowadays, but I don't blame players for taking money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowrangler @SocialistVoice Well yes, but a footballer's career is short and I don't blame them for making as much money as possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowrangler @SocialistVoice @fastestfredy A separate argument about the amount they're paid. Sports sponsorship existed in 1966, BTW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadowrangler @SocialistVoice @fastestfredy Eh? Sponsorship in sport is essential if you want sports professionals to be paid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialistVoice @fastestfredy @shadowrangler There will be serious implications for sports sponsorship if that actually happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialistVoice @pvtjen Yes JY was very badly treated in 2002, but he returned to Radio 2 for a 90th birthday celebration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialistVoice @shadowrangler I don't see much evidence of that myself. The BBC got a decent licence fee settlement but uses money badly.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>