<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How good would it be if I turned up to sign the papers for my new car and the salesman was like 'oh there's the keys, it's ready']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank Lampard and Steven Gerrard in the same year, there goes my childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See when your mind is racing but your trying to sleep, that's no a good combination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Straight to bed I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd do anything to see Walter smith back in the dugout, you don't see that passion these days https://t.co/InDykgyvq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunno whether to laugh or cry, this is absolutely dreadful, actually pathetic performance yet again away from home in a big game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shambolic defending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No idea what Halliday is thinking there, dreadful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handed hearts two goals on a plate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't help falling in love with Hyndman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of @lucy_morrice getting two unconditionals to her first choice uni! Well done!! â¤ï¸ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pathetic yet again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 honestly Norrie the man can't defend, I'd love to see the stat of how many goals we've conceded coz of him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't fall in love with Emerson Hyndman because he'll be away in the summer ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the laughs Efe Ambrose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice oh well would you look at that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual makes my blood boil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice @DisneyReactss that is VERY accurate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice defo no me shaking those hips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice my sentiments exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy and me actually speak to each other like a married couple of 40 years eh, it's actually quite worrying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and Lucy actual eat the most shite hahaha it needs to stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryredpath aw sorry bud I didn't see you!! I would have stopped otherwise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryredpath aye I was there filling up the shitey corsa, thankfully that will be getting rid of! Where were you off to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryredpath exact same, I loved my old car! Wee change of colour this time though, it's metallic blue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It shall be named Fred, in honour of Fred the red fiesta who is now sadly in the scrapyard in the sky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad to have finally gotten my car sorted! I'll be a very happy man in the next two weeks when my new one comes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiccardoBURROWS happy birthday my friend, I hope you have a good day and heather spoils you! Miss you! â¤ï¸ï¸â¤ï¸ï¸ https://t.co/HSKrCEIz1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice always got me â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_DannySimpson_ it was such a shame! Poured his wee heart out and she bumped him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really don't want to sleep alone tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WindassJnr is a laugh on twitter, what a ladðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only team that's letting me down as well man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wigan no won at home in 6 games, take Brentford and their 2-0 upðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 I rarely go over a fiver myself because I'm useless at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 neither do i, I never touched it! Ohhhh that's a sore one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 never take the early game Norrie my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now time for the coupon... Dunfermline, home of my girlfriend let me down last week. Obvious to take them again this weekðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Halliday doesn't half take some kickings through a game eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been impressed with that Hyndmann since he came on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't look like a team with only 7 minutes left, there's no urgency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same old story with Rangers, pass pass and pass with no quality or end product in the final third.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's his man! He loses him! You can't blame Hodson! Fucking losing count with how many goals Kiernan is costing us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IS KIERNAN DOING?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wallace is miles onside, what a poor decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MOH showing why he should be starting every week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craig Thomson is fucking rotten, that's a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a stonewall penalty!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barrie McKay is back to the best of last season, what a fine wee footballer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice @JPB1895_ Hahahaha aye your sure soon show them how it's done!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 aye mate, liability isn't an issue coz it's his fault, it's just waiting on the figure so I can start getting a new one sorted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 its been so long! Aye I have a hire car but now they're on the phone wanting me to start chasing up coz they want the car back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 so it's now getting a little boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 still nothing mate, disputing the valuation, waiting on the finance company to get back to it! the accident was 30th November!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This whole car situation is really beginning to get frustrating now, getting the same phone calls every week to tell me the same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossMcIntyre9 happy birthday Rossco, finally got there eh! Have a good day bud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever made the toastie bag is a genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't even know Matt Crooks had went out on loan ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice yeah I know your right, I was only joking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice do I though? Do I really though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and Lucy keep saying the same things at the exact same time to each other, like it's frightening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual wish I was following Rangers in Germany, it looks class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice @unclehxlmes nah don't please never do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous money https://t.co/Kohyvwbnpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit to Lucy for putting up with me for 6 months https://t.co/JZL4Xf37dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryredpath you seen the pictures? They can't even clear it because of the wind! Aye he's been charged for it, neither wonder!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ only went and flipped his lorry! Fanny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I canny believe a lorry tried to go over the bridge last night in that wind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually wish I could go back and relive Biffy Clyro in Glasgow, what a night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shite no having Lucy here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amount of times Lucy calls me an arsehole is unreal #arsehole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a wonderful woman  https://t.co/xHvA5dud7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to go a walk up Arthur Seat with Lucy but let's face it, my legs and lungs can't handle the climb anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a film inception is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barryredpath aye tell me about it!! It has to be done mate, it's our alternate reality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played all of the big teams with Everton in first 8 games of the season and sitting 7th... Legacy being built]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice @Kirsty_Baxter_4 you really really don't kirsty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice no please don't it will embarrass me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice I'm not a Gimp I'm actually just really cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy and I are in bed, I'm watching MOTD and playing football manager whilst she reads her book.. When's the wedding? ðŸ˜¶ðŸ˜¶ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice well that's rude and uncalled for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice your more than welcome, have a pleasant evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice sorry I'm a gimp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 some touch for the second though, got yourselves a player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norrieblack1 he's not the obi wan tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to check the Hibs team news but must have offended them in the past. Apologies to all Im a different person now https://t.co/fZoGC95Rgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there's one player I've never rated, it's got to be John Obi Mikel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back from 6 days off straight into a 4am start for one day only means a zero chance of any sleep tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice aye but it takes you about 50 million years to dry your hair so why would I go first??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Lucy get up and get in the shower so we can go for a cheeky Nando's??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice don't tell me to shut up on twitter in front of my friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucy_morrice I'll put American dad back on when you stop sinking your teeth into my arm like a fucking shark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucy turned match of the day off, so I took the controls and put it back on, so she bit meðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodddddytweedie tell me about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So lucky to have an amazing girl like Lucy with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year to all my friends and family when it comes!! Hope you all have a ball, pardon the pub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting spangled tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob Kiernan is still a massive liability. We were in control until they scored. Must improve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality of Celtic showed, credit to them. We performed better, still a massive gap but we know where to improve. Drop Tav now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally I think Tavernier has been murder today, murder for months]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>