<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How does overload lead you to procrastinate and how can you stop it? https://t.co/MBDH35HaxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know that you have superpowers you may have not been using?
Find out more….https://t.co/WPa0CN248z https://t.co/2znNNFD2dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evr bn stuck w a situation &amp; not sure wat 2do? Lstn hr &amp; fnd out hw 2 turn it arnd quickly! https://t.co/ySeF7N8Ez9 https://t.co/DsgLeRUkul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these words.
Want to learn the 5 simple principles that drive my success?
https://t.co/YwLwlLOxRS https://t.co/EYPkU3nBhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change anything in your life with these three steps https://t.co/8EIIot8zpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We go 1 step further n2 d ways n w/c limiting beliefs might be holding you back. Click here: https://t.co/Se9rbgD9eA https://t.co/QxMclalK0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab the free program at https://t.co/DYTe23KAeM https://t.co/3b3OzMVMzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a passion for contributing to people's lives. https://t.co/mW3kcYJcA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In ds podcast we look at a simple idea dat can powrfully reframe watevr challenge ur facing. https://t.co/IYUp2ABmeZ https://t.co/4GVu43nr0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power of thoughts and habits shapes your life. Listen more here: https://t.co/Z7oeVtnNrV https://t.co/p2BfbvaGJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear increases the closer you get to your goals. #truthbombs #purpose #motivation #lifecoach https://t.co/bBYSCQ6YMQ https://t.co/LpVLAWk4WJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find your calm in any storm. Just do this https://t.co/WsBDZTWVEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these words.
Want to learn the 5 simple principles that drive my success?
https://t.co/YwLwlLOxRS https://t.co/HhLSlGgvrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't leave this 'unchecked' Get the program at https://t.co/DYTe23KAeM https://t.co/EpnihvL0PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d love a follow on Snapchat - find me here https://t.co/mYOJGNGaI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived. Always like to stay close to great ideas! https://t.co/ZaKoJDQlCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived. Always like to stay close to great ideas! https://t.co/5ZONj9kAXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how to harness the single most powerful force in your life https://t.co/8tQUpzYiH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest post on instagram - how to change anything in three steps https://t.co/zM2AKhckuv #goals #effort #motivation #business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest interview with the amazing @adriennedorison. We talk life, business and so much more https://t.co/lTtu3M70gi https://t.co/2LsqvmYWsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE SCIENCE OF SETTING GOALS: https://t.co/jgm5FBmt1d https://t.co/SHDwWlI36k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can listening make you much more successful? https://t.co/RKNEIzNAQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help! I hate getting up early https://t.co/W7mbtX94xR https://t.co/VApH6nVWfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when you don't know what to do? https://t.co/RiQ1CHthd8 #personaldevelopment #personalgrowth #motivation #goals #hustle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We look at some latest research abt hw 2chnge d habits dat might be undermining ur progress. https://t.co/BOXlKS5usl https://t.co/tvEp0onZQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to getting up early and a strong morning routine https://t.co/W7mbtX94xR https://t.co/v2zVfVabJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all face tough choices at times. This will help you get some clarity https://t.co/gUh6YMM9Q9 https://t.co/QLNa2BIFzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N a celbrty obsessd cultr it oftn sims lyk success hapns ovrnyt. D truth s sumthng dfrnt….https://t.co/APAnYvMork https://t.co/AG0fSUOi9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab these quick tips on how to deal with being overloaded https://t.co/PnA5oumhor https://t.co/d5qGIWeUgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let being offended ruin your day. Read this https://t.co/jCOXc8uuY5 https://t.co/Ut7SEGLVjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get what you tolerate and here's some thoughts on how to shift it https://t.co/0n8R6LPCcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In under 10 minutes u can dscovr d entire purpose of your existence. That’s not a bad offer! https://t.co/RZgoUIzSV5 https://t.co/lKlOoXaPcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Affirmations Successful People Repeat Every Single Day - https://t.co/NovOBxSUwG https://t.co/a9opErjGOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hw much stress do u cause yourself by making one simple but very common mistake? CHCK HERE: https://t.co/wR8qzcaVHe https://t.co/o2BkW14XS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a morning person? The try this... https://t.co/W7mbtX94xR https://t.co/wJb3RGpCaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear's prbbly d thng dat holds u bak mor dan anythng els.It’s also d place wer d magc hapns. https://t.co/opBMxNG1VF https://t.co/k8HK5KRpoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the full post https://t.co/Zskv731I8d https://t.co/l6FGjo8CSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why daydreaming is good for you - https://t.co/pGFxsyouyw https://t.co/YJivqwKrtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really matters is not outcomes but your relationship with yourself and with others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when you get really stuck? Share your thoughts here https://t.co/RiQ1CHthd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one thing was holding me back for so long https://t.co/9jONAeekyn https://t.co/0G6DLbCMdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can you do when life is really tough? Watch this https://t.co/9HZZZfu5Bf #adversity #hardship https://t.co/vdtnPd5GgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never overlook the power of small decisions and their power to steer the ship of your life! https://t.co/Vv9Qtfgz6b https://t.co/8qXHfcLa2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find me on Snapchat here https://t.co/OnyciNp3Al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to learn! #lifecoach #lifecoaching #purpose #motivation #goals https://t.co/ATuMGSi3xP https://t.co/G31qUzcF2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why outdated mental software might be costing you big time https://t.co/B4Eykqae39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this in the library today? Just plain weird! https://t.co/ZvMcqUMSWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New passport arrived for keynotes in London and the USA. https://t.co/qMI5ZfX04H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do all successful people eventually figure out? https://t.co/9jONAeekyn https://t.co/zR3ti3QlNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why it's good to be really dissatisfied https://t.co/YCSUsdzvse #goals #motivation #purpose #hustle #crushit #lifecoach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the one big thing in life that really matters https://t.co/lw3OHVYPcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just posted on Medium about how we all need mentors. Can you have a quick read and post a comment?  

https://t.co/tdIqLhiiZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does 'deep listening' set the best apart from the rest? https://t.co/KolJngYT71 https://t.co/WMmLX8hlqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovering d thngs daat matr d most can help u dscovr wer 2allocate more tym &amp; energy &amp; live a more meaningful lyf… https://t.co/ySDvKwtuCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you'd like some daily motivational gold in under 90 seconds then check out my Youtube channel https://t.co/HBQmOf5x7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d love a follow on Snapchat - come and say hi. https://t.co/4nXP1DHDvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile at people. It costs nothing and it always makes you both feel a fraction better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you should ignore your feelings more often https://t.co/WCa7nnL8EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when fear is overwhelming? https://t.co/nn835b4qbK #fear #overcomefear #courage #courageous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just walked into the library and saw this on the main display? What’s the funniest book title you’ve ever seen? https://t.co/Bowvymfh3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try these five quick steps to get your progress into orbit https://t.co/YwLwlLOxRS https://t.co/3gARjxcAMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens on the other side of fear and how do habits and goals interact  https://t.co/nn835b4qbK #fear #overcomefear #courage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let blame, excuses and denial dictate your life https://t.co/h86BeAo7u0 #goals #motivation #purpose #business #selfhelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the full post https://t.co/lexv4IEqD6 https://t.co/psnQbdEWvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just never know n life how long uv got. Are you realising the power and preciousness of each day? Listen here -… https://t.co/47yO7hCEm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why being easily offended will make you unhappy https://t.co/9ApYssYaR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How one character trait can change everything in your business https://t.co/idsrOEMvBE https://t.co/xlQWZPjpvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crucial way to reach your goals https://t.co/pyFDhtHgUf #goals #motivation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The goal of life s 2 contribute and to contribute to fully, you need great people to walk with you on the journey.… https://t.co/696Ncp2LqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing I do at every conference https://t.co/KolJngYT71 https://t.co/g3EfMFI6Ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does learning to ask for help change the direction of your life https://t.co/rXfESpOiCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how you find the magic in life  https://t.co/nn835b4qbK #fear #overcomefear #courage #courageous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that these three steps will make your decision-making much easier https://t.co/gUh6YMM9Q9 #choices https://t.co/xHpl3akj03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes u have 2go somewhere before u arrive. What is 1 of d secrets that Steve Jobs saw that changes the world?… https://t.co/0oDQXKXOXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is now: How to stop procrastinating. - https://t.co/eYXkW9TjV1 https://t.co/QStIhLP6oH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the secret to getting up early and smashing your daily goals https://t.co/W7mbtX94xR https://t.co/XjyT5jzUxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my little brother! Great guy doing big things in life and business. https://t.co/hcgNmFHcO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great #truth that the great struggles to become truly human are within. https://t.co/2ux88wFxvE https://t.co/upsxWqVkt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try these 3 steps to get some clarity when you are not sure what to do in life https://t.co/gUh6YMM9Q9 https://t.co/f1vBRAKfDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evr bn frustr8d dat ur lyf s not wer u reli want it 2b? Well myb ds simple idea wil see u make a big breakthrough.… https://t.co/UBLgfDyksU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest post on medium - What to do when you don't know what to do! https://t.co/887PmEK1Q5 https://t.co/YRp1Yv6Qai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just written by my seven year old! #truthbomb #lifecoach #lifecoaching #goals #faith https://t.co/Db5lMnTO2s https://t.co/6VJLYg0tm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try these three steps every time you get stuck on a big decision https://t.co/887PmEK1Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story you tell yourself about yourself might be in need of change Check this out https://t.co/xcwRiqxvAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect wine and cheese combo for a perfect summer night https://t.co/gg0qe5Hevy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you on Snapchat yet? I’d love a follow https://t.co/O4yyRHBepJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the five pain points of every entrepreneur and business owner? https://t.co/mB7dLUMhl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Navy SEAL's Secret for Pushing Yourself Way Beyond Your (Supposed) Limits: https://t.co/VCfNKTVA0J https://t.co/XUVD0bK33J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s easy to be stuck w #problems. Don’t lose track of the times you were #brave #strong. https://t.co/WgVlGAJBHC https://t.co/gD3r9W378n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many of us spend our lives trying/wanting 2b sum1 els. Dscover powerful ideas 2 leverage d best of ur personality.… https://t.co/KR3anrMobY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People think I am an expert on #personaldevelopment but I also get stuck? Any ideas? https://t.co/RiQ1CHthd8 #personaldevelopment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these words.
Want to learn the 5 simple principles that drive my success?
https://t.co/YwLwlLOxRS https://t.co/209JYQX2hL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do many n Hollywood hav substance addictions, r ncapable of stayng married, struggle w chronic eatng dsorders?… https://t.co/rZB1hlG1AV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I get up every day at 4am?  How can u supercharge your morning effectiveness. https://t.co/W7mbtX94xR https://t.co/77phpmBXTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't waste your life watching pointless TV...you have so much to learn and so much to contribute. https://t.co/0Dt7t9L106]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest #Soundcloud post about the one post I did on Facebook that went viral https://t.co/dKlQnL5AZ8 https://t.co/7JrIVopGby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it worth spending your money on a personal coach? https://t.co/YWiHB269JH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 of the benefits of being fit &amp; active is that u get 2 pass on that passion 2 those u love. https://t.co/wXdgAO7p3T https://t.co/ArFmJ4KocU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should you consider getting a personal life or business coach? https://t.co/eM3m2dieSs https://t.co/e6hCYDadSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to see your business grow then you need to read this now https://t.co/mB7dLUMhl8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>