<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose I should really read through the whole JS language reference one of these days... https://t.co/srjqmXKQRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh cool, you can do string interpolation in JS! https://t.co/1JFst8jzSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deegolightly @Skyliting That explains why it's numbers and not "Jack Queen King Ace" above floor 10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby, you're dressed like the lead singer of a heavy metal band. https://t.co/g8GderJYRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just machines to make big decisions,
Programmed by fellas with compassionate visions. #igy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here at home we'll play in the city
Powered by the sun
Perfect weather for a streamlined world
There'll be spandex jackets, one for everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby's first office visit https://t.co/ZrOePUpYtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/cpSTpGmjzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea It's seeming like, to get realtime wind data, you'd need your own weather station. Or befriend someone who has one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea UK's "WOW" program has some more fine-grained Wgtn stations. No output API though. Maybe screenscrape? https://t.co/NkbTd2zDuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea The API for aviation weather gives you the half-hourly data for Wgtn airport. Not realtime, tho...  https://t.co/v0KxRheKrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that you follow Kai Ryssdal on Twitter, is soooo very @DylanShaver. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put socks on the baby's hands to keep him from scratching himself. Now I keep seeing them as… https://t.co/z8UBFZUwOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColineLimler Please tweet the lyrics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time once again to play Wellington's favorite game show - "Quake or Wind?!" ;) https://t.co/L6w6bcxMzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next Christmas
I'll give u my heart
I rly hope u
Won't give it away
This Christmas
I'll stay in &amp; watch
The Charlie Brown Christmas Special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse This is why it's so important to change your fingerprints regularly and not use the same fingerprint on every site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @CatalystNZ this is like 80% of the company. ;) https://t.co/LC7vYSMHuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bemiljen @seawall Lol, how exactly does one dress up as Neil Gaiman? Tousled hair, black sportcoat, and a Sandman trade paperback?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TetZoo Here in New Zealand? Probably just a flightless bird. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I can see the resemblance. https://t.co/4bMfWqnMMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flip gave himself a hickey from suckling on his forearm. https://t.co/Udkd7MxMIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby burrito and literal burrito https://t.co/ojtoXeymoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flip uses headbutt! It's super effective! https://t.co/ZmK2yoYoe9 https://t.co/12dh1Lmhmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My baby's going bald! :) If he's like me and his mom, it'll grow back blond. https://t.co/QT7P0Zog9u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seawall @Jinthelife And I've always wanted to be a parent someday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 AM and wide awake! https://t.co/7EaNrSLj4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seawall Our baby is a bottomless milk pit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the US, networks have letter names (eg NBC), and local affiliates have their own call sign, channel number (eg KVVU FOX 5 in Las Vegas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: In NZ, pre-digital TV's wd let you assign the "number" for the channel at each freq, cuz NZ TV networks have number names (eg TV1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally ordered a flatscreen TV to replace my aged 30in "sea anchor". Main impetus was the increasing scarcity of n… https://t.co/1O6MPlRnFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I figured it'd do the trick for the PB ice cream, which freezes into a brick. And it did! A little maple aftertaste, but it combines well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made maple ice cream last week, noticed it froze much softer than other recipes, and that the maple flavor was fairly subtle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solved the problem w my peanut butter ice cream recipe's over-firm texture. Solution: replace sugar w maple syrup (real or fake).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flip enjoying the sights at @zealandia @ Zealandia Ecosanctuary https://t.co/5RFJBP57DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/4F6XuGfOWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol, I suppose "200 million megabytes" sounds more impressive than "200 terabytes". But why stop there? How about "… https://t.co/JrmySSDqQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first time I've ever cooked a whole turkey! And the first time I've made stuffing. The bird… https://t.co/MdPmh9XVH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! https://t.co/MOn6p29kYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TetZoo Is it hard to keep your kids from playing with these? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did he have time to go shopping? https://t.co/9q0Y95VYvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TVsAndyDaly So has Don DiMello accepted a position in the administration yet? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samjarman When you put on the sorting hat it helps you tell which Hogwarts house you should join.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cord remnant's starting to look like the Sorting Hat from Harry Potter https://t.co/Sy7KwHNU3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a pretty big daddy longlegs! My hand for scale. https://t.co/brgmDitrVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 13. He's gotten so pudgy in the past few days! :) https://t.co/kZERdbyCLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea My fave hidden gem lately, is "Void Pyramid". Author's other Android game is great too. https://t.co/HLxEyXusHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea Currently installed, I've got "Climb!" and the FOSS "Simon Tatham's Puzzles", which is versatile but a bit flavorless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizzyrea I've played so many! Mostly Google store's "most popular" are play-to-win, so it takes some digging to find the good games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofNZ Mine's 13 days old. It's actually been pretty fun so far. :) Lack of sleep is the main annoyance. https://t.co/2QSF3K8XVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TetZoo Prophetic dream ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon Guilty as charged ;) https://t.co/i7R1tP0Iat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Express Yourself" is about using a breast pump, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ @seawall Tho actually, Flip's namesake, my grandpa, was himself 6'1". Lots of tall in my mom's family too, just not mom herself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ @seawall Indeed, the chart itself says only 80% accuracy, +/- 6 cm. &amp; squirmy babies hard to measure accurately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on his birth size, statistically Flip will reach my height around age 13, will end up about 6'. Takes after @seawall if so!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anzeljg Too late on the "no sleepless nights" part, but the love part is working out good. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Check out these guns!" https://t.co/a0Zaf5I5Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCuriosity I just have a lot of feelings. ;) https://t.co/uHEz8Glw23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCuriosity I also just listened to "Beautiful Boy", "Cat's in the Cradle", and "Little Kawai", so I think I may be cried out now. 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheesiest new parent moment so far: crying to Creed's "Arms Wide Open".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After consulting Google, my best guess is it's a Tachinid fly. Looks kinda like Tachina lurida.… https://t.co/fiySQv7OUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know what this bug is? Seen outside my glass door in Wgn Nz. Looks like a big, hairy, orange black striped f… https://t.co/Qydp90KiWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our little Kiwi https://t.co/avs4XR3VrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seawall @Skyliting Yep, he doesn't like being naked. Calms right down once he's dressed and picked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annemjw This is how he cries most times we change his nappy or clothes. The good news is he soothes instantly when he's picked up after. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lest you think it's all cuddles and coos. #angrybaby https://t.co/vBv83JHDX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatalystNZ He thought it was a little annoying that you couldn't use punctuation in the "parent's place of birth" field. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose the cord remnant, kid. It's really interfering with your belly cuteness. https://t.co/9vRG2G6BMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatalystNZ I used SmartStart just a couple of days ago for this little guy! https://t.co/B4SHkDzUWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 1 week birthday, Flip! https://t.co/GXSE0BYe4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert is a cranky kitty. https://t.co/5fbSbSBxke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowlick like a spiral galaxy https://t.co/BQdskt33ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rockin' out to The Three Suns. https://t.co/VKJID7kGOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cosplaying Emperor Palpatine. (Emperor Flipatine?) https://t.co/tmVTzelROz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little baby, big chair. https://t.co/ck3c1ySV2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sry_not4sale From his perspective, giant hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiny head! https://t.co/dAsDahYPy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to bring some food around for us new parents :) https://t.co/VvxVHTE6O5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you hate something, set it free. If it doesn't come back to you, good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby on my belly. https://t.co/Y8ataYLzFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says what it is. #BABY @ Wellington Hospital, New Zealand https://t.co/sCrAHIwSwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanShaver My donor-daughter w @bemiljen has a mild hearing impairment, so seems I've got a recessive gene for it. But aprly not @seawall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grumpybirb And his girl name is Lilian Adel Wells, if he adopts a female identity. Because being trans doesn't escape my naming rights. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Aww, your foot is the size of my thumb. So tiny! Wait, is that poo? How did you get poo on your feet?" #newparent https://t.co/Wd0yIpXiwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You hear that, Twitter folk? DM @eliasvonhelios if you're interested in being his gestational and/or adoptive partner. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanShaver Anyway, test came out good, no sign of hearing problems. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanShaver They're so careful not to pressure you on anything here. I wish I could just tick a general "not afraid of science" box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanShaver They wanted to leave a pamphlet &amp; come back later to get our decision wr to do the test. I was like, "Can you do it right now?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliasvonhelios It's up for grabs now! Time to have a baby!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More rejected names:
Herbert George "H. G." Wells Wells
Orson Welles Wells
Baby Jessica Stuckin Wells
Anhedonia Wells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normnz Thanks! It was a hand-me-down from one of Angie's friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejected names:
Laser Anubis Wells
Artesian Wells
Gerund Apostrophe Wells
Carl Marks Wells
Juan Nguyen Wells
William Walter Wells ("Webby")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting his newborn hearing test. @ Wellington Hospital, New Zealand https://t.co/5M3yqGzp9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/E1qfLGlW3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 2! @ Wellington Hospital, New Zealand https://t.co/2lq0eGqIWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington looking beautiful on Flip's birthday https://t.co/nOPb9AZe6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's got my toes! https://t.co/f5JIzUv04U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... except when he's doing Don Martin toes. https://t.co/z2w0elQInW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still laboring. We're on the tail end now though.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>