<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bomb them or arm them all to bring democracy &amp; freedom &amp; when they come looking for sanctuary tell them no we don't… https://t.co/Hw8QovEhsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new Commission of Inquiry into the Stardust tragedy should be established https://t.co/dk3RVdFWGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im hiring for a Constituency Office Worker for my office in Tallaght. More detailed info &amp; how to apply @ this link: https://t.co/mZYb8ahyVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGilbey yes hope to be there to listen and participate in the disussion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hans_Zomer @MiddleEastMnt arms not linked toany conflict not linked to war &amp; destruction &amp; definitely not linked to current refugee crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hdpdiplomacy @meraldanis @HudaKaya777 @PervinBuldan @PACE_President the repession of opposition &amp; of alternative voices continues unabated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending a Dublin Sinn Féin planning  meeting to discuss the needs aspirations &amp; demands of building inclusive com… https://t.co/KSS7qIc1PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke on Stardust motion yday. FF-FG-Endapendent coalition voted against establishing a Commission of Investigation https://t.co/bSXYKJBN8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a good meeting with the Head of UNHCR’s Protection Service for the Middle East &amp; N.Africa, Gráinne O Hara, today https://t.co/cTKG6ZTABu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All parties should support Sinn Féin's motion for redress &amp; compensation to victims of the tracker mortgage scandal https://t.co/3p95USrhdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stardust Fire families have campaigned tirelessly 36 yrs later they want answers they want justice &amp; they also want a Commission of Inquiry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke on the debate calling for a Commission of Inquiry into the Stardust fire tragedy 48 young people died 214 injured 36yrs justice denied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Govt must take action over suspected war crimes in Yemen by the Saudi coalition &amp; use of British cluster bombs https://t.co/af9IdTO9gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Govt must robustly stand up for the GFA in face of British Govt failure in its commitments &amp; DUP intransigence https://t.co/TfLEbfxk76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also have PQs with Min for Foreign Affairs @ 15.30. My Qs on the North/GFA, Saudi use of cluster bombs in Yemen &amp; Brexit will come up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be raising refugee crisis CETA &amp;Cyprus reunification talks in post-Euro Council statements in Dáil @ 13.45. Also Qs on Ibrahim &amp;EU Army]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Martin Mc Guinness a day of mixed emotions proud &amp; sad but  happy &amp; hopeful for the future &amp; delighted for Michel O'Neill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michele O Neill new Sinn Féin leader in North talking of building an inclusive peaceful Ireland for everyone a time for active citizenship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freddyforrestal there will be room for everyone in a United Ireland Fred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the United Ireland meeting very happy to be back in the Mansion House let's work to make the Democratic  Program… https://t.co/fFol3K4Sec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorhcasey yes you know your busses Conor maith thú]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running late &amp; hopped on a bus into the United Ireland meeting in the Mansion House circuitous route nearly taking as long as United ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DFB warn homeowners after old-style fuse board fire in Templeogue https://t.co/JTUbPkbgMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@molloy1916 the creationists might have an entirely  different view of that scenario]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The proposal to replace the Free Travel Pass with a €50 charge needs to be rubbished and not recycled https://t.co/2SYsXo5BA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trocaire @ThomasPringleTD yes all Sinn Féin TDs will be supporting the Bill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@savechildrenuk @GemmaMcK12 hope them lazy media that we all know &amp; fume  at not see it &amp; portray as stereotype -them sunnys fighting snowys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loreillysf @DublinSinnFein however came up with term &amp; concept of a' Fair Deal'was a genius with words but the reality is quite different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loreillysf @sinnfeinireland anger won't change anything but your vote might]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnbradysf while you were out walking looks like 'Banksy' was out running... well  out of paint anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great night at the Cuban Embassy's reception to mark the 58th Anniversary of the triumph of the revolution. G… https://t.co/fOqrzbfNdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New regulations surrounding the use of rickshaws are urgently needed and legislation is long overdue https://t.co/52vmssZgPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive developments in Cyprus reunification talks in Geneva this week. I passed on @sinnfeinireland's best wishes to Cypriot Amb in Dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian bank bailout highlights duplicity of European Institutions https://t.co/TanmswhufW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge turnout of community &amp; family &amp; friends at  funeral of young Reece Cullen in Martin De Porres church in Tallaght -truly heartbreaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobs for the boys is the Irish expression Transparency, fairness &amp; objectivity are all clearly  lost in the scramble to put their own man in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attended exhibition in Canadian Embassy Saving the Famine Irish the Grey Nuns &amp; the Great Hunger -Montreal pop 50,0… https://t.co/qniZrYDdC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HDPenglish probably not first fingers they broke or will break. Who is policing the police?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryMcElduff and there always them feckin dubs but the glass is never full unless your buying nollaig shona]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchin Commitments never lost it heroine out /I wish but southside brown unlike nth siders &amp; joey d lips &amp;  lip stick agus a well grá &amp; póg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteHollandSF ye a quiet one ( nominated driver every year for  some reason)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteHollandSF a good year for roses &amp; sure understandable  with all d  muck  about let's hope our Gerry got a new pair of wellies off Santa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c1aranquinn surely not anyone we know  but if you fit the description stay downwind and don't ever skip the queue in front of yours truly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas wishes peace love and happiness to you all https://t.co/PzHfNbdVQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writers who wrongly claimed Noel Kirwan gave lift to Hutch &amp; directly contributed to his death now shamelessly regurgitating  same bile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest mortgage distress figures are frightening. Issue must be solved but political will from FG &amp; FF is lacking https://t.co/X9uBRVETYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And with all those injured in the gun attack on the Mosque and Islamic cultural centre in Zurich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts are with those injured &amp; grieving in Berlin tonight after horrific incident claimed lives of civilians&amp; innocent Christmas shoppers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irish_news lack of cap on or lack cop on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalled at assassination of Russian Ambassador in Turkey. Intend to contact the Russian Ambassador to Ireland expressing my condolences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madiba's quote for activists &amp; an  approach to office for politicians including those in Ireland  including but not… https://t.co/FrQ6gs3MVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa lookalike arriving Tallaght village in a funky London  taxi. Had a  Brexit fright moment - hope the green elv… https://t.co/ulJokNGHgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GP Bernadette Scully found not guilty but case highlights complete  lack of support for families with profound mental and physical illnesses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report from the CatalanNewsAgency on @ForcadellCarme court case today. Thousands turned out in support &amp; solidarity https://t.co/uvMQx1fRlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome that our amendment to the Road Traffic Bill, to give the NTA powers to regulate rickshaws, was passed https://t.co/9uQHv6IDMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solidarity to the Catalan Parliament Speaker @ForcadellCarme who is in Court today. I wrote a blog post on her case https://t.co/O9E72EA8mE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O dear Minister Simon Coveney  got his housing fractions &amp; formulas wrong &amp; ends  up with red face &amp; to cap it all off it was a shinner spot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tied yellow ribbons to Xmas tree in my constituency office to show support for #FreeIbrahim campaign. Have some lef… https://t.co/YGug5BK7tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FF &amp; FG housing spat supposedly for hearts &amp; minds.... no rent certainty but breaking renters hearts &amp; driving  families out of their minds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a warm and positive meeting with @sergimarcen, the new Head of the Catalan Govts delegation to Ireland, with… https://t.co/Z5hRPvGFSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government suffered defeat tonight on the Sinn Féin amendment on the  lack of regulation around Rickshaws. (The vote was  58 to 50 )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School Transport Review brings no seasonal joy for school children https://t.co/uhXgyXbx5t https://t.co/DnjDerzrXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and @QuinlivanTD joined members of @Comhlamh's trade justice group at their Christmassy #StopCETA demo outside L… https://t.co/s6GHQdk1XO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of children across the state have been refused access to school transport meanwhile  parents hold their b… https://t.co/wGieeCc5N2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met members of the Rohingya community in Ireland outlined awful human rights abuses in Myanmar/ Burma in end to rai… https://t.co/9dPfld7qLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joined colleagues outside Leinster House tday well past time Government acted on extending voting rights to Irish c… https://t.co/ifYPc0Mqx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Govt’s failure to submit their Moore St appeal to the High Court on the time is bizarre, but extremely welcome https://t.co/0vYzz14KUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pending prosecution of Ms Forcadell, the Catalan Parliament's Speaker, is wrong and the proceedings should stop https://t.co/uNJIwG4qDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a need for a more positive and enlightened approach to senior citizen pensions https://t.co/rPnW6JaLNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposals to intro pay by weight bin system in 2017 will inevitably put additional burdens on hard pressed families https://t.co/tJy78UW7Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met Podemos MP @edumaura in Leinster House today with @Kathleensf1 &amp; @paul_gavan. Had a good discussion on politica… https://t.co/KysZqjSQ8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great entertainment at the South Dublin County Community Endeavour Awards &amp; well done Glenasmole Community Associat… https://t.co/4EvmIRHe5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joined thousands of others signing  books of condolences following  the death of Cuban leader Fidel Castro in the C… https://t.co/0BPnDpSNaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deeply saddened to hear of Fidel Castro's death. Ive extended my condolences, &amp; Sinn Féin's, to the Cuban Ambassador https://t.co/SyC4qFztqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My speech on our Bill to enshrine neutrality in Constitution. FF&amp;FG to vote Níl on 1 Dec, what will Ind Alliance do? https://t.co/kwZTDf61QW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is International Day for the Elimination of Violence Against Women.Domestic violence kills 1 woman every 12min https://t.co/DMj0jL6hDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completed a Dementia Awareness Session this week. A new approach is needed to support people with dementia… https://t.co/gWC4tQgGPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attended a Dementia Awareness session. New approach to support the 55000 people with dementia in the State is needed https://t.co/IV6vQTXijl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I raised the revoking of Faysal Sariyildiz's passport, a @HDPenglish MP, &amp; the 11 imprisoned HDP MPs in the Dáil https://t.co/epLFnZSRUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Irish Govt must urgently undertake an assessment of the impacts that Brexit would have on Good Friday Agreement https://t.co/2BguNSiAdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have Questions to the Minister for Foreign Affairs in the Dáil at 1.30pm. I will be focusing on Brexit and arrest of @HDPenglish MPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an informative meeting with the Cypriot Ambassador to Ireland today. Discussed issues of mutual concern and Cyp… https://t.co/Y4Ggb2nAnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday the Dáil will debate a Bill that I am bringing forward, with @aosnodaigh, to enshrine neutrality in Bun… https://t.co/9Mo34HbARa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a well attended &amp; timely
 'Alcohol -What's the harm' Conference  organised by the  Ballyfermot &amp; Tallaght Drug &amp;… https://t.co/vHjbfSsdqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met @HDPenglish activist to discuss the repression its facing in Turkey. I detailed @sinnfeinireland full solidarit… https://t.co/DfmYNdV5Eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple of empty seats in Dail chamber just now ' The Labour lads &amp; lassies must have took a sickie or found out about a new Tuesday club']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full House at Social Inclusion Week in South Dublin County Council &amp; enjoying music with colleagues Cllr Enda Fanni… https://t.co/TuHSkXpZ9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting #TravellerEthnicityNow https://t.co/lD5VhXCPF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was a pleasure to meet with members of the Nepal Ireland Society to discuss how to improve relations and links betw… https://t.co/v4BFgLbP75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone voting for the young fella in the middle or do we have wait till Florida decides ? https://t.co/DQsnPQmLjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Latinos may create a wall &amp; their votes the gulf  between Trump &amp; the Whitehouse what a  defining  moment in realpolitics that would be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Diwali Festival ( Festival of Light) in Celbridge and being entertained once again  by boys and girls in gre… https://t.co/pMmhs98LsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still awaiting statements of widespread condemnation from Irish political establishment following Turkish administr… https://t.co/uxG0OgdRCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke at a KurdishSolidarityIreland demo this afternoon to protest the arrest of HDP MPs &amp; Co-Chairs. I called for… https://t.co/57GQA9hrqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Govt must urgently resettle 200 child refugees from Calais in Ireland. Here is my my Dáil speech on the issue: https://t.co/VpDtQDkWqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling for the immediate release of the 11 @HDPenglish MPs &amp; 2 Co-Chairs arrested last night #Freedom4HDPdeputies https://t.co/9yqFJRo5On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit &amp; British High Court decision blows Enda's 'nod as good as wink' December Article 50 trigger prediction out of the proverbial  water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Saoirse Womans Refuge launch &amp; opening of the new childrens play facility ' Butterfly House' (named by one of children) a great addition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Turkish Government’s attacks and intensified crackdown on the media and press freedoms needs to stop https://t.co/YfSE4UQgMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joined my colleague Eoin Ó Broin in launching Sinn Féin Housing  proposals to speed up procurement &amp; tendering proc… https://t.co/JnRV767lw5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>