<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@evandeneykel form &amp; content working harmoniously! I assume driving habits reinforce his character traits, whatever they may be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evandeneykel obviously more concerned about you treading on his gun rights, then with putting on a straight sticker. Content over form...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My recs&amp;response to @EllieMackin: Lavalier Mics &amp; Audio for Video https://t.co/yVpyyrFWTP Post 2 in series on sound production &amp; podcasting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 @electricarchaeo @pompei79 @critt1967 &amp; look what's happened to ya'll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, I can do that British beer thing... @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/YllkOtZpZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudwaterbrew IPA Mosaic Exp 431. Long day, sickness, &amp; more tomorrow calls for... beer? @ The… https://t.co/cM4Z1mx93P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxberrytoast ask the Russians. That Android beast is a hackers opening course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of day... again. https://t.co/Lg9J2amoJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unguentarium Ha! No, just have the Monday post-lunch lull. Although, it would be nice to be in South Wales at a Roman fort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's productivity brought to you by.... Monmouth. https://t.co/iiBYQWLRxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’ve heard me mention ‘uneven geography’ much of it comes from Smith. Free Antipode special issue on his work https://t.co/VHUIe9lM1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vacuumed 1 room. Time for another coffee break... https://t.co/OistKovUQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday backdrop. Here till 5:30... @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/j3GyaxBaZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite the general feeling of winter, there's a pale lineup tonight. Here all evening... @… https://t.co/VMCiLJPpZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating approach to buildings &amp; human rights, research based 3D models, &amp; sun-paths! My 1st job was in an accid… https://t.co/rUJ9kDdSyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be useful to know: estimate what % of Latin lit we have? https://t.co/X8BJeu6J3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not sure many could read Being and Nothingness in a day… https://t.co/Gs7UevQrQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reissue of H. Lefebvre, Key Writings; no new material &amp; some texts are now avail full in Eng. Still contains plenty… https://t.co/bCJ1OGJGNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisalodwick mid-90s critical theory loves it! Great cheesy fad in titles. Although TRAC may have skipped it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaLodwick just the 's' to 'z' or capitalisation &amp; scare quotes? Use of scare quotes, parentheses, &amp; 're-' are all favs for a certain time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3,534 words (half way) into manuscript chap 2. My beer coaster is empty. Must fix that problem... https://t.co/wRyAm42foM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evandeneykel Not going to slather the apple in chapstick before diving in… Can’t have chapped lips after devouring original sin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxberrytoast Totally, I’m in the midst of chap on space-time &amp; sound in social theory. Good quick vid of Soja: https://t.co/pU9DkEHXVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should probably give @foxberrytoast Soja's Thirdspace so he can start formulating trilectics... https://t.co/GNMCHrwO5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing about speed of sensory nerves &amp; stimuli in contrast to cognitive thought, trying not use ex of academic publishing as opposite…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 @stephenjohnkay @pompei79 @pompeiana79 @stevenellis74 Calza (La Necropoli…) was initial, Galba coin is Baldassare 1987.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More discussion of @SarahEBond’s post on deleting your academia account &amp; OA scholarship.. Realms of my twitter fee… https://t.co/6LSwAfaVIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Merrifield on the 50th anniversary of Lefebvre’s Right to the City &amp; the cities of tomorrow https://t.co/E8PL9MBorO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @Ted_Underwood Fossil Hash is a thing so, short step to hash browns... https://t.co/TBWuDQpgsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['So, what happens if you try to fro it out now?' 'Wolverine. Or Crusty the Clown.' https://t.co/ZbhA6oyO3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pompeiana79 @raylaurence1 yes, need. Nuance limited by 140 characters...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's the society, stupid' -@Pompeiana79 on @raylaurence1's Space&amp;Society cons in Measuring the Movement Economy https://t.co/NpinAshdY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin yeah, BL &amp; I are meeting next week, will mention it. Soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin finished a book proposal before working at the brewery for 5.30 hours &amp; now at the pub...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Sat in the brewery. Got some smokies on: The Oak Smoked Blonde &amp; The Rauchbier @ Anspach… https://t.co/FeG7CPIcVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoiding social media b/c I've read 5 books on critical (Marxist) theory since Christmas &amp;… https://t.co/Ben9TVciF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Street noise: nineteenth-century Paris &amp; countryside for comparison... https://t.co/ChtukqAz9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBNo 11/20 Session IPA to round out a long day... @ The Jolly Butchers https://t.co/YuFqzOzHp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A(B+C)+D= uneven geography of sensory experience... We'll see how this turns out. https://t.co/p5pcYksOGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's the curl. https://t.co/Ok7PXCyJSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seraecbaker Thanks, I keep getting asked so, better share it w/ everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want a ex-sound engineer's tips on Podcasts &amp; Sound Production: Hardware? Well, I started a mini-series on the blog https://t.co/Fe0oDF1KlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo I just want to see Bill S. Preston, Esq vs Marty McFly in a battle of the 80s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great podcasts out there... https://t.co/YW4Kcud4C1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote a proposal for viva prep, now chopping thesis into the book. Intro is in the works... if I remember my colour… https://t.co/7fUhn3U7To]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/b61CUKBtBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@am_christensen John &amp; Paul discussing songwriting, ‘talking in music’ plays off rhythm &amp; understanding…  https://t.co/74cW08R5lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticking w/ the topic of Paris in the nineteenth-century for the next book from the Christmas… https://t.co/O367ZMcUb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to inform a Brit that most critical theory does not come out of Britain. He still wanted to argue me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Were I 2 bet, coming out of the pub, I wldn't expect 2 see an American wearing a baseball cap, smoking a pipe.' Obvs, U don't go 2 my pubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Session Cream Ale. The Saturday closer. @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/2n8N7iakck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Sat w/ these gems: The Dry Hopped Blonde, The Pale Ale &amp; The Experimental Imperial After… https://t.co/wiTdkKYh8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo that seems to be the good &amp; bad of Back to the Future movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DannyPAnderson great convo. You need more Marxist's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond Exactly! Best situation you never notice it. For podcasts, it doesn't mean tons of $, just good practices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond no prob! Spent a decade making (some terrible) things sound good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @ClassicsConfide use a simple (high-quality) field recorder so, not straight into a PC. Edits in GB. @mxmcadam @SarahEBond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond ...is key. Then U can balance vols &amp; eq out messiness. Better software =more options, not always necessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond lots of options, but min 2 mins through midi convert into GarageBand or better. Recording 2 lines.. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond having worked in live sound, $ &lt; time. Poor edit &amp; sound quality plague podcasts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pashulman @mxmcadam @SarahEBond worth looking at New Books Network https://t.co/3oDzXcAFxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evandeneykel @OAdonai @foxberrytoast @CEJBrenna currently jumping into other fav... https://t.co/MJ3kSBfWwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evandeneykel @oadonai @foxberrytoast @cejbrenna Agreed. Most of my beer sales are matching style, flavor &amp; brewing process to what ppl like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oadonai @evandeneykel @foxberrytoast @cejbrenna note what you like in beers, then look at ‘clones’ for ingredients. Lots of recipes online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catholickungfu @OAdonai @foxberrytoast @evandeneykel @CEJBrenna Go straight to all-grain brewing. You can make sourdough w/ leftover ingred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Geography is not an immutable thing. It is made, it is remade every day; at each instant it is modified by...action.' -E. Reclus 1905-8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I was going to be a neo-deconstructivist but mom wouldn't let me.' https://t.co/adZjYIhvyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllieMackin Yeah, that's a good one. I'm reading exam reports...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My current thoughts… Going for a cup of coffee right now. https://t.co/e5rsE1gNat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dessert. One of my favs. @ The Jolly Butchers https://t.co/WyekdbmtfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @raylaurence1 @gaffney_v @kdstrutt Well, I'm an archaeological photographer... https://t.co/ctbkJ0mbqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @raylaurence1 @gaffney_v @kdstrutt there can be only one. https://t.co/pwycWZWjE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post from earlier: using 3D models for research, not just pretty pics &amp; daylight analysis of shops. https://t.co/8ni9z1siiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenEllis74 @kaelinjewell @SarahEBond agreed, that's were both theory &amp; reconstruction should create a back-&amp;-forth. Not  linear progress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahEBond yes, I've had that convo w/ @StevenEllis74 as well. All models (3D or theoretical) should raise q's about sources.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post: Some Thoughts on 3D Models... https://t.co/8ni9z1siiS 
That's 1400 words &amp; fun w/ sun-path &amp; dynamic daylight models. Now #coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliemackin If Luther were around today, he would give Trump a run on Twitter trolling https://t.co/qzvFao13VH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LexiEikelboom sure, but rhythm is understood through 'hearing' (body &amp; ears). I lead w/ the auditory as a way into other the senses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesday roast. https://t.co/bzS5CdctVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @Ted_Underwood @github could build around 'rhythms' in data as 'music genres'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxberrytoast @LexiEikelboom I like the use of auditory metaphors in the posts. I think they are better descriptors of the complexity...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxberrytoast doing what @foxberrytoast does. https://t.co/pbzv0FGpWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s a model of internal daylight based on standard Ostia shop dimensions under a mezz fl… https://t.co/vl6h6g6m1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, well, well… All that banging on about shadows &amp; sun paths in models… This is fun. https://t.co/drGMG4MQxb Her… https://t.co/W1RuDrauJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pompei79 yes, exactly! I've already been through Italian copy a couple of times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pompei79 heard Carandini present on it. Lots of great pics &amp; Carandini saying, 'Oh, this is nice.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Christmas book started today... https://t.co/rpAEHuGSeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Lefebvre? Plus, new project Rome in Lefebvre's thought https://t.co/l9FS6O6amW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo like the surf-guitar &amp; mid-low distortion of tunnel shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post: #Lefebvre &amp; Ancient Space https://t.co/l9FS6O6amW Resources &amp; a writing project for the new year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DefJenWreckers a derby version of A New Hope. https://t.co/Z4cyndaaKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain does Haussmann. @ Letchworth https://t.co/6VxS3q5s79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK's first roundabout. All downhill from here... @ Letchworth https://t.co/XFPsC4jv2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: you want this beer.... @ Anspach &amp; Hobday https://t.co/ztH6eNvhtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @AnspachHobday &amp; found out I appeared in a Japanese mag. So, I got that going for me... https://t.co/eWHPfoXGuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lefebvre cover. Good to be back south of the river... https://t.co/BGwz7DtKot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@electricarchaeo @pompei79 drinks all around!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ewg118 @raylaurence1 @SarahEBond @pompei79 it's a mix, some is pre-Calza excavations. Depends on the street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raylaurence1 @pompei79 @SarahEBond @Pompeiana79 I hope it's a well heated rut...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AM_Christensen @MarriottLibrary just noticed *cold not intended vols]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>