<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[So maybe we should get a free pass on "Godwinning the thread" when it comes to YouKnowWho - because, really, he deserves the comparison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. What a match. Although I really wanted my man @Rafa to win - that was quite exceptional. So fantastic to see them again #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VAMOS! Oh bliss a 5-setter! C'mon Rafa (although these two are so wonderful I almost don't want anyone to lose) #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just in awe of that last shot by #Nadal. Pure poetry #FedererNadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa Federer won the first set, Rafa looks like winning the second - he's at 5:2 w Fed serving. It's epic already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's so great about this final is that they've both still got it. Beautiful tennis Roger and Rafa #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't be long until Dimitrov is a champion. What an amazing match #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.cant.breathe #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yussss! I just frightened my cat off the sofa with my victory yell for that tie break win. Go Rafa! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!! C'mon Rafa - give us the dream final we all want xxx #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh America - what have you done???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear USA - vote with love today, vote wisely, (&amp; dance a little!) https://t.co/ZcgXlV7fl2 - the world is holding its collective breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an excellent article - The New Yorker Endorses Hillary Clinton https://t.co/iZBTs9xeUI via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Wallabies you really pushed us hard - you had us for the first 65 minutes at least. Thanks for a great game! Go the ABs #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful try by Savea! Yay! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG THAT WAS AMAZING!!! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Score! That didn't take long.... :) #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimmin heck - that was some haka! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right then @AllBlacks - let's break some records and make history #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, the world loves Obama, you twat. The world despises and is horrified by you  #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey that was an utterly MASTERFUL performance by the All Blacks. Lovely to watch #RSAvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished @lecretiaschoice by my lovely friend @mattvarchar - compelling &amp; unputdownable - beautifully written story of 2 beautiful ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to an #AbFab party 2morrow. Am highly amused that I can source entire Edina outfit from clothes currently in my wardrobe #greattaste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came face to face with a hawk/raptor type bird in the Botanic Garden this morning. Kewl! Never seen one in Welli before #WildWellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShambushEvents just had the best time with the Kates in Wellington, New Zealand #DayofWuthering #Shambush https://t.co/6CW3GYHhWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameron, Johnson, Farage. Rats leaving the sinking ship that THEY sank. A bunch of cowardly hypocritical lying dickweasels #YouWontBeMissed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimmin heck! Now Farage is gone as well! Hooray and - is there going to be a single Brexit "mastermind" left by the end of the month?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badgermat I note he has also described himself as temperamentally unsuitable to be Prime Minister. So that's good #whothefuckisgove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right then pommy pals - what's the deal with Gove? Can anyone give me a quick summary/backgrounder? #betterthanboris ? #whothefuckisgove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell. British politics just gets weirder and weirder and more like a soap opera every day #Brexit #BoriscantHackIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be a proud Kiwi, but I'm also still a UK citizen. Petition: EU Referendum Rules triggering a 2nd EU Referendum https://t.co/jKJRuRL21R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today looks like it's going to be a good demonstration of why I quit being a Pom nearly 25 years ago...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping that common sense will win out over xenophobia and racism #Brexit #remain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikePethig wow how time flies when you're having fun! I thought August for my 20th anniversary - forgot I knew HTML b4 I went freelance ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SKYGO you are so annoying - jumping and stuttering and pausing all over the place. Aargh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Primetv_NZ fantastic! Thanks so much for the tip! Now all I want is for Soundbreaking to be made available on DVD...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted that MySky failed to record Soundbreaking on @Primetv_NZ - the Four on the Floor episode! Aargh! Anyone know where/how I can see it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to say, "Soundbreaking" on @Primetv_NZ is really bloody marvellous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank in that case you are completely forgiven :) Thanks v much for making the effort to find out. Great news &amp; great service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank online banking will not let me pay IRD bill (due today, Sat) until Mon, 2 days late (incurring a fine). This is CRAP. #fixyrbank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Wellington's cultural &amp; creative heart is being shut down by new neighbours who can't handle inner city noise https://t.co/ikfqtrSnWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pepsico makes billions while plantation workers are cheated out of fair pay &amp; benefits. #ConflictPalmOil https://t.co/SWpKDnaebw #immoral]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank goodness the awful Lockwood clip art tea towel didn't win. I wouldn't mind a change, but it needs to be a great design #nzflag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc phew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh noes! My new fridge is smaller than my old fridge on the inside while being the same size on the outside. It's like a reverse Tardis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't have minded a change. But the awful Lockwood clip art tea towel is nowhere near good enough to be our new flag #nzflag #RedPeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody Microsoft - why did you have to ruin Skype? Latest update didn't recognise username, email or password &amp; where is my contact list??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank thanks - that's good to know and a definite improvement. Why can't you extend that into nighttime as well? Surely mostly automatic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank it's VERY ANNOYING when I do an online GST payment to IRD and it won't go through until the day after tomorrow. WHY? #gonnagetfined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squee! We bought the beach! How blimmin cool is that? Shows the power of a great idea and what we can achieve when we all work together xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy that we hit $2million today. What an amazing Kiwi effort. And to my lovely #Webstock pals - don't forget to pledge! #buythebeach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csswizardry - hope you have had the BEST time at Webstock - it was great to see you here :) how was your fan club this evening? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord. I just don't get it Cindy. I'm somewhat horrified #webstock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting! #GiftAbelTasmanBeach just reached $1.5mill - and in The Guardian https://t.co/bgXjPbMKAi - c'mon Kiwis! We can do this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sineadboucher looks like the GiveALittle site can't handle the traffic right now - could be a good sign, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy moley it's almost a Democrat dead heat in Iowa - c'mon Bernie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas tree is finally coming down :( https://t.co/OKCho8XAuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So TVNZ couldn't afford to keep TVNZ7 (&amp; lied about the viewing nos) but they can afford a new channel just for blokes? What bollocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh nooooo - not Alan Rickman too? *sniff*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[would I have voted for changing to a different flag, do I think @AllBlacks flag should have been one of the choices. #redpeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got opinion polled about the #nzflag - which party do I vote for, will I vote for new flag, what do I think of the "design" of it 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DavidBowie - today i remember that awesome Serious Moonlight Tour gig Andy &amp; I went to in Sydney. Travel well Starman. You were perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronyaB oh well if Mr Fry says so, then it must be ok!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaupapa genius! Followed by Midwinter Tree, Spring Tree and then oh look - it's a Christmas Tree :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UmbrellarNZ all sorted, thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do you take your Christmas tree down? I've never had one before and I love it so much I want to keep it up for a while. June, maybe? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UmbrellarNZ - how can I rate yr help desk service when u haven't helped me! Submitted ticket on Dec 27 &amp; I'm still waiting #crappyservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got home after watching #StarWars - IT'S BLOODY BRILLIANT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norightturnnz fantastic! Thanks so much. I have just emailed you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norightturnnz hello! I imagine you're pretty busy, but can I email you about the wording of an OIA request?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Hedgehog Rescue NZ https://t.co/yBEWP1xGuT - got back home from delivering him to find Thorby II snorfling around on the path! 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa found this little guy on my path today. Meet Thorby I - 3 weeks old, now safely with the lovely people at 1/2 https://t.co/xUXrm6KSJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashmahal save us from bloody awful "design" worthy only to be a tea towel. Ugh. I will continue to fly #RedPeak cos I have found my flag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah. @dooce is coming to @webstock - that's pretty cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I'm drowning in emails :( #alittlelessconversation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squee! Finally got my flag flying. I hereby claim the Kelburn / Northland / Highbury junction for #RedPeak https://t.co/AfXdeaTcwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamhowe yes it wd invalidate your vote. U must not write the same number more than once. Vote 1 for #RedPeak &amp; leave the others blank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ClimateMarch https://t.co/kC2mlJ4hAq - hi @rnz_news pls revisit yr numbers! Should be 6,000 in Wellington and 15,000 in Auckland. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a great #ClimateMarch - we had a big turnout in Wellington. Thanks Vlad for the use of the caixa ;) https://t.co/Zw4O9KatHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join us at the Wellington #ClimateMarchNewZealand - Civic Sq to Parliament https://t.co/o4GXZ3h7g6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voted! Just picked the good one - didn't bother ranking the other 4. Am i allowed to say which one I voted for? #RedPeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@norightturnnz: Good riddance to snout and the PM's personal dirt-digger https://t.co/O0n0aKY32Z” Ha! Nothing more than she deserved :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh #Webstock! How could you make me choose between workshops w @beep &amp; @karenmcgrane and @csswizardry &amp; @lukew??? *sobs* Too much goodness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Jonah! How sad. Rest in peace Jonah Lomu - you were AWESOME. Spectacular video of all his international tries https://t.co/WJ30VP2zVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That #PikeRiver documentary was so desperately sad #wheresthebloodyjustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sigh* I really hate it when recruitment agents reformat my beautifully formatted &amp; perfectly laid out CV. I did it my way FOR A REASON guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so quiet outside. I think the whole country has gone back to bed for a celebratory snooze and a bit of a lie-in #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go for it Dan!  #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now would be good ABs #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok ABs - you've had your little rest - now it's time to get back in the game again. C'mon! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and a no-arms tackle from someone too #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seem to be rather a lot of head-high tackles by the Wallabies... #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YUSSSSSSSS! You could see it was only a matter of time. C'mon boys!!! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some amazing turnover being won by the #AllBlacks #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy moley! I'm freaking my cat out with all the screaming and yelling ;) #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a good haka #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squee! Nervous but excited. Go the AllBlacks! #NZLvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh! I appear to be supporting Argentina, going by the enthusiasm with which I greeted that little run #AusvArg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey that was quick #AusvArg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>