<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Dutton backs Donald Trump's 'mandate' to enforce travel ban https://t.co/93PpPDOdLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cameronsincIair @Paul_Karp think he cares?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1johnhampshire @smh I reckon it's a good idea. Worth trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara no, it's aimed at those who do nothing in times of moral crisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's folly is a once-in-a-century opportunity for Australia https://t.co/r4ujbr7zyc via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hottest places in hell' reserved for those remaining neutral: Former US Ambassador unleashes on Trump https://t.co/0UrtBSNpiY via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Abbott rebuffed after attacking Turnbull government on renewable energy target https://t.co/IhbzN9AGPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Morrison says Trump travel ban shows 'world is catching up' to Australia https://t.co/kADnwVWEqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavJenks @steph_gardiner Thanks for letting me know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answer: no RT Can we really call schools private when they get so much public money?

https://t.co/4Q9RWXoVMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajamesbragg fake think-tank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's absolutely right. Why would they spend so much time thinking about one of their single biggest recurring expen… https://t.co/GTwrr3HNxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Parkinson accepts Australia Day honour with stark economic warning https://t.co/9fEFo4tirI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what Trump voters said when asked to compare his inauguration crowd with Obama's https://t.co/IBIHq2aMRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm &amp; Lucy Turnbull, Peter Cosgrove, &amp; some of Aust's newest citizens (from Pakistan, Brazil, UK, US, China, Italy, Nigeria, Zimbabwe).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At citizenship ceremony in Canberra, a British lady, who's just bcome an Australian, was asked why she wanted c'ship: "Um, Brexit actually."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull addressing the Australia Day ceremony in Canberra. "My family's migrant story, like all of yours,… https://t.co/ikNjLNsaL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated Centrelink a fast track to Turnbull's demise https://t.co/yMFIyXetje via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola isn't it? more of these please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first days inside Trump’s White House: Fury, tumult and a reboot https://t.co/DQhAz4qt9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources say Trump's CIA visit made relations with intel community worse https://t.co/mmXyD95CHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumdav fanciful is the perfect word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara And it therefore wouldn't be the TPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@timwilsoncomau the TPP can't go ahead without the US. Re: the 85% rule. The US is critical. Read the final chapter https://t.co/vKFqrY7XCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull and the TPP: desperately pressing ahead despite negligible benefits

https://t.co/89wYdx1bSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[completely agree https://t.co/2NxPpF5xsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara the one weekend I wasn't there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a 'friend' says you should've been here.. https://t.co/Kcd62ryRnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. I've finally been summoned. https://t.co/EnunEQmar7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When was the last time that a retraction request so thoroughly confirmed a story?" https://t.co/6cEpNeflCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New South Wales premier Mike Baird announces retirement https://t.co/cq4bLQQgNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian pollies, like @SenatorMRoberts &amp; @mattjcan, have begun exploiting the term #fakenews, but this is what F… https://t.co/QG24ELdyq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts @quelsemme Pauline and I received an invitation (bcos we pestered) but not the PM (bcos he didn't ask for one) #fakeinvite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo-debt: Centrelink workers threatened with prosecution as bosses try to stem the leaks https://t.co/dW78bWh4dE via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor's Chris Bowen pushes for more women in senior finance roles https://t.co/R4mJZxqOuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gordonkerry not sure, according to wikipedia he is..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blokey culture of finance means we're missing out on a mountain of ability | Chris Bowen https://t.co/mabLba9e0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos wants to use America's schools to build "God's kingdom." She's about to get her chance. https://t.co/UeQCrISYgX via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor pushes for Senate inquiry into Centrelink robo-debt 'debacle' https://t.co/nZA7XLtwWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen Have a nice day, Van xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen Fair enough. Just got tired of reading more of your conspiracies. Carry on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen tht's ur best evidence? a derivative i/v based off the same i/v? Your RDN hate's clouding ur judgement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen That's not a matter of record. You're deliberately reading that literally for your own ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen "Precisely what he wants"? Has he told you that has he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bilbulbabe @vanbadham @smithmeyerjen it's ridiculous to get from that i/v that RDN's desperate for an alliance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham @Bilbulbabe @smithmeyerjen @HkarterKarter @EdwardJWHunter that's a ridiculous reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surge in marine life caught in NSW shark nets  https://t.co/suzy9maIj2 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plans for Australia to adopt a 'Google tax' welcomed by advocacy group https://t.co/nu2PcCMWZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinJBettles Oh okay thank you. Much clearer. So that bit about keeping his own phone and car, as though it makes a difference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinJBettles dear translator, what does that actually mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumdav Fake Representation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ping @mattjcan RT Crying 'fake news' is handy for politicians but toxic for democracy | Lenore Taylor https://t.co/cvkZ9GTPpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajamesbragg So taxes on people do create jobs! Good to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajamesbragg Hey Andrew, any new publications coming from your taxpayer funded think-tank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Keating castigates Rex Tillerson over comments on China https://t.co/HFwvHAHsIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banker caught up in Malaysian 1MDB scandal went on $8.2m Gold Coast property splurge https://t.co/YxIL7JPHqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A message to my doomed colleagues in the American media” by @Alexey__Kovalev https://t.co/qN2Nbb7hhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queensland MP Steve Dickson defects from LNP to join One Nation https://t.co/bXJ2X4iN3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump berated a CNN reporter, and fellow journalists missed an opportunity https://t.co/Yton4Ashyb via @cjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note to Centrelink: Australian workers' lives have changed https://t.co/VgZA60qAZy via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left Renewal: since when has taxing the rich &amp; saving the planet been so controversial? @leerhiannon &amp;@ShoebridgeMLC https://t.co/o20wQj6bV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and now for the Weapon of Stats destruction.. https://t.co/kNXz4Lv9Yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgnosis after all that time you'd have every right to keep it to yourself, but you didn't. Very generous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a bonus public service: Crikey puts the data into a spreadsheet. https://t.co/dqxKVQ8EVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government Begins Collecting Debt From Those Found Rorting Taxpayer Dollars | SBS Comedy https://t.co/Ym56cx94MI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatsKarvelas also helps to be a cabinet minister ($336,599) and to get $360 travel allowance for 1 night (compared to $264 a WEEK Newstart)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sussan Ley bought $795,000 flat on impulse on taxpayer-funded trip, from Liberal Party donor https://t.co/vsw2LlKcYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Centrelink’s data-matching process is so unfathomably high it would send a commercial enterprise out of business" https://t.co/A3WiwetB6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I was wrong on house prices in 2016 – and why I might still be proved right | Stephen Koukoulas https://t.co/jjtz79qM9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Company tax cuts wrong move, says Costello https://t.co/RQi5ZMkaSo via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've created their own evidence! Hope the response is not to cut funding to Centrelink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #Centrelink debacle is amazing. It's been initiated by a govt that believes govts make a hash of things &amp; therefore should be smaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaires get more leeway than vulnerable citizens. It’s obscene | Richard Denniss https://t.co/6AU3kgIiYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@1petermartin on the #Centrelink debacle

"[This] will doubtless be the subject of a Senate inquiry and probably a… https://t.co/RNVWQ8EV6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There were 1,224 inmates in the prison, built for 592. The prison's run by a private company that's paid according… https://t.co/uZgZr3Ldga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToniHassan It's not the same thing as having a nap in a driverless car on the freeway. He would've surfed anyway.The technology's doubtful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surfer gets shark-repellant device for xmas present, gets attacked the next day https://t.co/LnNoBUX6wW #Surfline via @Surfline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink's debt mistake: 'there's no way I could explain to them' https://t.co/aXxSkQbPS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Berger, art critic and author, dies aged 90 https://t.co/9e9rHul1ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetowncrier I'm a year older than Thomas Jefferson when he authored the DECLARATION OF INDEPENDENCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @MarieCo92176893 @GuardianAus it'd be good to see the breakdown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenPhillips_ANU @MarieCo92176893 @GuardianAus That's the govt's figure in MYEFO. They also say spots have increased 150,000 in last 2 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critic of Labor's GFC stimulus package paid $16,000 for Treasury paper labelling it counterproductive https://t.co/RhpIVVdXZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Martin: Labor ought to stop pandering to millionaires https://t.co/f2mI30GwTd via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Hawke blames decline in quality of politicians on intrusiveness of media https://t.co/PiH2LWqnaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBA broker tops fines list https://t.co/hjdBjKHXnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp true love is like Medicare - it's for all Australians, but the government's never believed in it, and now it wants to privatise it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@umabp "true love's like the Constitution - it's important, we know we should respect it, but you always wants to blow it up and start over"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call to suspend Centrelink system after single mother receives $24,000 debt notice https://t.co/kYFNoVjHbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's first solar panel road opens in Normandy village https://t.co/q0dU4BdURR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderfully written piece, as always https://t.co/3Px0FTWF1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo We're not going to engage with hypotheticals, Murph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mathias Cormann refuses to express confidence in Alan Finkel after climate criticism https://t.co/JRZ6Azzjyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef the answer was quite clear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo that's a shame @MattGlassDarkly. Can I ask how long ago that was? Here's an interesting piece on optimism https://t.co/j7bh8rGszP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor attacks 'treasury' report discrediting economic stimulus  https://t.co/7DuaHmKyYJ via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @1petermartin I can hear him from here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@1petermartin what do you have against Australian authors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can't wait to read the peer-reviewed study on the fed govt's response to the GFC in @simonbenson's story today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Vocal minority': Wife of Liberal Party powerbroker quits over lack of action on climate change  https://t.co/UW38A0wXUs via @smh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>