<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebeccaMorin_ @politico @VP Get rid of Bannon and Sessions maybe Indiana could hold there heads up. We are 48 out of 50 worse state 2 live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary You are for racism? He and Bannon are one of the reasons we will not stop marching. #TheResistance #changenow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ttancredo a legislator hummm.#TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @SperoNews humm you people of sane mind and body. I don't see anyone here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @SperoNews From a savage. #TheResistance #NoBanNoWall #impeachTrumpnow #nobannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SperoNews Thanks this Bud's for you! #TheResistance #impeachTrumpnow #nobannon #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SperoNews My nephew was stationed in Kuwait thank you to the Syrian people for you kindness #impeachTrumpnow #NoBanNoWall #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SperoNews Yes thank you Budweiser. #TheResistance #impeachTrumpnow #noracism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenoroho Whatch this guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenoroho #impeachTrump#theResistsence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews F*ck you racists. #impeachTrumpnow #NoBanNoWall #TheResistance #nobannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @BreitbartNews Well look how fair Breibart News has reached.  Check out this page @FAIRImmigration well well. #nobannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeOutLondon Thank you for your solidarity. We are greater together. #TheResistance #impeachTrumpnow #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Londonist Thank you for your solidarity. The American people. #TheResistance #NoBanNoWall #ImpeachTrump #noracism #no bannon #nokkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanAdamini Let's go everyone next time he's on air and ask him to clarify. #NoBanNoWall #ImpeachTrump #TheResistance @CNN @maddow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheriJarodus C*nt troll. Block this account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @ezlusztig @realDonaldTrump The so called president needs to step down. Stop embarrassing the PEOPLE of the USA. #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janicemiller621 @DeanLeh One is a true man and the other @POTUS is a so called man. #ImpeachTrump #Nokkk #SoCalledPOTUS #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Yes @CNN I always watch. That other show um...faux I hated it. Stopped watching it along time ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @KellyannePolls I think I seen a cup today for you. UNT but the ear made a C. #ImpeachTrump #NoBanNoWall #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewMccon Don't tell us to back this madman you call President. #NoToMatthew #Impeachtrump #WeAreAllImmigrants… https://t.co/ET873nlVSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill No President Obama did this. The poll was taken in Oct. Sorry @PressSec you lied again. #WeAreAllImmigrants #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Trump trolls. Why aren't they following fox news since it's trump TV? #impeachTrumpnow #BowlingGreenMasacre… https://t.co/13qsEUMVu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdKnowsStuff he's pitiful 15 followers. Troll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdKnowsStuff @CNN well Ed why aren't you on the fox twitter page after all they are the real news for you people. https://t.co/FAVRFQTt8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @POTUS We are watching. Are you allowing Russia to kill innocent people? Where is your outrage? And you want our military to respect u?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @POTUS What are you going to do?...................... Waiting...............]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJEnglish @POTUS You are making the world loathe you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent I love Budweiser. Thanks trumpets. More for true Americans. They probably drink moonshine in their trailers anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews @PressSec Can you ever really answer a question? Ut oh a question. He'll start stuttering now. You are weak. #impeachment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaChilders1 @KellyannePolls Oohh the horror. #DressLikeAWoman #Impeach45 #kellyannefacts #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msfried315 @mecLovesAmerica @Salon @SpeakerRyan I resign. Just do it. You can do it. And go hide your lying face.… https://t.co/KFc4cuKvLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@civilrightsorg @SpeakerRyan haha he doesn't have balls. Won't be re elected let alone President. https://t.co/zDOg9xteod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent I think women should sue if made to have oral sex. ALL THOSE BABIES!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews I think Bannon should go to private sector. His views are not America's. #DressLikeAWoman #TheResistance #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio @48Gailschwerdt @POTUS He is so incompetent. He learns from TV. He thinks he's Rambo. He's probably looking up competent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Impeach_D_Trump I agree. Maybe his hands would look bigger if people that he was WOMAN. #DressLikeAWomen #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #noban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfore0142 @PressSec Be sure to mention the Bowling Green Massacre victims. https://t.co/VfVLLRi5rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfore0142 @PressSec He is a wee little man in a big suit. #RacistWH #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #Impeachpresidentbannon #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_youhadonejob1 @mfore0142 one for @KellyannePolls desk. I bet she would like it. Going to order one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victims of Bowling Green massacre @KellyannePolls sad so sad. #NeverForgotten https://t.co/jADcERfm89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek @FluffscruffJrs How many more Russians are going to fill the WH? https://t.co/kfLrDWQzW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffthelad 😂😂😂going to borrow it. #NeverForget #bowlinggreenmassacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinOMalley @POTUS @ProSyn  Many,  not just millennials are resisting trump. He is losing those who voted for him. #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizenCohn @JimCassidy48 @HuffPostPol Let me guess @SpeakerRyan doesn't know what to do. Vote out all Republicans! Not for the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow  Seems trump trolls are following you. Sad so sad. #ImpeachTrumpYesterday #trumprussia #TrumpTaxes #theResistanse #trumpsdone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow  Bannon, Bannon? I bet he doesn't know they're black folks there. You know how bigly dumb trumps loyalists are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GabeS1313 @thehill Another trump voter needs some schooling. You can always spot em. #ImpeachTrump #nomuslimban #TrumpVotersNeedNewTrailers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtnance1 @thehill well Robert looks like you need a little school there idiot. What is ediots? a trump voter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hogsett aide apologizes for Facebook comments https://t.co/g5zgVoLoWE via @indystar Calling them coons! Racist and black. Indiana!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State worker says he was fired for being a Democrat https://t.co/vRgvNFiazb via @indystar Here's Indiana for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren I think you are a c*nt. Not because I've meet you but because I can. #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #TrumpRussia #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill @LindseyGrahamSC  Finally, thank you. AMERICA. #TrumpRussia #TrumpTaxes #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior There's a picture of you in the room when Sean Spicer gave a speech. Was you there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill I remember when people didn't trust Putin. I still don't. And people believe it's not about the power and greed and oil. #impeach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @dailykos @PressSec So we don't have to him stuttering his lies anymore yes! I love @CNN #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #Trumprussia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FluffscruffJrs @dailykos @tedcruz Liar with a girls voice. You are out of here! Go get em @alfranken. #kkkTrump #Trumprussia #stopsessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And everyone asks " why we don't trust the police". Our rights are lost. #ImpeachTrump #NotMyAmerica #Trumprussia… https://t.co/nMjsJpdeMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Section_131 @LindseyGrahamSC @SenJohnMcCain And nothing sad about what Russia is doing in the Ukraine? Wtf. People never vote Rep. again!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics @JK_Columbus Grandfather died of black lung in Tennessee. Hope they sue @realDonaldTrump when they start dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeedNews @realDonaldTrump the show sucks. Nobody watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjferg1252 @nuzzel @CNN You must be doing something right. I support and watch CNN. #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #Trumprussia #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior what's up with you and Flynn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morrison_deb @SenSchumer @NancyPelosi @sarahkendzior @intelligencer Why is Sarah there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust We didn't vote for @realDonaldTrump he lost by 3 million votes. We the true Americans apologize. #ImpeachTrump #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken Will you run for President? We are voting the Republicans out! @HouseGOP you are out of the house come election. We are woke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LotteLeicht1 @hrw @realDonaldTrump do something! We are watching you. Show us you are not in Putin's pocket. Now is the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How are you going to help Ukraine? Stand for something! They are being slaughtered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorSessions You are a racist and everyone knows! You will not last. #NoSessions #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #NoDAPL #TheResistance #MarchOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarrietBaldwin sorry Harriet it was towards another. My bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @Mediaite @tedcruz I can't take his voice and his lies. I will read about it. I'm sure the American people are Fkd anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP @POTUS We deserve an answer on this. So tired of all the lies. #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #NotoPresidentBannon #TheResistance #NoSessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cspan @HarriotBaldwin is a trump troll. An extremist for war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LEMONADE1992 Send all your family to fight a war a madman has been wanting. For glory money and greed. #NotMyPresidentTrump #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec  your stuttering lies will end you! Hey get a suit that fits. Hey tell you boss NOBODY will fight along side Russia. #TrumpRussia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @HouseGOP All you Republicans are racists. Sessions? We will vote you all out. #TrumpPutin #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #WeMarchOn #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedcruz  wow short memory. Oh and I HATE your voice it even makes my dog howl. Can you just write it down and show… https://t.co/W2mbQ7wntX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent Are people still watching @FoxNews ? My mom even stopped. She is a trumpgreter. It's a ridiculous show (not news). #Trumpgrets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why when you were doing your little skit for Black History Month was President Bannon not present? Just wondering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maitlandscully @SenateGOP People vote out your Republican! Spineless. #ImpeachTrump #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE #WeMarchOn #nobannon #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @tedcruz on his phone tweeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenBannon We are watching and waiting. You will be escorted out of OUR house. #ImpeachTrump #bannonroast #NoBanNoWall #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joselouis4077 @mfore0142 @politicususa @cherokeesher2 We dump trump too. #ImpeachTrump #TrumpTaxes #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GinsburgJobs @KoleHam @TPM @FoxNews They say whatever trump wants them to. Nobody watches them Mr. Trudeau. #ImpeachTrump #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCOUT @NBCNews LGBTQ makes up a lot of our military. With rumors of war with China this makes sense. Bannon needs to go! #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory @pahstock Good I watch CNN and hate @KellyannePolls she lies. And she scares my kids. #impeachment #cleanhouse #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertCKeating @SpeakerRyan You are a F*cking waste of time. #NoFkRyan #NoBanNoWall #impeachment #TrumpTaxes #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimTomJazz @DavidCornDC @tedcruz Didn't trump say something nasty about your wife Ted? Grow a pair of balls. Oh and I hate your voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harleydavidson Follows the American dream. #NoTrumpVisit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @politicususa @harleydavidson You guys rock. Thank you. #theresistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @POTUS Shameful people you are. Jewish and Christian? I don't think so. https://t.co/loDEmT7YyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Blocking Judicial Watch. Oh and FK you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Fact #ImpeachTrump #NoBanNoWall #ChildrenoftheRevolution #theresistence https://t.co/XqcJCk8Rgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@worldonalert @IvankaTrump @SpeakerRyan You feel good about hiding the truth about Russia? #theresistence #ImpeachTrump #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sentinelred @DarioDiBattista Again Bryon Fk off. Does anyone no this fk?#NoBanNoWall #impeach #theresistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sentinelred @DarioDiBattista Fk you Bryon you been there? STFU. Loyalists to trump. #QuebecCityMosqueShooting… https://t.co/yfj0QlyMQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarioDiBattista @IvankaTrump #NoBanNoWall #ChildrenoftheRevolution #resisttrumptuesday #theresistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lieslelove Never do. #NoBanNoWall #ImpeachTrump #WeMarchOn #theresistence #TrumpTaxReturns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump #NoBanNoWall #QuebecCityMosqueShooting #StandUpToTrump #WeMarchOn #theresistence https://t.co/b4gOFiRIao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Be sure and look. #NoBanNoWall #TrumpProtest #theresistence #MuslimChildren #QuebecCityMosqueShooting https://t.co/LWMC9k3aMr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>