<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic @dont_utter you won't even notice it slip by ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend beautiful ðŸ˜I have a fave b&amp;w of you going out the door - stunningðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is an apprentice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seem quickest way for me to blunt my knife is to sharpen my knife - lessons required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kris_Bartley Happy Birthday Kris, hope you are having an amazing day!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ @GoodBitchesBake that's gotta make things better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitbitSupport what's going on here I have developed a big bubble ðŸ˜¢ https://t.co/ezeHMWb3Uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz was about to dsy ow pod the garden looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx that's awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chocolate Zuchinni cake my @GoodBitchesBake this week. Vegetables for the night shelter ðŸ™„ https://t.co/q1VGl0nvE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic I'm sorry ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghettoanger learning those "who would you throw overboard " life skills ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic what's happened ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gurrlwithacurl perfection times twoðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gurrlwithacurl perfection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic @dont_utter what she said ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic Good luck hope all goes well ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend but if you had allowed 40 mins it would have taken an hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx ffs some things are crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic it's allowed ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz it's beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic not your problem! Also if manipulating by guilt you may not want them as tenants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffinmum I grew up using this term]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend I think so if that's ok not sure how it works - but will figure it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pregtester I'd get them stuffed and planted at the end of the prints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend what's goal day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic happy to talk - dm or text over the w/end and we can perhaps arrange to meet next week sometime if that works for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic I have good answers to this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrafteaChic just be kind to yourself and your feelings it's all real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ the moment you think about it, if that moment has passed go back in time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvenCoven Some for GBB and some for hubbies office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nastone72 good luck with that ðŸ˜Ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a while since I've been a @GoodBitchesBake Raspberry and Lemon heading to the night shelter https://t.co/2CeVZj4iER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend thinking of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz @gurrlwithacurl I have a friend who bikes with the change crew and they seem so awesome - so supportive &amp; great results go you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the cakes https://t.co/IkVmYD8q3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx good for you for getting it underway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If that wind is due to be double those last gusts, I don't think we will be here tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendyWings and when we did get it, it was still quicker to use a book ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beekaynz I thought I was living in a bubble not knowing this but was perplexed when there was not one apple at New World on sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gurrlwithacurl I'm with you there!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attempting to cull piles and piles of gym clothes - that went well ... I left the house for coffee it's all too hard https://t.co/ef7eOh0l8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz @gurrlwithacurl enough it I'll do it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz @gurrlwithacurl sitting in a cafe I literally just spat my coffee out reading that ðŸ˜„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The yummiest Quinoa and Chia Seed sweet treats https://t.co/xj3x06Bysd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx so that's ..it arrived at the us warehouse on friday according to tracking, they told me they had it on the Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx mine arrived on a friday and I was notified Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dairymanNZ guess I'm living in the past then ðŸ˜€ searching for eternal youth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend  o but I did get this photo sent to me https://t.co/YumdwQGzhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home alone and trying to make a meal from leftovers &amp; scraps while the boys eat fries at the soccer ðŸ™„ https://t.co/rcdl4bBz33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend I was curiousðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould baby steps ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beekaynz good for you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I mention I also swam a kilometer ðŸ¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have also made protein muffins and a not Christmas cake just to balance out my lifeðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I have done handstands, forward rolls and 60 burpeesðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews @BesameCosmetics You're right I needed to see that ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ they knew about your meetingðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikCarmichael where does one put 64 pairs of shoesðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dont_utter sorryðŸ˜¢some people eh! Can't choose family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend i am a master at thisðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvenCoven not for long ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz @Capt_Caffiend Oh man that's not what you need to come home to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikCarmichael looks like a pretty delicious routine to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz such a lovely photo ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend distant wave back ðŸ˜€and happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz where are you camping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a pet st the beach  and then left him behind. Good thing we never had kidsðŸ˜³ https://t.co/4w0RZzDrYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz best place to beðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paolabrett @cassieroma @kevinandamanda @WendyWings best butter converter ðŸ˜„https://t.co/JURtdUHsqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz I'm sorry- that's stinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx yeah we saw it too wondered if we were right but boy it moves fast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvenCoven @CrafteaChic are you sure they got it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ noðŸ˜³they came to my house several times and I always had an issue with itðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy ðŸ˜ https://t.co/xhjCB3qpYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz @mwgnz I want to cry right now - what year are we in not that this shit was ever ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwgnz @thedemlz my thoughts too photos are always good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I really want for Christmas is my carpark back ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz jeepers, dedication beyond the call of duty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedemlz maybe they haven't got it yet, pretty sure mine only got it today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay my #nzsecretsanta finally got her gift ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend so happy for you - well doneðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capt_Caffiend @CafeWeka we were all spoilt with a great selection ðŸ˜›]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffinmum That's awesome! well done you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muffinmum mine hasn't even got hers yet, I can't believe how long it's taking - seem weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dont_utter so frustrating that it takes so long, but good to have some answers â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dont_utter how's your husband doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdoughnutterx hope all went well - take careâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will my @nzsecretsanta ever get her parcel.  I'm going to out myself to her soon I feel so bad for her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wildechick  never doubted it for a moment... p.s. you looking mighty fine in that latest photo, only just caught up on it. ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wildechick @thekitchenmaid That's a lot of christmas ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my poor #nzsecretsanta giftee still hasn't got her gift ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CafeWeka that's so cool ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShoreGirlyGirl sounds awful, I think you should send to someone as punishment and just so you know I was naughty today. ðŸ˜Š Well done - enjoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay @MrsGreatnews nice to hear your voice, on my old people radio station ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dont_utter oh dear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimtairi @nzsecretsanta I know right!!!!!!!!! amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow ...I think my #nzsecretsanta has me pegged, a big big thank you who ever you are ðŸ˜ https://t.co/7D0G5XV3Mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicNicNZ @billymurray33 how cool is thatðŸ˜˜see the difference you make the gift that keeps on givingðŸ˜have an amazing Christmas &amp; breakâ˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Husband thinks I should have left this guy in America but he makes a great door stopðŸ˜³ https://t.co/pIQ37e1QNt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>