<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher it was fun! Had a good one man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We finally got our brands today and I got "Sassy Goofball", where is the lie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa rip (me too though)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SomerHollings #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever just have a nap and wake up feeling like you're in a different dimension? Because me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa it made me fall in love with Ryan Gosling again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervinJohnsonTV @vickycheaa I'm an apartment gal myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell when I have my period because I will willingly watch 'Try not to cry challenges' and sob heavily through the whole thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I'll just stick to communicating to people via the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervinJohnsonTV yeah thats what I'm talking about. I realise its only for awhile but its still for a while ya know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meladoodle thats so awesome congratulations!! I'm so proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reading these articles with tears in my eyes as years of rallying have been stolen yet again from women. Why should choice be illegal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharelleClare its like 50 shades of grey/black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa cries in jealousy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa that place is always packed and ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was supposed to be hosting a party tonight but everyone flaked so its cancelled... guess whos netflix and chilling with herself then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/QtmrbusSuN Tora - Jaigantic (Galimatias Remix)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher eyyyy thanks Stephen! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My summer of 2016 in 90 seconds: https://t.co/9wdpy3CQqL via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I added a video to a @YouTube playlist https://t.co/znQZcHURiP sakehands - ã€ŒToyã€| Jersey Club | US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ginger is coming back!!! I'm so happy!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dyed my hair blonde and I'm having a crisis trying to decide whether I like it or not haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lithiumsivan i have and it was good for me. But I was with another traveller so I wasnt too worried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa @paninibagel YES HOLY OK OK I need to check my moolah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm getting bombarded with guys being weird and poking me on FB help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa how much are tix?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna try go blonde today, we'll see if my hairdresser lets me lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa omfg that would be liiiit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Ok hes cool, just be super chill, not despo or anything
Him: Hey
Me: https://t.co/VsuCSBI8mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa I love them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had fun boogeying with ya last night @SharelleClare apologies for my drunk ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader if you see me at work please approach with caution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I do this to myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My best mate was joking about blocking me on FB and I was lowkey so sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CartiaMallan @irisnperritt i miss the fringe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meladoodle honestly me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some peoples low angle selfies got me feeling like they're looking at me like I'm an animal at a zoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I haven't been "Fangirling" over 5SOS for awhile now but seeing that vid of Michael kissing his GF still broke my heart wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paninibagel RnV updates are what I was living vicariously through this whole New Years period. GET IT GIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read "The perks of being a wallflower" because I the movie is my fave. Forever going to be crying in 2017 now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm turning 21 this year ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader and v single]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving 2016 just how I started it, drunk and confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for new years!! Excitement!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New years eve eve is lit tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa new job? Where at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa need to hang in the new year gal x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa Are these rap lyrics of your life story I will never know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just spent easily half an hour unliking dumb pages I liked back in 2012. WHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to go boxing day shopping by myself https://t.co/T94RrGDhra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danimansuttii #askdani Would you rather have jelly instead of bones or a naked mural of yourself in your bedroom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to colour my hair like this please and thank you (not this short though) https://t.co/QiXcBVOmBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas!! I'm currently fake tanning because I wanna convince my extended family that I've been outside this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CartiaMallan You two should date]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa I don't know but that is literally me all through SUMMER and I'm always like ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every summer its the same deal, I feel like I have achieved ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ this year argh, cue the panic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylansprouse fight me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've signed myself up for a presenting course next year, new year (hopefully a more) skilled me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quirpele because its a VAMPIRE BABY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa nope not at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely decked myself leaving Chow today. Don't attempt stairs in heels whilst texting. Its embarrassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader I watched back those videos today and honestly I'm so sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had an interview today and they had watched my 'rap' videos on youtube so they probably have stalked my twitter as well. Hi all! Hire me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I like - Bruno Mars. Yes yes yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work is going to be SO FUN today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me currently https://t.co/DdSOjBH4yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher true me too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharelleClare me all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schoolwork = lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader revisiting this tweet lol ðŸ†’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader lol how long did it take me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UnpopularOpinion I don't deserve this much acne thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished our group promotion and even though I looove my group I'm so bloody happy thats over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyMy_Sanders wtf rude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forever waiting for my late ass brother ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher Jeff the wiggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sophie_FosterXx holy shit you look hot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Abbyluloader but now I can't wait for my packages weeeeee ðŸ‘—ðŸ‘—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Monday has got my bank account cryinggg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applying for jobs in honestly so much more stressful when it's for your career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today has been great, but I am a mess now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervinJohnsonTV nothing bad man its just been a year eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly I don't think I've ever been so confused about life more than this year #RealisingThings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancing is a form of expression so my twerking is just me EXPRESSING MY EMOTIONS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum just stole my phone while I was sleepily cuddling with my cat. Its always a big Friday night with meeee https://t.co/ZStyj4Ompd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paninibagel i had a spot treatment from that range that was very good! Lasted me a fair amount of time too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa 7-11 - Beyonce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickycheaa jump around - house of pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on Marion st and this guy is definitely looking for a prostitute and he totally thinks I am one. Buddy leave me alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its going UP, on a Thursday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to see Red today... was pretty nice actually ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heres a smug deer because why not https://t.co/7WAgbTTXpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meladoodle or i think its white fox boutique. Both kinda pricey but cute asf. ASOS is really good too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cryingbcjonah literally me atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I slept pretty well last night but I'm knackered now. Just the stress of the EQ taking a toll I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'm studying from home today wew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quirpele i'm so done with guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WasteAbbysTime2K16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he turns out to be just like the other trash you've dealt with this year ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ME ASF https://t.co/jJRdejeOgX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>