<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@harmonycoward fuck, if they're listening to it more than I do, they're probably participating in a revival of it. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to @JasonIsbell's 'Speed Trap Town'... damn, his passing observations about sports on that song CUT every single damn time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACriticNamedKev for me it's Holy Shit. Fantastic track, great key change, perfect build-up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why in the Nine Hells has nobody made karaoke versions of Father John Misty songs? His material is perfect for my range...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So one thing Tinder has added is the list of 'most played acts on Spotify' to profiles.

I think they just added this to annoy me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently Voltorb didn't think I was white enough already... Fantastic records, though,… https://t.co/SAibXbGG8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrons, it's the weekend and the schedule is open - have fun! https://t.co/z0I5FdjxtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daringndreaminx believe me, I'm not. That's just medication reacting badly, lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hi_ImJustEthan ...you do know I can give you albums to listen through that are actually good? Like, any time, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, this got controversial fast: my review of the sophomore album from @starsetonline, #Vessels - enjoy! https://t.co/f3uVyxqa1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncommonNasa well, my go-to for that sort of low-key optimism is Brooklyn Nine-Nine, made by the same folks who made Parks &amp; Rec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncommonNasa ah, I see. Well, there's still some stuff in that vein right now if you're willing to dig for it. Not a lot, but it's there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncommonNasa lol, I don't disagree there was a lot of sanitized pap. Don't get me started about how much I fucking hate Friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthebowlinguy lol, check my instagram, already picked up 'All Hands': https://t.co/4CRqxpJdFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UncommonNasa ...I think we might have been watching different 90s sitcoms. Fresh Prince, Seinfeld, Everyone Loves Raymond, not so innocent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JediFlippyDoer I love Beauty &amp; The Beast, but I have SEVERE reservations about the live action version. Favourite musical is 'Chess'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Voltorb may have picked up three records on vinyl from @Bandcamp today...

It's a problem, but it's a good cause today. #ACLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchChampagne yeah, if I'm going towards punk/pop punk I'm sticking with Car Seat Headrest and Japandroids these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchChampagne not huge into Blink-182, honestly. Never really was growing up, never made my schedule. They're fine, I guess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchChampagne eh, fair enough. I couldn't get into them the same way, but to each their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchChampagne ...okay, I guess? I'm curious if I missed something in interpretation you might have picked up, that's all. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchChampagne lol, which reviews?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, that's beautiful. https://t.co/tomDzOuCiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That odd feeling when you realized you accidentally deleted @cloudnothings' 'Attack On Memory' from your iPod.

I mean, why? WHY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayburritos oh, I don't doubt there are people who have the charisma/commentary to say more, but like critics, definitely in the minority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayburritos it became a thing over the past year. 

Honestly, I'd argue it shouldn't be. Neglects analysis for overblown reaction shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, and on a different note... PATRONS, the schedule is open! Locks are open, list is overloaded, have fun! https://t.co/I7k6EsgaNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's drop the review early, shall we - the pretty damn good #NearTheWildHeartOfLife by @Japandroids! https://t.co/F27YpHQS3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyliewilson here's my advice: screencap and then post the image file. That way he doesn't get clicks back, which means further anonymity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smailesyecem haven't had a chance to listen to it yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this Starset album fifteen tracks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shexwavey well, that's the big difference between hard numbers and clearly defined policy trends and subjective art evaluation, I guess. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gradywsmith thanks, much appreciated. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardJohans13 do you think I've got time to run two YouTube channels, lol? And what sort of audience would watch me talk finance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardJohans13 hey, I have a degree in economics and I work in finance. You get the whole package. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now granted, this is a worst-case scenario... but Trump's administration is already testing the waters. Again, REAL ECONOMIC DANGER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, if you thought the fiscal crisis in 2008 or 1987 or 1929 was bad... WHOO BOY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd see a capital flight almost immediately from the US dollar and US investments, because now that value becomes linked to US gov't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the symbolism if anything means more, because it implies the US Fed is not independent, which would throw central banking into chaos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...mostly because he knows that just printing more money cranks up inflation and devalues the US dollar, which hurts worldwide BIG TIME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now the Federal Reserve is independent - if the US government tried this, the head of the Fed would resign and protest and tell him to GTFO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They could choose to fund with emergency measures (like Bush did with Iraq and Afghanistan), but why not go to the Fed to print more money?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say the Trump administration needs a sudden infusion of cash, because they got involved in some sort of war/infrastructure project...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, to explain how Trump could manipulate the Fed in a simple way (because simple is the only way you explain this)... okay, follow this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyliewilson global, given how much other countries hold US currency as reserve and build off of US Fed policy. This impacts EVERYONE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillMcAvoyACN, @KeithOlbermann, please signal boost this NOW - Trump's admin making plays to meddle with the Fed: https://t.co/2Nsyt3yXIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...well, let's say that if he watches the DOW as carefully as rumors say, he's in for the rudest awakening possible. THIS WILL BE BAD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And any sane government would understand this, but we're not dealing with sane. If Trump tries to interfere with the money supply/banking...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, more than anything, highlights Trump's administration's total lack of qualifications. YOU DON'T TOUCH THE FEDERAL RESERVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thus, it's a huge red flag when governments try to interfere with financial instruments they do not understand for political benefit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a very big reason why federal reserve banking operates independently of governments - insane complexity and insuring liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Background: this is Trump's administration testing the waters to meddling with the Federal Reserve. Modern banking relies on this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might be one of the most genuinely terrifying things I've seen from the administration to date. READ NOW: https://t.co/2Nsyt3QyzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@musicloverjd not surprised at all. More a failure to change with the time - I know plenty of record stores that remain open to this day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a brighter note, I review the long-awaited sophomore comeback from @Lauren_Alaina, #roadlesstraveled - enjoy! https://t.co/3JtFfKB9HV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theneedledrop but doesn't that entire case require both sides act in good faith? It's the prisoner's dilemma, except one always breaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ICYMI last night, new #BillboardBREAKDOWN, where the formula changes to boost country... for as much good it did: https://t.co/w2dIxFNNnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianYoshi you should, I'm listening to it right now and it's just as excellent as it was in January 2014. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad Voltorb finally got this in, some criminally overlooked indie country from early 2014.… https://t.co/ZzyIAJnUX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just filmed two reviews, one going up tonight. Trying to get ahead of the game here, it's crazy. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, it's not huge, and it's not in that territory all the way (I'd like it more if it was), but I can hear some of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone getting a bit of a modern Frank Turner vibe in some of the melodic compositions on this Japandroids album? Just a little?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Democrats, want to "find common ground" with the Supreme Court? Here's a nifty way to get creative with it - TH… https://t.co/yMuGPbEEsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, let's try this again: I team up with @thelpclub to tear into @train's #AGirlABottleABoat - enjoy! https://t.co/Vv5z1IzDIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EthanTone uh, probably not, I'm still not done editing yet. #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In support of #TrumpBlackout, I recommend #billboardBREAKDOWN. Last checked, it does NOT actively destroy the USA: https://t.co/tCP5JUHrhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch #billboardBREAKDOWN over #SupremeCourtPick - I have music, memes and marginally better hair! https://t.co/tCP5JUHrhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#billboardBREAKDOWN: more facts and insight than #SupremeCourtPick. Also better tailored blazers too! https://t.co/tCP5JUHrhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does @realDonaldTrump have 100+ episodes of analysis? I THINK NOT! Pick #billboardBREAKDOWN over #SupremeCourtPick https://t.co/tCP5JUHrhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my advice: don't watch #SupremeCourtPick - watch #billboardBREAKDOWN instead! Better entertainment by FAR! https://t.co/tCP5JUHrhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm supposed to watch @realDonaldTrump's Supreme Court bullshit? I've got editing and dinner and LITERALLY ANYTHING ELSE. #fuckthepageantry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...so Patrons, the SCHEDULE IS OPEN! Lots there to vote on this week, folks, let's see some movement! https://t.co/wKqknNAutq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasAugeri @fliptrackz it was better than I thought it would be. Decent enough song, though I don't really remember it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @Lauren_Alaina album reminds me a lot of @lucyhale's debut.

In case you're wondering, that's a VERY good thing. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fliptrackz assuming you're talking about The Backstreet Boys, start with Millennium and Black &amp; Blue. Avoid This Is Us and Unbreakable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a different note, I discuss post-rock and the newest album from @LightsandMotion, #DearAvalanche: https://t.co/a5E4DTdAa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are people doing good work and who make me smile. @Nash076 is one of these people. Support his show - WATCH N… https://t.co/iNFG1Zh29o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22Baxman not really. Every act makes a dud every now and then (although 'Stutter' was from Ever After and was a decent song in my books).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an easy one to watch, but if @KeithOlbermann is not directly on point I don't know who is. Genuinely powerful: https://t.co/U6agm4N2IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Resistance needs a soundtrack, and Voltorb has just the thing... #vinyl #hiphop #rap… https://t.co/mt4d1lODDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trot100News I'd need the digital sales/streaming data to verify this, but it seems to imply streaming got the boost here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @billboard rebalanced the Hot 100 to include Pandora and further weigh towards streaming.

If you can't tell, I'm not all that impressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike_pence, @Reince... 25th Amendment, Section 4.

What are you waiting for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itstherapcritic @ShadowTodd and yet the music video he did make last year was for 'Child's Play'. And he put it up on Tyga's channel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I shouldn't have to explain why a child's grasp of organization is not how you run A GOVERNMENT. 

It's just stupid. Full stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some context, this is an executive order that says for every regulation created, two must be deleted.

This is REALLY stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS NOT HOW YOU WRITE POLICY, YOU IMBECILES. #ITMFA https://t.co/zCwbsJdS2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Germandude2 you can't just spout off hate speech in Canada, there are laws: https://t.co/Stz4HNNp6o

Plus, you know, the whole Nazi thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RichardBSpencer come to Canada and try this in public, Nazi coward. 

'Cause we have the Charter, and you might enjoy Canadian prison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MusicNerdDavid the album is still being covered, your request is definitely going to be honored here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MusicNerdDavid yeah, you'll want to stay tuned for a day or two... Got something special planned with that. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ keep in mind the NDP have never gotten federal power per se, although they have been the lead opposition before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ we also have the NDP, which is economic left, social left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ not quite. Conservatives are closer to economic right, social left/middle, liberals are economic middle, social left/middle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ pretty similar, yeah. Not exactly, but there are close elements. I used to identify as Conservative for a while growing up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ pretty much, though some conservatives try to import socially regressive policies... and end up getting their asses kicked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on another bright note, I finally reviewed the great debut album from @nataliehemby, #Puxico: https://t.co/OUrtKTrc0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laughing_Cynic_ it's more aligned with the British system, albeit with more socially progressive politics because Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am far from the Canadian conservative I once was, but I'll call integrity when I see it. @jkenney shows @CPC_HQ r… https://t.co/yVFPMTu1Gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EthanTone dropping one tonight, hopefully! :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>