<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends Roja (from Iran) and Joel (from Tennessee) are married and live in Dublin. They've written this. It's wo… https://t.co/v2Ztg96CrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bit my tongue while eating a yogurt. Not sure how to explain that one. You don't chew yogurt. That's not what yogurt is for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrNeilButler Good timing. The Indo are publishing their school league tables tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevosideways @AnotherHalfPod I look forward to your work ESPN 8, the Ocho! https://t.co/dRlEGTcKox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevosideways @AnotherHalfPod Are you the Cotton McKnight of this shin-dig or are you more of a Pepper Brooks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinsullivan79 The paper is crap, the song is a cheesy classic and Mr Secada was writing about the difference between equality and equity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm writing a paper and just referenced a man named Secada. I now have this tune in my head. https://t.co/3iopKIZTnS @stevosideways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Everton are 7th. That's very Moyes-era. Young Eldrick Woods must like how things are shaping up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgirvan You will only find a ninja emoji if the ninja emoji wants to be found.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#edchatie https://t.co/dO3Dnm1gzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Not at all. It's chicken-counting time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the spirit of #BlueMonday, this is fair depressing stuff from @EwanMacKenna. https://t.co/rt9nCgSuok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was rather good. #efc #mcfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie Sounds good. We were doing a "you are the teacher" thing so the students did with the whole thing themselves. It was pretty cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiguelDelaney Why is his "value" a different thing to what Everton would accept in the current market?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie They all had to narrate their own part in the process. There was brown play-doh for the grand finale!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie One guy (the food) had to walk through. He got chewed up, soaked in stomach acid and churned etc. The appendix did nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie We got a team of our TYs to teach this to the rest of the group. They assigned roles to everyone; teeth, stomach etc....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 Funes Mori is worth an outside punt for a goal. Good at set pieces, like a crap Sergio Ramos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 If over 2.5 goals is any sort of price, I'd say that's likely. I reckon 0-0 at Old Trafford though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 That would do nicely. I wouldn't invest much in an Everton win though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terry_del Not at all Terry. I have people who take care of that for me. (I got a voucher from Santa.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create the cosy sensation of sheltering from a storm by sitting in the waiting room of a car wash and valet station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Virtualnsainity Copenhagen is lovely. They have street trampolines! Also, bring all the money you can carry. https://t.co/R12S3sisIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinsullivan79 We learned this one too. (We didn't do any marching or pick any cotton though.)
https://t.co/64a4yXz6Ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We learned a German WW2 marching song in 4th class. Anyone else? Or did Brother McGill just go off on one? https://t.co/xIAYcrrIBO #edchatie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheball @KavanaghsArklow Hasn't been at his best for a couple of years. Seems a good lad but he's lost pace and is less effective now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalekmad It's definitely less fun when you pay for it but I've found the targeting option useful for promoting certain events/activities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was brilliant. https://t.co/ZVIhtMdADr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler That's quite an exchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler The worst of those three still leaves plenty of room to be great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler The Lord sent me, and the Lord blows my trumpet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AprilSylvester That book is not quite the feel-good holiday romp  I was hoping for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebastulon @WhoresofYore @GeorgeMichael https://t.co/3G0ZPC0OTW He said both. The "gay sex" tweet was a reference to this song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler @Everton He's not wearing shoes you mad man. Just trainers with a stylish white stripe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 @TaittingerUK That is the traditional approach, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinsullivan79 Jaysis lads, it's catching on.... https://t.co/iUnxcGI7yM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas lads. May your day be filled with pineapples. https://t.co/JobwGAHbiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Gotta hit that stuff WWF style, off the top rope (or the couch).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamkanee It's possible you've put them in the wrong place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler They're very stylish either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Are they Chewbacca feet? Or some other furry dude?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up my new iPhone is taking longer than I thought and I'm not sure these chocolates will last until it's done. #FirstWorldProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An awful game. Neither of teams will do anything this year. #EVEMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddunctious Cheers Todd. I'll hang up my stocking just in case!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adrianweckler Fingers crossed Santa finds one soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adrianweckler They've very politely said "We don't have it and we don't know when we're getting it". Are they generally available?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adrianweckler iPhone 7Plus looks great. Ordered mine from @VodafoneIreland 7 weeks ago now. It was going to be an early Christmas present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Circle of Trust beat The Quizzy Rascals in a tie-breaker to take home the gold. @itsshanebutler @silver_bullitt… https://t.co/iliNanf9qO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terry_del @itsshanebutler @TransfersBot @WhartoJohn Definitely a joke. Also, would improve our team at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AprilSylvester Of course not. Santa was invented by a Japanese businessman during a visit to Dublin in 1997. He is very real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinMcDevitt @RTERadio1 This caption confused me. They left out one of your names! https://t.co/5OeyXqzI0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy comes to Bridge21. #AndysComing https://t.co/EfNtBmVUks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas music in the chipper. This is why the bad things happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#edchatie https://t.co/Y7t0J932tI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, sorry I'm late. I was in bed reading Twitter and lost track of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russeltarr @ailis_t 2016 will be the paragraph before the maps with the arrows showing the military movements and shifting borders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally Lots of racism all the same.... https://t.co/nYNyBAaDuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMullally 30% of Mexicans voted for him. A minority but a significant one. It's more than racism. It's definitel… https://t.co/kWifj5msyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton, Bruce Springsteen, Barack Obama, Mexicans, Women, the gays, People who can read, your girl took a hell of beating....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrNeilButler That's spot on Neil. Also, I read the first two lines and started singing a Backstreet Boys song. That'll be me for the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paud_ie @shanedbergin We mostly use social media to find people we agree with. It validates everyone's opinion, justified or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrNeilButler Above and beyond!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarrenJJF You know that episode of Friends where Chandler hates dogs and Ross doesn't like ice-cream?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🇮🇪 : Do you speak English?
🇨🇭 : Yes, with a proficiency that would embarrass you, pixie-head.
🇮🇪: Grand. Two for th… https://t.co/ZKFnR2trtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardmillwood @Bridge21Learn @DIY_Lab @bnighrogain We're in good company so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardmillwood @Bridge21Learn @DIY_Lab Thanks Richard. I'm sure you nailed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D_Sheridan37 A lot of people break in just to have a shit. Some of them steal things once they're in though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossOCK @itsshanebutler A valuable contribution all the same. Can we assume you'll be having a motivational word w… https://t.co/JXzGgttysW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossOCK @itsshanebutler You've set a bad example for the English Rosser. Or did you learn it from them in the first place?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler They should dock them 10 points in their World Cup group. Who would have thought that James McClean… https://t.co/kdzlICtU5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler What shitty behaviour. Like @RossOCK parking wherever he likes because he can afford the fines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Students’ opinion of a subject ... greatly influenced by the teacher and methods of teaching used in class" Yep. @CBCMonkstownpk #edchatie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like some interesting teaching/learning is happening @CBCMonkstownpk. Check it out. https://t.co/QkkH8upO4r @Bridge21Learn #edchatie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Virtualnsainity @zintendo Someone in Rathmines is trying to tear a hole in the sky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler @stevosideways Headache, temporary blindness, ear bleeds, loss of height, sleep crime, uncontrollab… https://t.co/W0nHddbwyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevosideways "OUR THING IS GREAT. GREAT. BUY LOTS NOW. IT'S GREAT!" We're like "Ah, it's grand. It might help a l… https://t.co/k8Bd7JcqLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 If it's stressing you, just remember the opening credits to Duck Tales where Scrooge McDuck dives into a g… https://t.co/KCXOgui3Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Bangladesh. A great win to end a brilliant series. There is nothing else in sport like a good test match. #BANvENG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Some traditions are worth maintaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magsamond You making a few quid on the side? 💷 💷 💷]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magsamond Surprised to see people focusing on cost. A modest fee is inevitable I'd assume. Once attendees are moti… https://t.co/85SNAAuiHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used YouTube to fact-check a Bananarama reference (Cruel Summer. 1983.) and now I'm listening to The Bangles. That's bad internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was still funny though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasn't a sex joke though. It was just that her friend and the mutual friend they mentioned  had both made the same comment on some issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An old lady on the train dropped a "That's what she said!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisteddoodles But surely hair is just life's most convenient towel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@silver_bullitt That whole sentence had fewer syllables than the two words I mentioned. Also, will you help me with my homework?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The phrase "statistically significant" has too many syllables in it. There should be an easy to swallow alternative. #phdchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USC bonus - Car Insurance increase = Free Money 2017. I spent most of mine on chocolate buttons. #Budget2017 https://t.co/LYWNfEbMPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanMacKenna Nothing will change either way so let's enjoy the night and focus on the next round of Viking Clapping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VickyWrites @GilmoreGirls As it happens, I finished series 7 last night. 8 weeks looks far too long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamer30 I wore my heavy winter coat yesterday. To be honest, I was a bit too warm. Life, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahMc95 @SeanBarron Love comes and goes. Pizza though. Pizza is forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsshanebutler Indiana Jones is on. https://t.co/Ys6yWGfdcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foursome/Fourball formats are great. More tournaments should use them. Like the Slams in tennis running singles, doubles, etc. #RyderCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerMc31 I remember Ferguson going daft with his midfield in the final in 99. Beckham in the middle, Giggs right wing. Happens to the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin players speak almost exclusively in sporting cliches. Brilliant, but a little boring. #DUBvMAYO #AllIrelandFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd have to feel for Mayo. But mostly, Dublin. #AllIrelandFinal https://t.co/KpBLahNqZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conpower Everyone with money! #Affluence]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>