<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington recorded the highest median sales in December, and median values rose almost $100,000 for the year (+20%… https://t.co/TzaDhYDWNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference a bit of cleaning and organising can make is always amazing! https://t.co/MgshVXgadr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home styling tip: you can arrange fresh summer fruit in the kitchen for a less commercial detail that will be sure… https://t.co/3AvuXu5smM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should we try 'lolly hunt' open homes to sell properties in Wellington this year? #treatyourself #funnyFriday https://t.co/njHHDusceb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property tip: keep any records of any upgrades or maintenance you've had done on the house filed and presentable fo… https://t.co/Up3E441tTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dutch architecture firm has unveiled plans to build a futuristic light-filled Y-shaped house in Taiwan:… https://t.co/GxsyGAvavK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Straight out of Enid Blyton, this treehouse for grown-ups comes with an outdoor shower, hammock and even a slide:… https://t.co/4B7DAjaDzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say goodbye to rose gold and Scandinavian styled interiors, folks... we've got new trends to expect in 2017:… https://t.co/qD0VRmaf1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course Wellington's 'Britten House' made the list! Let's have a moment for NZ's quirkiest properties of 2016:… https://t.co/Sd4IcMe5PD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which features make for a perfect family home? This mother's blog spells them out nicely for house hunters:… https://t.co/WCg03Ynb9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homestaging tip: if you're staging your home in the summer, set up some outdoor furnishings to highlight your... https://t.co/bsrNaAuXHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homestaging tip: if you're staging your home in the summer, set up some outdoor furnishings to highlight your home'… https://t.co/iTBQnWTFsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip: watering your garden in the cool hours of the night will keep the sun and windy Wellington weather from... https://t.co/BvL4l46Fpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip: watering your garden in the cool hours of the night will keep the sun and windy Wellington weather from dr… https://t.co/FW3iakrFI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This amazing indoor garden mantains itself! When are we going to get them in New Zealand? https://t.co/03FjoA1YGV https://t.co/99suwHW17s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This amazing indoor garden mantains itself! When are we going to get them in New Zealand? https://t.co/03FjoA1YGV https://t.co/cYgNjn01QV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip: got prickle summer problems? Spray your lawns with Turf Clean (for broad leaf weeds) or Prickle... https://t.co/cVRchjW1lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro tip: got prickle summer problems? Spray your lawns with Turf Clean (for broad leaf weeds) or Prickle Weedkiller… https://t.co/UbvRELono1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pantone 'Colour of the Year' for 2017 is 'Greenery', inspired by nature. Would you use 'Greenery' in your inter… https://t.co/mgoPVY0x4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Pantone 'Colour of the Year' for 2017 is 'Greenery', inspired by nature. Would you use 'Greenery' in your... https://t.co/K4XSt2Hnep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer homestaging tip: plant hanging baskets and terracotta pots with flowers for some bold summer colour around... https://t.co/1q2L07Klyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer homestaging tip: plant hanging baskets and terracotta pots with flowers for some bold summer colour around y… https://t.co/7J57APc7hJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer is a time for rapid garden growth, so ensure you pay attention to watering, weeding, feeding and spraying... https://t.co/7EIXP1dmjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer is a time for rapid garden growth, so ensure you pay attention to watering, weeding, feeding and spraying th… https://t.co/8eFeqgzOnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're having a shudder at these spooky 'probably evil' properties for Friday the 13th! There's 17 more to see... https://t.co/o0r8wOcLTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're having a shudder at these spooky 'probably evil' properties for Friday the 13th! There's 17 more to see here:… https://t.co/vme3Ti3X0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much is too much when it comes to tiles? Are you liking the look of this modern renovated bathroom? https://t.co/cJOF60mTkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much is too much when it comes to tiles? Are you liking the look of this modern renovated bathroom? https://t.co/n8fFhQzgN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer security tip: if you store valuables (like mountain bikes) in your garage, be sure to keep it closed as ofte… https://t.co/p3SiIu1FcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer security tip: if you store valuables (like mountain bikes) in your garage, be sure to keep it closed as... https://t.co/P0Tklsap8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our goal was to build a one-stop-shop for people entering the housing market." a perfect tool for first time... https://t.co/9VCQe3isQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our goal was to build a one-stop-shop for people entering the housing market." a perfect tool for first time buyers https://t.co/oo93QbCwSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could turn your open-plan living space into separate rooms in an instant with these fun looking building... https://t.co/LUliEJmY6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your surf boards and cameras ready because Surf's Up in Wellington this summer! https://t.co/XANDAruVEr https://t.co/tthOXVsYpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your surf boards and cameras ready because Surf's Up in Wellington this summer! https://t.co/XANDAruVEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property tip: take some time to be friendly and meet the neighbors. They can keep an eye on your property for you... https://t.co/rl2iNGeBRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property tip: take some time to be friendly and meet the neighbors. They can keep an eye on your property for you w… https://t.co/Ogr2LQIZ1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property tip: keep your home dry if you're going away for the holidays by turning off your water temporarily to... https://t.co/Lphtb0310K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property tip: keep your home dry if you're going away for the holidays by turning off your water temporarily to avo… https://t.co/fAZ8EVESIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making your rental prperty make you money: the top 10 features as told by Investopedia https://t.co/o1OygAQUdr https://t.co/Tnaj3Oo3y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making your rental prperty make you money: the top 10 features as told by Investopedia https://t.co/o1OygAQUdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget! If you're going away this summer make sure you book someone to water your lawn, especially if... https://t.co/nlEO99hlh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget! If you're going away this summer make sure you book someone to water your lawn, especially if you're… https://t.co/SMRpYO0pOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of dealing with guests who overstay their welcome? Here's how to make those visits more pleasant for... https://t.co/iLoqA6rsCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of dealing with guests who overstay their welcome? Here's how to make those visits more pleasant for everyone https://t.co/UwnuHXEvvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting your property over the summer isn't difficult - mostly it's down to common sense. https://t.co/wtiVKv2OKY https://t.co/DnxCOsaodU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting your property over the summer isn't difficult - mostly it's down to common sense. https://t.co/wtiVKv2OKY https://t.co/nb5CJEwWjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make 2017 the year you break those deplorable habits that are hurting your home.https://t.co/hCe1s2pOIr https://t.co/Hwl3N6a1Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make 2017 the year you break those deplorable habits that are hurting your home.https://t.co/hCe1s2pOIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very happy new year to our Facebook fans! https://t.co/hopK5as5n6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very happy new year to our Facebook fans! https://t.co/aNBNHLSfNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering what's on in Welly for New Year's Eve? Events and fireworls will take place at the waterfront:... https://t.co/plAbnnnzYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering what's on in Welly for New Year's Eve? Events and fireworls will take place at the waterfront: https://t.co/NNOo2MhS5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you be house-hunting in the New Year? Be sure to keep an eye on my latest listings: https://t.co/kco8dCkC0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, new look: how to update your home's interior without breaking the bank for selling your home in 2017!... https://t.co/sXcJy4O7iK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, new look: how to update your home's interior without breaking the bank for selling your home in 2017!  https://t.co/Xyt9SYIWC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider positioning a big mirror with a thin frame in places that need a little extra light. It will also help... https://t.co/9RgD1f7DjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider positioning a big mirror with a thin frame in places that need a little extra light. It will also help the… https://t.co/M02purRdEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going away for the holidays? Unplug your TV, computers, oven and other appliances to protect them from power... https://t.co/aFcbE7VtOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going away for the holidays? Unplug your TV, computers, oven and other appliances to protect them from power surges… https://t.co/AqXHfBRVZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make any dining room look brand new with a fresh set of modern dining furniture. You might find a nice set at the... https://t.co/PZZFOPEb5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make any dining room look brand new with a fresh set of modern dining furniture. You might find a nice set at the b… https://t.co/6bUI4qspHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping you have a wonderful long weekend with your friends and family! Happy holidays from the team and Steve Fejos! https://t.co/Lk9wjuYDM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping you have a wonderful long weekend with your friends and family! Happy holidays from the team and Steve Fejos! https://t.co/Yb1MeVx7KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you end up decorating your house or did someone make off with your lights? Share your decoration pictures in... https://t.co/jOyHi7QdgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you end up decorating your house or did someone make off with your lights? Share your decoration pictures in th… https://t.co/R8YKwVuLAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a festive Friday idea: how about a good old Christmas Light Hunt? Follow this year's map of Welly houses:... https://t.co/IWCHclia7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a festive Friday idea: how about a good old Christmas Light Hunt? Follow this year's map of Welly houses: https://t.co/3WRCQzYywr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be a property star featured on New Zealand's Grand Designs? Here's how you could get your chance:... https://t.co/QrU7udp22q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be a property star featured on New Zealand's Grand Designs? Here's how you could get your chance: https://t.co/8gxR8bQWw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuff have created a weekly home &amp; property newsletter: released each Friday afternoon and packed with... https://t.co/V4wTYRIkl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuff have created a weekly home &amp; property newsletter: released each Friday afternoon and packed with inspiration! https://t.co/QFaR3DYLbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington’s suburbs are a treasure trove of activities, sights and sounds. Which suburb is your favorite?... https://t.co/bYBYlANkNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington’s suburbs are a treasure trove of activities, sights and sounds. Which suburb is your favorite? 
https://t.co/0AUmSEwfL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festive add-ons to 'For Lease' signs give us a good laugh! https://t.co/Lpwkth9Rjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festive add-ons to 'For Lease' signs give us a good laugh! https://t.co/phcUrFYeW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling during the holidays: it's totally doable! Get proactive with your property these holidays using these... https://t.co/s0RxCdMj8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling during the holidays: it's totally doable! Get proactive with your property these holidays using these tips: https://t.co/H49xHIWmLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's this for lighting up a home for the holidays: this family have rigged their lights to dance to 'Let It Go'... https://t.co/HWlAC3RWUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's this for lighting up a home for the holidays: this family have rigged their lights to dance to 'Let It Go'  https://t.co/8fIlWdoCoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you just can't be bothered these holidays... https://t.co/BjgbzSaZjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you just can't be bothered these holidays... https://t.co/utdj7zV8rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the family coming for Christmas? Before you go giving the house a clean, why not start where it's dirtiest:... https://t.co/BPtoBYVcmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the family coming for Christmas? Before you go giving the house a clean, why not start where it's dirtiest: https://t.co/Zwqe9QdiWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old or new? Which kitchen design do you prefer? https://t.co/KCjMB9FAbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old or new? Which kitchen design do you prefer? https://t.co/IdajLt3Lby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature is playing a prominent part in homes in this new interior decorating trend. Will you try incorporating... https://t.co/hmCJ6dd0EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature is playing a prominent part in homes in this new interior decorating trend. Will you try incorporating more… https://t.co/UyUtdclbzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard about the Wondrous Wellington Advent calendar? It's an amazing website packed with free Welly... https://t.co/ETydLQCJ1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard about the Wondrous Wellington Advent calendar? It's an amazing website packed with free Welly treats! https://t.co/WimTF2QrZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you like to walk through an open home that smells like Christmas? Here's how to achieve that festive scent:... https://t.co/tyA4tTpsbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you like to walk through an open home that smells like Christmas? Here's how to achieve that festive scent: https://t.co/2gxyPJCIdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever heard of 'Mc Mansions'? Well, you have now! See architects critique these extravagant properties... https://t.co/1TMFcAggoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever heard of 'Mc Mansions'? Well, you have now! See architects critique these extravagant properties relentlessly:  https://t.co/W89A6448F9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love a house with character... #funnyFriday https://t.co/jr71WfDKm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love a house with character... #funnyFriday https://t.co/uTdXDs887Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Red Rocks is an excellent location for a spot of star gazing, seal watching or a coastal walk." https://t.co/V7PWzqpPRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait for it to warm up before you consider this sell-worthy feature in your home. A heatpump/AC unit is... https://t.co/HLQrO841gR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait for it to warm up before you consider this sell-worthy feature in your home. A heatpump/AC unit is gener… https://t.co/PaJupE8pkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top three benefits of browsing for housing while it's hot in the summer: 

1. Less competition for your preferred... https://t.co/dHVz3V230W]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>