<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past day - 10 new followers and 7 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New day, new tweets, new stats. 22 followers, 3 unfollowers. Via good old https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get daily? 31 awesome new followers for me! Grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 new unfollowers and 28 new followers (hello! hello!) in the last day. Via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 new unfollowers and 29 new followers (hello! hello!) in the last day. Via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 amazing followers in the last day and there will be more tomorrow. Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 24 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 19, Unfollowers - 12. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your daily stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy can you Tex me I am one off your cousin from Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get daily? 15 awesome new followers for me! Grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 daily followers. 10 unfollowers. Crowdfire doesn't miss a trick - via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 20 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget unfollowers, I believe in growing. 20 new followers in the last day! Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[53 amazing followers in the last day and there will be more tomorrow. Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 22 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past day. Thank you https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 22 new followers in the past day. I know them via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I think you will do good abd Hope all the best for you and your family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get everyday? I got 7 in the last day. Growing daily with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 tweeps followed me in the past day. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many followers do you get daily? 12 awesome new followers for me! Grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 41 new followers in the last day! Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 19 more followers in the past day. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump do you know the Kennedy family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennedynews is the Kennedy family read this page]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy you family of John f Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 amazing followers in the last day and there will be more tomorrow. Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 12 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing and engaging with the right tweeps - gained 15 new followers in the past day, courtesy https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 5 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gained 25 followers in the last day. You? Know your stats and grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 16 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 25 more followers in the past day. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow me on twitter https://t.co/oHYNhMlAhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 8 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found all 16 Twitter users who don't follow me back, thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a #iOSapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 50 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past day. Thank you https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 49 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 11 new followers in the last day! Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 15 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found all 34 Twitter users who don't follow me back, thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a #iOSapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 11 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 15 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past day. Thank you https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 9 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 new tweeps followed me in the last day. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 4 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past day - 11 new followers and 9 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 10, Unfollowers - 12. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your daily stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 5 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 9 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New day, new tweets, new stats. 9 followers, 6 unfollowers. Via good old https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year https://t.co/GKmzMaHoja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past day - 21 new followers and 12 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinbieber what up Justin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 13 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering how to grow on twitter? I gained 15 followers in the past day. This is the app: https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 tweeps followed me in the past day. Feels great! Do you also want to feel awesome? Check out https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 19 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 2 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 11 new followers in the past day. I know them via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 9 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 11 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 2 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the day have arrived. 7 new followers and 9 unfollowers via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 amazing followers in the last day and there will be more tomorrow. Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 new tweeps followed me in the last day. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 18 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past day. Thank you https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 4 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gained 11 followers in the last day. You? Know your stats and grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 new tweeps followed me in the last day. I find relevant people to follow with the #CopyFollowers feature of https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 10 more followers in the past day. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 16, Unfollowers - 7. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your daily stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 7 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 13 more followers in the past day. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 26 new followers in the last day! Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 20 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 new unfollowers and 10 new followers (hello! hello!) in the last day. Via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the day have arrived. 5 new followers and 8 unfollowers via https://t.co/ymIfSnLAwJ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 14 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 8 new followers in the last day! Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a rising follower graph! 13 more followers in the past day. Get your stats right here https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 tweeps followed (thank you!) and 23 unfollowed (goodbye!) me in the past day. Thank you https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gained 16 new followers in the past day. I’m growing my account the right way, are you? Do it with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stats for the day have arrived. 12 new followers and 2 unfollowers via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gained 10 followers in the last day. You? Know your stats and grow with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 4 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 new followers in the last day and it is more than just stats, I use it for growing my account! Try it https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers - 9, Unfollowers - 3. I didn't know it'd be this simple. Get your daily stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m ready to engage with my 15 new followers in the past day. I know them via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 7 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget unfollowers, I believe in growing. 17 new followers in the last day! Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number crunching for the past day - 13 new followers and 25 unfollowers. Stats via https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 16 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 16 new followers in the last day! Growing with https://t.co/ymIfSntZFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found the 10 tweeps who unfollowed me and thanks to https://t.co/sWpgHKgR4a I know who they are #iosapp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>