<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald 'Queen of Torture' images difficult to come by...has she not shown her face?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ceciliakang @anjucomet @MikeIsaac @nytimes Now how about Goldman Sachs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamkokesh And the other 50% just bafflegab!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zbig Yeah sure, Zbig, let's have another Cold War arms race!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp Hate to make fun of physical defects, but I can't stop thinking: Blancmange!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week on Gorilla Radio with Chris Cook, Andy Worthington, Peter Lee, Christina Nikolic https://t.co/pVPz3UElFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medialens Malcolm, what have you been paying attention too!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @CBCNews "Police treating as terrorist act... could later face  terrorism-related charges...ongoing  investigation."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snarwani Obviously, the Tommy's are merely hired hands...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeking input from cyclists: Would U pay to park in this? - https://t.co/795OzvK0jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week on GR: Tim Boultbee &amp; Human Rights in Mexico; and, Peter Verin Presente! - https://t.co/y3oo9wO98J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald First the curriculum, then the history!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcnswanson Can't surprise; they've still said nothing about 9/11 and Iraq hooplas...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp @DrJillStein @RalphNader Nader asked billionaires to step up...(Careful what you wish for?!).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiercedSkull @AndrewMitrovica What's diff b/w Trump admin &amp; Titanic? Titanic had better band! (Stole from Geffen doc).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Trump's real value is perpetuating 'president matters' myth. It's not a real car, Don &amp; the wheel's just plastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afroinstilettos Which president was she married to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Is this the same "Axis of Evil" author Frum who boasted of cheerleading US to war?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moazzam_Begg Perhaps his is an aspirational impulse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp Oh, if only it were true (to the David Rovics tune).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque So thaaat's why the Fibbers torpedoes Hill Clint!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medialens The wheel never sleeps. Indicates the new reality - Turkey/Russia allies, for now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Commie-friendly, community arena-ed Green Bay a Putin first pick, naturally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maureenclarem Getting medical check-ups too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week on GR: Cdn. gov't muzzles Mt. Polley mine disaster trial; Meeting Canada's new Russophobe FM Freedland. https://t.co/PVNEgqWgAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Oh, I think they've managed that already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can now follow Gorilla Radio podcast on https://t.co/wxmhB2jIl1 https://t.co/cugymzi3Lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Hardly compares with 'Starlight Tours' favoured by Canada's "Dudley Dorights" - https://t.co/LpAE71biQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcnswanson Goes with the new Plowshare Ultra M-16...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinahand All has a Jeremy Corbyn, scorched earth ring to it somehow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting All J. Edgar on Trump's Ass: Dirty, Dirty Tricks - https://t.co/mZ4YdwHsOZ https://t.co/6W2PP8tvOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's Generational Political Prisoners Hold Out Hope for Obama pardons. - https://t.co/EeXGUwISRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp Oh great, brains and teeth; now the Boomers are gonna want to live forever! Thx a lot science. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBlumenthal "He also[!?] meets with conservatives..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque It's pretty clear, the Democrats have sunk to using South Park scripts for their oppo attacks.… https://t.co/yXnD5tX4SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emptywheel How much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week on GR; Anthony DiMaggio &amp; Pathologies of Syria War coverage; David Fairey &amp; BC workers rights - https://t.co/2qG2VfLvVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald And, "Remember the Maine!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch "Squandered"? Only if you believe he wanted to accomplish what he said he did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There Is a War on Christmas, and it's happening in the Holy Land - No Christmas for You in Jerusalem - https://t.co/1ZBI8Sblww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence Chef Fails Russia Recipe: No Beets in Clapper Borscht - https://t.co/vS319l3db9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Remember too please the birth of "democracy zones".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@readwritenap Get over yourself; it's been in use for hundreds of years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRather This the same Dan "tell me where to line up, Mr. Bush" Rather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Mustn't forget all those car bombs, and latent cluster munitions and land mines...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch "Latte left" or "limousine liberal," "collaborative normalization" is much older than 8 yrs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinpodur @AliAbunimah "We could have saved the world, but we were too damned cheap." - Vonnegut the good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garthmullins @TheBeaverton Didn't see *Steal native land, *Bomb foreigners, or * Wreck environment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Evaluating 'New Truth' by necessary repetitions: False News/Russia Hack nearing reality!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaitiInfoProj Brand new boots and uni's always a bad sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This wk on GR: Satya Sagar on Modi's demonetization; Richard Kastelein on Europe's nascent Blockchain Party. - https://t.co/M0q1W8NyQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyHavenstein @Zaganashikwe 1out of 3's not bad...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardianworld "other activists"? Pretty generous description of traitor and fugitive from justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamkokesh @realDonaldTrump @RonPaul Sadly, not dead yet, just smelling bad! (Apologies to punk rock).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ignominious Departure: Obama's Grizzly Russian Hack Story Fails Smell Test - https://t.co/ikfmz0akAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@democracynow A generous, [anonymous] donor...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Interviews Hedges on this book in '02, before he "deserted" corpo news. - https://t.co/rbONjjYNsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch Are you saying, Donald wishes he had Putin's body!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxBlumenthal Don't believe Trump member of UN...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snarwani By their ID's you will know them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp @NatalieSMcGill Just imitating Jesus; turning water into ice tea..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This wk on GR: Sightline Institute's Eric de Place on Kinder Morgan; expropriated Ken Boon on BC's Site C Mega dam. https://t.co/MfJfj7FtUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp If Pence proven a robot, can Hillary still win?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald The idea is to drive Trump agenda into a corner. Now he promises "safe zones" in Syria. Mission Accomplished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald What's wrong with that? Commie China doesn't have a president, do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Juice Media Strikes Back - Standing Rock - https://t.co/5qwgwlRyGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewMitrovica CBC News rotten from root to stem. Watching it akin to toilet bowl swirl hypnotism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Maybe start w/ Brothers Grimm bastardizations, Walt you culture vulture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@democracynow But will they send them to protect water defenders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinahand And you won't; even "venerable" cbc practically lamenting end of fighting in Aleppo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Permissible too against other identified enemies of Trans-American Übermensch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week on GR; Robert Jensen on "Professor Watch" - Robert Parry &amp; Real vs Fake News. - https://t.co/UtCl1np8C9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald Is that "flammable" or inflammable"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald First person self-referencing is an early sign of madness - or royal ascension...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque I didn't know John F. Kennedy, Mr. Gates. JFK wasn't a friend of mine...but Donald Trump ain't no effin' JFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfcloutier @jricole Warped!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garthmullins But Clooney sez they're green...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch Can't Unsee that one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinahand Alternet's Mark Ames on Ukriane fascist connex to PropOrNot - https://t.co/OQOWEqBYr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Doubtless following hard on Aleppo terrorist, er heroic rebel, defeat - https://t.co/E0X0o53KWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stooge Newz: Connecting the PropOrNot Dots - https://t.co/OQOWEqBYr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaius_Publius @peterdaou Guess that means the Work Slave economy has achieved perfection!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp Wait a minute! I see a pattern developing here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, don't give him ideas. And, Putin=Hitler? Really!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErikaShaker @StuJT @michalrozworski @UberedOttawa Likely hoped child would be born in cab, rather than ho$pital...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque Lou Dobbs!? Is he still a thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @thinkprogress Same said for a senator from Vermont wanting to be prezident...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chinahand Oh shit! It's Iran and Russia destroyed Afghanistan...Now I understand...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque I wouldn't be so sure that battle is over...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vijayprashad That's a body cast! - love the design, can do without the shirt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week on GR: Mel Goodman &amp; Trump's Militarization Campaign; Dave Lindorff on Fake News = $ bonanza for State - https://t.co/aWhi8bSG1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian pm resigns following referendum defeat. - https://t.co/aBrr9725bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianChen @joshua__frank @propornot Speaking of gov't supported agitprop, surprised by Chen endorsement of Bellingcat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque I thought they were talking about PTSD veterans IN police force. Those Uni's an instant flashback!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PropOrNot's Useful Idiots" WashPost Cred Pillaried: https://t.co/pNpsKhVXYm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nader_Hasan_law @AnizAlani I thought this was decided last year!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeCamp Cuz a full-bellied ass never chases a carrot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empireburlesque To borrow from Kurtz: "You're not a mediator; you're an errand boy, sent by shopkeepers to collect… https://t.co/GuHFFYpTJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derrickokeefe No doubt using the Standing Rock template]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz @BiancaJagger But half way through his lips got tired...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>