<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to work Monday fighting the good fight looking forward to 2017 #problemgambling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to talk Collaboration to minimise harm from gambling with #hapaitehauora #zoehawke #lancenorman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to challenges of host responsibility for pubs and clubs and pokies - balancing risk and benefit #problemgambling #pubcharities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Racism Kept The World's Fastest Swim Stroke Out Of The Pool: @atlasobscura https://t.co/qfARsZpp59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos for Japanese students' roaring rendition of our haka https://t.co/8yOYVwNpwK via @OneNewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps harming and killing a child needs its own category of crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister John Key: Red Peaks for New Zealand Flag - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/JrWVjVhiB9 via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd rather buy new ski pants than Jeffrey Campbell boots #youknowyoulovesnowwhen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Air New Zealand and other Airlines will never use a longer Wellington runway. http://t.co/7nWbVmSXWZ via @ianapperley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ nice algorithm by the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ I'm koru 00080777 you have my details why not ring me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ did that too - why not ring me 021577904]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ did that twice and no response]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ where you don't promote killer tobacco as on airnz 726 melb to AK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous coffee ordering in koru lounge #airnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ why the 5 second flash - thank you for not smoking - image up on the screens on landing from Oz-weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not liking Morning Argument anymore bring back Simon Mercep @NzMorningReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Population Health Conference @QuitlineNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Manager Heaven or Hell  = Manager Habits" by @DrDuffWatkins on @LinkedIn http://t.co/yoKzko0Tly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NzMorningReport tried to be patient but can't hold off - bring back Simon Mercep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ these guys are taking a long time to respond to query on smoking msg on Oz flights perhaps a PR hold up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TV3nz ministers playing the public blame game is tiger by the tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillyRalston @Nigella_Lawson what's she shopping for get thee to Moore wilsons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the media silence on the stolen Nigerian girls please buy them Bill Gates and give them back to their whanau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spider/fly ring a bell E-cigarettes: no smoke without fear - http://t.co/m3Yxpen1OI http://t.co/rhGIoQJJ0K via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tidy up the adult playground brilliant Matt Bowden@CampbellLiveNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maurice Williamson - really! And Judith Collins - oh dear @TV3nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easter drinking laws on the ferry per person 1 pie 1 chips and 4 bottles if wine 2 std drinks in ea idiotic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems so unfair, floods and now earthquakes - thinking of the Solomons and supporting Unicef's work there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[another password reset so hopefully fixed now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changed password do hope the hacking has stopped - apologies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandmartian scary and true not sure we could use it nationally but midwives might be interested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ it was the last screen as the plane was taxiing to the arrival gate - cig in a crossed circle with smoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaping inside at my favourite cafe - not cool and just keeping a killer habit alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very disappointed in the thank you for not smoking video when arriving on @FlyAirNZ from Oz recently-completely unnecessary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got hacked with some random diet site - grr - trying to undo - apologies friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In less than 30 days lose up to 25 lbs while burning two or more inches with http://t.co/9kxOOP1OmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JGeek and the Geeks - Icky Sticky http://t.co/3XoxhmIO via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is Love [Edit] by Klaas, from #SoundHound http://t.co/d4DEnonU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgt nannie Olivia - I love age that never gives up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Olwage new York bound surely http://t.co/ggmzJAZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good points made https://t.co/ki0BS1RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching Prince Tui Teka on Maori Television time warp and great voices I remember when everyone sang like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[birthday brunch at mums and found marmite in the cupboard - whoop whoop! http://t.co/GYlcaQvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out the blow smoke ad future look-Sparks fly over ciggies in posters - National - NZ Herald News http://t.co/yiVtFzp6 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefit tightening won’t reduce unemployment  http://t.co/lT4mg54X via @garethmorgannz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the women are fronting for national - just saying Chch protesters target Parata http://t.co/MXuFmktD via @3NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spotted a very big belly with teeshirt words saying "I like to experiment" - with beer obviously : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim woman spotted with full head scarf and big pink teeshirt with the words - Hug Me - weird or am I missing something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[observed over 3 days at the sheraton bangkok how can Asian women eat so much and be so slim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if kneel canoes are in the olympics then bring on waka ama - outrigger at least has history and purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tobbacco industry is the leper not the smoker http://t.co/3lxy8tzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smokers are not the lepers its the tobacco industry that keep 650k NZers addicted  to product when used as directed kills 1 in 2 : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air New Zealand Presents: The Kiwi Sceptics. 'Lara Bingle', Episode 5 http://t.co/S3ASVY67 v=52_7BlQuZe8&amp;sns=tw via @youtube I love aotearoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[first crossings tv1 great programme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HSBC officer steps down in laundering scandal http://t.co/dzsbtFph via @3NewsNZ it took so long to see this shame follow the money honey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DomPost if teachers want to be paid for school camps and other out of classroom time then 4 weeks not at work like the rest of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teradar cats cats cats hard not to be jealous sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[loving the mypass technology for lift passes at Mt Hutt : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the heritage queenstown room view - nice : ) http://t.co/rvsRNPnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[snow time lodge wanaka - great food nice rooms open fire in the lounge and bar and good prices http://t.co/zw0xgFQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love the mypass system for lift passes lessons etc at My Hutt http://t.co/dLjGnbjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Aotearoa - coming down the mountain after a great afternoon skiing : ) http://t.co/qqkpLa3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[south Korea-wrong thinking. humans can't come before animals - we are codependent - leave the whales alone we are taking too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that rumble in Wellington reminds us all that these are indeed the shakey isles - not fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look in the mirror Rupert Murdoch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[struggling with my daughter forcing her through an education sausage machine that suffocates her - it must change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love this adv on tv tonight very cool http://t.co/sqOoNsAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[signs and fishermen lol http://t.co/LfAqA1JR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love winter I love Aotearoa http://t.co/rKx9Ja6j via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ball night beauties http://t.co/pIHTx3i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the whole is greater than the sum of the parts : ) Tiki Taane performs "Tangaroa" live at the VNZMAs 2008 http://t.co/OnIA6yiR via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the evidence for regulating drugs rather than banning them and funding the war - continues to grow http://t.co/nnnM505d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[belief follows action : ) Shawn Achor: The happy secret to better work http://t.co/2I2YUDaQ #TED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ sued by phillip morris cos health costs halved cos less people smoke - nuts!Groser rejects TPP concerns http://t.co/XgHT6ksh via @3NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groser rejects TPP concerns http://t.co/XgHT6ksh via @3NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's cold and I'm excited about skiing : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Brain ginger beer yes and moderation not required lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke_at_kin lol - click click click - someone's making a buck - cant wait for the movie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Naly_D learn to understand : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[school, factories that process children,strip out creativity and replace it with conformity, the smart kids fail themselves to get out alive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now that status quo won over change - what's the plan to stop the school system failing children. apart from friends who actually liked it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religious institutions protect only their own survival they never look after the people - history is testimony. people look after people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watch the facts emerge as the dust settles in the education story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[heading to rotorua for work and we should all be focussed on work and 3 women-we seeing if we can fit in a visit to the Polynesian spa! lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanBulfin really! might have to share playlists sometime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Been A Long Time (Axwell Remix) by TV Rock on #Spotify memories : ) http://t.co/5xycDS3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Lonely Boy by The Black Keys on #Spotify  http://t.co/VVd1aow8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love seeing young men caring about things that really matter - our assets - signing people up at the market today : ) http://t.co/sQaYnuYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tired of changing channels and finding the same song playing zm/edge! George fm come to Wellington please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGC_FANS sick of the critics l'oreal in aotearoa - your worth it : ) go for it boys and girls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching  Fraser High School send a boy home because he can't afford black school shoes - really! get your priorities right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lonely truth speaking up protects out own humanity http://t.co/zhMIixvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's hard to tell the difference between feeling good doing the right thing knowing it is the right thing you are doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wicked Game by Chris Isaak, from #SoundHound http://t.co/ZQPfMySc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so went to Mac for a $90 makeup/over and spent $200 - how did that happen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trinity Roots tickets, concerts and tour dates #Ticketmaster_NZ http://t.co/EtLDLD3v Tonight - Bar Bodega : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethos (Directors Cut) Full Movie http://t.co/gRkZiu7w via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the GC will do more for Maori aspiration than any health promo here at home-fitness health hard work ambition tumeke : )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Cinzialm: Great covers here. RT Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery. http://t.co/hDIuhEU2”love Mstt Corby]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>