<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT Hmmm.... The job of "Personal Food Taster" may be coming back in need...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Because if it becomes 'normalized' that America is already a killer, no one / fewer will flinch when he makes it one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump tweets judge should be blamed if 'something happens' - CNET https://t.co/dcOQeuer7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinmochrie I see so many kind-hearted / gofundme retweets from you. You have a heart of gold! (Most celebrities ignore most posts)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 Oh no! How horrible! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Who ya gonna take out to make a vacancy, George? ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory A guy in a Beef Jerky hat? Taking money to protest? Naw...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory Hold on - What makes a racist - if not words and deeds / actions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy Jealous! Great idea - better than super bowl. Stealing for next year!  ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Yeah - Bill (Clinton) bearly pulled off the 'aw shucks'. Pence can't work-it anywhere near Bill's finesse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriMelber If the sock is CLEAN it keeps bottled drinks cold. Done this for hiking / camping. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueTorontoGirl Not too loudly, though, because then they'll know someone's home - and keep knocking until you answer... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissamccarthy Absolutely stunning! You completely disappeared into the (Spicer) role - All I saw was Spicer! Bravo! Encore! Encore! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Land https://t.co/R1KI0atEO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curlymalloy Huh. And I thought it was a death star ice cube. https://t.co/inHT2HB0LT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldripvonwinkle @nickkristof OH - EW! That is SO not true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy And that's ok - because he's never going to switch lanes... :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio But if he says we are, and people accept it - then when he DOES act like Putin it won't make any waves. See the (il)logic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lev_Davidovitch You beat me to it! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ron Wyden wants to remind you—the FBI knows things about Trump and Russia that they're not sharing https://t.co/MkLxM2bNYx…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder: SchoolHouse Rock's 'Three Ring Government' https://t.co/51qgflCGsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SATIRE - Fake primatologist dissects Trump's tweets https://t.co/2qzASvGHcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump defends Putin over Russia killings allegations https://t.co/368aC5kRLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Trump bid to restore travel ban rejected https://t.co/sqBbo0R1P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoannePistonFan Run with this - illustrate it... The whole deal...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcatracy The Villain / Antagonist never thinks they're the bad guy. They always believe they are the hard done by, maligned do gooder...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iwearaonesie You know, there are movie theaters that will serve you small meals...  They're called VIP theaters. https://t.co/ZyMGx7Ruk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence: Neil Gorsuch to Join SCOTUS One Way or the Other | https://t.co/RUiWaH9Vpo https://t.co/pgjrUw56pO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErickFernandez Cambridge Dictionary - "so called" - used to show that you think a word that is used ... is not suitable or not correct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Trump is still tied to his businesses - CNN Video https://t.co/tgVLPlNEYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump attacks another federal judge with whom he disagrees - https://t.co/yiv5lwgIlV https://t.co/h79BnXyxF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeland Security suspends travel ban - https://t.co/yiv5lwgIlV https://t.co/eLD9mqAJzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is Why Poor People Can (And Should) Have Nice Things https://t.co/VgCUhIrP27 https://t.co/en2lKQh2DC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Nominee Neil Gorsuch Has a Troubling History RE:  Disability Rights Cases https://t.co/PYAGMIAlnc https://t.co/kmt1c655h0…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High radiation levels at Fukushima reactor is bad, bad news - CNET https://t.co/t9bN4RIlwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unprecedented number of leaks from WH imply fear of POTUS https://t.co/siznNexFym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's running America? https://t.co/3sKT5jYoGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torontoist It's so true - we've been pleasantly surprised by a Hardy's Bankside Shiraz after 9 - 10 yrs in the bottle. (So we're aging 8)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MommaUnfiltered Can I have a bit of both? (Forget specific things and people to make room for all the good stuff?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisBlundell NOOOoooooooo! Not the dog! Anybody but the dog! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbritt06 Hypervigilance :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cfcpac I know - it's so frustrating! I feel like yelling - "What's the matter with you?! How can you not understand this simple logic?!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump adviser cites non-existent Bowling Green 'massacre' defending ban - https://t.co/yiv5lwgIlV https://t.co/EsHPaOVMTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hill Republicans revolt over Trump's border wall - https://t.co/yiv5lwgIlV https://t.co/5Vt4glwW3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk: I will raise objections to Trump's travel ban at White House meeting https://t.co/1OH1ACFcWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deray 'cause girls (esp us white girls) are supposed to be nice, and seen but not heard, and if we can't say something nice, say nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert Well, I guess if you use 1 correctly they won't need the other...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico Merriam-Webster is going to have to update it's definition of candid... to include brutal, asshole...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie Speaks Out Against President Trump's Immigration Ban https://t.co/XaaXBSW1BV https://t.co/IJHK1wjnO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get out of my country." https://t.co/DfYF3SATTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer claims that Houthi rebel assault on Saudi frigate was an Iranian attack on a US warship https://t.co/9pup4fvPkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Christian - Trump at National Prayer Breakfast: 'Pray for Arnold for those ratings' - https://t.co/rIIh5xWx9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatens to pull federal support of California universities https://t.co/xZYrDIVoS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil Gorsuch, Trump's pick for the Supreme Court, was founder of "Fascism Forever Club" at his prep school https://t.co/bQqUehVZOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon: 'We're going to war in the South China Sea ... no doubt' https://t.co/eRP8QW0BN6 https://t.co/DVRrUeVfCn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me - or does VP Pence look like Race Bannon from Johnny Quest? https://t.co/hbuWZjLz2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Notmy_grabber Here's a pic - Race Bannon from Johnny Quest https://t.co/ONbeU4l2Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Notmy_grabber Actually, he looks like Race Bannon from Johnny Quest...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincentdonofrio @mag7movie Awwww :D :'( Happy and Sad; makes me think of my Dad... (He had a beard like that once he retired (early.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dubiousrhetoric And you should almost always put cheese on the not cheese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy If your Dr is incompetent perhaps it explains why you have an untreated psychiatric condition...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge orders emergency injunction and restraining order ending Trump's #muslimban https://t.co/cH021JXJyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP: In call with Mexican president, Trump threatened invasion. White House says it didn't happen. https://t.co/tkoLGYjA49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's voter fraud source caught in contradictions about non-profit he claims to run - https://t.co/yiv5lwgIlV https://t.co/GfeWtcYLy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel Maybe they're just testing the "chatter" to see who's a threat (to Trump) before they start the really scary shit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews This isn't new. Things like this have been happening for years. A bus dropped my son(5) at wrong stop - he was lost for hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenjmolloy It could be both if you work it right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorontoVino Dr. Jack Newman (brst fding consult) of Toronto gave me a similar R/x for wine to help me relax while nursing my 1st son in '87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marcmywords2 Yeah, but they always seem to do it at least 5min too late...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind-boggling graph of Trump's business ties https://t.co/3YobHngWC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon Stewart on Trump: 'We have never faced this before' https://t.co/1P6c7luSbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, as the controversy over Trump raged on, Prince Charles said that he fears the lessons of World War II have been forgotten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CP24 GTFO! That's FUBAR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrooklynDiocese I forgive you. But people will want more. What you said is incredibly wounding. You need to understand why &amp; help them heal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does 'cuck' mean and why are you being called one? https://t.co/oBVcZmpZXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincentdonofrio You seem like such a nice guy... And yet I see you having to deal with so many trolls...  Do you have a bullseye somewhere?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Baumflough Who's brave enuf to do this to his photos in the WH?  He'll lose his shit! :D LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_peech True, but since they are all so ctrlld / managed, I doubt many of them will be given permission to travel far unnecessarily/2shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_peech @mikerinder What revenue?  Aren't they tax exempt?  All those ppl can't refuse to eat and clothe themselves because mayor's words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonCentral Can't or Won't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamuraiKnitter That just means they're lazy racists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackplans So goes the ancient Chinese curse...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsapSCIENCE I SO miss this show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: Jeff Sessions grills Sally Yates on saying no to the president when she was nominee https://t.co/6XH0xkIvzA https://t.co/KmMIrdrJGL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A White House Utterly Devoid of Integrity https://t.co/XaaXBSW1BV https://t.co/qrfc9hRm1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The up-to-date list of companies that sell Trump brands https://t.co/CVsgmJu2O7 https://t.co/Uluu95J0xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Obama ban refugees in 2011? Fact-checking Trump's statements about Obama and refugees https://t.co/uPrehUAiNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xor Short of making the point to pay more attention to your environment, and that the seeming innocent Bundyesque guy may not be innocent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xor How good some sociopaths are at making themselves seem innocent, and harmless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seankent @colinmochrie made a new one up - It's an acronym made of the letter of his name... I think it's Lord Dampnut :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xor She described him as a child because he looks like he's 12. I've seen a photo. They published her quote - not that he actually IS one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monsterLUNCH Much better phraseology - we're not going to sway anyone to our side / change anyone's point of view with harshness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 Is that the technical term?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoodAllergyCAN It would be nice if their fries were actually just fries (only potato), too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fariharoisin I've seen the photo - he looks twelve... But they're lazy idiots for not doing their job / research.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZekeJMiller Ok - when your birthday comes, we'll remember and give gifts to everyone BUT you. If you complain, we'll say you're nitpicking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 The narcissist in him may have him keeping a diary and / or video tapes... If anyone can get those to Dems or Law = hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrspanstreppon Nor will they leave DJT alone with their children - the news has reported multiple times, now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 Yeah!  How does it hurt you that I didn't know that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrspanstreppon Yes, his piano teacher.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>