<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurahknight I directed Cat to Cycle Hack :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catdrew_ @Uscreates @cycle_hack might be able to help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news - and yet Westminster are against replacing car parking spaces with bike hangars https://t.co/hvsS7ZdQYF https://t.co/cLF4vV65Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @tweetymike West Mids police say in their latest blog post it had halved close pass complaints]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By me: Any cyclist in London could be a cop - Met Police to trial 'gold standard' of close pass operations #cycling https://t.co/nL0vyr5veB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnachadhMc @Privatecarfree @StopKillingCycl I'm out of the country (Portugal by train) or I'd be there. It's a timely event, in any case!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seventh day in a row we've had air #pollution warnings in #London. Don't think that run is a… https://t.co/XBv4kKci7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pavement cycling on Vanessa Feltz' breakfast prog. @MPSCamdenTnSgt handles questions of discretionary policing well https://t.co/wCX2OXojF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisneale I'll ask around...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisneale Hope you're ok. It's within borough of Hackney, tho sometimes red routes (TfL) extend into a turning (I believe Old St is a RR)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work from @Squarehighways fixing this after complaints ppl on bikes couldn't get through… https://t.co/ZT7BtbplqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VecchioJo sounds like it was a solid ride. I hope some fruit and veg came along later, too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cox_tom yes! Really excited for you about this. Sounds like it'll be a corker :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avon &amp; Somerset police to run close pass op from spring, but Greater Manchester force cites health &amp; safety concerns https://t.co/1yKOVtIh1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davearthur wow, I haven't heard that one in a long time - what a beautiful song. Can't help hearing "when the smiles were Genoan" though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Singyamatokun that is EXACTLY what I had in mind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Singyamatokun I'd probably bottle it and use the road. Is it possible to keep feet dry without deploying 'the goose'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cuckoojar haha yes they did! I shouted a cheery thank you to the guy as he got back in the truck. The novelty was wearing off a little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That puddle was great while it lasted. My preferred method of attack was the 'goose coming in to land'. Perhaps it'… https://t.co/Rh5IrprcJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendaPuech sorry to hear that, Brenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected WWII ordnance found - blimey https://t.co/a1DAmVn12F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSCamdenTnSgt @Trafficwmp I see a pattern emerging here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSCamdenTnSgt I see your pavement cycling action is garnering lots of attention, though - you're first on that one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinmckie @roadcc @MPSCamdenTnSgt we have covered Camden Police op, but probably should have mentioned in this story, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By me: West Mids Police close pass op could be rolled out to 16 forces. Is yours one? #cycling https://t.co/dT1Owcp1kU via @roadcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwenRogers @r_baruch Wmids police tell me they spent time with @metpoliceuk separately on this. Met's contention LDN traffic moves too slow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London air right now: toxic soup for breakfast, lunch and dinner #airpollution https://t.co/1Tgud9JbRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumberbeatRoads do you have a contact for your press office? Can't see on website. Am a journalist with enquiry. Thank you in advance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news from Cambridge - thousands more ppl cycling now on two roads with  protected cycle routes https://t.co/YfGrSSw9bM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a longer clip of Sadiq Khan talking about cycle superhighways and congestion h/t @Hackneycyclist https://t.co/tf2fIfBPTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was in response to this excerpt of LBC interview re: construction of cycle superhighways:… https://t.co/1brffjL1bA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanlondonandon @peterwalker99 the Mayor's office sent a clarification https://t.co/dJFN3TngVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hackneycouncil great to see; used to live very close to this crossing &amp; use regularly, with trepidation; some v dodgy driving around there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dean9476 @hackneycouncil actually you pay Vehicle Excise Duty, which is a polluter's tax; roads are paid for from general taxation, in fact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RantyHighwayman I never take cabs, and I didn't write that RMT presser - ask the RMT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just saw a guy wipe his finger on a snowy car as he walked past and put it in his mouth, without pausing #uksnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fussellface so long as you get home before midnight; after that you'll need skis on your pumpkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew it! At least I hoped it. TfL are using mini road sweep vans to de-ice the cycle superhighways. Safe home all… https://t.co/lWNOrS0cK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the justice system failing British cyclists? 16th January to share your experiences with the APPCG
https://t.co/r0zlLkSkkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DermotTcd who said that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The RMT's assessment of why people commute by bike is bizarre, to say the least https://t.co/svRDzTno2G ahead of to… https://t.co/jwWYn2oEuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpacePootler ha! thanks. The Afsluitdijk kind of blew me away, like: they have bike lanes EVERYWHERE. That's the point, v few network gaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LPSullivan I doubt TfL would go for it, unfortunately, but it's a fun idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LdnGreenCycles @LPSullivan @TfL I sense some sort of challenge brewing here ... grit showdown? If they're out of the shed anyway...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Al__S @CambsCC do you have a photo? I'm curious to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossiTheBossi @TfLTravelAlerts I know that cyclists dismount section well. Occasionally the signs disappear, only to be replaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...they actually say they'll keep cycle superhighways clear, which could just be a person with a shovel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TfL say they'll grit bike lanes ahead of the chilly weather... and there's gritting quad bikes(!) Are they like tho… https://t.co/dn0ddvuL1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely writing: The secret life of a food courier https://t.co/NYK4I4pMM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonmacmichael pretty sure they came to my home town Wiveliscombe, for a beer fest my dad used to organise, in the late '90s. Great stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teamsmilersuk Ah yes, LONJOG. That's the badger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys were doing LEJOG on ordinaries back in 1873. In tweed. @ The Running Horses https://t.co/U2v0GsmQzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuteness on full blast #kitten #catnews https://t.co/TGogbPJTUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I caught the Adventure Syndicate's @CarbonCycleKate before she headed for the high seas: If I Can Cross Continents by Bike, Anyone Can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinNightRide @CarbonCycleKate @adventuresynd thanks! bit of inspiration for the New Year. She/they certainly inspire me to ride more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should get a cap to go under my helmet so I can look a bit cooler next to you two @HartleyCycles @moveon2wheels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mycyclingresolution to ride in mud more with friends. These two brought bike frames they built earlier… https://t.co/8643W0qpg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenJennyJones Coal and gas also originate from decomposed organic matter, but they were formed long before medieval times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small new year miracle: dropped bank card and single glove at Shadwell Station earlier; policeman spotted &amp; handed them in. Happily reunited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charltonbrooker it was brilliant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas all https://t.co/OfyulgYsk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thank you @pewseyvelo for helping me with brake realigning and a caffeinated energy gel after all that mud! You've a lovely shop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how much mud happened to the bike and I on Thursday. Had to take both wheels off and… https://t.co/7Wj3guSu5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kim_harding actually that section isn't the NCN - signs tried to direct me onto the road but I ignored them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found a lot of mud today, and I'm knackered from skidding through many miles of it, but wow -… https://t.co/SeFVtTrdkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me for the next few miles #miniadventure https://t.co/nyIvzb5JWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous &amp; misty in Regent's Park this morning. Love seeing the roadies out on their morning… https://t.co/cJ5vu0LYu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bike and I made the train at Paddington. Excited about my mini adventure now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuttyxander like a greatest hits? In an average journey I see at least two stupid things, so I imagine those cameras see incredible stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjhawkins00 @roadcc I'm taking the train :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuttyxander how much footage are you trawling through to get these?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cycled to Stratford-overground to-Camden-cycle to Paddington-train to  Newbury-cycle to Bath. How I'm getting to the @roadcc Christmas party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London's new Cycling and Walking Commissioner just announced as Will Norman - currently Nike Global Partnerships Director]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By me: Proposed cycling ban in former global bicycle manufacturing hub "latest abuse of PSPO powers" https://t.co/25kisTh8DE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ibikebrighton I'll take your word for it. We couldn't get TV reception in my house in Somerset in the '80s, let alone Google Streetview :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bricycle @CityWestminster At last! That is good news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part clean, part archaeological dig - my commuter bike's chain and chain ring are unearthed https://t.co/TnAQcjNIG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neahevans @Braveheart_Fund @Kask_cycling @bilslandcycles @ScottishCycling bravo, Neah! Another win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former APPCG chair Ian Austin writing to May over Grayling dooring saying we can't have SoS for Transport who left scene in the way he did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some are inclined to drive thru Regent's Park at high speed. Traffic volumes too high; gate closures are essential… https://t.co/lbelrMcFwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustrating: no announcement on crucial part of the scheme-Regent's Park gate closures-until summer. Watering #CS11… https://t.co/HEaQyGrfGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening Bank junction up to those on buses, on foot and bikes makes sense. Current space… https://t.co/0XrrDUGEaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work from Waltham Forest https://t.co/Ea0abUa0l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wateeside great to meet you today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only if you spell it right #cylinderist https://t.co/YqhGlaeF0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PodiumAmbition @RevolutionUK I saw Neah in action on the track last weekend - what an impressive rider!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamvaughan_uk congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mragilligan @citycyclists I remember going to the die-in there, April last year - https://t.co/7fYFlKnwXt for Moira Gemmill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bikesandbabies I panic navigated! Defaulted to my old commuting route from Old St.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brilliant sense of direction https://t.co/d2WjzeufIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lkoch99 @LukeBurstow @VecchioJo @beztweets he's done a second one now, in which he's fixed the size of the van and done a speech bubble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets It would obscure the skyline if it were any bigger though. I never would have noticed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets this one made me lol the most]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mutiny on the Bobbin #makeafilmcycling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An American in Paris-Brest-Paris #makeafilmcycling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyadvd @roadcc @SpokesLothian On  new London cycle superhighways that left traffic lane would be held while cyclists had green &amp; vice versa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AmyMartin_ yes it only really tackles one problem, but it's a system used successfully in DK, ND, DE; could help. The joys of twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AmyMartin_  the theory is rule changes would help change that ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AmyMartin_ report says because no legal protection from turning traffic councils r unwilling to risk innovation &amp; build stop-start stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briseglace @roadcc @citycyclists that from pg 18 of the @Phil_PJA report produced by BC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>