<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tucks11 nice to hear from you Michael , glad you got out from that very large rock you have been under.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is always right to do what is right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough day for Willie Mullins ,he knows the territory, knows what to do.Min probably wouldn't have won anyway, Faugheen has been out for ages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect run for Presnting Percy at Punchestown with a view to Cheltenham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool in a difficult moment, we just have to all stick with it. Klopp is the right man if he gets three players in this summer on we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenny_dexter well done Lenny a real fan .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard times teach you a lot. That's why you can't regret what you went through, but rather be thankful for all the lessons it taught you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cracking days sport ahead looking forward to it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of good meetings the last few days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 30 points profit on our January selections https://t.co/me1GdqSr6g …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six weeks today we will be in the middle of the greatest show on turf .The Cheltenham Festival]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog " The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/olPhT3BXcH …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinblake2011 @AtTheRaces  Great piece Kevin the"our horses" is a great way of explaining the bond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re trying to keep everybody happy, the one person that definitely won’t be happy is you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking days spent watching the horses at leopardstown with @mikesylver06 #adaywithdel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some plan wins an incident packed Irish Arkle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melon very impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane fly a great champion perfectly captured https://t.co/WH7V3d8ISx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikesylver06 @LeopardstownRC whole again attomic kitten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fronnelly88 @Reddawwg champion chase or Ryanair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Cheltenham study night with @Reddawwg last night all races looked at!! and I mean all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Leopardstown for me today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreadful about many clouds gave everything always.A terrible shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a card at Cheltenham today, it looks like go either way for punters a pile of short favourites with some cracking handicaps perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to my old friend @peteredodonnell as he looks to guide @AshbourneRFC to all Ireland glory today.Go well Georgie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Taylor announces that 2017 will be his final year on PDC circuit, what a champion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With each passing day, our life gets shorter. Don't waste it. Don't waste it on negativity / nonsense. Spend it well. Live out your purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great punting day with Shaneshill (5/2) and Champagne West (11/1) winning for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A decent day couple of good meetings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to hear Hurricane Fly is having a life size statue unveiled @LeopardstownRC on Sunday well deserved. A great hurdler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Delboy goes in the 145 at Ludlow tomorrow how can he fail LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog " The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/wx7wUnBtce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news about Gordon Kaye I always enjoyed Allo Allo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baffled by Trump being concerned by his inauguration crowd figures,how needy is that making an alternative facts statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking day at Leopardstown its never disappointing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MullinsRichie @gerardbondie @mikesylver06 @LinnaneJonathan looking forward to seeing the natives of my adopted  home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a day watching the horses @LeopardstownRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great effort from Wayne Rooney. the press might leave him alone now.I am a little surprised it's only 250 goals to be uniteds top scorer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerardbondie he is a great bit of stuff love him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithwebs he is a great bit of stuff love him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jezki did what he had to do jumped well delighted with that.Really great to see him back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing Jezki back on the racecourse tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent day Dublin gets another xerox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racing regained its place as the second-best attended sport in Britain in 2016 with overall crowds the third-highest in last ten years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesday we need a tune so I will go for "Sugababes - Freak Like Me"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jharri81 go for Thursday ring you tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog " The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/lUasnkmp7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots on today 4 client meetings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have not seen Rio Ferdinand's reaction to Man utds equalizer yet yesterday look it up on line.its hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jezki on the comeback trail Over 850k in prize money. 13 career wins inc 8 Grade 1s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some hiding for City, Liverpool could have done it draw probably about right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched the whole Cheltenham Festival from 2016 last night with the @RacingUKOnline analysis and interviews. A great production]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A world class sleep in this morning , badly wanted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jharri81 very good JH you never lost it. Are you around for a coffee next week say wednesday or thursday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 C's of Success
1 character
2 competence
3 confidence
4 compassion
5 common-sense
6 curiosity
7 collaboration
8 courtesy
9 courage
10 calm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The name of the game is not to be afraid although there is much to fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No act of kindness, no matter how small is ever wasted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good day sales wise a few things moving forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog " The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/AyZCt7KYC6 …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go well Don Cossack a well deserved retirement awaits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots on today lets go to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmanutd86 tweet them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[48 team world cup what a shambles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to see Kempton close some great memories florida pearl ,kauto star and desert orchid wonderful Christmas memories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StarSports_Bet @losthillsman get on to these boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just started following this lad @VicenteFoxQue interesting stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Augusta Kate looked like she might do it to my eyes hard to be certain.Ruby was busy on her going to the last and then she put down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even as a  massive Liverpool fan, the disrespect Wayne Rooney gets in the UK media is incredible. You could not blame him for moving abroad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of  "Going Loco in Acapulco - The Four Tops" to start Sunday off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some cracking racing today. The veterans race is a great initiative at Sandown should be a cracker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right Friday lets do this, lots on today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things returning to normal, a few changes for the new year bedding in looking forward to seeing how they pan out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog covers all the Christmas action "The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/uKehIIYV4u …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure what Phelan could have done with Hull a real hospital pass of a job.I reckon he is better off out of it Hull are dire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased for Big Sam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathrynFry thanks cathryn nice to hear from you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog covers all the Christmas action "The Racing Week That Was" https://t.co/uKehIIYV4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right first day back to work . It will be "Wham! - Club Tropicana" to send us bouncing into work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great darts two super players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day of the holidays song it has to be "George Michael - Praying for Time". One of my favourite songs of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoying the show about Johnny Logan on Rte. A national treasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheltenham today a very competitive card,nice way to start 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Jools Holland new years eve show some serious operators on it UB40 and abc to name a few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City beaten happy new year reds great result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for 2016 which brought many great things for myself. Looking forward to 2017 to see what it brings, Happy New Year all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my nephew Jack 5 today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten years ago today I married my best friend and biggest supporter @ConstantineSibh .the best of times and the worst we have done it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With my nephews Daniel and Aaron at the races https://t.co/xNUJydYE1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent crowd at leopardstown https://t.co/d3jl4lUDzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a day watching the horses at Leopardstown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DelanyDavid @AndrewDelany not my best work today my mate don poli nearly got me out of it have to do better tomorrow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don poli ran his heart out https://t.co/k2ORzU07ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favourite twins @DelanyDavid @AndrewDelany enjoy the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its @LeopardstownRC today with @ConstantineSibh and the rest of the family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Altior v min could be one of the greatest arkles ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great days racing ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thistlecrack wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give the gift of horse racing this Christmas with our "Christmas Cracker Horse Racing Package" https://t.co/xXtK3TqiXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to one of my most loyal and talented team mate ever @darrylcalder on the arrival of your new Baby Boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St Stephens Day one of the best of the year for sure. A day of top class sport and fun]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>