<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyFett Oh 100% I would be an awful father. I do think I would be an awesome uncle though. All the fun and none of the responsibilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I never have children, because I will never be able to explain to them why America let a man this evil be pr… https://t.co/WJXjojZN7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JapersRink Ovie the playmaker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @JapersRink RIGGED! Crooked Gary Bettman!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our president is fucking unhinged. Absolute insanity. I can't believe we would probably be better off with Mike Pen… https://t.co/b1H1N69cE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimmyTheTruth @Buccigross I show no mercy to ESPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buccigross You also guaranteed Columbus would get 100+ points last year, so maybe you shouldn't be making bold statements like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quesada 2020! (Also, my iPhone autocorrected that to 'quesadilla' and I just think that's racist af, but now I actu… https://t.co/tQRVIfb9jO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tommy_Chalk @BeccaH_JR @YouTube That's bad hockey, but great TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to say congratulations to the people who voted for Trump. You are literally too stupid to insult. Enjoy regretting your decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always remember this: The @GOP would not even hold a vote on Obama's last SC nominee. They have no spine and no integrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see the GOP is cutting back on the hyperbole... https://t.co/PZeTLrRf46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich is hitting the crack pipe apparently https://t.co/rClVNdx4LF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine You're overreacting *Ottawa scores again* Bums. All of them. Get them all out of here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ouzym @WhiteHouse Who did UX on this shit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlowpokeWil @KyleCabana01 Quick we gotta write some songs https://t.co/abIgIlPoYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only describe this as a sound financial decision @gracehelbig https://t.co/gPWASgTPeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @krauthammer I got your copy of The Economist delivered to my office. DM me if you want that joint back. https://t.co/mD3mblBpUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimmy_Price I'm excited to see someone unexpected finally go to the Super Bowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Why can't you spell good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 Sean, he is owning us if you look at the alternative facts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC You're not good at this, Drew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC RT this so the whole world knows it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC How progressive of you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC *Body Mass Index. Please leave the medical terminology to the doctors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Only hicks watch the Dukes of Hazzard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 That's what my mom tells me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC I only use the finest, AMERICAN MADE lard in my cooking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC We're like Obama and Biden. Except a little more cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC I don't know. I'm sure they hurt Donald's feelings, but I don't know him that well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 Trump wouldn't know anything about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Thank you! That means a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 And the tiny hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 Yeah. Trump knows he's fat. You don't have to rub it in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Why wouldn't women be proud of their bodies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC I'm proud of the body God gave me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC The medical term is "Rectal Perforation"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 Some people are cucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC We don't have to be mad. Our hands are normal adult sized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Hey that's "Doctor Fatass" to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 I always attract the gay ones. Never fails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC Please stop calling the president fat. Have some respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC This is the gif the LAMESTREAM media DOESN'T want you to see!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals Again, Drew, didn't march. I'm too fat, remember?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Trump's not my president! I only answer to the black guy from the first 3 seasons of 24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals We know how it works. You text A B C or D to 99099 and find out the winner next episode!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals Donald, is that you? Did you get another twitter account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals It makes perfect sense! Drew has never seen a woman, so he doesn't know what they actually look like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals You mean nocturnal discharges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals TRUMP THAT BITCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals Trump told me that when you're a star, they let you do it. You don't even have to ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals I don't know. I didn't go. I'm afraid of women. They have cooties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Trump wouldn't have gone out like that. He'd have fought the Romans because he's tough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals You can eat your way through anything. Through Jesus, all things are possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @BrewmeisterSTC @CSNCapitals You think my fat ass was gonna march in the cold and rain? C'mon Drew! You know me better than that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Election? That thing where the person who got more votes didn't win? I thought that was fake news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Once again, jokes on you because I'm laying around being fat all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Trump proved that even a fat guy with an ill fitting suit can be president #inspired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Listen, just because they were fat doesn't mean they aren't women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals I just take it one tiny Trump-hand sized step at a time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Jokes on you, I'm only 60 pounds overweight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewcaps1 @CSNCapitals Jesus frowns on people who use language like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @realDonaldTrump "I love wall." "Do you really love wall, Donald?" "...I love wall!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't fucking wait until Mike Huckabee fucking dies. He's a worthless scumbag. Fat sack of shit. https://t.co/8bxMODV01N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I have five of class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradley_fox @WOAPGang Yo no shit all day long I was trying to figure out who the fuck she looked like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can't barely see your eyebrows fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaysonst @PMoehringer @Sully6827 He's also a horrible person. Can't ignore that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealelp Yo tonight is gonna be fucking wild!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianoland He put his defensive fwds out there. Same thing he always does. Pitt scored twice to make it close, and Trotz wasn't risking it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JapersRink @pfholden He was always a bum. I don't know why Caps fans loved him so much and obsessed about him after he left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sickunbelievabl They did the same thing with Quintin Laing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sickunbelievabl I don't know why Caps fans have a tendency to latch on to sub par AHL caliber talents and pretend they're amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @realDonaldTrump I see no reason why Russia would lie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @realDonaldTrump English isn't Trump's strong suit. Even his suits aren't his strong suit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBert07 @BrewmeisterSTC The Caps have arguably the best defensive team in the league right now, and Ovie still plays top minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @JohnBert07 The main objective of hockey: Scoar moar goals https://t.co/w3hl1o7UDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBert07 @BrewmeisterSTC Point production is a pretty good thing to care about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBert07 @BrewmeisterSTC Because Hunter was not a real NHL coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @JohnBert07 Fair point. He sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnBert07 @BrewmeisterSTC Ovie is a point per game player in the playoffs. I wouldn't say he's the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftspell @BrewmeisterSTC The holidays and a case of light beer and Trump tweets and me do not mix well. Or they mix great. I forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftspell @BrewmeisterSTC Yup. Real version was like 40 very's long until my mother told me to shut up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftspell @BrewmeisterSTC "TRUMP: The Motion Picture" starring Alec Baldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftspell @BrewmeisterSTC Best part of Christmas this year was wishing everyone a very very very very very very very very happy new year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftspell @BrewmeisterSTC Trump is the kind of guy who would star in a biopic about himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @realDonaldTrump Trump has the least imaginative vocabulary of any president. At least Bush said funny shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @LockheedMartin He's a terrible businessman. He's just a great bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @LockheedMartin @realDonaldTrump They'll never see it coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @Salon Gotta spend money to make money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Reagan Years are a shitty fucking cover band anyway https://t.co/S0VDqjUWdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @shaftspell @realDonaldTrump Dude, he knows more about the hackers than computer people do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportspickle No, but I was eliminated from the playoffs buy a guy who forgot to set 4 of his roster spots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jlindy @AndyRichter @TEN_GOP Without the Bible Belt states, Trump would not be president. I say they're pretty much useless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stringhama Washington fans are the absolute worst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter @TEN_GOP It would be nice if Tennessee, and the entire South for that matter, wasn't in the US anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrewmeisterSTC @realDonaldTrump @shaftspell We all know exactly what he means by 'refugee'. He means a non-white person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalsHill @BlueJacketsNHL @NHL White people ruin everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyFett @DrJillStein Stein panders to the radical conspiracy theorist left, and it cost her the 5% of the popular vote she was aiming for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyFett @DrJillStein Jill Stein is so fucking stupid, she made Bernie Sanders' supporters vote for Hillary.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>