<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Declaration of the Independence of the Mind: An Extraordinary 1919 Manifesto Signed - Einstein, Russell, Addams, ... https://t.co/HCWPmbgYPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lustig on processed food: a critical review https://t.co/MR8v8unBpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Weeks In: The U.S. Government Under President Trump - The Diane Rehm Show https://t.co/xClItOdUXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Harford — Article — How Politicians Poisoned Statistics https://t.co/fIBe0jRaLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ipsos MORI | Publication | Enough of Experts? Ipsos MORI Veracity Index 2016 https://t.co/7R6YN1rVKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is life the way it is? Michael Faraday Prize Lecture - Dr Nick Lane

Nick Lane of University College London... https://t.co/v59eX0Tq07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top 15 would-be blockbusters in the pipeline prepping for a 2017 launch – ENDPOINTS NEWS https://t.co/r8FoHM9iB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two charts show how fossil fuels could peak by 2020 | Carbon Brief https://t.co/JEjlHg4V2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This mysterious $2 billion biotech is revealing the secrets behind its new drugs and vaccines | Science | AAAS https://t.co/cWXToGpzVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gucci was a super friendly cat who met all at the clinic. She enjoyed being fed treats. I fed her many times. I... https://t.co/DK86JbFRls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Burgers Around the World | Departures https://t.co/Y5iZoCAFGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limitations and risks of meta-analyses of longevity studies https://t.co/I5LYSV9f0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump has announced he will “get rid of and totally destroy” a 60-year-old rule that blocks... https://t.co/ysliNfLG63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Dakota GOP Repeals Anti-Corruption Act Passed By Voters | The Huffington Post https://t.co/0lskJ02WSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[LMAO] Repros Announces New CEO 

Repros Therapeutics Inc.® (RPRX) today announced that [CON MAN] Joseph S.... https://t.co/YXrYRAD0Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[WTF!] New Orleans surgeon accused of rape, illicit filming of patients loses pre-trial challenges

An Orleans... https://t.co/CiCvdrJsN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blood Donation and Testosterone Replacement Therapy

BACKGROUND: Polycythemia is the most common adverse effect... https://t.co/jOLZwCkN6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Wins by Losing a Court Fight Over Debt - Bloomberg View https://t.co/y4U93efFx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nutraceuticals" in Relation to Human Skeletal Muscle and Exercise

Skeletal muscles have a fundamental role in... https://t.co/6wyJIw31K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strenuous Exercise and Cardiovascular Disease Outcomes

Purpose of Review - This review summarizes several issues... https://t.co/qWPRdOH5G3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The “Evil God Challenge” by Stephen Law on Vimeo https://t.co/jWmk8CLLv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey of instructions for authors on how to report an update of a systematic review: guidance is needed. - NCBI https://t.co/sVegIsjyP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There must be some kind of way outta here
Said the joker to the thief
There's too much confusion
I can't get no... https://t.co/a8qw6XkQjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is GnRH regulated in GnRH-producing neurons? Studies using GT1-7 cells as a GnRH-producing cell model.... https://t.co/6uGhjV8WvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Mice] Silencing Myostatin Using Cholesterol-conjugated siRNAs Induces Muscle Growth

Short interfering RNAs... https://t.co/73oNGoIG7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tadalafil Improves Lean Mass and Endothelial Function in Nonobese Men with Mild ED/LUTS

PURPOSE:... https://t.co/O7peU7ermi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low Testosterone, but not Estradiol, Is Associated with Incident Falls in Older Men

Fracture risk is determined... https://t.co/hQZqRjLM2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine questions those protesting against Donald Trump's immigration ban must answer | Coffee House https://t.co/hds15BO4ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] A Review Of The Biomedical Innovations For Healthy Longevity

The field of biogerontology and regenerative... https://t.co/nuMzshn2I8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safety of Very Low Low-Density Lipoprotein Cholesterol Levels With Alirocumab  https://t.co/4CPwcBDCdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chips ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Widodo, Shut down the Bandung Zoo now! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/n9C936wo1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garrison Keillor: Trump is what he is, and God help us now - Tulsa World: Opinionfeatured https://t.co/ToQMCcdvZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinayPrasad82 @nytimes Like a bullet to the head might be more apropos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec City mosque attack suspect known for right-wing online posts - The Globe and Mail https://t.co/S3Pmma2OBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the humanity! Poker computer trounces humans in big step for AI | Technology | The Guardian https://t.co/2nO71xIodf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: Full Text of Draft Dissent Channel Memo on Trump Refugee and Visa Order - Lawfare https://t.co/q6aZzRN4Bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannah Arendt: From an Interview | by Hannah Arendt | The New York Review of Books https://t.co/9aSauzYc3h?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homage to Tsavo 

Listen to Dr. Dame Daphne Sheldrick, founder of the David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust, share her... https://t.co/Lsy1rOG5RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Our Time, Hannah Arendt https://t.co/BQV1fxCORw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doughnut Plant | Making doughnuts by hand. Home of the world's first Crème Brûlée doughnut. https://t.co/H4rWn6aRgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time lapse captures boxer puppy's first birthday - YouTube https://t.co/arsXHcG8LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson, Trump and the South China Sea |  https://t.co/oq1B3erxAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson, Trump and the South China Sea | The Diplomat https://t.co/oq1B3erxAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trial Balloon for a Coup? – Medium https://t.co/Z6Dq7a5UOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Dylan The Times They Are A Changin' 1964 - YouTube https://t.co/0tOUTEIuXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sicily’s Superior Cannoli: A Guide for Connoisseurs—and Skeptics... https://t.co/qf6iUM4HkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eliot A. Cohen Responds to Donald Trump's First Week - The Atlantic https://t.co/ZFkxhAAGGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In sport ‘no positive tests’ is not the same as ‘there is no doping’
You know the most remarkable thing about... https://t.co/do95u2fu4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Guide to the GOP Tax Plan – The Way to a Better Way by David A. Weisbach https://t.co/aqSAkQtWRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketers Exploit The Aged With Unproven Brain-Health Claims https://t.co/YPGSFANmQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] [Clomiphene] Testosterone Deficiency In A Man Interested In Preserving Fertility: NYU Case of the Month 

A... https://t.co/Sq6w61CzQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Troubling Rise of the ‘Genotocracy’

Imagine a world where dating services offer predictions about which... https://t.co/vz8d8QWBAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] The Cost of Seeking an Edge: Recurrent Renal Infarction in Setting of Recreational Use of Anabolic Steroids... https://t.co/1gocY0pz35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 BBC One Documentary President Donald Trump The Kremlin Candidate? 
https://t.co/IUSeabL7DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin's Way 
https://t.co/5nWxZRVjBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AIDS in Russia: Immune to reason | The Economist https://t.co/G1gpS2R1f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Duma’s war on women: Why Russia is about to decriminalise wife-beating | The Economist https://t.co/FiXtPzBHb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign policy: The fog of wars | The Economist https://t.co/qldaK6UfYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family suspected a caregiver was abusing an Alzheimer’s patient. So they installed a camera.

Brenda Floyd was... https://t.co/YXwSzPx38Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rachel Carson 

Featuring the voice of Mary-Louise Parker as the influential writer and scientist, Rachel Carson... https://t.co/sb9SPNfQue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Maher Unloads on Trump: ‘This Is About a Guy Who Never Brought a Woman to Orgasm’ - The Daily Beast https://t.co/TQeAcPQcW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California clears hurdle for cancer warning label on Roundup https://t.co/3xgGNLnwGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Delusion of Alternative Facts - Scientific American Blog Network https://t.co/MNL0kqSTD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tower of Cards (part 1) – Christo's blog https://t.co/EUwJgOZwnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To tackle the post-truth world, science must reform itself https://t.co/bRkXzS8Ada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Role of Free Testosterone Levels in Patients with Metastatic Castration-Resistant Prostate Cancer Receiving... https://t.co/P1qMwJDMsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer-based personality judgments are more accurate than those made by humans https://t.co/hBMyOSlmSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelWosnick @nytimes Has a nice ring to it ... #LapDogTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[movie — When Elephants Were Young https://t.co/fX5D3O0qfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat Stevens - I Love My Dog[s] 

I love my dog as much as I love you
But you may fade, my dog will always come... https://t.co/xSCTVPnXdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] Is Hemoglobin A1c the Right Outcome for Studies of Diabetes?. [No] 

The goals of treatment of type 2... https://t.co/RDZwHiTNfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crystal Structure of an LSD-Bound Human Serotonin Receptor: Cell https://t.co/JfsDlapDoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] The Effect of Endocrine Disorders on Lipids and Lipoproteins

A variety of endocrine disorders can alter... https://t.co/3vbiIEAsIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testosterone Deficiency and Sleep Apnea

KEY POINTS
• Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) is associated with altered... https://t.co/o2bFLffqYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testosterone Prevents Protein Loss Via The Hepatic Urea Cycle In Human

Context: The urea cycle is a rate... https://t.co/dNlGuoz0Bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erythropoietin as A Performance-Enhancing Drug: Its Mechanistic Basis, Detection, And Potential Adverse Effects... https://t.co/7eSBfNF5SY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a first, Alaska divorce courts will now treat pets more like children... https://t.co/TBvVXuuW7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump cranks up the crazy to 11 in this ABC interview. Highlights and full transcript. / Boing Boing https://t.co/PprIg99BuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did humans evolve big penises but small testicles?
Humans have a much longer and wider penis than the other... https://t.co/QUz3J8gscR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man with Bionic Penis Must Endure Two-Week Erection to Finally Use It 

Andrew Wardle has been a virgin his... https://t.co/Evv0z0cTwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dermatologist-level classification of skin cancer with deep neural networks : Nature : Nature Research https://t.co/bPOYOomJbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A solution to the single-question crowd wisdom problem : Nature : Nature Research https://t.co/W9Tf7HySbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allman Brothers Band - One Way Out - Closing Night At The Fillmore (6/27/71) - YouTube https://t.co/b0agSCMCDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Butch Trucks, Allman Brothers Band Drummer and Co-Founder, Dead at 69... https://t.co/3Gcjugkcrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] Targeting Hypoxia-Inducible Factors for the Treatment of Anemia in Chronic Kidney Disease Patients... https://t.co/FksOP60Cgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usain Bolt stripped of 2008 Olympic relay gold after Nesta Carter fails drug test

Usain Bolt is no longer a... https://t.co/442VKvL0hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategies That Athletes Use to Avoid Detection of Androgenic-Anabolic Steroid Doping and Sanctions

Highlights
•... https://t.co/ahgHHzXczx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first days inside Trump’s White House: Fury, tumult and a reboot - The Washington Post https://t.co/5Fdiuqmu3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You walk into the room with your pencil in your hand
You see somebody naked and you say, "Who is that man?"
You... https://t.co/k6AnfNN8hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, where have you been, my blue-eyed son
And where have you been, my darling young one
I've stumbled on the side... https://t.co/oPEVzu8KbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Alright, Ma (I'm Only Bleeding) - YouTube https://t.co/RuwMnCH0LG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Molecular Psychiatry - Cannabis use and risk of schizophrenia: a Mendelian randomization study https://t.co/ZL6xVOALST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone is murdered, they always investigate the spouse 1st.  And that pretty much tells you everything you... https://t.co/MfVN8NpSsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] Cardiorespiratory Fitness and Adiposity as Determinants of Metabolic Health – Pooled Analysis of Two Twin... https://t.co/o258dy2cQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] Pharmacokinetic Evaluation of a Single Intramuscular High Dose versus an Oral Long-Term Supplementation of... https://t.co/2xYQEzHpj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[OA] Kisspeptin Modulates Sexual and Emotional Brain Processing in Humans 

BACKGROUND: Sex, emotion, and... https://t.co/wy0ES025t3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Written evidence submitted by Nicole Cooke MBE (BDA0012)   

I have been asked to submit evidence to the Culture... https://t.co/EIV5x3Yo4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate Code Red: Antarctic tipping points for a multi-metre sea level rise https://t.co/33TS3x2t5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swapping Systematic Reviews for Celebrity Endorsements   

The actor Ben Stiller has written an essay on prostate... https://t.co/SRjmCM1b7E]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>