<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@hammerqos Nice pic. Looking forward to a home game on Saturday. Been ages since at ER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1.3m sign petition to stop a 70 year old idiot embarrassing a 90 year old woman. 

Sounds like a scene from most bowling clubs at weekends 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although trump is a complete clown I'm not signing any petition due to the line about "causing embarrassment to the queen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are now debating the pros and cons of waterboarding cos Trump is a fan. Crazy times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what the value of my house is excluding the bedrooms? https://t.co/UAKrdtWjWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Terry May to give Trump a quaich as sign of friendship. Over now to our media to call it a British drinking vessel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This headline from @SkyNews is awful - plotting?

MPs plotting dozens of Brexit amendments  https://t.co/9TNmqMkD1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianPe07306064 I was told to block the person. Seems to work a treat 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MixuDave Thanks Dave. That's it done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know how you remove yourself from a list that you don't want added to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TippingPointITV always good for a giggle. 

Country in English beginning with q?
Kuwait
ENT stands for ear, nose &amp;?
Teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now for BBC Scotland to tell us it's a good thing Holyrood has no say at all after #SupremeCourt ruling #indyref2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaorAlbannach Worrying stat. My partner works in a care home. Only 1 voted so 96% does seem wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hammerqos I think every Hibs fan knew at some point there would be a shocker. Awful challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a pub full of maroon cord wearing lads as draw came out. They are not happy drawing us #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billydoyle07 I could have got back quicker from east end park than it took to get out of the pink palace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steps in the Wheatfield must have been built for Ronnie Corbett's wee feet #GGTTH https://t.co/r0raokUNf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheatfield stand. Just not fit for purpose #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freezing fog &amp; visibility under 100yds. How will ref Alan Muir cope when he can't see a handball against Hibs from 2yds #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in today's sports section we patronise another part time footballer who has a job we think is worse than a sports reporter #ScottishCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holyroodboxing Looking forward to seeing what happens to Mr Doyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Djokovic forgot to take his anti Istomin tablets today at the @AustralianOpen #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mums and sons day this morning at the wonderful @GilmertonCove #Edinburgh https://t.co/uR9UvsUwEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hammerqos @74frankfurt Absolutely Lindsay. Riordan was a joy to watch. A real favourite for us Hibees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray Down Under

https://t.co/dI9sluFhN3 

Nice pics porty @kelawin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Theresa May's leaked speech on Tuesday will be a big step on the road to an independent Scotland… https://t.co/HVXWc1kOCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rare giant white pacman terrorising the streets of #Edinburgh today https://t.co/MPLopINCPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be fun. Fill yer boots Frankie https://t.co/GdwY1gJIpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavyTolmie I always stop at the church ruin just before this. Beautiful spot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if we hadn't had a second vote for a devolved Scots parliament it would be Willie who? https://t.co/1HVv47cbAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to ticket office at 10:30. Looking like over 2 hour wait for anyone coming down for cup tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiz shows like @ITVChase ask questions on London Underground routes. Never ask about stops on @EdinburghTrams #saughton 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNewsHQ can your presenters stop saying "have a look at this". We've all grasped the concept of TV now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarchOnLaddie Was a great night mate #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think the residents of Palmerston Place care that I've got mcginn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queuing for a Jarkko Wiss at Easter road. Great to see the stadium so busy #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3:30 beers in town 
6:00 Italian restaurant Leith Walk
9:40 sunshine on Leith?
#GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legod0407 Correct mate. It's a funny old place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hibs2152016 Aye folk checking how many tickets sold every 2 secs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billydoyle07 Folk counting dots on their pc to see how many tickets sold on ground map]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulstewarty Folk obsessed for the last two weeks about how many tickets sold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only Hibs fan who isn't getting excited about the dot count on hibs net?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianPe07306064 Great spot and guests love it as tour buses don't do that road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today at Rowardennan by Loch Lomond @lomondtrossachs @lovelochlomond https://t.co/X9uznss5FL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #YearinSport. Go inside the app and watch my 2016 on Strava. Make your own at https://t.co/yojtqMItQE. https://t.co/jIlica7T7k #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big match in Scotland ends in a 2-1 away victory to the team in green @HibsOfficial #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falkirk and Hibs Fans Fighting 

Stay safe Hibs fans. It's like a war zone. Casualties may be high 😉 https://t.co/jl7HcP5I3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoof - chase - repeat 

Levein will be awfy proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wee stroll on the beach before today's tour. It's a tough job @VisNorthBerwick https://t.co/PLCIaVPf1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never a day goes by without Dawn French &amp; Kate Middleton and their impact on Scotland being at the forefront of my… https://t.co/zHtstc5E0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another wee snap from the beach this morning at North Berwick @welcomescotland https://t.co/z4vkYLsJYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning from North Berwick https://t.co/pWsCAd6R4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 2 @BBCScotlandNews unable to show due to technical difficulties 

If you've got nothing good to say then say nothing at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2016In4Words Hibernian and Andy Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btsportfootball apologising for a saints player swearing 

Any comment on sectarian singing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@exiledhibee He's a plum. We've had some awful managers but he really tops the lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rangers just like Arsenal says Butcher 

Our game is bad enough without his ramblings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itv please check your facts and stop making things up. It's not free to park in all Scottish hospitals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another first for the great land that is Scotland https://t.co/n2MNH1CaD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A moment of Scottish history in St Andrews https://t.co/xPq2zg7VJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not long now til penalty for hearts starts trending again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForeverMcGregor @HibsOfficial What a pressie. Well done Linda #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@friendlydragon I think, rightly or wrongly, it's a comment about the people that attend rugby in auld reekie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must have cost a wee fortune on wrapping paper https://t.co/LXBwqQRcgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestPilton @EdiHelpingHands @HibsOfficial Nice one Mikey. Just off to shops to get my donation and then off to the Leith San Siro #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#stormBarbara causing havoc and @spfl asking fans to travel from Glasgow to Dingwall. Football in a storm is mad. Call games off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chezally Just mad that it even gets a mention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second headline on the itv news is that the queen has a snottery beak. Pray for the windsors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today looking at The Five Sisters of Kintail @welcomescotland @VisitScotland https://t.co/loj0zXOPly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tricky drive weather wise to get to Eilean Donan but always worth it @welcomescotland @1EileanDonan https://t.co/DAo7eDxyGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0604Arb1320 One of my guests got blown over today. Welcome to Scotland 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today at Loch Bay and it's a bit wild https://t.co/HAlsyIestG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Images from around #skye today @welcomescotland https://t.co/BknSa1l7Om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning from Portree before the storm really hits @welcomescotland https://t.co/hIiDpJUBox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hammerqos "Relax with a capstan full strength "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wee detour to catch the sunset over Loch Shiel and Glenfinnan late this afternoon @welcomescotland @N_T_S https://t.co/eHuBXG7wAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a great lunch with stunning views at @ClachaigInn @discoverglencoe @welcomescotland https://t.co/mqhypLcDXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some images as we head to Portree for the evening @welcomescotland @mvscotland https://t.co/dsziZmEps1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Portree tomorrow. Glad it's a better road https://t.co/2BhsLIL0Lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyMcRorie @CodeAud She was very impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @theSNP give Ruth a shot on a tank it should be enough to get #ScotBudget through Holyrood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great night tonight at Carrick Knowe bowling with #persevered tour and @HibsOfficial with my lad @Jamieking_97 and… https://t.co/Fc6UrjScN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bankaudits1 Aye I passed school earlier and saw they were there. Spreading the love #GGTTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bankaudits1 Good laugh Mike. And then we watched the cup DVD. I've had worse Tuesdays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wee hibees night out in Carrick Knowe bowling club tonight. Great night #GGTTH https://t.co/H5RpOfHiCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davybrook If it wasn't for the pensioners pointing out where they had a bag off i could almost hear the musical greats 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hibee_10_6 Scottish cup at carrick knowe bowling club from 7pm tonight on #persevered tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punctured bicycle on a hillside desolate #memories https://t.co/Y12RiWdrj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoorWullie @AngGallacher I mention this censorship on my outlander tours and the guests are stunned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching those American football players having a brawl with full protection on. Only way to hurt each other is by a Chinese burn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMalky STV news around about 6pm tonight gave it a few mins which surprised me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add in the fact Scottish salmon is UK's biggest food export. We would do just fine and they ken that #indyref2 https://t.co/pTzNyCjExJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting in Greyfriars having a cheeky beer watching everyone taking Bobby's photo. So I decided on the clinkers shot https://t.co/cGiS1Jmz8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord advocate speaking now in Supreme Court for Scotland. Time for UK media to be distracted by cute kitten pics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onercetin1 you are right. Trust me we do have better refs but not many. Good luck for season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the Craig Thomson penalty from last night. Welcome to our world Besiktas fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today by Loch Venachar @lomondtrossachs https://t.co/EVuwtXkYUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit dreich around Loch Lubnaig today but still nice @lomondtrossachs @welcomescotland https://t.co/DbPLFGRV2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Calum_McC they came about 15 minutes after you left mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwr66 just a wee coffee while we waited]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>