<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tagged! Go team #eCoach https://t.co/gkKnBSCb40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh, Google is recommending me the Donald Trump Soundboard app. I need to rethink my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go team #eCoach https://t.co/idmskMWwJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 43 minutes, 27 seconds going 5204.5m. https://t.co/18cLk1wuj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garminau my forerunner 235 doesn't do heart rate anymore since a software update that won't install. please fix asap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New bling! (Old watch, new red strap) https://t.co/hN5XR1okyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 32 minutes, 3 seconds going 4006.5m. https://t.co/tHUbMQcQ2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 34 minutes, 48 seconds going 4003.6m. https://t.co/a7jJFJryyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 47 minutes, 46 seconds going 9810.7m. https://t.co/V4UYDzuR5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 42 minutes, 33 seconds going 4960.0m. https://t.co/7iYKtemtyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My office https://t.co/s5ffeUD5fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 19 minutes, 13 seconds going 2377.9m. https://t.co/j4HLo57Fp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FraudStop lets you quickly and easily challenge false #Centrelink debt letters #notmydebt #fraudstop https://t.co/eRW7vCUHu0 via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 42 minutes, 8 seconds going 4486.5m. https://t.co/azx2X0Q3QK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh, it's the git police. `git stash clear`]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOP has to be my favourite instruction. I could do NOP all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 3 minutes, 36 seconds going 6024.4m. https://t.co/2siQ5myJlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selfie with my dog. Resemble much? https://t.co/YaTN23j3uT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 27 minutes, 32 seconds going 9172.0m. https://t.co/RrAzW2ZX9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 38 minutes, 44 seconds going 4921.5m. https://t.co/SgXrxQdEuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 49 minutes, 34 seconds going 5168.5m. https://t.co/ZnZqL9W23k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else getting brownouts in Rutherford? Too many air conditioners running :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 35 minutes, 21 seconds going 4021.5m. https://t.co/SGpbQ6RXjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 32 minutes, 2 seconds going 3472.0m. https://t.co/LMtR0g6v2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@00d4n1 you would hope so, but i wouldn't be too sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ffs @XeroAPI - all apis returning 403 !== "degraded performance", it means your service is completely unavailable. https://t.co/d6hLzLxToX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 48 minutes, 4 seconds going 5144.8m. https://t.co/7dOIWQrNvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 40 minutes, 50 seconds going 5035.0m. https://t.co/peNlOvdpbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out #mylastfmyear at https://t.co/os23lJNbIY via @lastfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 37 minutes, 49 seconds going 4004.7m. https://t.co/6zsrdGAgii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 41 minutes, 15 seconds going 4275.3m. https://t.co/TCilq96o3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 18 minutes, 55 seconds going 8940.7m. https://t.co/eS5k5o6xRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tagged! Getting sunburnt waiting to go in https://t.co/Za8eNwrI7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 36 minutes, 8 seconds going 5031.9m. https://t.co/1M3J6SlBc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 17 minutes, 45 seconds going 2299.1m. https://t.co/ZgX3wDmWVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 20 minutes, 59 seconds going 2545.7m. https://t.co/4Dd1H34gMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can we expect from Australian climate politics in 2017? - https://t.co/Gj89sXrvJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['MASH' Star William Christopher Dies At 84 - https://t.co/LdjbkwHtmj - 2016 snuck in another death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though it's an error, I have to start repaying my 'debt': Centrelink debt victims - https://t.co/HTBotk1V8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet papers 1992-93: Australia reluctant while world moves towards first climate treaty - https://t.co/LrHE8HG1aT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend of mine suggested that I try to do every parkrun in NSW in 2017. wdyt? https://t.co/mXWYdvEjNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 43 minutes, 17 seconds going 4971.5m. https://t.co/AdV1B53JB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 37 minutes, 48 seconds going 4967.5m. https://t.co/QZc5YuhRQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andy_snow Install a third party rom on an android, with the app you want them to use, and delete everything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 35 minutes, 42 seconds going 4976.9m. https://t.co/92JC9bXVDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Critical Zero-Day Flaws Found in PHP 7 — One Remains Unpatched! - https://t.co/L9MCADnhew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem attorneys general threaten lawsuits if Trump repeals climate plan - https://t.co/1hr6jIj4ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 27 minutes, 28 seconds going 9188.0m. https://t.co/uKCeUEn3To]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first 3 years of running... what will next year bring? https://t.co/5Aq67Pezd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmbhurgri @SaraMG I found disabling plugins which I wasn't using helped my phpstorm speed. It comes with the kitchen sink enabled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Waiting on stock - but no idea if or when it will arrive. I've been without a phone for almost a month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Companies Are Trying to Hire More People on the Autism Spectrum - https://t.co/6P1aCSkAJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraMG It doesn't help that if you're hosted with AWS, hundreds of spam bots register with invalid emails which blocks your SES account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraMG jetbrain's intellij ides such as phpstorm are java and they're quite good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Yes, phone is assessed, it wasn't covered by warranty, and it can't be repaired, but they can't supply me with a Nexus 6p, no stock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraMG Did another celebrity die? Who was it this time? Please be Justin Bieber or Donald Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My TOP 5 dev tools:
1. @googlechrome
2. @phpstorm
3. @smartgithg
4. @discordapp
5. @Spotify
#MustHaveDevTools - What are yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus I put a phone in for warranty repairs on 1st of December and you can't give me an ETA on when I will get a replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Home PC is not coping well with mixing work and play over the holidays. Booting Ubuntu then Windows is messing… https://t.co/KImJWilTmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched https://t.co/N0b8h1YgMz - best 30 minutes of viewing ever. Immediately purchased the game on steam! @kungfuryfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@binnightbot omg the bins! I nearly had forgottens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Why is your customer service so terrible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 23 minutes, 9 seconds going 8600.2m. https://t.co/qow3FxDQ2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4th search result. Lolz. https://t.co/vKCBbaCjGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which #parkrun time could I potentially beat next weekend? https://t.co/ETVXjydhNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Reality Therapy Could Help People With Depression Find Drug-Free Relief - https://t.co/bVjb0S5Eac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will Artificial Intelligence Mean for Education? – The Tech Edvocate - https://t.co/ysbBbFlS4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emily is trying to tell me something. I wonder what it could be? https://t.co/ImnAIUnqFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 35 minutes, 30 seconds going 5021.3m. https://t.co/Tu7iNwLHOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 35 minutes, 16 seconds going 4919.2m. https://t.co/GG5941xllB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tagged! snuck a selfie of myself with Toby https://t.co/QL28F1DAUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[snuck a selfie of myself with Toby https://t.co/UEFR3crcoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@binnightbot oh wow I'm so excited! Amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 23 minutes, 22 seconds going 2974.0m. https://t.co/KYOEMWXOID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink urged to stop collecting welfare debts after compliance system errors https://t.co/LZmTRGQxa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This psychedelic NASA video shows how CO2 spreads in the atmosphere https://t.co/SeA3Lys5AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How an old Drawbridge helped Microsoft bring SQL Server to Linux ... https://t.co/cjlhDeMItL https://t.co/Dlppma3mgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GetUp! - Congratulations! This is a big win for Grandpa... | Facebook https://t.co/3Vrk9ytp1E https://t.co/AQNVD1UGwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallout is Coming to Minecraft https://t.co/wq7tM6V3yk https://t.co/9T8bBh73sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmacca6060 look forward to it, might take me a while to get back to 30 minutes anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deardsy I'm doing ok today. Off to Hornsby to buy a new car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 39 minutes, 5 seconds going 4958.1m. https://t.co/utnHxT8usA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adidas' new 3D-printed sneaker will cost $333 a pair https://t.co/wV4IyIVUvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD’s ‘Ryzen’ chips integrate neural nets for killer performance https://t.co/6lsfgQsHc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On climate change and the economy, we're trapped in an idiotic netherworld https://t.co/vxN6Q26PRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British man jailed over plan to kill Donald Trump https://t.co/JceT6Z9xY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stared at 15 grams of Seroquel for at least 30 minutes before deciding not to take it. I was so close tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Sharon and I might be taking a holiday together in the psych ward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deardsy nope, my wife has attempted suicide and I'm seriously considering doing it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've made a FACS report, telling them that if Toby continues living in this house that Sharon and I will kill him… https://t.co/ghTIW9ZJ7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Cheshire? Seriously Microsoft wtf? This has to be the worst todo list application EVER.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 35 minutes, 33 seconds going 4106.6m. https://t.co/WEHv0Roi0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kmacca6060 Love your doughtnuts ;) https://t.co/zZDJOXtSYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 1 hour, 29 minutes, 4 seconds going 10002.8m. https://t.co/h8CiZ5XsTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a Run on Strava for 37 minutes, 56 seconds going 4946.4m. https://t.co/GO87LrBFoZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deardsy How's life post Futura? Keeping yourself busy? What you been up to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only run half of these 8, got some places to try. https://t.co/hZuzzVsHMH https://t.co/EraNh9WIFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just backed The PHPDiversity Rainbow Elephpant on @Kickstarter https://t.co/NCVvD4FQrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned a bumper sticker from @DashMobile: Speed Racer https://t.co/JjKTsopZN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XeroAPI Our API requests just timed out again and I still can't submit that support form. Do you plan on doing anything about it?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>