<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Deluxe River Cruise - Celebrating New Special Interest and Bicycle Trips https://t.co/kAetO8t76e #travel https://t.co/ymoEAOwDST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Perfect Hotels in Times Square for All Budgets and Needs https://t.co/uYegSFz3XX #RewardingExperiences https://t.co/cVQonkiANZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Cancer Day &amp; My Continued Giveback to My Cancer Family https://t.co/48EOgqapyC via @TraveliciousDee… https://t.co/fwV6YENloM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 10 Things to Do in Kyoto, Japan https://t.co/zJ6SeGQKoe by @youcouldtravel #Travel https://t.co/5NQ3ceNOxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitCA Thanks! Most of our 2017 travel is booked, but one day we'll get there. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bosnia &amp; Herzegovina - A Road Trip Spotlight in Photos https://t.co/4HwOgFqX9d @Jones_y #travel https://t.co/DZsvqq1duj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eview7 Anything with avocado gets a thumbs up by me! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitCA We will! We got our motorcycle licenses a few years ago and this would be an epic ride #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time we met up with @JohnnyJet #TravelSkills https://t.co/PLkL3JelNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q10 Post a photo from a trip to California! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sometimeshome @spankyandsarah Yes! Not enough places to that anymore #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JTKron I loved seeing them. They lived up to the hype and are so impressive #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q9 What's the most beautiful, memorable, not-to-be-missed sight along the California coast? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitLB @Mattieologie I would love every one of those dishes! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spankyandsarah I love live music when I eat #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@always5star @kamgharana Thanks for the heads up. I only went to the touristy spots since I've only been to SF once :) #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyJet @PacificaCoC @innoutburger I wouldn't expect you to say anything else :) #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarperTravel @thePROGRESS_sf @lazybearsf @LordStanley_sf @InSitu_SFMOMA Well, that is a work of art! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8 I haven't spent enough time in California to choose one #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q8 What's your favorite restaurant in California? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@always5star Fisherman's Wharf is fab. I've actually been there. We've hardly been anywhere in California, so I'm proud :) #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyJet @PacificaCoC Love this picture! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@exploretravel1 @quirkytraveller Thank you. It was a great tour with @UrbanAdventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A7. I don't know, maybe Bubba Gump Shrimp because it was in a Hollywood movie? #TravelSkills https://t.co/dgWIyfBm7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q7 What seafood dish makes you think of California? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitCA We haven't. Looking at all these photographs makes me want to take a motorcycle trip! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love NorCal? The Ultimate San Francisco Photography Guide https://t.co/GecGQAepRu by @ericbravo #TravelSkills https://t.co/OOYoI5yI4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to California...72 Hours in San Francisco https://t.co/2jwFkQSR9J by @yonderpostcards #travelskills https://t.co/Fo3zszP0R1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q6 What's the best airport along the California coast? Why? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchmyvr @FunBeachHouse , Hey, @JimByersTravel  chose that town too :) #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SantaBarbara Fantastic reflection #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VisitCA That is beautiful! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a5 Alamere Falls, Point Reyes National Seashore looks pretty awesome! #TravelSkills https://t.co/zdDJJMdm24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@always5star Agreed! I have to go back and do another road trip through California #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q5 What's your favorite California beach or beach town? Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DameTraveler @travelskills Nice shot! And beautiful coast #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this Photography Guide to Big Sur Coastal Drive https://t.co/oyzFDOmC99 by @PhotoTraces #TravelSkills https://t.co/lJGMXAtmyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmdenouden That looks like a great trip! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 Yes, 4 years ago we drove from San Francisco to Los Angeles #travelskills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__windrose I've only been once and I loved it #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q4 Have you driven or would you like to drive the California coast? Where? When? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjmcginnis @nataliediscala @PacificaCoC That looks gorgeous #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who do you want to visit @PacificaCoC with? Tag a friend! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kamgharana @KayleneChadwell Thanks for the fix #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A3 It's winter in Canada right now. I'll take either #TravelSkills https://t.co/tUm196dT9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q3 Are you more NorCal or SoCal? Why? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come join the chat! It's all about California today on #TravelSkills just use the hashtag :) https://t.co/XzhKQi3FbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@visitsantacruz That's a beauty! #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A1 I think awards season would be a fun time to be in California. #travelskills https://t.co/UtoN0b8wNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q2 What's your favorite time of year to be in California? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandLopers Totally! I haven't been often, so I am going to get a lot of inspiration #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@always5star @travelskills Lucky you! We're in snow and heading north for more snow! although I love the adventure  #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@etspencer @tweetNATJA @LandLopers @aaronhuey @HeckticTravels @NatGeoTravel Thank you! We're pretty stoked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TravelSkills ROLL CALL! Where are you joining the chat from today? Share a pic or selfie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandLopers They look fabulous #Travelskills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out: 10 Best California Beaches You've Never Heard Of https://t.co/bHHy9PssN2 by @ourwandersblog #TravelSkills https://t.co/ZcZmfzlMq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q1 What’s your favorite spot on the California coast? Why? #TravelSkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream Trip! Cappadocia Hot Air Balloon: Not All Flights are Created Equal https://t.co/VNAfnkExgR #Travel… https://t.co/SxkQ5pfI0H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Chris! Have a wonderful weekend! https://t.co/rVcJY1lCpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChurchillWild We love Canada too! Especially walking with Polar Bears and Paddling with Belugas with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTGlobe @dashboardlife @2travellingtots Thanks so much you two! Love Kristen and Siya too and right back at ya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still time to enter! Win a Deluxe River #Cruise - Celebrating New Special Interest and Bicycle Trips… https://t.co/drm96orQTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo! @WiartonWillie predicted an early Spring. Know where he lives? Check out our post on the area of Wiarton… https://t.co/V78Ob6gMNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got something to add? Discover #Canada: 36 Amazing Adventures from Coast to Coast https://t.co/NILpq62lGl… https://t.co/MWreFNX6sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inflowtravel @byrnephoto_uk @Audiotravels @LocalAdventurer Looking forward to seeing you all in April!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DangerousBiz Thanks for the retweet Amanda. Great seeing you in NYC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@headed_anywhere @tweetNATJA Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheeseWeb_eu @SeeNewBrunswick @KouchibouguacNP Thank you for contributing. We were so inspired by our fellow Canucks! #Canada150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travelcanucks Thanks for sharing your amazing surfing experience! I can't wait to go to Tofino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bizarreglobehop Thanks Pritta! We're looking forward to coming back to Helsinki and getting than two days. I missed so much esp. being ill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seeusoontravel Thanks for sharing your Canada experiences! We love our country. #canada150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevenGodfrey1 Thank you! It was difficult to choose, there are so many adventures to be had in Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParksCanNunavut Huge thanks to @hikebiketravel for sharing her experience. We can't wait to visit one day ourselves! #ExploreCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36 Amazing Adventures from Coast to Coast https://t.co/NILpq6jX4V Thanks to Gr8 contributors tagged in the photo!… https://t.co/FTTAekz2hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Gold Medal winner from #NATJA Polar Bear Photos: Be transported to the Wild Edge of Manitoba… https://t.co/vSM3HT0Hgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMcCool Thanks! It's the first time I entered in the writing awards, so I'm pretty stoked. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to have won bronze at #NATJA for my article Rio Favelas - Out with the Gangs, in with the Tourists… https://t.co/fn8l8Z2u0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tdacycling Weird story, we ran into Randy on the bus at Park n Fly the other day at Pearson. Small world! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tdacycling Thanks guys! Hope all is well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyberZizo Glad to hear! Hope you are having an amazing day at training!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lavidashannon @Claudioula It's a great post isn't it? Thanks Claudioula for sharing your experiences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shootip You're welcome. Glad you enjoyed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lax2nrt Thanks Jen! It's a good time to come to Canada with our weak dollar and 150th Anniversary! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to have won some awards at #NATJA including Gold for Best #Travel Blog &amp; Overall Excellence in… https://t.co/HdstTI6Wmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ice Climbing The Canadian Rockies, A World Class #Adventure https://t.co/TbS9UaaZux #ExploreCanada #travel https://t.co/FbkMqeSS23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world needs more travel: “Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness" ~ Mark Twain #quote… https://t.co/2GZbEQdTh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must be the change you wish to see in the world" ~ Gandhi. - Something to think about. https://t.co/1v5uaGaXny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cappadocia Hot Air Balloon - Not All Flights are Created Equal https://t.co/VNAfnkExgR #travelo #ttot https://t.co/ikHOaMlhpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Deluxe River Cruise with @VantageTravel - Celebrating New Special Interest &amp; Bicycle Trips… https://t.co/vKYCnzIxpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*New Video* Best GoPro Accessories for the Adventure Traveller https://t.co/XLtfLBvKD9 #Travel #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great stay with @ihgrewardsclub at @StayTimesSquare in #NYC #pricelessexperiences https://t.co/HrpWUb4YWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cappadocia Hot Air Balloon - Not All Flights are Created Equal https://t.co/VNAfnkExgR #Travel #LoveFromTurkey https://t.co/kvLz9D90U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met the amazing @SpudHilton last night! What a great guy! https://t.co/Q6z10u750u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a Deluxe River Cruise - Celebrating New Special Interest and Bicycle Trips https://t.co/kAetO8t76e #travel… https://t.co/ihMW9OQQql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TravelingAnna @joeybear85 @wynnewin @Its_Katka @TripWhisperer It was so awesome to see you! Glad we had a chance to catch up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antarctica virtual reality with @QuarkExpedition at #nytts https://t.co/zozv3OayMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PassepartoutHom @cntraveller good to stick with that :) . #travelskills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandLopers @PassepartoutHom @cntraveller they have those too! #travelskills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tryingbrevity I couldn't imagine it on New Years Eve. That would be nuts #travelskills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A10 We'll be in Scotland driving the North Coast 500 #TravelSkills https://t.co/kwfgh8CZ0f]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>