<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessfraz would you like to save this file? Would you like to overwrite the existing file? Yes shut up dammit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirRice switching to MMP 20 years ago looks like good planning rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui how will I get to equifoss when my phone breaks next time??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreid how about a Jason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman do you mean rheumatic fever or earthquakes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcmansionhell how did the US get the zoning laws it got? Is it just "don't let the poors build next door"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna you mean GPU design isn't finished yet???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna presumably the last A0 hardware got melted 18 months ago?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver many programming books are easy to bin, maths doesn't get obsolete in quite the same way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fanf Dalwhinnie is pretty different to Laphroaig...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timClicks I would guess the opposite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cstross oh good timing, I've got about 10% of the revolution trade to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessfraz it's related to gpg of course it's impossible to use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkakar I did this a year or so ago I think. Are you still using Emacs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dabeaz more code is not the answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessfraz there are people on Caltrain who aren't doing that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecheney nah, basin reserve in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screw this, let's go to the cricket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserWhyte81 I didn't realise I ate that much gü that month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreerBerry dirk gently (although it's a bit tough on the baby brain)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn has it tried to maim you yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjg59 oh, not netlink then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rakyll actually i guess any fixed-instruction-width architecture, has anyone compiled k8s for MIPS yet? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarb wow. Is anyone else still there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rakyll ppc64 too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarb can't see there being much play today somehow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman better idea, be born with cloth ears and avoid caring about audio quality at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hawkieowl @brettsky that's no header]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirRice I like my 5x, the 6p seems comically huge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui oh god I got in trouble for taking the sheets off the bed without "help" the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman @ned0r it wouldn't be very Douglas Adams if two versions of the same story were in any way the same would it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cstross or excession ('a more efficient way of torturing humans has never been invented')]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normnz misparsed that as 'dominated the world of sailing for 470 years', was confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver that Kolmogorov sure got lots of interesting things named after him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn @RhyvenNZ the prediction did not turn out to be accurate. but it was pretty plausible at time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pinboard ideally also avoid the initials JA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope te horo blackberry is ace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn it's great for getting your phone out of a pocket, less great when your phone is on the desk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monsterlemon @Pinboard lesswrong and related things I think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope would it be better or worse if *he* did bring down the nats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessfraz oh man I haven't wanted to punch libtool in the face since 1999 or so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman thought you were talking about the operating system for the first 10 or so words of that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver at first I thought you meant the c compiler was being built in the inner loop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ @DylanReeve wait till the kids graduate to midsomer murders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFromHereNZ they're pretty bad for natives https://t.co/zWJQxDzsuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearyanthony what the heck happened today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA flight comes in paper bags, probably waxed tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ at least two!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui the basic antidote to impostor syndrome is realising noone has the faintest idea what they are doing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDCali @bradfitz pretty sure that's 255^15 if you're really determined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sil they seem to be called bon-bons here, a completely silly name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui where else but upper hurt could that be happening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui you repeat yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA optimus prime or the changing voltage kind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna the story about bats was my favourite bit I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver @arcatan well pedantically there are two :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver @arcatan tbf I can see the appeal of trying to do serious probability without getting bogged down in measure theory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radix wasn't there an enormous flame war on distutils-sig about that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman now there are people dying in Berlin :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress was Mary Wilson in the building at the time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope has your little man started childcare yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen can they just save some effort and declare that it will be in place for 5000 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcmansionhell that entrance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisjrn @tveastman yes, good point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman omg, vin diesel! Had no idea at all who he was when I watched that on the cinema :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnat something something per capita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ promising ms 4 she could watch food TV this morning seems pretty tame in comparison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glyph @mumak can it be made retrospective?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glyph surely you of all people should know better by now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work on my team! https://t.co/uKs6qnZFCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fijall I have just had a baby so don't think I get any say in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's game: testing old versions of the code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kb gets a bit vague at some point, do the descendants of Saxons count as colonisers in the UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreid maybe whole threads are infuriatingly hard to read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ hm no, this doesn't look like any situation I've been, no, not at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@compybara @aurynn IBM will be able to sell you something, I'm fairly sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dabeaz so you want to terrify people when reading code over the phone too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver fair point. Have we tried governance by dice roll yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRMacIver as much as I disagree with the current UK government, petitions would make a pretty stupid way of deciding policy I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearyanthony coal is gud?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcquillanatorz pike place market is great, gum wall is icky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tveastman reddit is lots of different things really, r/Wellington is mostly fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedjgould @mpt PM mpt has a nice ring to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcmansionhell what is going on with the tiny door in the confinement room??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rakyll heh I tried that and failed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf status gained by flying economy is abooby prize really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA bivouac has some pretty big outdoor research hats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui still doing the hospital commute but things going ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui sad I won't be getting a new fb profile photo today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidcrawshaw better hope you understood the spec ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna hmm, i guess you gotta check for the presence of tentacled brain-eating horrors as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna I thought of a new piece of life advice: pick a speciality muggles are not interested in at all (linkers seem OK for this :-p)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidascher pretty sure it means stealing fruit with the goal of making cider, not just in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui yes and no. everyone getting very impatient now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwhudson probably this one though https://t.co/IMoLeWDfPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought I felt a small quake, look at geonet, um, I guess it might have been one of these six in the last 10 minutes #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitsuhiko we had one of those last week, fairly small though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pinboard @TechCrunch wait, this seems familiar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitsuhiko I just can't get over feeling like a twit when I talk to my phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliafshar much as I like Orwell's writing, brave new world is a more accurate dystopia really]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>