<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebodyshopuk Try the wonderful Skin Care Diagnostic Tool at The Body Shop https://t.co/Vb0lVSdLpW
#WinningwithLYBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebodyshopuk Try the wonderful Skin Care Diagnostic Tool at The Body Shop https://t.co/Vb0lVSdLpW
#WinningWithLYBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Sorry, didn't get this message. But yeah, that's how it works. Don't get my presents early so Dan will have to wrap em up lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Danke, danke! I am so happy :) Pity it's not my birthday yet now though lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Lookit! Mama has agreed to buy thee babies for me! Excited doesn't even cover it!!!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/cEfzwjGOKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Maybe but they look more like cats than red pandas do imho. I need to go to bed now though so I must… https://t.co/Z8xoemtLjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Irrelephant! They're not cat like. I might as well say baby giraffes are cute. I'm right but it's not the point :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura That they do; no arguments. But you won't sway me. Ocelots are a favourite of mine. So let's both jus… https://t.co/KvWMR3l8s3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AmeAmeSakura Or how about this serval kitten? https://t.co/I9RBzwxN4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YmF9y7Wjqf
@AmeAmeSakura Will this adorable ocelot kitten raise the stakes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Okay. Wait a sec while I bring on the cuteness. I just love that derpy serval :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/inY3SQUwpA
@AmeAmeSakura Because servals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura @EmrgencyKittens Zohmygoodness! But I am more of a serval girl. Or ocelots :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki @AmeAmeSakura Sadly I have marginally too much self control to buy a fresh tub of sweets every time I bake… https://t.co/sGZEHCD8an]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki @AmeAmeSakura Haha, indeed it is, sir! Though I dare say I could bake with Quality Street if I had any. I'm… https://t.co/71d2Q77bQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Don't be crazy please. They are as bad as Cons. Get real running trainers with some bounce in the sol… https://t.co/RWZg1oHSHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki @AmeAmeSakura Reckon they look pretty appetising. They smell ace, at least :) I'm reliably informed they ta… https://t.co/o3u6SSN0Km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura I haven't made them before so I couldn't say, but they do have tiny pieces of chopped Mars in them to… https://t.co/jHumY0NOfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Especially now I have iced them and topped each with a small slice of Mars Bar :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura And in the spirit of being healthy, I will not feed you all 18 cupcakes I made today! Promise! :p Havent even iced the buggers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura God woman, shut your tongue! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing my girl @AmeAmeSakura today so I had to up my #makeup game since her #eyeliner is always #awesome.… https://t.co/cydnpjRsyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I took a plane through your bees! #shittestsonglyric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it's #fullmoon and #friday13th and you're sitting wondering how long it'll take for your crazy to show. So, in advance, #ItWasntMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thelegomovie #lifelessons: It's all about #perspective
"I step in mud, I got new brown shoes. It's awesome to win and it's awesome to lose"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki "Bough" I grant you. Not sure beau counts though as we stole it from the French. I just hope the same person didn't pick all 3 words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's currently bugging my happiness that bow (ribbon) and bow (bending at the waist) are pronounced differently. Who felt the need?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki Dude, it's meant to go in your face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friendly face and some good chat is sometimes exactly what you need. Hot chocolate and pizza help. Finishing the night with wine. #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier You finally did it - You cracked Google! https://t.co/sNA159o1eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura We had homemade trifle but cherry cheesecake sounds nom! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura I had the difficult job of eating the rest of the haribo 😂 Pity me! Some is actually still in the cupboard :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Hmm, maybe not :p Nah, I'm sure you can follow instructions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura No, no. I trust you. Wrapping it in different paper was enough :p xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Now you have to make me lunch 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura @ARX7Laevatein ... ... ... Ahuh. So you do. If it takes you more than 20 secs to eat I'll be disappointed lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Only 8 more days til you get to open the other two I gave you! Xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Thank you so much sweetie! I love my presents! And your wrapping was beautiful, as always! Xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura The way I've seen you snaffle it, plus you told me, plus I was conferring with @ARX7Laevatein lol. Gotta get it right for xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Why are you telling me lol? I bloody know! I bought a ton of haribo and sat picking the eggs out just for you 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Give me 8 weeks first lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Just in case you somehow missed that they were snack pots! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura This is literally how I approach all food 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura My mum wants to steal the cat ones. She says they're gorgeous! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura This was one of the first things I bought - brought this back from England for you! :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura That's fine. My tags are bossing me and I'm bossing you with numbers lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Not to worry - I found said instructions and am actually capable of following them lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Great minds apparently do think alike. Do you think we both like Pusheen? https://t.co/9jz1HxIKFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura And I'm being bossed around by gift tags 😂 https://t.co/gGSckBAxJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Dedication to the cause when even bags and gifts are candy cane themed! https://t.co/X3vqy9uYzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura 1 first of course you choob :p But in a festive way, of course lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Where to even begin? https://t.co/NsS5rllRcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#edxmassol When you accidentally invite your Dad to a Bhangra Christmas rave! @RianneMiller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura @ddalmang0430_ I love the angry looking one! ^^ So kawaii!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're wrapping a birthday present and you have to remind yourself it's for your bestie to convince yourself not to just keep it 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Oooh! Pretty and delicious! :D Like moi! Hahahaha! 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura I has red hair now https://t.co/8aMjOLDhzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skipping to the next song when you only have 25 seconds left of this song because you break all the rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also I love how #WerewolfWednesday was already a thing. I bow to your superior #hashtagskills , Twittersphere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a scale from 1-10, how worried should I be that the guy in front of me on the bus smells like wet dog yet has NO DOG? #WerewolfWednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Home Alone, crying like a little bitch, but I just put on my eyeliner like "Would you just please not?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl spending Fri cuddled up with kids/partner or out drinking&amp;I consider today a win because I made two kinds of soup &amp; didn't kill myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you look so pissed off in town that shoppers part around you like the Red Sea, just to avoid coming too close and risking losing a limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That bizarre moment when you dream you're in a club and the beat's about to drop but you get woken up by your weird jazz-funk alarm instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer, nachos and Deadpool? You're playing my jam!
#nightin #Deadpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're talking to the glow in the dark plastic bats in your cupboard you probably had too much to drink. 
# bringbackhalloween #drunk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've been tired when twice in the same night you dream about yourself sleeping! 😅 #dreamsleep #dreaming #sleepception]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeartScotland If Monster Mash doesnt get played on the radio today I am gonna be so disappointed! #halloweenonheart #monstermash #halloween]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imjennim Gotta love your style Jenn so I borrowed it for Halloween! https://t.co/BcWrihn4GV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BethesdaStudios Halloween cookies done in style. And I'll shout at you if you try to take them! https://t.co/lsUTt8BDMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic cookies and extinct dinosaur cookies. What is life? 
Robin on my bat cookie.
#ironic #biscuit #Robin #Batman https://t.co/lSY7FkBQbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it's love when your boyfriend will spend an hour icing biscuits with you. #Batman #Joker #cookies… https://t.co/jQlF9qgJzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you look forward to today so much but then you dream about Hong Kong and wake up feeling gutted that you aren't there. Party over here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura To be honest, nobody wants me to have another bottle right now anyway but I'd murder a pizza!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki I had winter berry flavour but I looked at the label. It was raspberry, blackcurrant and apple. Aren't they summer fruits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki Hope you appreciate the effort of googling and copy-pasting the π symbol :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 bottles of cider brings the fact that your mum is in your phone contacts under "Dude Bro" to whole new levels of hilarious!
#funny #drunk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura @TokyoFashion @jk_rowling @HarryPotterFilm Ron, Ron, Ron Weasley! Never wanted to cuddle him more - and that's impressive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing outside the tesco recycling area waiting for my sister to pick me up and I admit that's a bit weird but is there any need to glare?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Thanks chick! Been looking forward to it for days :D Going to Chopstix after I realised how awesome it was with you :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Besides I needed chopping boards for ages so just gave up and bought plastic ones so prob won't buy him even tho I want to now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura While that would normally be the case I am off to Livy with the sister to see Bridget Jones' Baby and go shopping :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura Oh my glob! That's the cutest bloody thing! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboy Bebop still has the best theme tune of anything, ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please feel free to add me in #Pewdiepie #TuberSimulator as Snowflakefaerie
#allthesubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish anything in my life was as perfect as Morticia Addams' lipstick! 
#addamsfamily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @HeartScotland playing the soundtrack to my childhood on the #timetunnel this morning. Epic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you buy a winter coat and the next day it's obligingly 9 degrees &amp; you actually get to wear it! #WinterIsComing https://t.co/8aut2tu0wa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That #awkward moment when you want to ask what someone's lovely perfume is but can't because you have to preface it with "you smell nice".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched three children #Gangnamstyle their way over a zebra crossing. Very very pointedly, staring at the drivers. #WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki I expect the Americans can just about cope, thanks to the good ol' hotdog. Besides, "toad in the hole" is a far worse offender!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling My stepdad took a photo and I wrote a poem for it, inspired by Harry Potter. Please read it, if you can.
https://t.co/YnX6FHnOWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura You'll need to check another tesco then pumpkin. I was gonna but you one as there were only 2 left but 1 was marked. Gomen :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maisie_Williams Was so jealous of the Kate Spade chocolate milk bag you had that I made my own! Only £4 though! :p https://t.co/HCUEs1BGuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DIY adorable bag made from a pencil case I bought in #Tesco! Just add ribbon!
#DIY #fashion #bag #kawaii #ribbon https://t.co/gT0RXnJPri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found the cutest pencil case yesterday in @Tesco and with use of a knife and ribbon turned it into cutest bag ever! https://t.co/c7mdEvY04J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zin5ki It is the very specific type of ladybird, the mother-in-law-bird. She comes to your house and judges you. Do you feel the judgement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeAmeSakura True story! And ate honey chicken with hardly any honey and a fruit salad composed only of strawberries. I fail at hostess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #BigBoss look - when you're so tired you can only keep one eye open. Eyepatch, robot arm and head shrapnel accessories sold separately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone sits beside you on the bus so you can't change songs on your ipod without them thinking you're trying to grab their ass :/]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>