<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS FLASH: popcorn-flavored Tic-Tacs taste as crap as you imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1970s is here to show us the way: https://t.co/5tF5G9VKtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut down the internet. We're done for the day. https://t.co/9z2J3P33Uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FB needs to hurry up and add a laugh/cry button 😬😭😓🤢🙄😱]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since eating my feelings has not fixed the world's problems, I guess I'll try to sleep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY CRAP: DeVos questionnaire appears to include passages from uncited sources https://t.co/FNRoOlfw9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well played, Senator Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the pressure on: https://t.co/4hfOsmdk0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datageneral thx Mr Taussig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's interesting how many people contact me about applying for a PhD and don't spell my name right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@visualosmosis &lt;3 thank you so much for coming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crusty old Berliners are great when they're in a good mood. Also when they're in a bad mood, if you're not the target of their ire…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerpintor if it is, I started it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, now I know what happens when you forget to pick up your luggage from Baggage Claim. Gonna be here a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit. Was just re-reading Ngai's _Ugly Feelings_ on the plane; had one of those conceptual breakthroughs I used 2 have in grad school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi now that is a good interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerpintor You'll be tickled to hear that I did end up sprinting across the airport in my woolen coat and a cashmere sweater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Black Madonna, interviewed in The Quietus: https://t.co/UYtUK0FZfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilynussbaum @Will_Lynch …culminating in approx 30 minutes of panicked productivity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a flight to catch so I ain't mad that this Uber driver is going so fast, but I'm a bit scared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerpintor 100m Formalwear Sprint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, now would be the perfect time for all trains to Birmingham Intl Airport to stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successfully taught a seminar on no sleep. I guess all those years of raving finally paid off. @blackmadonnachi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi love u bae. Praying to TBM and hoping for her/your power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp, it's been a while since I've pulled an all-nighter, but at least the marking is done. Off to prep my 9am class!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally found a diss track that I had been trying to ID for ages… https://t.co/Q0InEHmmfS (NSFW AF, MF)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My "Up Late Marking Overdue Essays" soundtrack: https://t.co/SvPQeKgVmU @djshiva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DON'T FORGET: Two years till midterm elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you dress up nice for work and then sprint two blocks in a woolen coat to catch the bus and now you're sweaty and gross but still formal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kate_galloway yeah, the challenge for me is that the deadlines that I 'can't miss' are always admin/teaching, not research.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The usage of 'progress' as a transitive verb is kinda terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That special paralysis when you have so many upcoming deadlines that you won't meet anything and you don't know where to start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JFC Harborne High Street at rush hour is the absolute worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datageneral @womensmarch note the rally cutting mic's to keep people on sched: applied 2 trans POC speakers but not Michael Moore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fabianholt yay! Glad this is out in print. I have to change some of the readings for my Music Festivals course as a result...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi &lt;3 u, you boss-ass bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi this is the best. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHUT UP EVERYBODY, ANGELA DAVIS IS TALKING. #WomensMarchOnWashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Janelle Monae is a gift none of us deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["FEM THE FUTURE!" - Janelle Monae #WomensMarchOnWashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Aquí estamos y no nos vamos!" / "We're here and we're not going away!" #WomensMarchOnWashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Si no nos dejan soñar, no los dejamos dormir!" / "if they don't let us dream, we won't let them sleep!" #WomensMarchOnWashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the live feed of women's march on Washington and feeling lifted. Sophie Cruz is the absolute best. Solidaridad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On our way to the Women's March in Berlin. Anybody else going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCanonic @soundstudies there's a surprise....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to suppress your appetite and lose weight? Think about how often the seats in buses and trains are cleaned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteley_rose plz make this happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ugh, I can tell within 1-3 sips if a coffee is going to give me a headache. #overExtractedAbomination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We offer 'distance learning' degrees, but whenever I see the abbreviation 'DL' I think 'downlow', e.g., 'Down-Low PhD in Music'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My classmates and I were repeatedly told not to submit an unedited PhD diss. to publishers, but it's amazing how many I see published.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Yay, snow!', says the person working from home today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protip: it is possible to eat too much Sichuan chili oil. #unforeseenConsequences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! Just replenished my stock of 'angry lady' chili oil. It's flavor-time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The British 'Cheers, thanks' system of passive-aggressive work-delegation is a thing of wonder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm always a bit disappointed that Poundland is a cheap shop and not a swinger's club / gay sauna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagicRealismBot not so much magical as entirely envisageable, this one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking up watching this BBC reporter standing on Chicago's Navy Pier trying to maintain composure in winter wind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am astounded by my own relentless optimism that my workload will abate sometime in the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to the office and fighting the urge to run home and crawl back into bed. #notTheRealnessIordered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi @united that is appalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inthegapbetween only if it's wee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relevant to many folks I know : White Nationalism and the Ethics of Medieval Studies 
 https://t.co/0yOJghz3lE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovering simpsonswave videos now. Afterparty fodder for days: https://t.co/QUREwE4JXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yukoasanuma can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quoted from MetaFilter: 'Can we wrap Billie Lourd and Gary Fisher in bubble wrap, just to be safe?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home! But not before one final indignity: followed around the .@marksandspencer at B'ham New Street like a thief, buying milk &amp; sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, at least my luggage showed up when I landed in Manchester. Now, to find a train to Brum and steal a few hours of sleep b4 Berlin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmgentry Solidarity. I just tried to do Toronto - Frankfurt - Birmingham and ended up in Manchester and nearly 10 hours late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what this airport restaurant needs? An overexcited 5-year-old throwing tantrums and stealing the toys of other children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's appalling how little of the seating in the int'l terminal is non-paying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fuckery is strong at YYZ / Pearson tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The .@AirCanada brand is deteriorating. What good are ML lounge passes that are invalid nearly everywhere? What 'loyalty reward' is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first rule of Ryanair is never fly Ryanair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to return to my sister's apartment and drown in cat hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sister, holding a stray post-it note: This is garbage, right?
Me: EVERYTHING IS GARBAGE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this day and age, any hotel that does not offer free WiFi does not merit the mention 'luxury' or 'all-inclusive'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tropical resorts are full of young couples who seem to think that nobody can tell they're getting each other off in the pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I know any ethnomusicologists of tourism in Mexico, especially specialising in Quintana Roo &amp; the Mayan Peninsula?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datageneral a few moments earlier, I saw some cloaca-on-cloaca action between some macaws. And the butterfly sanctuary was lit af.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are ducks in *%#$ing trees here. https://t.co/XomElI4vBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast of champions https://t.co/a5HRIor36F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctaj no, alas, but I am very interested in hearing what you find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirCanada it's quite simple: 'Guest Pass' vouchers aren't valid for int'l ML lounges, but I'm an expat and int'l flights are all I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirCanada , you continue to make it harder for Aeroplan members to actually use the Maple Leaf lounges. The AC brand is eroding...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In UK HE, the long tail of Taylorism is wound tightly around our ankles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djshiva @blackmadonnachi Twang Factor: 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's earworms, on repeat: Chopin Ballade in G; D. Parton's "Jolene"; Krakatau's "Egrang Funk". (Blame @blackmadonnachi for 1 of these.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi Yes, yes, yes. It ain't like you didn't work hard for it. XOXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleepless in Marylebone station: this hot chocolate better fix everything that is wrong with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW TF isn't enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Landed in Brum (late) and on my way home to spend the night preparing for tomorrow's lectures. Wheeeee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh lord help me, I'm about to share this flight back to Birmingham with a Brummie school group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blackmadonnachi Pal Joey's "Party Time" is still one of those tracks I'd happily listen to on repeat forever: https://t.co/g7Q7u2vf6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@konratz no worries, Konratzchen! I understand completely. There'll be other opportunities. LG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone needs to write a melodrama / opera re: that moment when you're looking forward to the first sip of coffee but it's TERRIBLE. #agony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My apologies to the student whose midterm essay now smells of Malaysian 'belacan kangkung'. It was delicious. #noRegrets #noBreak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a Ted Chiang fan, Arrival was very satisfying. I just hope there's a director's cut with more language nerdery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerpintor there are some instructional videos out on the interwebs. Just turn off SafeSearch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG Cards Against Colonialism. Just in time for Yearly Gift Season: https://t.co/vYbwlUgjKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMGM HigherEd exploits this: I can't let my students or colleagues down; if I neglect my research, I only harm myself. (2/2)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>