<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait till #Trump resurects The US Whaling Fleet #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am off down a Panda vortex https://t.co/IY7qusWM1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really every adviser to a Government, around the world are buying the back catalogue of The Apprentice at the moment #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccohanlon I like the flee idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so where will the homeless be banned from next #Melbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican government says Trump never threatened to send troops to Mexico https://t.co/3s82N6u2bV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US solar power employs more people than oil, coal and gas combined https://t.co/BqZiO5wPrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Malcolm Turnbull could ignore the facts and fund the myth of 'clean' coal https://t.co/H68N8fvptV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand for oil and coal set to peak in 2020 amid renewable energy revolution, report says https://t.co/0UPOHVYn1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When does the #EPA start trending, Soon me thinks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcom put his money into Corey Barnadi #abc730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rare Space Age #BBC Technics vinyl console appears on #eBay https://t.co/pM7TwYagU7 via @FACTmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There seem to be a fair few politicians and their acolytes about Who's faces appear to be about to fall off at the mo #auspol #brexit #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TimTams, an #Australian Favorite, Arrive in America https://t.co/ok79qQDuyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To show that world isn't all nuts at the mo @davidtaniscoocks  Baked Roman Broccoli &amp;Mozzarella &amp; Olives https://t.co/osthI0FUkr #NYTCooking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetUp I know, I am ahead of the curve on that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetUp Then they will go after the pensioners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Paraphrase, You are only as good as your worst policy #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice look #Melbourne Arrests made as police move in on rough sleepers' Flinders Street camp  https://t.co/8y1ehVQmgS via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetUp @BCAcomau She is probably right, mainly because once a pub has this https://t.co/vFfQCP5Mk9... no need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Righto, what beautiful gateway to world is #twitter going to show me today....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government is too cowardly to stand up to fascism https://t.co/Ky3Lkl9O1H via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnewsPerth Fucking Hell thats the most uncaring thing I have read today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost wife bothering jazz https://t.co/R339laIe3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is a pension crisis looming maybe we need more people working full time to pay Tax  #auspol... maybe even more people period]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only just found out #LeonardFrench died. He did the NGV roof and some awesome enamel paintings https://t.co/4CobIhlMDo via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FA Cup fifth round draw: non-league Sutton to face Arsenal https://t.co/mabzzd2zLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so #LNP that's 34000 Cars that get overseas this year from #Toyota......Zero next year on your watch #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to #Australia. #auspol Frantic phoning among CEOs: How to address Donald Trump immigration ban? https://t.co/hExcrem4eK via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know it Little Malcolm and His Struggle Against the Eunuchs #johnhurt https://t.co/BHK5GOMiPk..... Party of Dynamic Erection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I recon I am about 40% efficient at the mo. Thanks to #Brexit #Trump &amp; way down Little Malcolm and His Struggle Against the Eunuchs..#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be fierce, furious, and fight! Join the Raccoons of the Resistance! | First Dog on the Moon https://t.co/zj8fBoGr1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are expensive shoes worth it? Here's why I changed my mind https://t.co/pS14wqXqAM via @ExecutiveStyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesssss...Donald Trump's folly is a once-in-a-century opportunity for Australia https://t.co/GbX36qLwg3 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey the year I was a FF team owner. My man No 4  #CastleCombe Formula Ford 1600 Race October 1990 https://t.co/ajKbkXRjHp via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to LOVE watching these #TVR Tuscan Race #CastleCombe May 1990 https://t.co/BHOcMfCaQK via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @3wombats @billshortenmp there is some passion there....spot on...More please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am now the embodiment of lefty hippyness. Just ordered a  
#Yuba Cargo Bike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like #Can, This will be your bliss. Thx @AndyVotel &amp; @StuartMaconie Freakier Zone, A Can-Packed Playlist https://t.co/VsyExK9QMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump smashes record to get fastest majority disapproval rating ever https://t.co/MQScuokXnY via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I am not a Trumpist, I seem to have lost Followers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qatar airlines have a fair few #Boeing 787 on order.... just saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is legalised cheating an alternative fact, become a bit confused with my mother tongue at the mo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind America, access to abortion is a 'nightmare' for many Australians | Van Badham https://t.co/58aIGn0FAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Good-bye to the Last Pillar of the Free, Open Internet #auspol https://t.co/khwcJIRmQH via @selectall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody Added Paul Ryan to the Invertebrate #Wikipedia Page #auspol https://t.co/wpyswtL7y6 via @selectall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When does the Reichstag fire happen. Next week #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJohnsonson @3wombats he always looks ill to me. anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some idea of what its like to live with zero money. Got no idea what its like to live with no hope. Cant be good. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the age of bleneded families and #globalnomads. Lets turn the clock back.  #brexit #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy boy this afternoon https://t.co/GMG0nXZbke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henryhopefrost Is Start Money still a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waitimg for #nickcave https://t.co/mPBeQUijh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my God, #nickcave. TONIGHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suppose its about time I read about Crystal Meth use by #Nazi. Might come in handy https://t.co/xdY0vSZgO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the odds on @Trump lasting the year @BetfairUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day my lawyer advised me to get a gun was the day reality came to an end

https://t.co/UH0CVu6niF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because #inxs https://t.co/gfjDsSpMuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alway good to start with Jazz from the night before https://t.co/gcCIqzJiHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there is a Mustang in rear view https://t.co/dGk5A8o5Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LugubriousLarry turned it off. Spending the night on my phone,like every other night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobs for all? In the US that idea is about to be tested to destruction

https://t.co/sYxESGWtGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#abc730 Nice group of people. But somebody under 40 might have been good. I do love Prof Blanney though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Year of the cock did start in 2016. Didnt it?  #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinguisticIdol @JohnWren1950 go on then. Nameless one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mein Kampf, Vol. 1 Chapter 8.  It was all about Gods Mission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing #octonauts https://t.co/xCjqwjEktN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Falafel https://t.co/2AYvDAcrJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Company that employs 15,000 in Britain has a warning about #Brexit https://t.co/bCmVos0iwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Ecclestone’s 40-year reign as F1 chief reaches end of road after takeover https://t.co/72s6JZlmqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccohanlon now wait and watch all the @linkedin emails arrive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Media Became One of Putin’s Most Powerful Weapons https://t.co/IJ6YiusxkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like we are all on the bus #trumpton #trump https://t.co/PGfZaMGtWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sold two paintings today...wooohooo #art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trumps team didnt want Pauline or Malcom to fill two seats Says something.Not sure what #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Gandhi's 10 Rules for Changing the World, by Henrik Edberg https://t.co/EgWEAZXyBd #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do follow some lovely people
 But this space is begining to be vile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May must know the EU plans to punish Britain. It has no choice #brexit https://t.co/6RPcEitRPJ via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats Fucking good then .  https://t.co/a1ICUhgpyM via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January the time for an idle artist to be arty. Got some pickies going up next month #art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanHartley_ and dont have a proper name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Readers recommend playlist: the best of your 1980s 12-inch singles

https://t.co/ALXgpVYTmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKR1MKR2 Too many consultants... with you all the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant get a #Census right, Cant fund an #NBN, Cant get #centrelink debts right.  #LNP need an experienced IT Director instead of the teaboy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a #manuelocampo is out. Fab fab and double fab with fab on top #art https://t.co/Kq7A6PIZiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best #hockney in the #ngv at the mo https://t.co/J8m3DP50NH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the #hockmey exhibition at the #ngv https://t.co/LIS6RMclUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deemadigan Couldn't even get a gig as a paid seat sitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it seems a future of 5/8ths inches, furlongs and chains now awaits the UK, Glad they taught me mm,cm etc when I grew up there #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have never cried(tears) for your country. Maybe you should #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Law Repeal Could Cost 18 Million Their Insurance, Study Finds https://t.co/xs5PUHSQJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard_littler You want some Arum lilies or Funeral Lilies as they can be called]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I still lived in the UK would feel rather resentful today having worked wirh #EU companies all my life #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BofA_News All of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldnt be happy if I was #mini thanks to the new 1970s #ultratune ad
 Minis dont catch fire do they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blinds are down https://t.co/rnLZZ5t1zY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ I have a shit load in my garden.What a pickle: UK gripped by courgette shortage

https://t.co/IrGjzaD4nP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I look at this thing, all I get now is quotes from 1940s man. #auspol...#Twitter had its day
.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Cernan, the last person to walk on the moon, dies aged 82, Nasa announces https://t.co/lbKqQMMA7F via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still cant put one of these windscreen sun blinds up in my car.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>