<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Second time in 24 hours that the White House has explicitly framed the Russian invasion as a "conflict along the Uk… https://t.co/br2OtQwUEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacklgoldsmith I just don't have that much confidence in his ability to play the long game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey. Didn't. Read. The. Order. https://t.co/RrR37EbE2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1bobcohn @TheAtlantic @TheAtlanticFoto Um...wasn't this done originally by @britishmuseum?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @jaketapper If something happens to the judge, whom do we blame? 

You?

You. https://t.co/g3qm9Lxlqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; that's only beginning. If you truly believe he's crossed a line, you better get to work making the case. Demonstrations alone won't cut it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will be up to media and public to convince @BobGoodlatte6 and other members of the House Judiciary Ctte that POTUS's actions merit it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...that President Trump has done enough to merit investigation. @BobGoodlatte6 isn't going to find that on his own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all fairness, @BobGoodlatte6 isn't going to just suddenly decide it's time to hold such a hearing. He's going to need compelling proof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media should start asking @BobGoodlatte6 what his view is on questions such as the President's statements on the judiciary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...at least that we know of.  But those of you who seriously think he has need to convince @BobGoodlatte6 that he should start the process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobGoodlatte6 is going to be hesitant to hold hearings 16 days into presidency, especially when POTUS hasn't yet done anything impeachable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobGoodlatte6 and the Judiciary Ctte currently focused on what they see as a pro-growth, anti-regulation agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impeachment: neither easy nor fast (nor should it be). To start @BobGoodlatte6, chair of House Judiciary Ctte, woul… https://t.co/b3pjqyvxiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban Even if he does, Senate would still have to convict him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @seywarddarby &amp; her team! Proud to to have supported @IRISCT.  It's not too late for you to do as well!… https://t.co/N4MTZD74T3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Has anyone ever briefed you on existing vetting? DHS, State already conducted "extreme" vetting long before you came along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lot of observers saying Gorsuch needs to reject Trump's statements on judiciary.  Yes. But what about Sessions? He too must reject them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markknoller Does a tweet constitute an executive action?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Had to be escorted" or "asked police to escort him"@ABC? Former means protesters were attacking. Latter means he w… https://t.co/wjuaSJmFJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much. https://t.co/mx66WdgkTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: "If we don't play by *my* rules, you're all going to die."  

Such petulance doesn't work when my seve… https://t.co/z1UIDUkWmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you suggesting someone's is? https://t.co/jqrBn5c7yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan So you're going back to the "plug our ears and hope he goes away" strategy? That worked wonders for you this summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @ThisWeekABC Note the lack of the first person plural in that sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lrozen Reminds me of time I knew my boss was to be fired &amp; he didn't. Had to balance his demands, their expectations, &amp; my integrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Fair point. When his team listens to the 1000s of moderates already in govt, including SecDef, SecState, &amp;SecDHS, I'll agree w/you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More on @GuernicaCentre &amp; @tobycadman's work to bring to justice those responsible for Syria crimes. https://t.co/fduNWw0RSf @Strat4Humanity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Strat4Humanity partner @GuernicaCentre &amp; @almubernabeu for their work to bring Syrian perps to justice! https://t.co/PqpLDD6Yfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of those defending POTUS once condemned Obama for so-called "apology tour." Maybe we should call this Trump's… https://t.co/WseiOV3brU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under the #immigrationban, the soldiers we're training would not be allowed to enter the United States. https://t.co/JDtEmlG02G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crucial report by @OHCHR on situation in Rakhine (Myanmar/Burma). Essential that, amidst our domestic crisis, we no… https://t.co/9O9kbHJM6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchMcConell When history of this time is written, you will be IDed as one of President's most craven apologists.… https://t.co/JjBvLaLR0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, but very idea of a POTUS channeling Chomsky &amp; Assange using talking points from Soviet-era Pravda still inspir… https://t.co/ZnnE02PyhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amjoyshow @MaxBoot We have a Republican President echoing Noam Chomsky and Julian Assange, using talking points from Soviet-era Pravda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSasse The conscience of a conservative. https://t.co/4dVVGaoxSc  #ThisWeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FIRE_THE_FOOL suggest "and Constitution" or "and Bill of Rights" rather than "and Amendments." Most people won't know what that means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol A little over the top, but the point holds. We on the left now cite Reagan the way you on the right ci… https://t.co/Lj9qMyYXeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. It's crucial that we stand together against the greater threat. He will just come after LGBTQI rights later. https://t.co/zf30KZf62b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still suffer cognitive dissonance on this, but we on left now cite Reagan on foreign policy the same way that Rea… https://t.co/813cqT6WHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man should never wear an American lapel flag again. https://t.co/umH1XaX8oF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Godwin's law feels archaic these days. https://t.co/pNSj4LzYPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi what makes it even worse is that it doesn't even make sense. If Huckabee really thinks this, shouldn't it be boys DO cry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note The language. It's "peace along the border," not restoration of stolen territory. #SudetenLand https://t.co/xp3ncsCPbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstrations &amp; judicial action crucial, but there's a third leg of the stool: political accountability. 2018 elec… https://t.co/6PJnXTnvbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good stuff, but framing has been around for years - @GeorgeLakoff and @FrankLuntz are masters at it. https://t.co/c2y8eQdXeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're probably convinced that Khizr Khan and other immigrants stole all the copies. https://t.co/sFRFEysNdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What is our country coming to? A restoration of constitutional principles and the rule of law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to remember that new US president is not the only major transition right now. https://t.co/JuqOBNDqTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcfaul You forgot the part about a president who respected the rule of law, treaties, and international human righ… https://t.co/L7RFbJucOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#immigrationban is a success regardless of court decisions: POTUS has convinced base that terrorists, refugees, &amp; immigrants are same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Lewis_ @speechboy71 @DanAdamini Srsly?? You just called for the extrajudicial shooting (and possibly killing) of civilians? #ruleoflaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madeleine, Why so understated? Not suggesting you go off deep end, but it wouldn't have been out of line to call i… https://t.co/A2rfAqw89k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you perhaps maybe quite possibly could absolutely definitely are a bit too late to this party. https://t.co/R5SO1VQO4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay classy. https://t.co/LfvJYrXlAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It’s great,” [Bannon] said of the book, “for seeing how little mistakes early on can lead to big ones later.” https://t.co/fV1x9y6fi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul There are plenty of heartland Republicans who've benefitted. They all just happen to be part of the 1% that… https://t.co/JBsdFCIuwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might want to speak to those Germans who felt/feel the same way about Alsace-Lorraine. https://t.co/hZvaKQi1QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't stop paying attention because of one news story. https://t.co/HiNXb7LoUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, you may not know this, but typing in all caps is considered yelling.  Just thought you'd like to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth reading -- an implicit critique of Trump, particularly on nuclear policy. https://t.co/uwNvlardor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USUN But DON'T just randomly cut missions. That's penny-wise and pound-foolish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usun To reform PK, train them properly w/GPOI; support deploying adequate troops; fix procurement/chain of command. https://t.co/aaaklRJl8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who think the only thing that happens @UN is the Security Council, a brief primer. I suggest you give it… https://t.co/N6xI707pAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell did Tajikistan do to us? @nytimesworld https://t.co/q5bKToB1iF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin Makes sense. The WH is in denial on a number of fronts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlikely?  He stood up when few others did. https://t.co/qS8M260DOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpaceDC @AP So WH TVs tuned to RT instead of Fox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. It should start with commitment to alliances, support for human rights &amp; atrocity prevention, defense of UN an… https://t.co/pQXl0cxZUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_Schiff No Uncle Fluffy, he. https://t.co/cU32gY6l2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other candidates would've have been far worse. Abrams won't pursue @Heritage_Action or @freedomcaucus's radical ant… https://t.co/ixKqnGNgjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelcrowley I agree. As Dem, NGO activist, &amp; former 44 &amp; 42 appointee, Elliot is someone we can work with. Good record on human rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to add insult to inaccuracy, refused to name him. https://t.co/QRwZbvNl1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Are they unable to go one day without undermining the constitution? We're moving rapidly toward threat-to-the… https://t.co/5uNS8COqsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recalls @brooks_rosa story: WH official to DOD: "What about civilian control of military?" DOD: "Still exists - you… https://t.co/zCSe4UM0an]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read his essays, people.  He's the American Orwell. https://t.co/mgm8eBfQ5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's not bad enough to refuse entry to refugees.  Let's penalize those who help the few that make it through the… https://t.co/y90lfcZaT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. @realDonaldTrump's tweet was not "political." Condemning it would not be taking a position on an issue before… https://t.co/n0YXXgZDml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMAROSA @KFILE @HillaryClinton Whatever you do, don't tell the @realDonaldTrump. He might fire you. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanitarian &amp; political crises in #Cameroon, #Gambia, and #Nigeria seem far away but have huge implications for US… https://t.co/yCvQWRI4JV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinkahl Power/influence of OSD/SOLIC &amp; SOCOM been growing for years; rest of Pentagon defers too much &amp; Congress… https://t.co/wabqTUSEE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Romney was right. https://t.co/GMlDn2ts0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 @politico Oh for God's sake. They should be charging non-profits a discount, like most other conscientious businesses do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then imagine a world where they get fired. We need to stand up for our foreign service officers who, like the milit… https://t.co/JvU7CdN0kZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow – refusing to allow people to leave is both a violation of core human rights principles &amp; a classic authoritari… https://t.co/8EX2yT9Ilj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Gorsuch is a good man. But unless he rejects POTUS's "so-called judge" tweet during his hearing, Senate should not confirm him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every senator should ask Judge Gorsuch about the president's tweet. Every. Single. Senator. Over and over again. https://t.co/KEpZfrPjRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. Especially the part about our president's silence on Quebec City compared to what happened in Paris. https://t.co/FeNgccecw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to insist on tying "the left" to awful actions of anarchists, you've got to own the role of "the ri… https://t.co/TNSYCWaT1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odds are pretty good that Sessions was one of those who voted yes. https://t.co/Tc04qoe1yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good point. Perhaps the ones whose leaders know that, were any countries to be targeted, it should have been theirs. https://t.co/ARXwq0ifIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does @washingtonpost call @joshrogin reporting "opinion"?Stories like today documenting the dustup over the ban, should be on front page]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To paraphrase Graham Parker, compassion is no ordinary word. https://t.co/3foQ0DOmi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in the rest of the world… https://t.co/uK225jImj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a scary is the fact that he has over 43,000 likes. https://t.co/BpfShhzgNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent reporting by @joshrogin. Country now must rely on the integrity of 2 former generals &amp; Exxon Mobil CEO.  https://t.co/4KTAlPHG4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good lord. A petulant child tells the press they are not behaving. https://t.co/hYs1YxXXyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure this is going to come up in Gorsuch's hearing. https://t.co/3yI024w9cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox @brianbeutler Countries not band are staying silent because they are afraid. Also, have we ever had such an aliterate president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes you think that their view of all citizens is any different? https://t.co/4MmawmJLKk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>