<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A bitch https://t.co/dWWK4zHBPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I got a bag of Carrots and (feat. ror's hand comparison) https://t.co/uVwUjFpd7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skeletonfarms HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ the Wendigo drawing with Jesse is 2 years old now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also drew a Roscoe and my cat, Sasha https://t.co/4gVavgTkAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls hire me to draw godzilla all day thanks https://t.co/SykKutPIHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skeletonfarms the mouse one is adorable......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok!! I think I got his look down. Antaeus, the Dragonborn Cleric https://t.co/PyhpikZywU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fucking love He-Man and She-Ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I have discord now if anybody wants it 
My username is Antbears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dnd boy who... needs a name https://t.co/1h4Ftabvnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am going to draw them soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've made a dnd character that idk if I'll ever use!! Thanks to @Floorboreds for helping me do this for literal hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Creep prob my fav found footage movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching yet another found footage film (Creep)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get u a man that can do both https://t.co/D4X5Ul7EEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giraffe anthros are scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did that shindan things that said my trainer was a giraffe that loves hte protein https://t.co/9wd9E60RYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wells feat. Ror's goat boy https://t.co/coNwnhWtct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woops got my ear bit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agenderwhatever Bioware back at it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bought myself the Hannibal show on blu ray today, really happy I can now watch it whenever ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ror is playing thru re7 again ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna use my camera more.. try to go out n take pictures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am terrified of Kazuma Kiryu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thesandlord is the spot soft? If it is it's probably a cavity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiderExy thank uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm rewatching Hannibal and its giving me a lot of inspiration... really good show to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you know what, my art is alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Jesse, Roscoe and the Wendigo https://t.co/9xkaM314qN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doodling Blair to loosen up a bit https://t.co/qC5vrtHKF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aethercrayons thats what it looks like yeah.. wish I didnt throw out the paper that came with it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any idea what batteries this thing would use? AAA for reference https://t.co/ROZwoHJ7lV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im watching sonic boom and idk what this says about me but: it's funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss all this time I thought Pidge was girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching Voltron I Guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey https://t.co/JEKZb7187i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss hey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory and I have recently purchased Resident Evil 7 and Yakuza 0. Honestly these games are so good and I'm thoroughly enjoying both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L has no eyebrows and it's taken me this long to realize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Death Note and how ridiculous it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re7 is Stressful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@becooldaddyo IM GLAD U LIKE.... she's such a great design I couldn't resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard y'all like dragon ladies with big boobs https://t.co/SAVk18LERd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@becooldaddyo  a Kheer for u https://t.co/LktmCIXMIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I only wear crewnecks and tight fitting pants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drew a self portrait thign and it ended up looking like soft bruce lee https://t.co/R9gfwYmKqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this cat with all my heart but Boy Is He Annoying Me Right Now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fenny was laying on me so I decided to do some paw studies https://t.co/NE8PLtdnmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if I should get back on FA for the sake of furry comms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drew the top 1 first and Rory said she looked too cute so https://t.co/PQVLsleQdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who's getting RE7 cause he's a baaaad boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What https://t.co/LLE6kjJK3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal struggle https://t.co/WQ4i7teEcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss im a slut for this anime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm rewatching Death Note again... why dont I own this damn show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss theres lots of decent body horror in it tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss almost laughably bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So about an hour and 20 mins into the movie V/H/S is a... boring found footage compilation with some ok stuff sprinkles in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiderExy it sure was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This movie was worth it only for girl's eye being popped out by knife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I always find myself watchin these damn found footage movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching V/H/S y'all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2009memerevival o thank u!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2009memerevival if u have a ref or somethin I'll see what I can do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey if anyone has drawing suggestions hmu,
I'm recovering from surgery and I wanna get back into drawing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little doodle of Ramsey and Nova (who belongs to @Floorboreds ) https://t.co/oNcBlWgwmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doodling my maned werewolf boy Ramsey https://t.co/ZDcRavizts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're finishing up the Scream Show tonite and... well... ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss granted that I have only watched the 1st Scream movie so idk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory has brought this up while watching but, I too, would rather that the Scream TV show not actually be affiliated with Scream at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Suda51 is... cute..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy translating every so often is sooooo awkward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aethercrayons @rottenmusclepup â¤ we had lots of fun toooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She never just lays on my lap like this.... https://t.co/7j8lqGHOee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nova and Rams r so good... Aly we have so many good boys https://t.co/UosS6WUPWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm kinda bummed I can't get Biohazard right away cause I'm savin for Digimon.... I love survival horror but... digimon..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'll yeah https://t.co/401nQmCvJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're watching the Scream TV series and its alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zinfogel aaa thank u! I really appreciate the compliment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss closeup head https://t.co/fcO2yXDIzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A collab between @GoodMorningJoel @xSmilingMashton  and myself https://t.co/gLcQZYIZz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doodling Dog Marius. I just about filled up this sketchbook!! https://t.co/ZDYTlxOH7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do y'all ever think about Leon https://t.co/j5iveP2Dpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss -the few bands I own physical media of. Anyway they're pretty good! I'm listenin to Neon Zero currently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Local band I can really get behind... I first heard them in London opening for Marilyn Manson and they left quite an impression. One of-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listenin to Die Mannequin's newest stuff ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘ I really love Care Faliure's voice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these nerds https://t.co/gX0yrqlE4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Roscoe and Jesse https://t.co/pr9fuZWwtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aethercrayons @deve @rowdydirtyboy it'd be so cool to get a group together! I ought to really read up on how to do... anything tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aethercrayons fair enough! I don't either... it seems a bit daunting but I don't know the first thing about DMing lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aethercrayons sameeeee.. it'd be so fun! I don't rly have anybody else that wants to play w me tho (or have the room) u_u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Antbearss I really like how Lynch and Frost work together to bring out the best in eachother. It's amazing that this series even hot made]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back on the topic of TeePee:
After restarting season 2 recently
I honestly couldn't recommend it enough. It's just so bizarre and charming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always wanted to play dnd as a cleric class... I hope 1 day I can ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's too bad the actress that played Audrey Horne in Twin Peaks isn't in too much else :( I think shes quite good tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[birdmans and dogpersons https://t.co/xsHSynW3My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres a cryptid in my house https://t.co/zCZVNo94uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate this movie already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're watchinf Alpha and Omega Legend of Sawtooth Cave https://t.co/y8NPgess4W]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>