<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoveling snow can wait, #squash can't!!  #BlackKnight https://t.co/KYEmvjcHtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I own it on vinyl, cassette, CD and digitally.  Yes, bought it 4 times.  Rumours is 40 years old today. @LG1043 https://t.co/S7OkRQdkW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Tsawwassen February https://t.co/7BiEHmx4md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone seen that Groundhog????  I want to talk to him.... @LG1043 
#bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to watch the #Superbowl at Costco... lots of big screens and great snacks.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowfall warning for Metro #Vancouver.  YUP, SNOW 2.0 @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time in its 140 year history, this year's Westminster Dog Show will include cats.  What could go wrong???  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Valentines coming up, it appears we in BC are the most romantic. Wait... VALENTINES IS COMING UP??? @LG1043 https://t.co/ZBRekWoyUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #GroundhogDay and if our West Coast Groundhog sees his shadow, he takes a 6 week Hawaiian vacation. #Vancouver @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which BC city is the "most romantic" in Canada?  @LG1043 
https://t.co/Ipq2SYSN1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we had cell phones in the 70s.  @LG1043 https://t.co/QGD0tYAB2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February is Grapefruit Month. And coincidentally, it's also Squirt Yourself In The Eye Month. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser just trolled Trump with this amazing Super Bowl ad. @LG1043 https://t.co/BEBSdnfGGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you checking out tonight's "conjunction?"  https://t.co/01UrQQmiJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car2go launches luxury Mercedes-Benz fleet in #Vancouver.  If it's a Mercedes S Class, would that be an S Car Go? @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crosby, Stills, Nash &amp; Young on #TurntableTuesday.  Which hit will we play?  Listen at 8:50 @LG1043 https://t.co/qhoTr3h8Bi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the Venus and Mars rock show and the moon has been invited.  Best to view after 8 tonight in #Vancouver @LG1043 https://t.co/XeAtErVRj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A study says you'll eat less if you eat with your eyes closed. Nothing ends a meal faster then stabbing yourself in the chin with a fork.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SETI is investigating a strong signal from 94 light-years away...The message is "send more Reese's Pieces." @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a fan of "Easy Rider" and "Born To Be Wild" you gotta watch this. @LG1043 https://t.co/3MoO3see1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm playing all those great songs you grew up with from the 60s 70s &amp; 80s AND sending you to see Elton John in Vict… https://t.co/wrw08OJ7uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my ride on Strava.
https://t.co/UPM53kgzhn https://t.co/jFp5M95bbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't need to tell me twice. https://t.co/zwtUbouV6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty terrific place to walk your dog.  #PointRoberts  So lucky to have it in our backyard. https://t.co/z2w2PYHGYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch as Mr Clean gets down and dirty in this Super Bowl Ad. @LG1043  https://t.co/pJK0pga5ef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This picture was taken yesterday by my friend John in #Victoria.  I think he is rubbing it in, don't you?… https://t.co/PEsYj0eSuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Superbowl is next weekend, that means the pre-game show starts today.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas prices down in #Vancouver... and on Friday!!  How often does that happen?  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ronniestanton, I said "Fair Dinkum" on the air today.  Happy #AustraliaDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fastest growing group of smart phone users is senior citizens.  I predict the new iPhone will have a bifocal screen. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wayne Gretzky. Think he always has 99 candles on his cake.  @LG1043 https://t.co/7AAqL8kRCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #AustraliaDay to all you transplanted Aussies in #Vancouver like @SuttoZ953.  I'm going to pass on the vegemi… https://t.co/Y7Y0zXBoBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fan of the old Archie comics?? This is filming in Riverdale, I mean #Vancouver right now.  Looks good.  @LG1043 https://t.co/O1VWsWGOW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced on @LG1043 Queen and Adam Lambert July 2nd in #Vancouver.  Congrats to Ron in Langley who won Beat t… https://t.co/UrIaLCE4vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Tyler Moore and the greatest 4 minutes of comedy television ever.  https://t.co/3Lmr1BTspC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear about Mary Tyler Moore passing.  She turned the world on with her smile.  @LG1043 https://t.co/eYwYnT2PIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #RobbieBurnsDay, so go see his statue in Stanley Park.  Then go have a few stiff belts before you try Haggis. @LG1043 #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A glass of red wine is the equivalent to an hour at the gym says the University of Alberta.  How many hours are there in a bottle?? @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graham_hatch Poolenalena Beach in Wailea.  But heard them at every beach we went to.  Very Cool!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #robbieburnsday!!  Bag pipes, haggis and of course whiskey.  @LG1043 #Vancouver https://t.co/ABGRWMDxiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Neil Diamond's birthday at 8:50 with this classic hit.  #TurntableTuesday @LG1043 https://t.co/Ewapu3e6H9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When designing your van ALWAYS do the door open test. @LG1043 https://t.co/t3YY9f8juk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La La Land with a record tying 14 #Oscar nominations including best picture.  @LG1043 https://t.co/LwQ1aMiIku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 5 reasons I procrastinate,
1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two amazing things about this video. One, a Sea Turtle slowly making his way and secondly, the… https://t.co/y007fPqjEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deas Island Regional Park 😎🚴#DeltaBC #cycleBC https://t.co/Bqexe9plf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm back on air tomorrow on @LG1043 unless @graham_hatch wants to get up at 4am one more day?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the... https://t.co/uz6dc2MLe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The washroom is the first door on the right, watch your step. @LG1043 https://t.co/2QbPVs1h7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things were a little different 2 years ago in #Vancouver @LG1043 @theprovince https://t.co/1rj46UyWd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Parks Board reminds you that #TroutLake is the only safe place to practice your Salchows and Triple Axels.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life in #Vancouver these days.  @LG1043 https://t.co/Au6dcZy3YQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Parks Board says #TroutLake is officially safe to skate on. Remember when ice skating, never judge a brook by its cover. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News today about how coffee is good for you.  I could get into all the specifics and details but suffice to say, its good for you..enjoy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McDonald's has opened a restaurant inside the Vatican.  The fryers are operated by actual friars.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, what did you do today??? https://t.co/RoYbueZvKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She had a football?  Let me watch that again. https://t.co/ZjnBTzD3jU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eliz_bonner Ahhhh, the days we dream about in January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver's most precious mineral???  Road Salt!!  Available for free at 10 city fire halls at 9am this morning.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby It's Cold Outside @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Jr Hockey Semi Finals today Canada vs Sweden.  You'll want to find a really big screen with lots of friends wearing red.  #GoCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new study shows taking a break from Facebook improves your mood.
It also gives you more time to spend on Instagram &amp; Twitter.  @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shelleyocean a cyclist would also enjoy going downhill at top speed 🚴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My year in sport (cycling) https://t.co/ESdR3pwmzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't recall making a New Year's resolution to pay more for gas??  #Vancouver @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #TurntableTuesday and you'll hear track 5 at 8:50 on @LG1043 @johnmellencamp https://t.co/MaJil1c8dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best sports photo bomb ever!!  @LG1043 https://t.co/R07SPJWJxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vehicle you need for your #Vancouver commute.  @LG1043 https://t.co/pBkzCKv7Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry - there will be plenty of parking spaces available at the fitness club soon enough. @LG1043 #happynewyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lululemon guy Chip Wilson’s home in Point Grey assessed $75-million. 
Your winning lotto max ticket wouldn't cover… https://t.co/DNj0aKIl1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, something you don't see everyday...or ever, in #Vancouver.  @LG1043 https://t.co/faU7RtnOp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking down the Christmas tree, found where the kids hid their vegetables from Christmas dinner. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No price on this wine, so "I'll make them an offer they can't refuse" @LG1043 #vino https://t.co/cmwFhF5TQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first sunset of 2017. #SunnyTsawwassen #BeautifulBC #Canada150 https://t.co/g5tSYHEmI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, 11:30 already?  This year is flying by.   #happy2017 #Canada150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to a bird singing in my backyard.  Gotta be a good sign!  #happy2017 #Canada150 #SunnyTsawwassen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last ride of 2016
https://t.co/qFGRS0CT58 https://t.co/IQsiNrLt81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Donnelly &amp; Sons singing national anthems.  4 times as good!!  #OCanada @Canucks https://t.co/lQ32rji1B1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's #NationalBaconDay Merry Crispness!!   @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think we'll be able to find homes for these goodies in #2017 😎and never say no to breathe mints.  @LG1043 https://t.co/2SI068CGvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not going to lie, my heart hurts seeing the Eagles without Glenn Frey.  None the less, a great tribute at the… https://t.co/58VcNQItm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DOUBLEJGLOBALBC Excellent story on the Burnaby Winter Club!  Great stuff.  #local]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new winter ride #NorcoSearch.  So far I've tackled snow, rain and mud with flying colours. https://t.co/AgMU4GJYTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time between Christmas and New Year where you don't know what day it is, who you are or what your suppose to do. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've been eating too much when the sweater you got for Christmas that was too big, now fits perfectly. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw #RogueOne last night and the last person you see is Carrie Fisher.  Her line "you brought hope."  RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iantheCROAT that Crown Royal was the BEST, but had a very short life.  If you know what I mean!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FINALLY finding time to start reading @deejayred "The Last DeeJay" @LG1043 https://t.co/FIsUWP5Wl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't judge...and please speak softly. https://t.co/RobAqj6Vxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Tsawwassen Polar Express complete with ski hill and gondola.  #DeltaBC https://t.co/GUdVjxFy5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Karting, new Christmas Eve tradition.  Super fun (and competitive) #SpeedersRichmond https://t.co/7ogncH2wbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas!! https://t.co/QOe2ovHIHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you received a Christmas gift from me with a roll of Scotch Tape and a pair of scissors inside -- please send those back. @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20% wait until the last minute to Christmas Shop and if you're one of those people,  I'm here to tell you...ITS THE LAST MINUTE! @LG1043]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the feeling that Santa has the eye chart memorized. https://t.co/ORYx3lYYEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this is happening https://t.co/5KehX3QAsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shelleyocean @LG1043 Have you been into the egg nog already??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, BEST Christmas song ever!  @LG1043 https://t.co/EkArrqzz82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chocolates made in #DeltaBC!  Better dig in and support the local economy.
@LG1043 https://t.co/RTXyZ4sltE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to set your scale back 10 pounds.  #Christmas @LG1043]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>