<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KSoltisAnderson and Mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneGoldmacher it's why the vote on DeVos is today, before his confirmation vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse i wouldn't think it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse so you're saying there will be multiple upsets by 10, 11, and 12 seeds this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is disgraceful https://t.co/B6W4oZhnyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni yeah, that always happens with time machines #butterflyeffect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson Raiders are going to go the way of the Islanders. get kicked out of their stadium, and have nowhere to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson i was honestly waiting to see your take on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller it's basically this https://t.co/pRiZrJw0b5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well, that's interesting thinking https://t.co/FlvBjVkU6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_prototype focus on the kid. always focus on the kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood so @markberman says Ragsdale returned to being deputy director]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarcasticRover be glad you're on mars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni you're hired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneGoldmacher Monday night massacre coming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByDavidMurphy that would involve data, which they don’t believe in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbeindit it would help if Georgetown and Pitt didn't completely fall apart this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenTremendous @robneyer you may just want to make that an evergreen tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheeraf @karaswisher google has already said nearly 200 workers are affected, and called it painful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel oh, god no, i can't take more commercials about barbara comstock. i'm not in that district and i wanted to pour wax in my ears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[true for lots of websites https://t.co/tquWrmAExw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporter in training #journalism #toddlers #firstamendment #toddlersofinstagram #media @… https://t.co/Y4e5Pfr6ll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs better get it. tequila will be more expensive soon...maybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why would around leave the left coast to cover the Mets? so many better teams to cover. right @whoisdoni https://t.co/4lb723Bgyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait, losing 30 years of institutional knowledge is a good thing? https://t.co/tAfIaj4udH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for guac lovers, this will increase the price of avocados https://t.co/MwxKKKs2TO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtannenwald @PhillyDailyNews next Nova win?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_prototype that's my point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this, a million times this https://t.co/7FuSbcll27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tatecurtis you’re more serious than they are anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP it's also a violation of international law to torture people, but that's back on the table too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is this honestly an issue in Virginia? https://t.co/qJ4RziBVgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TestudoDave don't you know the feds can only spend money on defense and security. to hell with everything else #sarcasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lmcampo sigh, fine, i guess we'll keep you here ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lmcampo your state's definition of hate crime and mine are not the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans in multiple states fail to understand that whole 1st Amendment thing https://t.co/dj4Q2TwGcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller i can't wait for 50 states to say no to little fraud, while his DOJ says massive fraud. that'll be fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Ermann to be fair, Pitt has regressed as the season has gone on. they were in good shape when they went to CP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller my point being that people this unqualified for a position would never even get a full senate vote. Carson is a joke for HUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More and more convinced the Senate is a joke https://t.co/TPlptHUL1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake can someone point out how Rs were howling about use of Executive Orders under Obama, and now not a peep under Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake doesn't he have a 10-year term anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gab_rose1 I get it for OOC games, to an extent, but in conference, not at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gab_rose1 “bad scheduling” is being used against both MD teams this year. It’s bunk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller the extent of my sartorial rhetoric is basically this quote: "Don't you hate pants?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro this is called giving someone the benefit of the doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfloyd10 what did CONCACAF do? more arrests?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillMcAvoyACN wait, he had a spine to begin with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops A+ Airplane reference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel anything Fleetwood Mac?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyGlockner refs version of alternative facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slmandel Cubs opened the door, now we're all doomed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix so you're going to drink yourself to death?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnshelPfeffer @sheeraf won’t matter. It’ll be official US policy just at the announcement. Can of worms will be opened regardless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix sean spicer #worstweek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC well he did say he wasn't going to start until Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodmanESPN Gary Williams is probably still sabotaging her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greggagliardi they were moved to a new account, @POTUS44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson would be a perfect time to take Rocky for a walk....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson i miss my old apartment. i would have sat in the window, drinking a beer(s), watching from safety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum fair assessment. thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum ranking him ahead of Jackson?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robneyer only if ordered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsprof56 he was outside the zone on replay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse this would be a good public service announcement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni sorry, soccer fan too. forget sometimes that is not ubiquitous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phinally! https://t.co/9A14jUfNEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni ha if only. probably would share a stadium with Tottenham (who, coincidentally, is building a stadium for that purpose)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni smart money is on the Jaguars. maybe the Chargers. Jets just paid a shitload for a new stadium, so they aren't leaving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni bet a team moves in the next 4 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so how much should i bet that a NFL team will move to London in the next 4 years? https://t.co/skEStUiRPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pbump and his (marginalized) VP was John Adams. still an amazing crew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller you would be so surprised how hard it is to create good, effective headlines. such a hard skill to master]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson seriously though, how hard is it to look up the date of a picture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_prototype i hope it's a comedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson pretty much https://t.co/hnUtEnyTFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson i never will say that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeschlossDC @pbump false. Buchanan was sworn in March 4, 1856, which was the date used until 1933]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson thanks for the needed comedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lloydamiller so i changed the channel when I got to "asks"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeneps also for more money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattfusf secession dreams are just that: dreams. entire state's economy would tank instantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be more excited for the World Cup in 2026. https://t.co/w1L642iuHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP DNI is an appointed/senate-confirmed position, right? and National Security Advisor is not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsBlakeJohnson we've talked about this. what you do in your private time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terpstationmd needs to work on free throws too. Will draw a lot of fouls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse just the teams you planned to see that day, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyersfansindc your favorite was radar, clearly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyersfansindc yeah, you should #mash #classic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyersfansindc i mean, it's not that far from Hershey. Flyers need to make it happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting idea https://t.co/IAf6myAUUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeneps not sure a ton of people would be upset if he went after Swift. she's always in feuds as it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse knew about the non-rev sports. Nice to see the thaw up higher though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D1scourse thawing of relations between old ACC guard (pre-2003) and Maryland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snidog @robneyer the original statement was since 1970. Pilots weren't allowed to move to Milwaukee until April 1970.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whoisdoni padme was queen, then senator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ceolaf @robneyer i think the idea of the original post was MLB has been stable since 1970 compared to other leagues. just missed teams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robneyer you could do that, but you also need to remember the number of moves in MLB in the 50s and 60s. it's not really objective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robneyer @royalsreview false. Rangers (DC), Brewers (Seattle), Nationals (Montreal) all have moved since 1970.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>