<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We need Twitter to silence LGBT hate. Homophobia, biphobia and transphobia have no place online #no2LGBTHate… https://t.co/kUSZpDXQJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am STILL getting "Your Highlights" emails with tweets from SOMEONE I HAVE BLOCKED. Get your shit together @Support @Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in many states even convicted rapists can be given visitation rights, forcing people to see their rapists over… https://t.co/RNSFbRc2Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpinionessWorld yeah and that's what I was clearly criticizing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg it's so much better, it's not even a contest. Better plots, better twists, better relationships, better etc https://t.co/v9Hx5xe1A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What must it be like to have so little self-awareness that you can't even see you're a giant hypocrite, I wonder? https://t.co/8xvoEGbWIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpinionessWorld @alexandraerin Was Hobby Lobby baptized? Does Hobby Lobby attend church? It's a business, it can't have a religion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, "religious freedom" is code for "Christian" conservatives legally being able to force their religion down anyone else's throats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the hell is in favor of the Muslim ban? Someone in Eastkabumfuk Pennsylvania who pointed to Borneo when asked to identify Yemen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson when even PAPA JOHNS thinks something has gone too far....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski would rather have the basilisk tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstTimeTrek ikr? I had a nightmare last night I had to flee to Canada :-/ I haven't gotten a full night's sleep since November]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you know a minority of any type living in the US, you know someone who is probably living in terror]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White cis men are the single greatest safety threat in the US and Canada. I can't believe we let them walk around wo extreme vetting. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vodstok fwiw Sharia in itself is not extremist, in fact some parts of it are the only reason women have some rights in some countries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tbh a lot of Evangelicals and Mormons don't believe Catholics are Christian, so *I* wouldn't be able to pass a "Christianity test" either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now @Canada states on refugee info page that coming through US means you might not get refugee status...that's gotta change, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ybbkaren @Evan_McMullin the Republican love for false equivalencies is what got us into this mess. Not glad to see it's still alive &amp; well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aqua_womann ... Which one do you consider the hot Genji skin? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already Loisiana declared resisting arrest a hate crime--now think about how often completely passive black people are accused of resisting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For ex, the "religious freedom" bills that are only made so "Christians" can discriminate against LGBT+ people will become more powerful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that the #MuslimBan is only the beginning. If they somehow end up getting away with this, they'll start coming for everyone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread on racism/xenophobia in Australia: https://t.co/4bTPv7p4hd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Normally I might still go, but next week I have to deal w my parents justifying voting for a VP who wants me dead b/c "it's just politics"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to go to the protest today but I'm pretty sure I'm coming down with something :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol I used to live a mile from where the Obamas are going to live and work a few blocks away (also they're going to be right by Pence)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been going Lyft-only since the first hints Uber was working with Trump. I actually find it very nice (no inter… https://t.co/pXRmsbmDEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin the problem is many Republicans still hate many of us. Hard to work with someone who thinks you're a 2nd class citizen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GOP does not get to distance themselves from this. They let this hatred fester. They have proven themselves un-American to the extreme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any politician who votes 'yes' to any Trump appointment from now on is legitimizing his hate. They must not be allowed to win re-election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America was never necessarily great, but it used to be so much better than this. I miss being able to believe in my country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread: https://t.co/J0BW16M3SH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damianholbrook @Pontifex @realDonaldTrump Were they Catholics? I know Pence isn't and his type tend to hate Catholics/the Pope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect Americans: Deport all white men!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear @PlayOverwatch and @BlizzHeroes have gotten just the worst people in chats recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like those of us in Virginia have even more phone calls to make (and primary opposition to look into) https://t.co/grjDmTOj8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But if Trump wants to "protect" the US.... #WhereIsTheGunBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/cVOSfDPYwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact all those people were in town for #MarchForLife but didn't turn to a protest against the refugee ban prove it's a #MarchForDeath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are WAYYYY more likely to be killed by their husbands than a terrorist. Straight relationships haven't been banned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In America, statistically you're more likely to be killed by a cop than a terrorist. Banning people b/c of this sort of thing is idiocy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is a scary place right now and I feel so, so sorry for the children who have to grow up in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything Trump does to isolate Muslim Americans, to hurt MENA countries, is propaganda that Islamist groups can use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's generally accepted the reason pre-9/11 the US didn't have the same terrorism issues as Europe was b/c we accepted/integrated people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having studied international security more intensely than almost everyone working for Trump, I can say that the ban is a HORRIBLE idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahjeong If it's a question of whether the average American read something, it's generally safe to assume "no"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vodstok ouch, I don't think Ana will be happy about that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just so upset, I've felt close to tears for hours. America wasn't perfect, but Trump &amp; GOP are tearing apart what made it GOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TinaDuryea @JKH2 @dianelyssa @TheDemocrats if the Dems give them an inch they'll take a mile and everyone else will suffer for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstTimeTrek @overwatch yeppp so much reporting and blocking :-/ idk if it was the election or if OW started advertising somewhere or what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vodstok @overwatch tbh ever since the election I've been seeing a ton of racist shit in the chats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in @Overwatch had to deal with someone saying "deport this coons already Trump" and blaming a loss on us being "minorities"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[App idea: it would match up Evangelicals w Muslims who wish to enter US--one side gets to babble, which they love, other learns just enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amount of white people I'm hearing complain about avocado prices is getting ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[* lbh of course I am, but maybe slightly less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These tourists in town for #MarchForLife are the worst yet. I'll never complain about how rude school tours are again*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure my linter is infested with gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone blatantly misspells your name after multiple emails with your correctly spelled name -.-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That stupid "Your Highlights" email sent to me from @twitter includes accounts I have blocked -.-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2020 I will be over 35 and more qualified than Trump to be president--scary thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, less, let's attack a woman who wasn't even in charge of the decision but not attack the sexual harasser in the… https://t.co/Oqlvg78Mr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So gross: Girls Think Boys Are Naturally Smarter, According to a Disturbing Study  https://t.co/PdMG12yx5d via… https://t.co/6anUDLFh1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump got the "most" for something! He should be happy! https://t.co/mr9ZJWJiuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RMiffed Maybe a definition issue--to libs 'small govt' means less govt interference etc To Cons it means smaller democracy larger theocracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But of course they're making no effort to do that. They just hate EVERYONE that's not them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think one thing that pisses me off most about Trump regime is that everything they want can be done in way to offset damage to Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["small government" was their first #alternativefacts decades before they were popular https://t.co/NImyKSCvvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INCREDIBLY JEALOUS https://t.co/iC6Iwhn2f3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliadeanneh @markiplier @thenoblepeanut I'm sooo bad at scary games, anything where who I'm playing could 'permanently' die scares me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliadeanneh @markiplier @thenoblepeanut omg I've been watching that, too, his fear gets me even more worked up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who supports torturing children until they commit suicide is headlining something that is clearly NOT proLIFE https://t.co/QQpiRA5rkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scalia found a way to screw people over even in death https://t.co/dazMM4lTy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When no govt $$ can go towards erectile dysfunction treatments/vasectomies,then I'll believe anti-abortion movement cares about "God's Will"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread on Mexico tariff https://t.co/b5XiP6okTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Newsies is being shown in movie theaters (the Broadway version) and I really want to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomenTechSummit @DataLensDC HALF your keynotes are men right now, for a women's conf, in an industry where women are underrepresented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My talk WAS accepted--I think it's bs to have a male keynote lecturing women about their own experiences… https://t.co/g9PaUgwkRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that he is a Jewish man who has had to deal with Nazis multiple times in just the last few days https://t.co/gVUuPdfzGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump and the GOP honestly put money into the wall, every collapsed bridge going forward should be considered their fault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriseppstein @EmilyGorcenski I was, too, until I realized Trump probably doesn't even know it (might not even know what she's done lbh)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't get over all the comments on this article complaining about "liberals". It's a fucking movie made to shock… https://t.co/YUuL68yDO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsElizaDivine another: preg women who get measles are at high risk of miscarriage etc, but low risk vaccine not legally required]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsElizaDivine until "pro-life" force laws that will make us donate blood, bone marrow, and spare organs, they're just obvious frauds lbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to refer to my apartment as installation art, titled "I'm too stressed about survival to clean"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will accept this headline https://t.co/kVwNY3TXtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really want to talk to people about #Overwatch being set in a post-Trump world and how much it works--weakened intl institutions, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of my Senator https://t.co/lh6MRX0Jbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DereckCurry "white working class", the people that Trump and Sanders pandered to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DereckCurry *shrug* If that's what the alt-left wants to accuse anyone who's not WWC of caring about, might as well own it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DereckCurry Wonder if we can use some form of the words "Identity Politics" lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RMiffed in all honesty, my mother's doctor suggested it, and if I had actually killed her I would have not had a healthy childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly I need 24/7 #puppybowl Just for the next 4 years, constant Puppy Bowl that I can put on when I can't take life anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I might change my next tattoo idea, think I might get a Star Wars Resistance logo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antichoicers: "What if your mother had aborted you!"
Me, in 2017: "Damn, I wish"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimShoeCrzy @LuthorCEO yet everyone complained about how awful the quality of our education was! Poor kids today, surprised they can add]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motherfucking Loudoun County https://t.co/7jlJQ7Cu90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, thought of a new username--should I change the one on this account &amp; use this username for a prof one or lockdown this account? hmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still can't get over people's bs about Clinton's emails when freaking OPM has to provide me w free identity protection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuthorCEO There was an article back in the GWB days, like, "Lex Luthor would have given everyone free gas" (ie been better at it)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, no, whatever will she do? Banned from one whole radio station, she's such a nobody that's going to just ruin he… https://t.co/JluFROZn7y]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>