<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL Imagine Chelsea win EPL and no player in team of year. Unheard of. Is there bias against NE ? No.1 score def - no players !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL 1 x Special team All Pro Player. Brady/Belichick - ignored again. NE seem to play a different game. They aim for rings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilreynoldsnfl Can you ask Brady if he's asked Kraft to tailor the fifth ring specifically for his thumb ? Next year start the second hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrywinter Simply a Champions League spot for FA Cup winners would do it. If winners already top 3 then reverts to 4th place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilreynoldsnfl @SkySportsNFL All Pro team with a token player from the best team !! Makes it look a bit silly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flybe When will you have flights from Cardiff to Dublin released for October 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AerLingus Hi, wondering when your Autumn 2017 flights Dublin - Cardiff will be available?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madds_jm @YouTube Cheers. That's Sunday evening sorted !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEgaa Gavin next year has McCaffrey and Rory O'Carroll back aswell !!! #DUBvMAYO #SundayGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colettebrowne Discrimination if she got tickets. Expense of real fan. She should ask Delaney or Hickey to get one !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonLeagueCrowd @GNev2 So long as the loyal 117 in unfashionable years are still catered for. Hardcore fans lifeblood of clubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrywinter imagine Greg Dyke doing this to most committed Eng fans. Dictator &amp; Pat Hickeys choice for IOC !!! https://t.co/phbcCSgIwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD Going on years. Someone someday will sort this. Who's going to have the guts and get the glory https://t.co/ALUM2hiBpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland There for the first, will be there for the last but behind the goal in Ibaraki will struggle to ever be beaten #legend #keane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MCATEER4 No need to defend Keane. 67 goals do that. 67 in 145 =46.2%. Rooney 53 in 115 = 46.0% with Gerrard/Scholes supplying !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD Only thing real fans want is fairness. Pity we didn't qualify for World Cup in Brazil !!!  https://t.co/jVi9CtALyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsport Alex Ferguson leaves League champs. Same team 7th next season. Carruth says Billy Walsh going has no impact !!! Looking silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelVaughan @piersmorgan Odds for draw after all out (20/1). Odds for draw after batting again (8/1).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower Very true. But the 1/5 the odds ew rather then 1/4 ew means all other 7 you paid out less on place part. I'd Garcia !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball Martin Tyler report. Did schedule cost France? It saved them. Rd16 France 7 days rest, Ireland 3 !!! Tired players 2nd half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themichaelowen Your FA investigating performance. Bet no looking into criteria of how coach chosen or why Redknapp not even interviewed !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieSadlier We would've lost anyway. Stood off and admired Belgium all day. Anyone will look a good player with no pressure on them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNewsHQ @SkySports #ssnhq #euro2016 Expected airport type security. IrevSwe Paris Monday. 1 x frisk - nothing major]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossgillwedding @anthonyl86 @airfrance @AirFranceIE @cityjet AF say same. Just not worth any risk for me so chose extra night in Paris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossgillwedding @anthonyl86 @airfrance @AirFranceIE @cityjet Air France. Websites say 6.25 and 17.05 on Sunday are Cityjet. 9.10 AF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dylanp87 Yeah they did it. Did it over Twitter. Wasn't many seats left at that stage a couple of hours ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossgillwedding @anthonyl86 @airfrance @AirFranceIE Also rang and confirmed Air France operate. Cityjet normally do daily but not Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dylanp87 Its gonna be cancelled. No alternatives on Sunday. Air France operate. I thought Cityjet but confirmed otherwise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airfrance Thanks very much for your help. I understand it's a very busy time. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airfrance Yes please do re-issue for Sat 11th. Can you confirm when all complete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airfrance I contacted call centre. Flight ready to change from Sunday 12th to Sat 11th. I now can't contact centre as its closed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@airfrance Flight AF1617 Dub to CDG 12th June impacted. What are your suggestions here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE I need you to follow me to DM I believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE AF1817 and AF1617 are identical bookings and operated by Cityjet on Sunday 12th June. Why has one suddenly changed (AF1617)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE Firstly my flight says "operated by Cityjet" as the one today AF1617 was. Why is it different now when earlier tweets said same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE Can you confirm AF1617 on Sun 12th is operated by Cityjet as per booking which states this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE When can I get refund. Travelling Dub to CDG 12th and return 14th. Need to now book alternate on SAME dates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE What is your policy on strikes called. We would need to rebook. Refund should apply ? Can't wait till last minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirFranceIE I have flight on 12th to CDG from Dublin. Returning on 14th. Are these affected by Pilots unions strike called 11th - 14th June]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Rory's day not yours @EndaKennyTD. Did you tell him on the green you said Ryder Cup was between "Britain and the States" - Bad PR day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasByrneTD Just abolish the thing and move on. It's gone anyway. FF the one doing FG the favour facilitating them not other way round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changed referee to prevent Leicester bias !!! Did they then ask Spurs who to suggest #lcfcvwhufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland In the stand behind the goal !!! 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEbusiness "More customers" could technically mean 2. How many have stopped. Amazing they can say more customers but can't total amount !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickfitzg @188BET If you could go back and ride one race over again. Which one and why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coral What are you backing with your head that your heart says something else eg. Un De Sceaux / Sprinter Sacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly Why would Mary Lou vote to reduce DC to 2 seater. Tactical no.2 to FF. Has any CC contested an election after doing job !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocDems #ge16 3.7% in 14/40 constituencies is 11% really. Labour equivalent is 8%. 7 seats is realistic now. 4th largest party !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#newstalk @socdems 14/40 constituencies = 8%. Labour 34/40 = 9.2%. AAA 25/40 = 5.7%. GP 40/40 = 3.6%. Using Poll %. Seat Returns ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#leadersdebate #ge16 This has been a disaster for EVERY one of the 4. The winners are the smaller parties and they're not even there !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonHarrisTD Your leader has 32 minutes to save an election meltdown. 76 seats to 50 odd !! Legacy of FG, your boosting FF. Shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeamusjKearney @SocDems Google Dublin Mid West and you'll see who Derek Keating is. Btw 2011 - FG 76 seats - Health care costing = €0 !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeamusjKearney @SocDems I hope Derek Keating did not leave any "hot air" on his seat before leaving as she'll be sitting in it in 4 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never seen Varadkar look so flustered. McGrath has just demolished him. If he's destroyed, imagine how Enda Kenny going to look. #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EndaKennyTD Better tell Michael Noonan that so. He's saying 2022 now !!! Bit like 8/10/12 billion. 17 days left to get your story straight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieGHannon homeless/healthcare/childcare, not to mention the 8th. Be honest, did that speech set out strategy to solve let alone sell it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly Can you measure the sweat lost !!! Heard nothing because actually thought he might not last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieGHannon You need to watch it on TV. Looked uneasy unsure and now know why PR guys don't let him on tv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fgaf16 The only thing I'm watching this speech for is wondering will he actually last till the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL #skynfl Patriots summed up by Butler. 2.50 left stops TD at 1yd line. KC score with 1.22 left.   Did his job !!! #pats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL #SkyNFL How big was the OT drive by Arizona offence/Palmer going into next week given INT's, near picks and Seattle game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nflnetwork #peytonstart If you lose its harder to justify losing with Manning on bench. Playoff teams will be much much tougher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rtesportawards Michael O'Neill the outstanding manager. For any doubters it's the equivalent of Wicklow winning All Ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KildareGunner @barrybrosnan @mcgivo @Madds_jm @ryan_ger @WhelanNi @JCos1982 @baggio90 Like 2012. Tough but a dream for the supporters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bbcpanorama #fifa Brilliant. Come on the FBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @ryan_ger @WhelanNi @Madds_jm @JCos1982 @baggio90 @mcgivo Liverpool 33/1 2 weeks ago. 6/1 now. Odds on by Xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @Madds_jm @JCos1982 @WhelanNi @baggio90 @KildareGunner @mcgivo @ryan_ger Liverpool not brilliant. Just rest are shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madds_jm @barrybrosnan @JCos1982 @WhelanNi @baggio90 @KildareGunner @mcgivo @ryan_ger 33/1 - best 7 played away. Klopp. 6 pts off - value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @WhelanNi @baggio90 @KildareGunner @Madds_jm @mcgivo @ryan_ger @JCos1982 Not my car. Unless nicked from the Point !!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RaceToSB50 If New Orleans can score 50+ v Giants. What do guys think Patriots can score !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GNev2 @SalfordCityFC Proper football. No nonsense. Well done. 90 minutes of that puts premier league to shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rtept Hope Miriam learns from BBC guy. Ask hard questions, demand no waffle answers. Imagine what a host like that would do to Enda !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrosnanDamian @LaughingFooty @TheOddsBible haha. That might be Llyodee taking a corner in Zenica. Running low on players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @mcgivo @WhelanNi @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @JCos1982 Arsenal now favourites ahead of Liverpool for Europa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @mcgivo @WhelanNi @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @JCos1982 Devastating for Arsenal - Olympiakos score]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KildareGunner @barrybrosnan @WhelanNi @mcgivo @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @JCos1982 Top of the league, resting all the kids in CL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhelanNi @mcgivo @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @JCos1982 Arsenal fans on edge of seat watching Zagreb match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhelanNi @mcgivo @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @JCos1982 She should have played up front today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgivo @Madds_jm @baggio90 @ryan_ger @barrybrosnan @KildareGunner @WhelanNi @JCos1982 Calm down. It was only Chelsea away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL @neilreynoldsnfl Is there any possibility of getting NFL Network as part of Sky package?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNFL #nfl #NFLGameDay 3 extra games AFC v NFC as per inter conference. 1 home, 1 road, 1 neutral = 16 international per year !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madds_jm @KildareGunner @WhelanNi @barrybrosnan @ryan_ger @mcgivo @baggio90 @JCos1982 Klopp v Ancelotti next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KildareGunner @WhelanNi @barrybrosnan @ryan_ger @Madds_jm @mcgivo @baggio90 @JCos1982 Arsenal great bet today. Usually choke about Easter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ybig 650 tickets!! Tough place to get to. Friday of 3 days is easily easiest travel date #playoff #euro2016 #ireland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland @ybig @RTEsoccer @RichieSadlier One year on. Have lessons been learned or is Santa Delaney still in action. #fansdirect #tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YouBoysInGreen Had to get SFA ticket in Scotland. Now no FAI record of being there could count. 4/5 away. Please not Bosnia !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 Vikings away week 13. Need to get to there with 5 in a row. If lose there, Arizona last game aswell it leaves them no room]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 Can see next 3 wins before Arizona home. In business then. Carolina home next tough &amp; Dallas away without Romo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 Yes but 6 losses and they could struggle. Tough schedule must go 9-2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 They are best defence but Arizona will win West. Two undefeated in south. 6th seed only and tough trips. Vikings danger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 Pats were 20/1 at 5-0 in '07 when I backed them for season unbeaten. 25/1 here is any team 16-0 only.Not sure about Seattle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarraghFarrell1 I have 25/1 on an unbeaten team. Worth a bet. GB and NE good enough. Denver away for both tho. Gillette is class. 51pts !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@labour You got shafted. Giveaway for FG voters. Even Paddy Power has decreased the betting on your no. of seats. #budget16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly That's odd. 32 in class for our kids !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower 1/6 November. Would be good advertising to pay out early. Can't lose too much !! EK going mad before budget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KildareGunner @mcgivo @Madds_jm @barrybrosnan @ryan_ger @baggio90 @JCos1982 @WhelanNi Unless the "transfer committee" sacked it's pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgivo @barrybrosnan @ryan_ger @Madds_jm @baggio90 @KildareGunner @JCos1982 @WhelanNi That was a players mutiny. More like Chelsea really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrybrosnan @ryan_ger @Madds_jm @baggio90 @mcgivo @KildareGunner @JCos1982 @WhelanNi Everton got rid of Moyes at Utd. Time for Rodgers now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelleab1983 Are u not out on the town with the Aussies in London !!! Expect you'll be seeing gang green win tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan_ger @Madds_jm @barrybrosnan @baggio90 @mcgivo @KildareGunner @JCos1982 @WhelanNi They're worse then Liverpool]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>